TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
May	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1731	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1731	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
;	O
being	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
1st	O
and	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Cummins	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Bettesworth	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Peace	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Burdon	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Calston	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Heems	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nitson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weaver	O
's	O
Bartrum	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Jefferys	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mendal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indictd	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Loftis	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cane	O
Chair	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
,	I-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Child	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Swetman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
George	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
and	I-pers
Esther	I-pers
Gibbert	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Amoth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Nathan	B-pers
Everard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
Calamanco	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
perceiving	O
,	O
followed	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Bobbins	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
Journey-woman	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Mantles	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Staple	O
and	O
Pin	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Gin	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
of	O
North-Hall	B-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
24	O
Harrow	O
Tines	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Valentine	B-pers
Seveer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Welsh-Society	O
pass	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
well	O
dress	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Merchants	O
Clerk	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
perceiving	O
her	O
Apron	O
move	O
,	O
she	O
clapped	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
her	O
Pocket	O
Apron	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
flung	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
crowd	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rowlet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Boxes	O
with	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
being	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Clock	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Chanel	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
to	O
secure	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Clock	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Reputation	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
De	O
la	O
Ware	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Carr	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Crick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
frequent	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
abroad	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
calling	O
divers	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Dikson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Red-Lion-Court	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
challenging	O
her	O
with	O
,	O
2	O
Men	O
came	O
and	O
bully	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
lose	O
his	O
Life	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
lose	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
Tunns	O
in	O
Prince's-Street	O
,	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
catching	O
up	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
return	O
the	O
Watch	O
without	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
got	O
her	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
were	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
as	O
a	O
Pledge	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
for	O
having	O
had	O
carnal	O
Copulation	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Spreadborough	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Kilvington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bellas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Lady	O
being	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Corps	O
was	O
carried	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
her	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
safe	O
in	O
Boxes	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Locks	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
being	O
faulty	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Smith	O
to	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
new	O
Lock	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
instead	O
of	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
new	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Lock	O
'd	O
up	O
safe	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
to	O
mend	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
that	O
wanted	O
mending	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
afterwards	O
appear	O
'd	O
)	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lydia	B-pers
Bowd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold-Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
him	O
about	O
4	O
Months	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Impudence	O
to	O
wear	O
the	O
Gold-Watch	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
having	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
where	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
examining	O
her	O
if	O
any	O
Person	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
herself	O
.	O
Makepeace	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-Broker	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
stealing	O
them	O
but	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Silver-Tankard	O
and	O
Gold-Watch	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-Broker	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
50	O
Guineas	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
save	O
a	O
Life	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
she	O
should	O
hold	O
up	O
her	O
Hand	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
than	O
he	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
slip	O
away	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
Rebeccah	O
Perry	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
frequently	O
visited	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
behav	O
'd	O
herself	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
modest	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
favour	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
10	O
l.	O
upon	O
a	O
Gold-Watch	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
straitned	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
before	O
Marriage	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
Fortune	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Marriage	O
was	O
not	O
yet	O
known	O
to	O
his	O
Relations	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
10	O
l.	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
redeem	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
by	O
her	O
desire	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
more	O
Money	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Days	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
since	O
absconded	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
-	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
gotten	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
troubled	O
himself	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
-	O
Coats	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
60	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
200	O
l.	O
of	O
his	O
Friends	O
in	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Things	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
Gentlema	O
n	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
with	O
her	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
)	O
with	O
Bock-holes	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
who	O
kiss	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
wanted	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
12	O
Bells	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
he	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Parcel	O
to	O
a	O
Baker's-Shop	O
in	O
Hatton-Garden	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
)	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
Things	O
was	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Porter	O
brought	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Silver-Tankard	O
,	O
Salver	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
Richard	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Fellow	O
that	O
is	O
sled	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
catch	O
him	O
(	O
he	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
)	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
trouble	O
my	O
self	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
declared	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
but	O
confess	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
no	O
hurt	O
should	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
proceed	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Coats	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
catch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
once	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sutton	O
depos	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cane	O
Chair	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
Liquor	O
,	O
than	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Eley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine-Creed	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
12s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Fitzgenald	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Matts	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	B-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Diana	B-pers
Houseman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Houseman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Guard-Rooms	O
at	O
the	O
Palace	B-place
at	I-place
Kensington	I-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
those	O
Apartments	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rowland	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Strongarm	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Warr	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bridget	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
felonious	O
taking	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Foresight	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Cave	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
Half-penny	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
Leaden	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
each	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Wilcott	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Coleman-Alley	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pretended	O
to	O
Kiss	O
her	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
which	O
Handkerchief	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
Jones	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hubbins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Watch	O
Cases	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peregrine	B-pers
Tawney	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Cows	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
at	O
Wilsdon	B-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Tibal's-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
New-Farmer	O
there	O
,	O
having	O
lately	O
taken	O
a	O
little	O
spot	O
of	O
Ground	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Acres	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
6	O
Cows	O
,	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hoare	O
,	O
but	O
whose	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
swore	O
the	O
Cows	O
to	O
be	O
theirs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Grounds	O
.	O
They	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Cows	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
whereas	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
lost	O
till	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Woolls	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
and	O
Dawson	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
themselves	O
were	O
all	O
about	O
10	O
,	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Cornwal	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissors	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Plank	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar-Window	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
unpinn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Person	O
had	O
gotten	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
through	O
a	O
Hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
Floor	O
to	O
let	O
down	O
Coals	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
the	O
Apprentices	O
,	O
who	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
with	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Coals	O
,	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Workmen	O
's	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
searched	O
,	O
the	O
Scissors	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Points	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Money	O
Drawer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
shut	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
Plank	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
shut	O
out	O
,	O
lay	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
not	O
availing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Faithful	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
half	O
peck	O
Loaves	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Trent	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
a	O
Nights	O
to	O
his	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
Loaves	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
share	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Trent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Check	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joel	B-pers
Farrington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edgerly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
at	O
Cranford-Bridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
little	O
House	O
over-against	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Thatch	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
coming	O
with	O
Pails	O
,	O
soon	O
extinguish	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
it	O
broke	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
it	O
broke	O
out	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
stripp	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Thatch	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
it	O
broke	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
again	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Widington	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
Stones	O
throw	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Edgerly	O
had	O
built	O
him	O
a	O
pretty	O
little	O
Hutt	O
,	O
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Snowden	I-pers
saying	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
much	O
Trade	O
of	O
late	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
Coaches	O
and	O
Waggons	O
seldom	O
stopping	O
here	O
since	O
the	O
building	O
of	O
Edgerly	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
long	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
two	O
Men	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
Guinea	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Snowden	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
being	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
two	O
's	O
time	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
burnt	O
down	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Thatch	O
was	O
on	O
Fire	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
looking	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
burned	O
bravely	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
Alhallowtide	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
Mr.	O
Edgerly	O
's	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
too	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
Edgerly	O
had	O
more	O
Business	O
than	O
he	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
Alteration	O
in	O
a	O
Month	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
several	O
breakings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
any	O
Hand	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
having	O
any	O
concern	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Expressions	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
use	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
times	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
talk	O
very	O
wildly	O
;	O
once	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
100	O
Devils	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
after	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Spit	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stuck	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Arse	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Arse	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
hopp	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
lost	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
mad	O
Man	O
ever	O
and	O
anon	O
for	O
3	O
Years	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Thatch	O
was	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
stood	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
as	O
unconcern	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
there	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
like	O
Cyphers	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
often	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
bound	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
pains	O
to	O
extinguish	O
the	O
Fire	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
indifferent	O
whether	O
it	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
likewise	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
inoffensive	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
the	O
least	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
nigher	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
than	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
100	O
Yards	O
off	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
Belladine	O
Silk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Silk	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Checker	O
'd	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
be	O
ing	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bastock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsely	O
and	O
fraudulently	O
Forging	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
under	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Yarman	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Thomas	B-pers
Teawen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Seat	O
of	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hodson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass-Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowds	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
26	O
Pound	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Ticking	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
living	O
in	O
Service	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
she	O
dwels	O
with	O
a	O
Sister	O
at	O
St.	O
Neot	O
's	O
in	O
Huntingdonshire	O
;	O
that	O
thither	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
provided	O
a	O
Room	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
so	O
many	O
Tokens	O
of	O
an	O
intimate	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
Reality	O
of	O
his	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
come	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
by	O
the	O
Waggon	O
the	O
next	O
Journey	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
)	O
were	O
to	O
receive	O
her	O
at	O
Highgate	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
come	O
up	O
accordingly	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
not	O
meeting	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
with	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
receive	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
conduct	O
her	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
)	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
Bundle	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
near	O
Sir	O
John	O
Oldcastle	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Room	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
expected	O
,	O
provided	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
expected	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
till	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
Landlady	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
be	O
content	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
prevailing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
resolute	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
Hanover-square	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
about	O
all	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
from	O
one	O
place	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
solliciting	O
her	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
leading	O
her	O
about	O
up	O
one	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
another	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
dark	O
,	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
she	O
accidentally	O
met	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
overjoy	O
'd	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
Joseph	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
were	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
Clothes	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
heard	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
bid	O
the	O
Coachman	O
drive	O
to	O
,	O
so	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
Clothes	O
,	O
the	O
Landlady	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Box	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
her	O
Clothes	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
worth	O
little	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Landlady	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Air	O
the	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
up	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
some	O
high	O
Words	O
pass	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
expected	O
from	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
that	O
were	O
but	O
just	O
met	O
together	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Absence	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
soon	O
coming	O
both	O
down	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Hanover-square	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
stayout	O
late	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Wife	O
at	O
a	O
Mantua-makers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Gown	O
which	O
she	O
would	O
alter	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
out	O
a	O
great	O
Bundle	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Esther	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Strangeway	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
George	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Strangeway	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
for	O
9	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
having	O
stolen	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
heard	O
off	O
till	O
of	O
late	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Importer	O
of	O
Wines	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
vended	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Customer	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
there	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
officiously	O
introduced	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Master	O
or	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rose	O
from	O
her	O
Seat	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Window-shutters	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
got	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Cane	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Mistress	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
Bitch	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
That	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Guinea	O
demanded	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
to	O
Justice	O
Midford	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Breeches	O
being	O
down	O
might	O
lose	O
his	O
Watch	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney-Corner	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dogwell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
follow	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cord	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Peruke	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Kilby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
he	O
remember	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
off	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
pretended	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Feagin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grinley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburgh	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
four	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Tarrant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
Companion	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
buying	O
of	O
Pigs-Feet	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Half-Moon	O
Tavern	O
,	O
drank	O
2	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
eat	O
Veal-cutlets	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
behind	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
an	O
Egg	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
off	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
his	O
Friend	O
and	O
Mary	O
Watson	O
going	O
into	O
another	O
Chamber	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
laid	O
his	O
Breeches	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Bed	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
something	O
chink	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
nothing	O
.	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
found	O
another	O
between	O
the	O
Sheet	O
and	O
Blanket	O
.	O
He	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
Robb	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Friend	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
came	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Ring	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
admit	O
her	O
to	O
Bail	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
Ring	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
thought	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
might	O
swallow	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
clap	O
'd	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
might	O
put	O
them	O
some	O
where	O
else	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
save	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
own	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Balak	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather-Trace	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
her	O
Royal	O
Highness	O
the	O
Princess	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Highness	O
's	O
Coach	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
Play-House	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
Spare	O
Trace	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
;	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Kingston	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
326	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
;	O
they	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
receive	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Jonathan	I-pers
Delile	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
occupying	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
carried	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Edward	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
and	I-pers
George	I-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Felony	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
Lodging	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hewlet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
common	O
Receiver	O
of	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
feloniously	O
receive	O
4	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cheese	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Low	I-pers
's	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
George	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
entice	O
and	O
encourage	O
Boys	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
thieving	O
,	O
lodg	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
what	O
she	O
pleas	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Things	O
they	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
them	O
spend	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Hock	O
of	O
Bacon	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
Gammon	O
of	O
Bacon	O
of	O
18	O
Pound	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
3	O
s.	O
-	O
Perkins	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
stole	O
Mr.	O
Low	O
's	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
18	O
pence	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
spent	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
Gin	O
.	O
and	O
Hot-Pots	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
These	O
Evidences	O
were	O
very	O
little	O
Boys	O
of	O
about	O
12	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
said	O
)	O
tho	O
'	O
by	O
their	O
Stature	O
one	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
above	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
.	O
The	O
several	O
Facts	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coventry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
defraud	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merick	I-pers
of	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
by	O
false	O
pretences	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Red	O
Wine	O
and	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Sherry	O
,	O
and	O
Change	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
Grocer's-shop	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Wine	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
suspicious	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Boy	O
take	O
care	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Wine	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mees	O
,	O
a	O
Grocer	O
,	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
buying	O
Half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Plumbs	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
change	O
the	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Sherry	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Red	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
watching	O
her	O
,	O
saw	O
her	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Fellows	O
that	O
before	O
stood	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
assisting	O
him	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pursuing	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
ran	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Tower-street	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Baynes	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Baynes	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blewet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
for	O
an	O
100	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
William	B-pers
,	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Malton	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Bearer	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Innis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Baynes	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Prince	B-place
William	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Charing-Cross	I-place
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
his	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
finding	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
remaining	O
Part	O
of	O
an	O
100	O
l.	O
he	O
having	O
exchang	O
'd	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
in	O
buying	O
3	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
;	O
that	O
indeed	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Baynes	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
Mistress	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Supper	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
thought	O
proper	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
when	O
the	O
Boy	O
brought	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
Baynes	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bank	O
Note	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Baynes	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Baynes	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Blewet	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
blaming	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Monkey	O
,	O
and	O
whipt	O
out	O
a	O
Poker	O
he	O
had	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
resenting	O
the	O
Treatment	O
,	O
there	O
ensued	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Artery	O
of	O
his	O
Breast	O
cut	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
Purse	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
his	O
Papers	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Papers	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hannah	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
flung	O
the	O
Bottle	O
that	O
cut	O
his	O
Breast	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Baynes	I-pers
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
after	O
his	O
Purse	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
,	O
pull	O
out	O
several	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
so	O
much	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
Blewet	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Blewet	O
were	O
Fighting	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
where	O
stood	O
Baskets	O
of	O
Bottles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Chairmen	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Porter	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
advancing	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
that	O
Account	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Baynes	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Supper	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
Rabbit	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Innis	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Rabbit	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
sup	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
first	O
,	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Baynes	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
Servant	O
to	O
tye	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
Country	O
Woman	O
she	O
was	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
an	O
Irish	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
her	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
to	O
this	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
to	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
you	O
!	O
denying	O
any	O
such	O
Contract	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
no	O
Wine	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
resenting	O
his	O
leaving	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Purse	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
that	O
Blewet	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Innis	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
where	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Bottles	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
torn	O
almost	O
off	O
,	O
having	O
Papers	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Baynes	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
diligently	O
for	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
remember	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
stop	O
Payment	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
either	O
Date	O
or	O
Number	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baynes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
charge	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
to	O
recover	O
my	O
Note	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Baynes	O
had	O
before	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Papers	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
dropp	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Fight	O
with	O
Blewet	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
praying	O
for	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
it	O
to	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Theodore	B-pers
Willett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
18th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
Henry	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Messieur	O
s	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
not	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
nor	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
18	O
Years	O
,	O
having	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730-1	O
,	O
delivered	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
by	O
his	O
said	O
Masters	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
8796	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Year	O
,	O
imbezzle	O
and	O
convert	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
the	O
Money	O
committed	O
to	O
his	O
Trust	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
his	O
said	O
Masters	O
to	O
deceive	O
and	O
defraud	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Trust	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
charge	O
himself	O
with	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
10716	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
5391	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
then	O
produce	O
Cash	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
1900	O
l.	O
and	O
odd	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Cash	O
,	O
and	O
600	O
l.	O
and	O
odd	O
in	O
Notes	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
being	O
allowed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
since	O
the	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
paid	O
away	O
great	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
receiv	O
'd	O
great	O
Sums	O
from	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
except	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
imbezzel	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
of	O
that	O
individual	O
Money	O
,	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Trust	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
within	O
that	O
Statute	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
being	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pimm	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
their	O
Lodging	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mendes	I-pers
de	I-pers
Costa	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
Bashrite	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Beauffet	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
fast	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
at	O
7	O
found	O
some	O
Panes	O
of	O
Glass	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Casement	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
missing	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
employed	O
to	O
do	O
Business	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
some	O
Misbehaviour	O
had	O
been	O
forbid	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Palmer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
them	O
10	O
l.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
notice	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gunter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Palmer	O
sent	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
weigh	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
seen	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Glynn	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lynn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Stock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
near	O
the	O
Romish	O
Chapel	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
one	O
Hall	O
;	O
that	O
Glynn	O
shov	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
Hall	O
and	O
Butler	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
matter	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
Butler	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
something	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
beat	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
left	O
for	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
off	O
his	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Buckle	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
his	O
Neck	O
between	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
scramble	O
up	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
attempting	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
dead	O
yet	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
,	O
grasp	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
some	O
Minutes	O
before	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
John	O
Hall	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
Drinking	O
and	O
Gaming	O
together	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
Countryman	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
an	O
Irish	O
Man	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
so	O
were	O
they	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Watchm	O
an	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
Butler	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
hold	O
the	O
Hat	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stock	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
Glynn	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
hard	O
Labour	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Waterman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
Rounds	O
,	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
latter	O
had	O
been	O
barbarously	O
us	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
stabb	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
and	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bloody	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
almost	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Hall	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
that	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Knife	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Hall	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
gave	O
the	O
Wounds	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
Butler	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Hall	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Glynn	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Butler	O
's	O
Direction	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
Glynn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Dyer	O
in	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
stabb	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
and	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Parts	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Condition	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
ever	O
known	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Hall	O
;	O
and	O
Glynn	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Dartford	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
these	O
Evidences	O
were	O
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Flynn	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Glynn	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
wrought	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lay	O
one	O
Night	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flynn	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
but	O
in	O
Contradiction	O
to	O
those	O
Evidences	O
,	O
Ellis	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
Ellis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Glynn	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
Glynn	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
an	O
out-cry	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Condition	O
before	O
mentioned	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Woodmash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ormesby	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Left-part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Left-Pap	O
,	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner's-Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Ormes	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ormes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Neighbours	O
and	O
their	O
Wives	O
having	O
been	O
walking	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
by	O
Chelsea-Fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
discoursing	O
together	O
,	O
was	O
often	O
interrupting	O
their	O
discourse	O
,	O
and	O
intermeddling	O
with	O
what	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
they	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
desist	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
to	O
themselves	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
Blockhead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scholar	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
Latin	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
Tradesmen	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
Latin	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
taking	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
Brandy-Face	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hers	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
a	O
Brandy-Face	O
,	O
than	O
his	O
was	O
a	O
Jew's-Face	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Mulatto	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
swarthy	O
Complexion	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Company	O
several	O
times	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
himself	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Chair	O
nearer	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
always	O
be	O
putting	O
in	O
among	O
their	O
Discourse	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
drank	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Pints	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
they	O
paid	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clap	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drawing	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
shreik	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
her	O
Head	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Company	O
that	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
turning	O
it	O
again	O
saw	O
her	O
Husband	O
take	O
his	O
Hand	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
instantly	O
drop	O
'd	O
down	O
dead	O
,	O
never	O
speaking	O
a	O
Word	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
following	O
Mrs.	O
Ormes	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
thrust	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
holding	O
up	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
one	O
stroke	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
closed	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
set	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Backside	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Cane	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
him	O
one	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
drinking	O
with	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
draw	O
'd	O
a	O
Stool	O
or	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
unuibers	O
bene	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
forcing	O
his	O
Discourse	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
talking	O
Latin	O
,	O
repeating	O
the	O
first	O
distich	O
in	O
Cato	O
,	O
Si	O
Dens	O
est	O
animus	O
nobis	O
ut	O
carmina	O
Dicunt	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
they	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
Discourse	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
a	O
Scholar	O
,	O
calling	O
them	O
Scrubs	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Ormes	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
going	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
something	O
about	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
the	O
reply	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
said	O
,	O
Jews	O
were	O
circumcis	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
laugh	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laugh	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
signs	O
of	O
Anger	O
or	O
Passion	O
upon	O
that	O
Account	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flourishing	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
not	O
heard	O
any	O
blow	O
struck	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ormes	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
spoke	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
neither	O
saw	O
nor	O
heard	O
any	O
blow	O
given	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Prudence	B-pers
Middlemore	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
troublesome	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
his	O
Pint	O
of	O
drink	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
past	O
help	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
had	O
penetrated	O
the	O
left	O
Ventricle	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Company	O
were	O
talking	O
very	O
profanely	O
,	O
and	O
laughing	O
and	O
Haspheming	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
bearing	O
their	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
reprov	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Irish	O
Rogue	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
caring	O
to	O
stay	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
paid	O
his	O
3	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
deliver	O
him	O
from	O
such	O
Company	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
thrusting	O
him	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
striking	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
having	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
retreated	O
6	O
or	O
8	O
Yards	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
desist	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Moor-Cocks	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
a	O
game	O
at	O
Skettles	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
or	O
Stick	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
blows	O
;	O
he	O
retreating	O
backwards	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Yards	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
thrusts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
Yards	O
off	O
.	O
Prudence	B-pers
Middlemore	I-pers
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
how	O
the	O
Skettle-Ground	O
was	O
situated	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
if	O
this	O
Evidence	O
stood	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
stood	O
between	O
the	O
Skettle-Ground	O
and	O
the	O
Yard	O
where	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
Bell	O
affirm	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
where	O
he	O
stood	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
playing	O
at	O
Skettles	O
with	O
Bell	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
Sword	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
she	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Yards	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
there	O
been	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Blows	O
struck	O
as	O
Bell	O
had	O
sworn	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
positively	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
blow	O
struck	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catharine	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harle	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
leaden	O
Bullet	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Maid	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
stooping	O
almost	O
double	O
,	O
holding	O
her	O
Hands	O
at	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
Dick	O
has	O
killed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
shot	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
shot	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
setting	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
attempting	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Cordial	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
immediately	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
?	O
But	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
fire	O
the	O
Pistol	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
shoot	O
;	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Pistol	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
above	O
10	O
Minutes	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
before	O
been	O
any	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
some	O
Words	O
might	O
have	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Months	O
before	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
lift	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
has	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
you	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
Mischief	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
Kidneys	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
probing	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
Ball	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
kick	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
3	O
Months	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
my	O
Temper	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
provoke	O
me	O
?	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
be	O
subject	O
to	O
your	O
Humour	O
?	O
That	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
cross	O
the	O
Arm	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
accidentally	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
wilfully	O
.	O
That	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
he	O
using	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
Knives	O
,	O
found	O
fault	O
that	O
she	O
always	O
took	O
a	O
clean	O
Knife	O
to	O
eat	O
her	O
Dinner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
taken	O
down	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
concerning	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Highgate	O
and	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Thornton	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harle	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
had	O
complain	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
Richard	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
subtil	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
18	O
d.	O
for	O
carrying	O
2	O
Boxes	O
for	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
before	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
Words	O
about	O
the	O
making	O
some	O
Water-Gruel	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
saying	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
thus	O
reward	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
for	O
nursing	O
him	O
two	O
Weeks	O
?	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
Mortal	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
at	O
Times	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
insinuate	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
have	O
shot	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
for	O
Landanum	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
being	O
interrogated	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
indeed	O
been	O
cut	O
of	O
Order	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
apprehended	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Cold	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
Things	O
proper	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
no	O
Disorder	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
or	O
Head	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Signs	O
of	O
Lunacy	O
the	O
Day	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
his	O
Business	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
The	O
Apprentice	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
5	O
Grains	O
of	O
Opium	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
kill	O
your	O
self	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Design	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
something	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
