TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1731	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1731	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
24th	O
and	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lee	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Eldrige	I-pers
,	O
Adam	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Millan	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mayer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Ledbury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
Percival	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Anger	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shippey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Rae	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodworth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Birchenough	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
March	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Mary	O
Woodworth	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Birchenough	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
that	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
keep	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
for	O
her	O
use	O
;	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
part	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
Birchenough	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
Woodworth	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
plead	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Birchenough	O
owned	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Woodworth	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nehemiah	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waston	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
but	O
offering	O
much	O
less	O
than	O
the	O
Value	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
buying	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Muslin	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
shewing	O
his	O
Companion	O
Muslin	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
walking	O
forwards	O
and	O
backwards	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Diaper	O
lying	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
perceived	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
hastily	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
his	O
Companion	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
(	O
but	O
his	O
Companion	O
got	O
off	O
)	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Simon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
trifling	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Heskew	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Giffard	I-pers
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Shirt	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purcel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wreckstraw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wreckstraw	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
presently	O
ran	O
out	O
crying	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
first	O
put	O
the	O
Glass	O
into	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Window	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Glass	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
Window	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Oxen	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
Field-Keeper	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Oxen	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
News	O
brought	O
him	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Green-Yard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Round	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
stand	O
at	O
Moore-gate	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
driving	O
the	O
Oxen	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
enquir	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
them	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
pretending	O
to	O
have	O
found	O
them	O
astray	O
in	O
Goswel-Street	O
,	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Oxen	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
an	O
Owner	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
another	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Oxen	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Barbar	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
near	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
frequently	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
selling	O
Chandler's-Ware	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
Lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Chamber-Door	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
hung	O
up	O
the	O
Key	O
on	O
a	O
Nail	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
in	O
that	O
Morning	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
he	O
supposed	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stock	O
of	O
a	O
Turnover	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
near	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Apron	O
full	O
of	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
should	O
never	O
see	O
her	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Kings	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
proof	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Feildhouse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Housing	O
of	O
a	O
Dray-Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Dray-Man	O
having	O
left	O
the	O
Dray	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Customer	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
emty	O
Casks	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Housing	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Plea	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Trace-Chains	O
,	O
and	O
Iron-Pins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
also	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mercy	B-pers
Ingrain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wallup	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
near	O
Marine	B-place
Square	I-place
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
Arm	O
round	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pints	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
thrust	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Chair	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wak	O
'd	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
picking	O
the	O
last	O
Shilling	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
Why	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
able	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodings	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
thinking	O
that	O
proper	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
reason	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Nathan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hannover-Square	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
informed	O
by	O
David	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Parcel	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Plate	O
(	O
though	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Parcel	O
open	O
'd	O
)	O
he	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Plate	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
charge	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Diamond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Timberlake	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canister	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Canister	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Carney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Shift	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Elgar	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
at	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
draw	O
her	O
some	O
Drink	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
pretended	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
Nurse	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pursuing	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Plates	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
-	O
Seal	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
seeing	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
robb	O
'd	O
several	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Job	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Boiler	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Guinea	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
drank	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Candle	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
held	O
him	O
while	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
lik	O
'd	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Guinea	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Noland	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Allwright	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Boys	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Flannel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Seth	B-pers
Aylwing	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
Flannel	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Flannel	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Allwright	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
,	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Armstead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Dinah	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ellis	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Armstead	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
;	O
therefore	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Ellis	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
Armstead	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Solomon	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Soldier	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	B-place
,	O
with	O
the	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
selling	O
Canes	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
)	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
hipp	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Soldier	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Cane	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
threatened	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
violently	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Cane	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
holding	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Soldier	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
up	O
the	O
Matter	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
He	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
putting	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Street	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boston	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wilmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Iron	O
Pins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Felix	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
and	O
Josiah	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
and	O
Felix	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
and	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
stealing	O
Lead	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Messieurs	O
Nicholson	O
and	O
Calvert	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelbrugh	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
B	O
-	O
took	O
the	O
Pin	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
handed	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
B	O
-	O
;	O
B	O
-	O
had	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
uninhabited	O
,	O
a	O
Padlock	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
Seth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
watching	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
those	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Padlock	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cover	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Palace	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
King	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
us	O
'd	O
to	O
frequent	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Kitchin	O
to	O
buy	O
broken	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
in	O
cutting	O
it	O
into	O
Pieces	O
with	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
offered	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
to	O
Mr.	O
Holden	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Board	O
of	O
Green-Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
cut	O
in	O
Pieces	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Gaton	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Ryland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Fortington	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
being	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
they	O
haled	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
damning	O
them	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
abroad	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
Ryland	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
Eaton	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
no	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
part	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
living	O
God	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
live	O
and	O
die	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
rather	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
then	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
meeting	O
with	O
Ryland	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
also	O
.	O
-	O
Fortington	O
confirm	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
Hood	O
over	O
her	O
Face	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
Courage	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
much	O
fear	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Law-Suit	O
depending	O
upon	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
proceed	O
to	O
the	O
Tryal	O
;	O
so	O
no	O
Evidence	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Malachy	B-pers
Southy	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Water-Man	O
's	O
Silver	O
Badge	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
twelve	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Falconbridge	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
George	O
Abraham	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Waterman	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Falconbridge	O
,	O
wore	O
her	O
Badge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
dressing	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
having	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
by	O
upon	O
another	O
Boat	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
who	O
were	O
Watermen	O
's	O
Boys	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
afterwards	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
)	O
took	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Badge	O
and	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Coat	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
-	O
Henry	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
seeing	O
the	O
Coat	O
hang	O
on	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Cholniley	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Badge	O
and	O
Buttons	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Coat	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Badge	O
and	O
Buttons	O
to	O
Katherine	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
(	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
run	O
away	O
)	O
for	O
32	O
s.	O
the	O
Badge	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kilham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
,	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Sash	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
Body	O
without	O
Doors	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
under	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
putting	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
some	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Olive	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Iron	O
Bolts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Fonseca	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27	O
h	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Cooling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Seat	O
of	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Beddoe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
,	O
two	O
Chairmen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Seat	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
not	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Tompson	O
inquiring	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
pass	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
and	O
indicted	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Seat	O
;	O
they	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
admiring	O
,	O
interrogated	O
Justice	O
Giffard	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Examination	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Commitment	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Seat	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
advised	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
them	O
for	O
Perjury	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Vindication	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilmer	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Hats	O
,	O
Value	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pack	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Hats	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Stanwel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stole	O
the	O
Hats	O
.	O
-	O
Shipton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Wilmer	O
brought	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Hats	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Idle	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Glass-House	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
by	O
Pilfering	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	B-place
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
two	O
Girls	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
consented	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
intruded	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
round	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
herself	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
slung	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
and	O
Constable	O
confirm	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
their	O
apprehending	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
what	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
left	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
deposit	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
as	O
the	O
mentioned	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
except	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Husband	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
and	O
to	O
him	O
was	O
married	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
was	O
again	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
being	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
opened	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
21	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
Artifice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
very	O
disagreeable	O
to	O
his	O
Relations	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Barbadoes	O
,	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
several	O
Months	O
:	O
but	O
pretending	O
the	O
Country	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
probably	O
rather	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
tired	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
desirous	O
of	O
trying	O
some	O
variety	O
;	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
they	O
cohabited	O
for	O
several	O
Months	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
very	O
bad	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
convers	O
'd	O
with	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
besides	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
happening	O
to	O
become	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
by	O
some	O
Arts	O
and	O
Inducements	O
he	O
married	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
several	O
Months	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
Husband	O
living	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
heard	O
her	O
talk	O
of	O
Marriage	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
their	O
Wedding	O
;	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
putting	O
on	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
joining	O
of	O
their	O
Hands	O
together	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
wish	O
'd	O
them	O
Joy	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
and	O
by	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
married	O
them	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
Clergyman	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
's	O
Father	O
arrested	O
him	O
the	O
very	O
Night	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pukering	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
married	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Mortram	O
,	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
gave	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Ring	O
put	O
upon	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Bisket	O
over	O
their	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
's	O
Father	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Son	O
was	O
ruin	O
'd	O
by	O
marrying	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
afterwards	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Father	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
nine	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
had	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
about	O
as	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
cohabited	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
after	O
their	O
Marriage	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
own	O
'd	O
one	O
another	O
as	O
Husband	O
and	O
Wife	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Hustlewood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
was	O
still	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
that	O
Day	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
also	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
furnished	O
her	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Leicester-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
her	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
Wedding	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
saying	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
cohabiting	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
Mistress	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
being	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
so	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Occassion	O
to	O
call	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bilby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
wound	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
did	O
throw	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Blows	O
,	O
Bruises	O
,	O
and	O
mortal	O
Wounds	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
languishing	O
,	O
liv	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
10th	O
to	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
did	O
die	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
felonious	O
slaying	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
in	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
mind	O
me	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
in	O
my	O
Cellar	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
Glass	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
you	O
Lye	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Pail	O
and	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
House-Brush	O
that	O
stood	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Son	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
making	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Hussey	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Lye	O
?	O
That	O
then	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
push	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Post	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
into	O
the	O
Chanel	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
near	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
bled	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
remained	O
speechless	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
strong	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pains	O
of	O
Death	O
were	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
Dr	O
.	O
Steward	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
under	O
the	O
Spleen	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
mortified	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
the	O
Mesentory	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
outward	O
Contusions	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
being	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
Blood	O
was	O
settled	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
dead	O
Persons	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
suppose	O
the	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
to	O
proceed	O
from	O
any	O
inward	O
Distemper	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
some	O
outward	O
Bruises	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Duddal	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Body	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
Instestines	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
Kidney	O
was	O
mortified	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lateral	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Spleen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
of	O
Opinion	O
it	O
proceeded	O
from	O
outward	O
Bruises	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Plucknet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Nurse	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pail	O
on	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Pain	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Doctor	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
proceed	O
from	O
inward	O
Bruises	O
.	O
T	O
homas	O
Wilson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
great	O
Violence	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Grate	O
of	O
the	O
Common	O
Sewer	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
Mr.	O
Munden	O
would	O
die	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
although	O
she	O
were	O
hanged	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Timbrel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Smith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tap-Room	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
two	O
Bottles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
one	O
Glass	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
lie	O
like	O
a	O
Fool	O
and	O
an	O
Ass	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
catch	O
up	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
and	O
strike	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Attempt	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Hand-brush	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Son	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
push	O
upon	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
with	O
his	O
Face	O
upon	O
the	O
Grate	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Peach	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
push	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
die	O
and	O
be	O
damned	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
and	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
her	O
Fist	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
against	O
a	O
short	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Grate	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
die	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
die	O
and	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Everington	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
Side	O
with	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Hand-brush	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
own	O
Son	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saying	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Hussey	O
,	O
Hussey	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Lye	O
?	O
but	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
Blow	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
first	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
in	O
her	O
Cellar	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Lye	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Hussey	O
,	O
you	O
Lye	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Lye	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
Lye	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Pail	O
and	O
swung	O
it	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
hit	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Brush	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Son	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Munden	O
threatned	O
to	O
push	O
her	O
down	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
making	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
over	O
a	O
short	O
Post	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
coming	O
towards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
following	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
I	O
Lye	O
you	O
Jade	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
her	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
go	O
you	O
down	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
both	O
drunk	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
me	O
do	O
?	O
I	O
stand	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
Head	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Pail	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Hand-Brush	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
push	O
with	O
her	O
two	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Common	O
Sewer	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
penney	O
weight	O
of	O
silver	O
Waste	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Silver-Spinner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Winder	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Servants	O
had	O
complain	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
miss	O
'd	O
Plate-Waste	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scale-draw	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Waste	O
was	O
weigh	O
'd	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
it	O
wanted	O
weight	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
taxing	O
his	O
Man	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Waste	O
was	O
weighed	O
again	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Scale-draw	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
having	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
lighting	O
the	O
Fire	O
he	O
weighed	O
the	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
there	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Coals	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
calling	O
down	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
the	O
Waste	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
made	O
up	O
just	O
the	O
quantity	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
Grains	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
suspected	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
other	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
intrusted	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
weigh	O
'd	O
the	O
Waste	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
7	O
penny	O
weight	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Weight	O
was	O
2	O
oz	O
.	O
13	O
penny	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
mark	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
that	O
which	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
up	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Scale-draw	O
,	O
the	O
Weight	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
mark	O
'd	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Godding	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Master	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Waste	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
had	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Trade	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
let	O
her	O
Daughter	O
go	O
to	O
Work	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
occasion	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
Daughter	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
swore	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
transport	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
500	O
l.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gadsbey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
Conversation	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
Daughter	O
a	O
Charge	O
to	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Waste	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
,	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sorting	O
of	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
might	O
not	O
lose	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
whereas	O
he	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
that	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Shed	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
for	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
gone	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Maid	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
his	O
Sister	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Waste	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
yes	O
;	O
for	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Waste	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Canliff	I-pers
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Trade	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
does	O
give	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
with	O
her	O
Work	O
,	O
Waste	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
that	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
says	O
is	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Waste	O
of	O
that	O
Business	O
is	O
generally	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thinks	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
Waste	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Horse-Shoes	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
of	O
about	O
60	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
camein	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
suddled	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
Day	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
chusing	O
Parish-Officers	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
abus	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
his	O
Debts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Daughter	O
to	O
the	O
Hop	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buckle	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
desiring	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
his	O
Debts	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
ago	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
searce	O
a	O
Shoe	O
to	O
your	O
Feet	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Coat	O
to	O
your	O
Back	O
,	O
though	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
Proud	O
now	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
his	O
Elbow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
against	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Chimney	O
:	O
The	O
Fire	O
was	O
just	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
fresh	O
Coals	O
thrown	O
on	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
parted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
keep	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Arm	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pot	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
hurly-burly	O
the	O
Deceased	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
Victualling	O
House	O
in	O
Whitecross-Street	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Everet	O
came	O
in	O
blowing	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
sink	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Prosick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
more	O
fit	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
your	O
Bed	O
.	O
T	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
my	O
poor	O
Dolly	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Body	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rattled	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dying	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
came	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Liquor	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
suddled	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
spilt	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
shaking	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Everet	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
about	O
begging	O
for	O
Work	O
,	O
you	O
borrow	O
'd	O
30	O
Pounds	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
your	O
Wife	O
's	O
Funeral	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Pounds	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
unpaid	O
yet	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Everet	O
rose	O
from	O
his	O
Seat	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
one	O
Foot	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
buckling	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
height	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
justled	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Elbow	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Everet	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
these	O
Affronts	O
of	O
you	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
Shaw	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Shaw	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Pot	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Shaw	O
run	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
over	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
push	O
'd	O
one	O
at	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
strove	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
Everet	O
behind	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
held	O
,	O
and	O
Everet	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God-sake	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
strike	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Everet	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Complaint	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
give	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
any	O
Occasion	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Plumstead	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Son	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
Murther	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
very	O
carefully	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Fissure	O
nor	O
Fracture	O
,	O
nor	O
Contusion	O
;	O
but	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Eye	O
a	O
small	O
Redness	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
rais	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Nail	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
Body	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
might	O
cause	O
any	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
died	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Father	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Redcross-street	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
to	O
Murther	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
beer	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
any	O
Occasion	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
that	O
grew	O
very	O
Ill	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
continuing	O
very	O
Ill	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Shaw	O
had	O
punch	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Elbow	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Rogue	O
Shaw	O
has	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wych	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
and	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver-Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Skilling	O
and	O
five	O
Keys	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Chelsea-Fields	B-place
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
Dark	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
beat	O
him	O
very	O
heartily	O
,	O
and	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
narrow	O
Escape	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
Andrews	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Hat	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Pye-Fields	O
near	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Green	O
Purse	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
from	O
his	O
Friend	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Night-Gown	O
;	O
that	O
George	B-pers
Wych	I-pers
beating	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
the	O
Butt-End	O
of	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
backwards	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
directed	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
were	O
they	O
lodg	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
-	O
Brown	O
.	O
-	O
Brown	O
,	O
a	O
Beadle	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Brown	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
Brown	O
,	O
Wych	O
,	O
and	O
Anderson	O
,	O
just	O
out	O
of	O
Kinsington	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
them	O
,	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
some	O
ill	O
design	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
God	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
all	O
here	O
together	O
?	O
But	O
as	O
to	O
Williams	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
following	O
,	O
Brown	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
him	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Boarded	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Brown's-Gardens	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
Wycb	O
lay	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Clothes	O
being	O
off	O
,	O
having	O
only	O
his	O
Shirt	O
on	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
found	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
a	O
stud	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
;	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
Andrews	O
in	O
Bed	O
alone	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
.	O
That	O
examining	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Wych	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Things	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
in	O
search	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Fellows	O
had	O
thrust	O
the	O
Things	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Keys	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Dutch	O
Skilling	O
,	O
Andrews	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
Justice	O
Blackerby	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
did	O
own	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
and	O
other	O
Robberies	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
next	O
following	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Brown's-Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Wych	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
and	O
Brown	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
Wych	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
lodge	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
1	O
or	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Keys	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Keys	O
and	O
Pocket-Piece	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
Andrews	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Seal	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Thorp	O
.	O
-	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
Wych	O
and	O
Andrews	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
they	O
own	O
'd	O
this	O
and	O
other	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
Williams	O
that	O
Day	O
at	O
a	O
Barbers	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
all	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
George	B-pers
Wych	I-pers
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Educated	O
at	O
Westminster-School	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
sear	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
true	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Tutor	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Years	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Wych	O
had	O
been	O
Sick	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
for	O
two	O
Months	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Sick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
attended	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
interrogated	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
upon	O
what	O
Account	O
he	O
did	O
attend	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Salivation	O
.	O
-	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Anderson	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Ware-House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
about	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
lay	O
out	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
kept	O
had	O
Company	O
.	O
-	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Williams	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
till	O
about	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Chapman	O
,	O
sold	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
other	O
Goods	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
Cambridge	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
while	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
intrusted	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
several	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
Months	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
tho	O
Jury	O
found	O
George	B-pers
Wych	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Anderson	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
acquitted	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
George	O
Wych	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Andrews	O
and	O
William	O
Williams	O
,	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
Hanover-Square	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Seabrook	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Common-Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
2	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
near	O
Buckingham	B-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
having	O
a	O
lighted	O
Link	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
five	O
Men	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
put	O
out	O
your	O
Link	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
taking	O
them	O
for	O
drunken	O
Men	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
?	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
Your	O
Bl	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
you	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
put	O
out	O
your	O
Link	O
;	O
and	O
Wych	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Link	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Foot	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Stud	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
their	O
Faces	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
his	O
Link	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
describ	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Officer	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
throw	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
;	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Stud	O
found	O
on	O
Wych	O
's	O
Bed	O
was	O
his	O
Stud	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Seabrook	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
confirming	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
George	B-pers
Wych	I-pers
took	O
the	O
Link	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Foot	O
;	O
that	O
Anderson	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
himself	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
but	O
four	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Night	O
following	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
having	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
near	O
Stretton-Ground	O
,	O
Seabrook	O
and	O
Williams	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
Wych	O
and	O
Anderson	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Brown's-Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Dubois	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
Brown	O
and	O
Wych	O
by	O
the	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
but	O
Wych	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Dubois	O
brought	O
Brown	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Robbing	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
a	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
accordingly	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beadle	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Saunders	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
These	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
again	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Seabrook	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Joseph	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
,	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
his	O
Night-Gown	O
in	O
Chelsea-Fields	B-place
,	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Thorp	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Landlord	O
,	O
in	O
Brown's-Gardens	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Robbing	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Guinea	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
stare	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
pretending	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
they	O
shar	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Trials	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Wych	O
and	O
Anderson	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Williams	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wych	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
fourth	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Wedding-Ring	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stone	O
with	O
a	O
Hole	O
and	O
String	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
broad	O
Way	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
near	O
Orchard-Street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Wych	O
took	O
off	O
her	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
Andrews	O
took	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stone	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
the	O
Stone	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
common	O
Pebble	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
natural	O
Hole	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
String	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
for	O
her	O
Fancy	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Lucky-Stone	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
likewise	O
;	O
but	O
Williams	O
and	O
Seabrook	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
gone	O
home	O
.	O
-	O
Tireman	O
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
two	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
sate	O
one	O
down	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
broad	O
way	O
,	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
some	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
caus	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Woman	O
shrick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horses	O
mov	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
cry	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
fright	O
,	O
and	O
burst	O
out	O
a	O
crying	O
;	O
that	O
himself	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
telling	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
was	O
by	O
and	O
over-heard	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
describing	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
.	O
Dubois	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
latter	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
Brown	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Wych	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Stone	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Andrews	O
's	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
also	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
desiring	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
in	O
Chains	O
;	O
before	O
Sentence	O
was	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
why	O
Judgement	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
pass	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
according	O
to	O
Laws	O
made	O
no	O
reply	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
his	O
Soul	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
4.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Anderson	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Wych	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
30.	O
John	B-pers
Allwright	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
E	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
Sarah	O
Birchenough	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boston	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Carney	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Diamond	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fieldhouse	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	O
Hall	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Heskew	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Astew	O
,	O
alias	O
King	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Noland	I-pers
,	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purtel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ryland	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shippy	I-pers
,	O
Malachy	B-pers
Southy	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilmer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
3	O
.	O
H	O
-	O
S	O
-	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wynch	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bilby	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
,	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
1.	O
Jane	B-pers
Carney	I-pers
.	O
Books	O
just	O
printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
.	O
LA	O
Plum	O
Volante	O
.	O
Or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-hand	O
improved	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
most	O
Swift	O
,	O
Regular	O
,	O
and	O
Easy	O
Method	O
of	O
Short-hand-writing	O
yet	O
Excant	O
.	O
Composed	O
after	O
Fifty	O
Years	O
Practice	O
and	O
Improvement	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Art	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Observation	O
of	O
other	O
Methods	O
and	O
intent	O
Study	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
Aditions	O
of	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
amended	O
,	O
By	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Miraculous	O
Convention	O
from	O
Popery	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
or	O
Joseph	O
Perry	O
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
:	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Goy	O
of	O
Divine	O
Grace	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Protection	O
of	O
Divine	O
Providence	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Goodness	O
of	O
God	O
Manifested	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Military	O
Discipline	O
.	O
The	O
Word	O
of	O
Command	O
,	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Exercising	O
the	O
Musket	O
and	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Carbine	O
,	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
performed	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Horse	O
and	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
B.	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Singing	O
Master	O
's	O
Guide	O
to	O
his	O
Scholars	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Psalms	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Translations	O
;	O
the	O
Old	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
By	O
several	O
Hands	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sternhold	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
Barron	O
,	O
Patrick	O
,	O
Tate	O
and	O
Brady	O
,	O
Milbourne	O
and	O
Sandys	O
.	O
Contriv	O
'd	O
for	O
Common	O
Use	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Tunes	O
in	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
By	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ewelm	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
Singing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
further	O
Guide	O
to	O
Parish	O
Clarks	O
:	O
or	O
,	O
any	O
other	O
religiously	O
and	O
devoutly	O
disposed	O
to	O
make	O
Use	O
of	O
these	O
Instructions	O
.	O
Being	O
contriv	O
'd	O
for	O
common	O
Use	O
,	O
by	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
Ewlem	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
Singing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Spelling	O
,	O
Containing	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
,	O
B	B-pers
,	I-pers
C	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Children	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
Alphabets	O
and	O
Syliables	O
,	O
with	O
short	O
Rules	O
and	O
Examples	O
of	O
dividing	O
Words	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Rules	O
for	O
true	O
Spelling	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
Writing	O
of	O
English	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Question	O
and	O
Answer	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Two	O
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
useful	O
Words	O
,	O
whose	O
Spelling	O
or	O
Sense	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
mistaken	O
.	O
Also	O
Christian	O
Names	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
J.	O
P.	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
fifth	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
.	O
Price	O
9	O
d.	O
The	O
Greatness	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Unspeakableness	O
of	O
the	O
Loss	O
thereof	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Causes	O
of	O
the	O
Losing	O
.	O
First	O
preached	O
in	O
Pinners-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
ow	O
enlarged	O
.	O
and	O
published	O
for	O
good	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Bunyan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Shop	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Sold	O
to	O
all	O
Stationers	O
and	O
School-masters	O
in	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
,	O
Pieces	O
for	O
Christmas	O
,	O
Easter	O
and	O
Whitsunside	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
wholesale	O
and	O
retale	O
,	O
curiously	O
engraved	O
on	O
Copper-plates	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
King	O
George	O
the	O
II	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Jerusalem	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Temple	O
of	O
Solomon	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Geometry	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Haman	O
in	O
ed	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Hunting-Piece	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Grammar	O
and	O
Writing-School	O
.	O
9	O
Christ	O
's	O
Burial	O
.	O
10	O
The	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Show	O
.	O
11	O
Moses	O
in	O
the	O
Ark	O
of	O
Bull	O
rushes	O
.	O
12	O
History	O
of	O
Tobit	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Christ	O
's	O
Ascension	O
.	O
14	O
The	O
seven	O
Sciences	O
.	O
15	O
Dorattis	O
and	O
Fawnia	O
.	O
16	O
History	O
of	O
Judith	O
and	O
Holosernis	O
.	O
17	O
The	O
four	O
Evangelists	O
.	O
18	O
Stool-Ball	O
.	O
19	O
Joseph	O
flying	O
into	O
Egypt	O
.	O
20	O
Crucifixion	O
;	O
And	O
many	O
others	O
i	O
whole	O
Sheets	O
and	O
half	O
Sheets	O
:	O
Likewise	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
an	O
Elegiac	O
Poem	O
in	O
Commemoration	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Most	O
sacred	O
Majesty	O
K.	O
George	O
,	O
engraven	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Also	O
Gospel	O
Mystery	O
Emblematically	O
illustrated	O
engraven	O
on	O
a	O
large	O
Copper-plate	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
CATO	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Case	O
and	O
History	O
of	O
Self-Murder	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
and	O
Display	O
'd	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Principles	O
of	O
Reason	O
,	O
Justice	O
,	O
Law	O
,	O
Religion	O
,	O
Fortitude	O
,	O
Love	O
of	O
ourselves	O
and	O
our	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
Example	O
;	O
A	O
Solution	O
of	O
this	O
Problem	O
,	O
whether	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Sense	O
,	O
Goodness	O
,	O
and	O
Courage	O
,	O
ever	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
can	O
,	O
Kill	O
Himself	O
?	O
Particularly	O
calculated	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
Nation	O
:	O
Occassion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Stabbing	O
Himself	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instances	O
.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Lecture	O
,	O
deliver	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Oratory	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Henley	B-pers
,	I-pers
M.	I-pers
A	I-pers
.	I-pers
Publish	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Hearers	O
.	O
A	O
speedy	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
ITCH	O
,	O
As	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George's-Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
is	O
Sold	O
,	O
A	O
WATER	O
which	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
ITCH	O
,	O
or	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
offensive	O
Scent	O
;	O
and	O
hath	O
been	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
Years	O
Experience	O
:	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
Prepared	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
The	O
true	O
Essence	O
or	O
Spirits	O
of	O
SCURVY-GRASS	O
,	O
both	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
most	O
Excellent	O
in	O
all	O
Degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Great	O
Elixir	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
called	O
DAFFY	O
's	O
ELIXIR	O
,	O
truly	O
prepared	O
from	O
the	O
best	O
Ingredients	O
,	O
very	O
useful	O
in	O
all	O
Families	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Half-pint	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
Published	O
,	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
,	O
of	O
A	O
PRACTICAL	O
TREATISE	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Second	O
Thoughts	O
on	O
the	O
Consequences	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Simple	O
Gonorrhea	O
,	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
from	O
Venereal	O
Embraces	O
,	O
Self-pollution	O
,	O
improperly	O
called	O
Onanism	O
,	O
or	O
Natural	O
Imbecillity	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Virulent	O
Gonhorrhea	O
,	O
or	O
Clap	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Lues	O
,	O
or	O
Grand	O
Pox	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
plainly	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
exact	O
Degrees	O
of	O
Difference	O
;	O
with	O
their	O
Signs	O
.	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
Prognosticks	O
,	O
and	O
Cures	O
in	O
all	O
Cases	O
,	O
their	O
Beginnings	O
,	O
Progress	O
,	O
and	O
fatal	O
Periods	O
,	O
when	O
neglected	O
or	O
unskillfully	O
managed	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
their	O
absolute	O
Cure	O
,	O
without	O
Violence	O
or	O
Injury	O
is	O
compleated	O
.	O
With	O
proper	O
and	O
effectual	O
Remedies	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
several	O
Stages	O
,	O
prescribed	O
and	O
recommended	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
that	O
proposterous	O
way	O
of	O
Venery	O
with	O
Machines	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Dangers	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
little	O
expected	O
)	O
which	O
attend	O
that	O
vile	O
practice	O
.	O
Also	O
many	O
other	O
useful	O
Discoveries	O
relating	O
to	O
Infections	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
not	O
before	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
annexed	O
,	O
a	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
practice	O
of	O
Salivating	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Whole	O
fitted	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
Patients	O
as	O
young	O
Practitioners	O
.	O
By	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CAM	I-pers
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-Church-Yard	O
;	O
also	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
E.	O
Midwinter	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
;	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
J.	O
Hodges	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
Mackeven	O
at	O
the	O
Lamp	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
Price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
Just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
of	O
,	O
The	O
Spelling	O
Dictionary	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
common	O
Words	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
Tongue	O
,	O
carefully	O
compared	O
with	O
the	O
original	O
Languages	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
are	O
derived	O
and	O
marked	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
pronounced	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
DYCHE	O
.	O
Pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Sold	O
by	O
R.	O
WARE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Sun	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
at	O
Amen-Corner	O
.	O
Also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
large	O
House	O
Bibles	O
,	O
Folio	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
six	O
Maps	O
of	O
sacred	O
Geography	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brief	O
Concordance	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
easy	O
finding	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Places	O
therein	O
contained	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Downame	B-pers
,	I-pers
B.	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Bound	O
in	O
Calf	O
Leather	O
-	O
1	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
per	O
Book	O
.	O
And	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cutts	O
at	O
2	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
Ditto	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
fine	O
