TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1731	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1731	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
Aland	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Thoroton	B-pers
Pocklington	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pardoe	I-pers
,	O
Tobias	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Latham	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Woollaston	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Skelback	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pewford	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spurling	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Loughton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Furbur	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Biggins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Rushout	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ogbourne	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Nebury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dehue	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Balladine	O
Silk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
under	O
Pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Silk	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Antonio	B-pers
Key	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
's	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Carnegy	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Twisted	O
Web	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
Diaper	O
Web	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Sheep-Skin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farrer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
William	O
Carnegy	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Bennet	O
being	O
observ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
wait	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
daily	O
,	O
(	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
Prayers	O
at	O
St.	O
Sepulchres	O
Church	O
)	O
and	O
frequently	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
to	O
watch	O
and	O
mind	O
rightly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
before-mentioned	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
also	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bennet	O
,	O
by	O
Carnegy	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Carnegy	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
various	O
Times	O
given	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bennet	O
.	O
Bennet	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
Carnegy	B-pers
;	O
but	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
being	O
contradicted	O
by	O
Carnegy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
not	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Samborn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
hung	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pass	O
by	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Door	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Gown	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
sells	O
old	O
Clothes	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crafts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Saws	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Joiners-Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Crossby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Stockings	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
hung	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Saws	O
,	O
and	O
Joyners	O
Tools	O
,	O
it	O
to	O
pear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tools	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Vernon	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
awak	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
bargaine	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
half	O
hundred	O
Weights	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rollings	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge-Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Both	O
these	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk-Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Shugbrug	B-pers
Sill	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
July	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Cambell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lamb	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Dismore	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Dismore	O
Brown	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
and	O
being	O
stunn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
fall	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
felt	O
some-body	O
pulling	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
his	O
Rings	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
sent	O
Notice	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hardy	O
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hardy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
,	O
having	O
brought	O
the	O
Rings	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wil	I-pers
ford	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Rings	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Lad	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Rings	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
two	O
other	O
Boy	O
s	O
,	O
that	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
probable	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
depos	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Upp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
Westminster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Brass-Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Emly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Emly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shifts	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Sandish	I-pers
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Shifts	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Linen	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Garden	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
hung	O
up	O
to	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
-Juby	B-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catharine	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
No-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Stockings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton-Gown	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alban	I-place
's	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baylis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Macculler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
about	O
2	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
taking	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
absented	O
himself	O
from	O
his	O
Service	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Coghill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Holdsworth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
owing	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
desiring	O
to	O
Lodge	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
without	O
paying	O
either	O
Debt	O
or	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
hanging	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
at	O
his	O
Bed	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
Swearing	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Renny	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Dowglas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Kenny	B-pers
Urquart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gabriel	I-place
Fenchurch-street	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
Country	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
he	O
usually	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
Effects	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Renny	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Son	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
late	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Box	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
(	O
which	O
contained	O
that	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
in	O
India-Bonds	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
)	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	B-pers
Dowglas	I-pers
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
jarr	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Notes	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Note	O
had	O
been	O
paid	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
India-Bonds	O
were	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Son	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
did	O
find	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
jarr	O
,	O
and	O
Dowglas	O
coming	O
from	O
behind	O
it	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kenny	I-pers
standing	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
some	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
went	O
that	O
Night	O
back	O
to	O
Kennington	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
his	O
Father	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Dowglas	O
's	O
being	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
he	O
did	O
find	O
the	O
India-Bonds	O
under	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Renny	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
India-Bonds	O
,	O
nor	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
Dowglas	O
's	O
being	O
there	O
was	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
her	O
Sweet-Heart	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
courted	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
7	O
Months	O
before	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dowglas	I-pers
made	O
the	O
same	O
Plea	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
Urquart	O
's	O
being	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
Ship-board	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Edmunds	O
at	O
Rotherbith	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Watch	O
hung	O
at	O
his	O
Bed's-Head	O
in	O
his	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
also	O
lay	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
stolen	O
away	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cabbin-Window	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
37	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Piggot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Morrice	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Billiard	O
Stick	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
the	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Person	O
.	O
Captain	O
Littler	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
were	O
playing	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Billiards	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Colt	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
laid	O
a	O
Bett	O
of	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
Game	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
glued	O
into	O
the	O
Billiard-stick	O
dropped	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
sent	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
mended	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
happening	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Dispute	O
about	O
the	O
Bett	O
while	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
young	O
Rogue	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
along	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
this	O
Dispute	O
had	O
not	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
the	O
Billiard-stick	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
so	O
bad	O
consequence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
falling	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
perceiving	O
his	O
Head	O
to	O
bleed	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
common	O
broken	O
Head	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
amends	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Water	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scissors	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Hair	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
wash	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
bleeding	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
fell	O
a	O
trembling	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
into	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
immediately	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Fit	O
anon	O
;	O
and	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
immediately	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Wilks	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
injured	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
lov	O
'd	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
all	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
behaving	O
himself	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
would	O
play	O
at	O
Billiards	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
.	O
Captain	O
Colt	B-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Blow	O
given	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
could	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
Boy	O
any	O
hurt	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Blow	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
little	O
Rogue	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
staid	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
this	O
Dispute	O
had	O
not	O
happened	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Blow	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
,	O
that	O
could	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
Boy	O
any	O
Injury	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
any	O
Passion	O
,	O
or	O
angry	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
the	O
Blow	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
with	O
any	O
Intent	O
to	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
repeat	O
the	O
Blow	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
the	O
Blow	O
was	O
given	O
with	O
any	O
Violence	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
hurt	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
apprehend	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
mortal	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
Evidences	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
much	O
greater	O
Blows	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Son	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
thinking	O
,	O
without	O
doing	O
him	O
any	O
Injury	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Blow	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
with	O
any	O
Violence	O
;	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
it	O
about	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
came	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
saved	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Life	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
for	O
sooner	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Coronal	O
Suture	O
,	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
divided	O
the	O
Pericrarium	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
Fracture	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
apprehends	O
that	O
the	O
Concussion	O
had	O
wounded	O
an	O
Artery	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
have	O
thought	O
it	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Blow	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
Instrument	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
about	O
three	O
Ounces	O
of	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
third	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
trepanned	O
immediately	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
saved	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
by	O
preventing	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
pressing	O
upon	O
the	O
Vessels	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tast	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
strong	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
slight	O
to	O
see	O
such	O
Symptoms	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
Wound	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
Instruments	O
to	O
trepan	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barnet	O
,	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
in	O
strong	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bled	O
freely	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
prob	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
fractur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
been	O
only	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
such	O
a	O
Blow	O
could	O
have	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
Convulsion-Fits	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Mayne	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
his	O
Mate	O
to	O
Barbadoes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
or	O
strike	O
a	O
Man	O
a	O
Blow	O
all	O
the	O
Voyage	O
.	O
Slingsby	O
Bethel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
Conversant	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
or	O
Guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Misbehaviour	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
good-natur	O
'd	O
,	O
Honerable	O
,	O
and	O
inoffensive	O
Man	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner's-Inquest	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
one	O
Morgan	O
Jones	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Coat	O
with	O
Plate	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
down	O
Fig-Lane	B-place
last	O
Lady-Day-Eve	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Body	O
,	O
quick	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
Horse	O
's	O
Reins	O
,	O
lean	O
'd	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
his	O
Mane	O
,	O
and	O
stooping	O
down	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Horse	O
Pistol	O
against	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Things	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thinks	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Gambier	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
positively	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
an	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Blanket	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
growth	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
wasted	O
,	O
being	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
lain	O
there	O
several	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sweatingham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
at	O
Work	O
with	O
her	O
picking	O
of	O
Strawberries	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
a	O
Child	O
cry	O
?	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
continually	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
a	O
New-born	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Ears	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
her	O
Escape	O
?	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
herself	O
to	O
be	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Power	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
(	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Pond	O
to	O
wash	O
a	O
Mop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
going	O
to	O
wash	O
a	O
Tin-pot	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
her	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
feel	O
how	O
soft	O
it	O
was	O
grown	O
in	O
a	O
Weeks	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
tracked	O
her	O
by	O
some	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
than	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
Months	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
appeared	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
lank	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
had	O
look	O
'd	O
big	O
before	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gathering	O
Strawberries	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
like	O
Question	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
Mary	B-pers
Sweatingham	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
her	O
Opinion	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Growth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Blakesly	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cotteril	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Bottolph	O
's	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
privately	O
steal	O
a	O
Watch	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dyche	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
take	O
a	O
Guinea	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dyche	I-pers
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
without	O
causing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
or	O
giving	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wailes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Seed	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Boy	O
taken	O
in	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
Ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
Inn	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Ostler	O
's	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
himself	O
a	O
new	O
Suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
hired	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bell-Size	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spent	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Little	I-pers
Bess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Rose	B-pers
Merriweather	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
having	O
gotten	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
so	O
till	O
about	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
had	O
handed	O
out	O
two	O
Spoons	O
to	O
her	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
surprized	O
by	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Darwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
and	O
stealing	O
10	O
Cotton	O
and	O
Worsted	O
Caps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
1729	O
;	O
but	O
No-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowsel	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Malloon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Fans	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pendleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Darwel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Iredel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gowns	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gowns	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Coslin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Shannel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver-Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fitchet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Iron	O
Cheeks	O
of	O
a	O
Grate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Rawler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
producing	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Camfield	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cambel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Black-Friars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1727	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
about	O
4	O
Years	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Drawer	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
admiring	O
how	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
keeping	O
it	O
under	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
try	O
an	O
Experiment	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
by	O
marking	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
a	O
Cross	O
on	O
the	O
Curl	O
of	O
the	O
Hair	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
side	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
done	O
so	O
before	O
Witness	O
,	O
she	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
after	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
miss	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
goes	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
desires	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
she	O
her	O
self	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
desire	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lent	O
,	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
mark	O
'd	O
Money	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Burket	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
borrow	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Desire	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Bradley	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
mark	O
'd	O
Money	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Swore	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
mark	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
to	O
confirm	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
own	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
taking	O
a	O
Guinea	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Chick-Lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
apprehended	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
Brass	O
Locks	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Michael	O
James	B-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Nanny	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
so	O
fully	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Brannan	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Linen	O
and	O
Woollen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
herself	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seized	O
Martha	B-pers
Brannan	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
Row	O
with	O
Bundles	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
at	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
secured	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
coming	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
call	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
did	O
pawn	O
a	O
Hood	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
where	O
Mary	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Brannan	I-pers
,	O
lodged	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Brannan	I-pers
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
inticed	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
Mary	O
Row	O
,	O
who	O
promised	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Husband	O
worth	O
200	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
Clothes	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
appear	O
handsome	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
Martha	O
Brannan	O
and	O
Mary	O
Row	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
knew	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
-	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Waterman	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
Buttons	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left-side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
Half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
11	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
having	O
no	O
Weapon	O
drawn	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
unlawful	O
slaying	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Manwaring	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Palfriman	I-pers
depos	O
ed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
charge	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
stabbed	O
me	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
asking	O
,	O
Who	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
White	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
Door	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
Snuff	O
twice	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
looking	O
towards	O
Abington	B-place
's	I-place
Coffee-House	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Grey's-Inn	I-place
Gate	I-place
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
white	O
Clothes	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
laced	O
Hat	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
bid	O
the	O
Deceased	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
off	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
no	O
Blood	O
.	O
That	O
another	O
Porter	O
cried	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
charge	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
Damage	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
replied	O
,	O
There	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
go	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Porters	O
pulled	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
to	O
charge	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
near	O
Grey's-Inn	O
Gate	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
scrub	O
Rascal	O
that	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
Constable	O
charged	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
replied	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
killed	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
I	O
will	O
kill	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
stopping	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
thrust	O
it	O
towards	O
his	O
Right-Breast	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Puddle	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
up	O
his	O
Legs	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
He	O
has	O
murdered	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
my	O
Death	O
's	O
Wound	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
afterwards	O
flourish	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
round	O
about	O
him	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
setting	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
shut	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
while	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Puddle	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
push	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Lord	O
Jesus	O
receive	O
my	O
Soul	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
murder	O
'd	O
me	O
this	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
Minutes	O
.	O
That	O
two	O
Men	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
backwards	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
fuddled	O
?	O
Reply	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Push	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
dropped	O
immediately	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Middle	O
behind	O
,	O
drew	O
him	O
out	O
backwards	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
staid	O
near	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
till	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
and	O
carried	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
being	O
ready	O
to	O
tear	O
him	O
in	O
Pieces	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
he	O
sat	O
very	O
still	O
,	O
said	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
,	O
till	O
News	O
was	O
brought	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
!	O
Charles	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
make	O
a	O
Push	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
into	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
That	O
they	O
answered	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mob	O
being	O
ready	O
to	O
tear	O
him	O
in	O
Pieces	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
near	O
two	O
Hours	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
seemed	O
very	O
melancholy	O
,	O
but	O
observed	O
no	O
other	O
Disorder	O
in	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
pulled	O
his	O
Wig	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
his	O
Stock	O
right	O
;	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Opinion	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
some	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
as	O
have	O
been	O
before	O
deposed	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edmundson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Abington	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
run	O
by	O
his	O
Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
to	O
have	O
broken	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
fancy	O
Fellow	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
employ	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
prodigious	O
Shreich	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Manwaring	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
dead	O
!	O
and	O
ran	O
two	O
Doors	O
beyond	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
strutted	O
and	O
gave	O
himself	O
such	O
Airs	O
,	O
that	O
though	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
distracted	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
into	O
Abington	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Mob	O
being	O
gathered	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Justice	O
,	O
Justice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
wounded	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
with	O
a	O
Bravado	O
,	O
shaking	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
stepping	O
boldly	O
along	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
secured	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
without	O
Difficulty	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
take	O
care	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
are	O
upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
examined	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
had	O
penetrated	O
between	O
the	O
ninth	O
and	O
tenth	O
Rib	O
,	O
inclining	O
upwards	O
through	O
the	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Diaphragma	O
,	O
had	O
opened	O
Aorta	O
magna	O
,	O
and	O
entred	O
the	O
Left	O
Ventricle	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
immediate	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
being	O
gone	O
through	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Deval	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Walingsly	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
push	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Porter	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
stripped	O
off	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
viewed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bruise	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stafford	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
crazy	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Scrub	O
and	O
a	O
Villain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
even	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
crazy	O
?	O
Reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
Instances	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
used	O
to	O
resort	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Brother	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Stafford	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
crazy	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Porter	O
came	O
to	O
Wahnsley	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
no	O
Wound	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Lord	O
Stafford	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
mad	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
to	O
live	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
this	O
Imagination	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
Proficiency	O
in	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lawyers	O
envied	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
murder	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cutchet	O
was	O
the	O
principal	O
Author	O
of	O
this	O
Conspiracy	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Lord	O
Stafford	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cutchet	O
was	O
a	O
good-natur	O
'd	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
and	O
a	O
Villain	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
perceiving	O
him	O
disorder	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
give	O
Order	O
to	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
again	O
to	O
deny	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Conversation	O
being	O
troublesome	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
dangerous	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Diggory	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Laundress	O
at	O
his	O
Chambers	O
in	O
Grey	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Bathing	O
Tub	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
jumpt	O
into	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Clothes	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
Water	O
into	O
it	O
three	O
Quarters	O
full	O
,	O
she	O
believes	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Shirt	O
on	O
,	O
she	O
finding	O
them	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
jump	O
into	O
it	O
Head	O
foremost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Apothecaries	O
for	O
a	O
Gally-pot	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
his	O
Dog	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
did	O
one	O
good	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
the	O
other	O
good	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
down	O
his	O
Books	O
from	O
their	O
Shelves	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
piled	O
them	O
up	O
on	O
an	O
Heap	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
his	O
Clothes	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
his	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
mad	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Chambers	O
the	O
mad	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Chambers	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
as	O
ugly	O
as	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Glass	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
to	O
view	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Shutters	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
such	O
Freaks	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Laundress	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
also	O
wanted	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
complained	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
disturbed	O
by	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
a	O
Spinning-Wheel	O
in	O
the	O
Chambers	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Primate	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
Night	O
nor	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
wasted	O
his	O
Fat	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
remove	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
or	O
carry	O
his	O
Bed	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
whereas	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
owned	O
them	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Town	O
for	O
near	O
3	O
Months	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
mad	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
her	O
Knowledge	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Senses	O
for	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
complain	O
of	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
Spinning	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Chairs	O
and	O
Tables	O
were	O
moving	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
frosty	O
Weather	O
he	O
pulled	O
his	O
Feather-Bed	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Bedstead	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
two	O
Boards	O
on	O
the	O
sacking	O
of	O
the	O
Bedstead	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
a	O
Bolster	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
so	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
at	O
the	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
Bedstead	O
,	O
covering	O
himself	O
only	O
with	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
like	O
covering	O
;	O
and	O
made	O
Plugs	O
with	O
white	O
Wax	O
to	O
stop	O
his	O
Ears	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
hearing	O
the	O
Buzzing	O
of	O
the	O
Spinning-Wheel	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
all	O
the	O
Devils	O
in	O
Hell	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
all	O
the	O
Night	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
his	O
Limbs	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Use	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
confounded	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
mad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Devil	O
in	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bewitched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
his	O
Windows	O
all	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
disordered	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
frequently	O
fall	O
a	O
Laughing	O
when	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Randal	O
Scotcher	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Chambers	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
did	O
see	O
his	O
Bedding	O
lie	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
time	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
Ghost	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Ghost	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Richardson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
Lett	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
Chambers	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
whimsical	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
asked	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
crazy	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
complaining	O
of	O
Noises	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
of	O
Spinning	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Body	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
those	O
Chambers	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Noise	O
made	O
him	O
mad	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cat	O
as	O
mad	O
as	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
twenty	O
times	O
a	O
Day	O
to	O
stroke	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Devil	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
Devils	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
Bullets	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fire	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Chamber	O
to	O
fright	O
the	O
Devils	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
many	O
Whimsies	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
really	O
did	O
think	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
crazy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Porters	O
used	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
her	O
mad	O
Tenant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
his	O
firing	O
the	O
Chambers	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Porter	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
before	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
set	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
picked	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
which	O
standing	O
very	O
dangerous	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
cross	O
Rail	O
of	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Chamber-Window	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Devils	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
rattling	O
Noise	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
though	O
with	O
great	O
Difficulty	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
much	O
Danger	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
get	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bever	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
since	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
Complaint	O
of	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
Day	O
nor	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bromfield	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
Complaint	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
walked	O
about	O
the	O
Inn	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
if	O
the	O
Noise	O
continued	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
dissuaded	O
him	O
from	O
doing	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
bring	O
himself	O
into	O
Trouble	O
by	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
considerable	O
Effects	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Noise	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
almost	O
distracted	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cat	O
quite	O
mad	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Akersly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Laundress	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
complained	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Disturbance	O
all	O
the	O
Winter	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
bring	O
her	O
Wheel	O
down	O
and	O
spin	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
spin	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
above	O
three	O
Nights	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
she	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
Noise	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Devil	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
an	O
Eating-House	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
Dine	O
there	O
with	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
;	O
but	O
of	O
late	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
troublesome	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
leave	O
his	O
House	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
their	O
Order	O
deny	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Dine	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thetford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
,	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
use	O
odd	O
Gestures	O
and	O
Expressions	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Recourt	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
frequent	O
her	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
(	O
ever	O
and	O
anon	O
)	O
been	O
Guilty	O
of	O
so	O
many	O
odd	O
whimsical	O
Actions	O
and	O
Expressions	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
imagin	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
,	O
he	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
thrust	O
his	O
Sword	O
into	O
Witches	O
if	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Devil	O
he	O
would	O
chain	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
perceiving	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
obey	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crook	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Lord	O
(	O
the	O
Lord	O
Stafford	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lord	O
into	O
the	O
Closet	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Lady	O
Plowden	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
sit	O
at	O
my	O
Uncle	O
's	O
Closet-Door	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
stir	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
crazed	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
several	O
times	O
he	O
had	O
Din	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
burst	O
out	O
a	O
Laughing	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
several	O
Signs	O
of	O
disorder	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Lord	O
had	O
Information	O
in	O
France	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
disordered	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
Plowden	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Uncle	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
alone	O
with	O
the	O
Lord	O
Stafford	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
much	O
affrighted	O
with	O
his	O
odd	O
Behaviour	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Lord	O
Stafford	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Measures	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
shut	O
up	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Devan	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sometime	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
by	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
affected	O
with	O
a	O
deep	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
(	O
where	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
Dine	O
)	O
was	O
so	O
Frenzical	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
accounting	O
it	O
dangerous	O
to	O
converse	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
How	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
frequented	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
burst	O
out	O
into	O
a	O
violent	O
Laughter	O
when	O
all	O
alone	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
once	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
leaning	O
his	O
Head	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
with	O
Tears	O
in	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
saw	O
him	O
looking	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
fell	O
a	O
Laughing	O
with	O
Tears	O
trickling	O
down	O
his	O
Cheeks	O
;	O
that	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Club	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
above	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
speaking	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
till	O
his	O
Lord	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
him	O
any	O
Injury	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
him	O
consin	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
How	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
late	O
was	O
always	O
in	O
some	O
Melancholy	O
Posture	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
very	O
frightful	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
18	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
for	O
fear	O
it	O
should	O
augment	O
his	O
Disorder	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
knocking	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
sent	O
up	O
her	O
Niece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
got	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stamp	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Devil	O
!	O
the	O
Devil	O
!	O
the	O
Devil	O
was	O
there	O
!	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
affrighted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
burnt	O
the	O
Orders	O
of	O
the	O
Club	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wainscot	O
with	O
the	O
Candle	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cutchet	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
observ	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
staring	O
wistly	O
in	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
bursting	O
out	O
into	O
Laughter	O
without	O
any	O
visible	O
Occasion	O
,	O
his	O
offering	O
to	O
throw	O
Drink	O
into	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
last	O
Easter	O
drinking	O
together	O
with	O
Company	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
Provocation	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
hir	O
'd	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
to	O
Spin	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
his	O
Guts	O
wamble	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
whimsical	O
Notions	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
those	O
Accounts	O
(	O
though	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
respect	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Lord	O
his	O
Brother	O
)	O
yet	O
he	O
avoided	O
his	O
Company	O
of	O
late	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
Disorder	O
of	O
his	O
Mind	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mayer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
accounting	O
him	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
did	O
by	O
the	O
Solicitations	O
of	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
acquaint	O
Mr.	O
Strickland	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
desiring	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
Care	O
of	O
,	O
who	O
accordingly	O
gave	O
Orders	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
for	O
several	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Disorder	O
had	O
encreas	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
gradually	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Uncle	O
Strickland	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
down	O
his	O
Baggage	O
by	O
the	O
Carrier	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Huntington	O
,	O
being	O
come	O
thither	O
,	O
he	O
quitted	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
took	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
Post	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
Dover	O
,	O
Calais	O
,	O
Roan	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Paris	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
this	O
great	O
change	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Strickland	O
saying	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
disguising	O
his	O
Nephew	O
's	O
Lunacy	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
his	O
Brother	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Stafford	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
receive	O
advice	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Disorder	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Strickland	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
was	O
necessary	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
approve	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
England	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
Days	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
came	O
to	O
h	O
im	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
offering	O
to	O
throw	O
Drink	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cutchet	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good-natur	O
'd	O
honest	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
deserv	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
madded	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
his	O
Enemy	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
saying	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
greatest	O
Villain	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
spoke	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
fully	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Disorder	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
Doctor	O
Ayre	B-pers
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
his	O
Consinement	O
being	O
retarded	O
,	O
this	O
Accident	O
happened	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Lunacy	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Coffil	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
38	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Huffam	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Huffam	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
informed	O
by	O
Capt	O
.	O
Leman	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Bureau	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
38	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Captain	O
Leman	B-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Bureau	O
being	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
missing	O
,	O
Madam	O
Huffam	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
Colonel	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
riding	O
to	O
Acton	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Turnham-Green	O
,	O
where	O
describing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
new	O
Frock	O
and	O
a	O
Horse	O
at	O
Brandford	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Oxford	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
High-Wickham	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Stoken-Church	O
Turn-pike	O
,	O
but	O
miss	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
Islip	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Worcester	O
,	O
gave	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Turn-pike	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
at	O
Pasbur	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Broomsgrove	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
obliged	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Review	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Persons	O
at	O
Pasbur	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
Ludlow	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Ludlow	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Bureau	O
,	O
and	O
stolen	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
buying	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
either	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
or	O
sold	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Colonel	O
Somebody	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
his	O
Son	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
seeing	O
,	O
and	O
liking	O
,	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Saddle	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Saddle-Cloth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
spent	O
of	O
the	O
38	O
Guineas	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
15	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Crown	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
Farthing	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
and	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
Nine-pence	O
Half-penny	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
between	O
Islington	B-place
and	O
Oldstreet	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
one	O
Edwards	O
,	O
a	O
Painter	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
espy	O
'd	O
two	O
Men	O
coming	O
from	O
behind	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
attacked	O
Edwards	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
getting	O
beyond	O
Edwards	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
London	O
side	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
turning	O
to	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drawn	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
Pass	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
thinks	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
as	O
he	O
supposed	O
,	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
which	O
Opinion	O
he	O
is	O
confirmed	O
in	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
desiring	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Habitation	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Scandal	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
cast	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
not	O
appearing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
his	O
Partner	O
distress	O
'd	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
attack	O
'd	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
and	O
Edwards	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Partner	O
falling	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
this	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
Wounds	O
with	O
some	O
Instrument	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
with	O
what	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
3	O
Months	O
at	O
Islington	O
before	O
he	O
recovered	O
of	O
his	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
over-powered	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
throw	O
into	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
stripp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
pulled	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
many	O
times	O
affirmed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
two	O
Persons	O
again	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
recovered	O
of	O
his	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Prisons	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cask	O
of	O
Small-Beer	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
upon	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
affirmed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
And	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempting	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
had	O
put	O
this	O
Robbery	O
into	O
the	O
Information	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Gravetz	I-pers
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
whereas	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Gravett	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Staton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Time	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
should	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
among	O
several	O
Men	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
his	O
Size	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tickford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Tickford	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Hat	O
,	O
Hat-band	O
and	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
Henry	B-pers
Tickford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
Thomas	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Brothers	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Hendon	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Fig-lane	B-place
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
stood	O
behind	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
Man	O
cry	O
'd	O
Hyp	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
falling	O
back	O
.	O
bid	O
them	O
keep	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
they	O
both	O
fired	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
up	O
at	O
their	O
crying	O
Hyp	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
shot	O
his	O
Brother	O
in	O
the	O
Forehead	O
and	O
Cheek	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
never	O
speaking	O
one	O
Word	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
lived	O
afterwards	O
33	O
Hours	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
slung	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
made	O
him	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
Money	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
it	O
by	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
for	O
killing	O
him	O
too	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
that	O
one	O
Brother	O
had	O
been	O
killed	O
in	O
coming	O
from	O
another	O
Brother	O
's	O
Funeral	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Third	O
must	O
be	O
killed	O
too	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
length	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
leave	O
him	O
alive	O
to	O
bury	O
the	O
old	O
Rogue	O
his	O
Brother	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
behind	O
,	O
or	O
coming	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
supposing	O
more	O
Persons	O
might	O
be	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Funeral	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tickford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
brought	O
Home	O
at	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
Condition	O
,	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Forehead	O
and	O
Cheek	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tickford	I-pers
at	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
his	O
Wounds	O
were	O
Mortal	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
upon	O
opening	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
one	O
Bullet	O
had	O
gone	O
quite	O
through	O
the	O
Cheek	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Cotes	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
and	O
Murther	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
shot	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tickford	I-pers
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
Gloves	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
This	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
4th	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cask	O
of	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
these	O
Robberies	O
before	O
Justice	O
Danett	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
capitally	O
Convicted	O
on	O
three	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
it	O
unnecessary	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
on	O
this	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bernard	B-pers
Fink	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Amy	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Green	O
Stone	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Nutmeg-grater	O
made	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
gift	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
three	O
other	O
Gentlewomen	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
between	O
Dirty-Lane	B-place
and	O
Southampton-Street	B-place
,	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
several	O
Men	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
there	O
was	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
scurrilous	O
manner	O
their	O
Money	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
Watches	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
that	O
Drinkwater	O
stopped	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
Bernard	O
Fink	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
demanded	O
their	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
that	O
Himself	O
and	O
Drinkwater	O
had	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
Armstrong	O
and	O
Fink	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winnet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Partridge	O
and	O
Drinkwater	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
or	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Nutmeg-grater	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
which	O
they	O
borrowed	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Payton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Green	O
Ring	O
from	O
Bernard	O
Fink	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
upon	O
Partridge	O
's	O
Information	O
;	O
that	O
Fink	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
suffer	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
one	O
admitted	O
before	O
.	O
That	O
Fink	O
did	O
own	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
before	O
.	O
Armstrong	O
and	O
Drinkwater	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
Drinkwater	O
and	O
Fink	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Armstrong	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Warrington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Lampree	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Edward	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
over-against	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
several	O
Persons	O
attack	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pace	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Himself	O
coming	O
down	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
Jack	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
stopped	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
Yates	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Hanger	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
over-against	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
another	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
Allen	O
)	O
first	O
,	O
Armstrong	O
pulled	O
away	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
about	O
a	O
100	O
Yards	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
another	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
called	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Hockley	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
a	O
Chaise	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Watch	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
William	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
and	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Chatham	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Robbed	O
Mr.	O
Sutton	O
off	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Evidence	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Lawrence-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Pound	O
,	O
that	O
Night	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Bur	I-pers
roughs	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
for	O
stopping	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
from	O
Eight	O
till	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Twelve	O
they	O
all	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
Burroughs	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Pace	O
and	O
Westshire	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
Pots	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
,	O
and	O
Pace	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
Two-penny	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
saying	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
saying	O
there	O
was	O
less	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
Punch	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
Yates	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
her	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
small	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
to	O
convince	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Yates	O
and	O
Armstrong	O
had	O
drank	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
Lampree	O
before	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
Pace	O
with	O
them	O
but	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Whetton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
near	O
King-street	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
setting	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
a	O
Lamp-Post	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Yates	O
ran	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Hanger	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
Burroughs	O
,	O
hearing	O
an	O
out	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
and	O
'Squire	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knows	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
all	O
by	O
sight	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Lampree	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Robbed	O
a	O
Man	O
near	O
St.	O
Giles	O
