TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1731	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
VII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1731	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kingsley	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ansel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Rymel	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Life	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunce	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Harvis	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Gig	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Falkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
stepping	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
turning	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leaning	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Money-Drawer	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
printed	O
Cotton	O
,	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
Holland	O
Cloth	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Badgwel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
Steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
pawned	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Armsteads	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishosgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
's	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Governors	O
of	O
the	O
Hospital	O
of	O
Bethlehem	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lead	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Counting-House	B-place
of	I-place
Bethlehem-Hospital	I-place
,	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Moorfields	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
Persons	O
watching	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
seen	O
upon	O
the	O
Spot	O
of	O
Ground	O
where	O
the	O
Lead	O
had	O
been	O
hid	O
;	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
come	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
watch	O
'd	O
had	O
not	O
Patience	O
to	O
stay	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Eunice	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
Gold-rings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ramsden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Drinking	O
pot	O
,	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
and	O
Tea-spoon	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ludington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hacker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cushee	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin-Cambel	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
near	O
Smith-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taxing	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
Tom	O
,	O
or	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidences	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
Violent	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
several	O
Warrants	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
praying	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tickner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Tinsley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
a	O
Gardener	O
,	O
and	O
dwelling	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
their	O
Goods	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
4	O
l.	O
as	O
she	O
stood	O
talking	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
standing	O
close	O
by	O
her	O
)	O
she	O
felt	O
a	O
Jerk	O
at	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
clapping	O
her	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
:	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropp	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
at	O
her	O
Feet	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
examining	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
cut	O
near	O
the	O
Bottom	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
upon	O
her	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
throw	O
away	O
something	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Knife	O
)	O
which	O
a	O
Boy	O
took	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
:	O
As	O
likewise	O
did	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
pickt	O
up	O
the	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
single	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Everett	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Quern	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Broad	O
Lawn	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
some	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lawn	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lawn	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Matilda	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
find	O
the	O
Lawn	O
concealed	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dominique	B-pers
Pilla	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Kettle	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bag	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
,	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Marriages	O
being	O
proed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blakemore	I-pers
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
forthe	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
felonious	O
Slaying	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Skettles	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennesfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Dispte	O
about	O
the	O
Game	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
Bett	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
at	O
Highgate	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Company	O
(	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
)	O
were	O
called	O
to	O
give	O
their	O
Opinion	O
who	O
had	O
won	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
gave	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
What	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
A	O
Man	O
,	O
or	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
.	O
And	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
stagger	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Blows	O
were	O
struck	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
being	O
on	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Knees	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
John	O
Hall	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
under	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennesford	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
did	O
come	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
bleed	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
bleed	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
find	O
a	O
Confusion	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
Quantity	O
of	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoonful	O
all	O
over	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Fall	O
might	O
occasion	O
a	O
Confusion	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Circulation	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
might	O
be	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
Man	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eustace	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Wyffes	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
24	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Mead	O
,	O
Wine	O
,	O
Beer	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
Last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
giving	O
the	O
Jury	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
Bolster	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brinsley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ames	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
that	O
whereas	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ticking	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
afterwards	O
receive	O
the	O
said	O
Ticking	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gunn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Skellet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Mounthaugh	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Bower	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
George	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Paradise	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Stock-buckle	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Boy	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Man	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
)	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Cane	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
his	O
Fellow-servant	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Cane	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Cane	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
touch	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
when	O
William	B-pers
Nabs	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Fellow-servant	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
the	O
Cane	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Boy	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
a	O
Stock-buckle	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Pretence	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dowle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
for	O
a	O
Decoy	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
several	O
Times	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
set	O
,	O
who	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
apprehended	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolworth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botoloph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgat	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Parcl	O
of	O
quilted	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
May	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employed	O
in	O
Quilting	O
by	O
the	O
Pros	O
ecutor	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Silk	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
M	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Clothes	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Batton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Bassishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Packing-sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Packing	O
cloth	O
was	O
laid	O
over	O
some	O
Packs	O
of	O
Cloth	O
at	O
Blackwell-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
ragged	O
thing	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
worth	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
,	O
not	O
worth	O
2	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
supposing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
who	O
better	O
knew	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
accordingly	O
rated	O
it	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
came	O
nearer	O
to	O
the	O
true	O
Value	O
,	O
did	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
121	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lead	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
of	O
that	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabella	B-pers
Matchet	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
William	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Martindale	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
lain	O
there	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheets	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lancelot	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Catcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Mary	B-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Things	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
Chandler's-Shop	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Penny-worth	O
of	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fully	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hannover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Varnham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter-Dish	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sampson	B-pers
Hodsdon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Quaile	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
sent	O
the	O
Gown	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cutic	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
and	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Hat	O
of	O
one	O
Squire	O
Jone	O
's	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
Gown	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
going	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
such	O
Things	O
left	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
,	O
who	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
an	O
Officer	O
was	O
a	O
fetching	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
apprehended	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
,	O
Ezekiel	O
Everet	O
,	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Gown	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Mates	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Donald	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Trevet	O
,	O
Pot	O
,	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Iron	O
Ware	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Goodal	I-pers
,	O
their	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
using	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
another	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Monro	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
stolen	O
cut	O
of	O
a	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
hung	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
observed	O
to	O
lurk	O
about	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
watch	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
stolen	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Gold-ring	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Person	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Anne	B-pers
Helmes	I-pers
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Anne	O
Helmes	O
being	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
5	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
uncapable	O
of	O
giving	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
the	O
Mother	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Benham	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
lye	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Breeches	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
familiar	O
Conversation	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
no	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
took	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Irwin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Left-part	O
of	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Left-pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1726	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Briggins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Prince	O
's	O
(	O
now	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
)	O
Guard	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1726	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
drank	O
half	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
together	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Opera-House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Gaming-house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
owed	O
him	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rang	O
the	O
Bell	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Wicket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Gaming-house	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
Orders	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
Wicket	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drawing	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
thrust	O
it	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Wicket	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Nothing	O
,	O
except	O
you	O
appear	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
over	O
to	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
till	O
lately	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
him	O
immediately	O
upon	O
his	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Reason	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
serve	O
him	O
so	O
too	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Gaming-house	O
when	O
Charles	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
was	O
murther	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Bell	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Gaming-room	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Irwin	I-pers
has	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
lived	O
but	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
at	O
the	O
Gaming-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rung	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
or	O
two	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Rogue	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Irwin	I-pers
,	O
has	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
went	O
well	O
from	O
Home	O
about	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
Home	O
wounded	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
only	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
to	O
be	O
laid	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
immediately	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Presgrove	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
an	O
Inch	O
in	O
Length	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
given	O
with	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
:	O
that	O
it	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
Left	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Thorax	O
,	O
and	O
penetrated	O
the	O
Ventricle	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
impeach	O
'd	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Briggins	I-pers
;	O
to	O
support	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Elpick	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
Thomas	O
Askington	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Briggins	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Soldier	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
except	O
as	O
to	O
Whoring	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
likewise	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
hasty	O
,	O
passionate	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
formerly	O
stabb	O
'd	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
10	O
Inches	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
did	O
not	O
die	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Wife	O
20	O
s.	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Genew	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pewter-Plates	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
7	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Cups	O
,	O
a	O
Gold-headed	O
Cane	O
,	O
2	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
contriving	O
,	O
procuring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
betting	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Genew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Feather-Beds	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Furniture	O
of	O
Beds	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Genew	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Thief	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
got	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
by	O
a	O
Key	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
procur	O
'd	O
from	O
one	O
Thatcham	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
an	O
Old	O
Iron	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Bagnal	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Thatcham	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
agreeing	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
Davis	O
and	O
Tracey	O
mov	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thatcham	O
's	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
Tracey	O
furnished	O
them	O
with	O
Hampers	O
,	O
Tinder-box	O
,	O
Flint	O
,	O
Steel	O
,	O
and	O
Matches	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Robberies	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
also	O
had	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Charge	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pistols	O
;	O
which	O
Hammer	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
2	O
Wigs	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
a	O
Board	O
in	O
his	O
Barrow	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Barrow-man	O
for	O
selling	O
Fruit	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Several	O
of	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
confirmed	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
especially	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
the	O
Wigs	O
in	O
Tracey	O
's	O
Barrow	O
.	O
Gill	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Bagnal	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
Tracey	O
by	O
a	O
Stratagem	O
got	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Davis	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
against	O
Tracey	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
That	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cow	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Brice	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Brice	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Cow	O
was	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Field	O
near	O
Woodford-Bridge	B-place
and	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Heather	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Cow	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Cow	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
procured	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
Vouch	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Cow	O
to	O
the	O
Green-yard	O
;	O
and	O
sending	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
Essex	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Cow	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Green-yard	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Swallwood	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Jane	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
privately	O
take	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Nelty	O
,	O
45	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Catherine	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Lace	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Vine-court	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
shewing	O
her	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
high-pric	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Lace	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
some	O
Liquors	O
,	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
,	O
his	O
Lace	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Box	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
since	O
absconded	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
Lace	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
lent	O
them	O
5	O
l.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
Clayton	O
saying	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
sent	O
it	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Ireland	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
requiring	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Person	O
might	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
justify	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
mention	O
'd	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Cheshire	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
declar	O
'd	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
sthat	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Tobacco-box	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Good	O
Night	O
,	O
Ladies	O
.	O
-	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Brodiere	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
;	O
as	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
them	O
by	O
Jane	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
denied	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
Jane	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Lace	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
was	O
but	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
it	O
,	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
the	O
Lace	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Crownfield	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crownfield	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
passing	O
along	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
,	O
about	O
12	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walk	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
talking	O
of	O
the	O
Building	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
a	O
fine	O
Building	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
stopping	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
clap	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Watch-string	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
shove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
which	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
Fright	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
Money	O
!	O
That	O
this	O
occasioning	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
came	O
up	O
(	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Doors	O
off	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
supposes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
aware	O
of	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
securing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
a	O
naked	O
Bayonet	O
dropt	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
with	O
Bullets	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
jagged	O
Knife	O
;	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
to	O
unscrew	O
the	O
Barrel	O
of	O
the	O
Pistol	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depsos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
dropping	O
of	O
the	O
Bayonet	O
and	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Bullets	O
and	O
Knife	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hector	O
'd	O
much	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Reputation	O
,	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Horse-shoe	O
Alley	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
Scandal	O
put	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
high	O
Words	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
saying	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
You	O
assaulted	O
me	O
,	O
not	O
I	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
Bayonet	O
and	O
Pistol	O
dropt	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
These	O
Cirrcumstances	O
were	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Alford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Julian	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Rebecca	B-pers
White	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Half-Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
Four-pence	O
Half-penny	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Flint	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Thatcht-house	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Pint	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
for	O
a	O
Cousin	O
who	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
being	O
over-against	O
Hungerford-Market	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
at	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
calling	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
was	O
just	O
stepping	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
drag	O
'd	O
her	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
when	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Yards	O
towards	O
Hungerford-market	B-place
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
Fan	O
;	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Chairman	O
!	O
Chairman	O
!	O
And	O
the	O
Chairman	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
People	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Bulk-woman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Soldier	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Bulk-woman	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
Push	O
,	O
or	O
hit	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
turning	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
No	O
Chair	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
her	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
by	O
Violence	O
up	O
towards	O
Hungerford-market	O
;	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
forward	O
to	O
the	O
Prince	O
Frederik	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
heard	O
an	O
Outcry	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Punt	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
Pocket	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
stood	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
Fan	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fan	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Right	O
Side	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Duke's-Court	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
Archway	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
,	O
Stop	O
,	O
Thief	O
!	O
And	O
there	O
were	O
Fellows	O
with	O
Links	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Church-porch	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hyat	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Burgess	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Fan	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
(	O
whereas	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Frenchman	O
(	O
i.	O
e.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
taken	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
examining	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hyat	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Justice	O
Du	O
Val	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Lawley	O
was	O
also	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Bitch	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
and	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Pocket	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lock	O
of	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
:	O
He	O
thinks	O
the	O
Purse	O
had	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Brass	O
candlestick	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
another	O
Name	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Purse	O
?	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
heard	O
it	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Machine	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Machine	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
attempt	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Duke's-Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
up	O
the	O
Steps	O
of	O
the	O
Piazza	O
of	O
Covent-Garden	O
Church-Porch	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Nook	O
at	O
the	O
Church-Door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
Breath	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
Sweat	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
dropp	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Chin	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Pocket	O
in	O
his	O
Right-hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fan	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
thinks	O
from	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
her	O
Dear	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
little	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
Should	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
her	O
who	O
struck	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
parted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
Pocket	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Half-Guinea	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
impeach	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Noble	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Service	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
under	O
no	O
Necessity	O
of	O
doing	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnorth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
sold	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Plow	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
at	I-place
Stocks-Market	I-place
,	O
and	O
passing	O
along	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
breasted	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Bag	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
at	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
dropp	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
present	O
,	O
whose	O
Depositions	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
more	O
probable	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
dropp	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
shallow	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Halstead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
15	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Rum	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
him	O
sometime	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
Misbehaviour	O
;	O
but	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Rum	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Warminger	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waybank	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
half-pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dalbys	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Basket-Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
)	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
Home	O
with	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Herbs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mug	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop-Window	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
Herbs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Mug	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
leaving	O
her	O
Basket	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
2	O
Tumblers	O
,	O
a	O
Punch-Ladle	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canister	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bozini	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Canister	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
ran	O
along	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
just	O
taken	O
it	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather-Boots	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boots	O
were	O
hung	O
at	O
a	O
Cobler's-Stall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mary	O
Hudson	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
upon	O
Rachel	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Little	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hurr	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bibb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Journeymen	O
Taylors	O
and	O
Bedfellows	O
,	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Bibb	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Purse	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Coverly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Cutty	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jessop	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Town	I-pers
;	O
but	O
No-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Pilowe	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Dess	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
No-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradbourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldermanbury	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Camblet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Snee	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Footman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sent	O
them	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Carrier	O
to	O
a	O
Brother	O
of	O
his	O
at	O
Newport	O
in	O
Shropshire	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Carrier	O
at	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
,	O
directed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Laurence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
have	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
ty	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Garter	O
round	O
his	O
Waste	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Handle	O
hanging	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lametta	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Nicks	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Alway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Watch	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Watch	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
a	O
lame	O
Fellow	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
Holford's-Alley	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Margaret	O
Lametta	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
her	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Alway	I-pers
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Lametta	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
kissing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Alway	I-pers
came	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Landlady	O
in	O
pawn	O
for	O
Six-Pence	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburgh	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
3	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
2	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Higler	O
)	O
having	O
sold	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-Market	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Angel	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
?	O
and	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
them	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Sliding-Door	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
early	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
boasting	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Gang	O
what	O
a	O
Night	O
's	O
Work	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Abigail	O
?	O
And	O
hearing	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Manner	O
before	O
related	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
to	O
walk	O
the	O
Streets	O
this	O
10	O
Years	O
)	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Drawer	O
that	O
drew	O
the	O
Wine	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
attended	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
informing	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Company	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
paid	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Reason	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Old	O
Bethlehem	O
,	O
from	O
about	O
9	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
till	O
12	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
Joshuah	O
Winnock	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Blackson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Luke	I-pers
Trowers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Man	O
's	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
and	O
Chamber-fellows	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Stay-maker	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Crochet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Onley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
That	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Edmund	I-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Lambert	B-pers
Ludlow	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Downey	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ventland	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Vickland	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saxon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
being	O
near	O
Creed-Church	B-place
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ventland	I-pers
got	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
loving	O
and	O
kind	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Downey	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
directly	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
Ventland	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
lifting	O
up	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
Swore	B-pers
,	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
d	O
id	O
not	O
let	O
his	O
Wife	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
lose	O
his	O
Life	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
lose	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchman	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
Downing	O
;	O
and	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
offering	O
him	O
first	O
10	O
s.	O
then	O
15	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
20	O
s.	O
promising	O
him	O
also	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
Treat	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Ventland	O
ran	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
Downey	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mary	O
Downing	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
Ilive	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
forc	O
'd	O
two	O
Women	O
down	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
-	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
probably	O
come	O
by	O
some	O
damage	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
-	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
was	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Ventlana	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
her	O
walk	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
Buss	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refusing	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Buss	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
Swore	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
Watch-house	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
my	O
-	O
come	O
sailing	O
by	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
see	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
black	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
frighted	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
3.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Irwin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
37.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
,	O
William-	O
Edmund	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradbourn	I-pers
,	O
Eunice	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crotchet	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dowle	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gigg	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Halstead	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Mates	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Mac-Donald	I-pers
,	O
Dominique	O
Pilla	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Quaile	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Show	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Tickner	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Varnham	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Ventland	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Vickland	O
,	O
Enstace	O
Watkins	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waybank	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
9.	O
George	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cavew	O
,	O
Jane	O
Hall	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mac-Culler	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Noland	I-pers
,	O
-	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
Isabella	O
Walpool	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
.	O
Whip	O
'd	O
2.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Car	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Batton	I-pers
.	O
Richard	O
Burton	O
Fin	O
'd	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
3	O
Years	O
after	O
.	O
Books	O
Just	O
printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
.	O
LA	O
Plum	O
Volante	O
.	O
Or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-hand	O
improved	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
most	O
Swift	O
,	O
Regular	O
,	O
and	O
Easy	O
Method	O
of	O
Short-hand-writing	O
yet	O
Extant	O
.	O
Composed	O
after	O
Fifty	O
Years	O
Practice	O
and	O
Improvement	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Art	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Observation	O
of	O
other	O
Methods	O
and	O
intent	O
Study	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
Aditions	O
of	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
amended	O
,	O
By	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Miraculous	O
Convention	O
from	O
Popery	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
:	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Glory	O
of	O
Divine	O
Grace	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Protection	O
of	O
Divine	O
Providence	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Goodness	O
of	O
God	O
Manifested	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Military	O
Discipline	O
.	O
The	O
Word	O
of	O
Command	O
,	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Exercising	O
the	O
Musket	O
and	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Carbine	O
,	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
performed	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Horse	O
and	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
B.	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Singing	O
Master	O
's	O
Guide	O
to	O
his	O
Scholars	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Psalms	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Translations	O
;	O
the	O
Old	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
By	O
several	O
Hands	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sternhold	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
Barton	O
,	O
Patrick	O
,	O
Tate	O
and	O
Brady	O
,	O
Milbourne	O
and	O
Sandys	O
.	O
Contriv	O
'd	O
for	O
Common	O
Use	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Tunes	O
in	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
By	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
of	O
Ewelm	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
Singing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
further	O
Guide	O
to	O
Parish	O
Clarks	O
:	O
or	O
,	O
any	O
other	O
religiously	O
and	O
devoutly	O
disposed	O
to	O
make	O
Use	O
of	O
these	O
Instructions	O
.	O
Being	O
contriv	O
'd	O
for	O
common	O
Use	O
,	O
by	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
of	O
Ewlem	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
Singing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Spelling	O
,	O
Containing	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
,	O
B	B-pers
,	I-pers
C	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Children	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
Alphabets	O
and	O
Syllables	O
,	O
with	O
short	O
Rules	O
and	O
Examples	O
of	O
dividing	O
Words	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Rules	O
for	O
true	O
Spelling	O
,	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
Writing	O
of	O
English	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Question	O
and	O
Answer	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Two	O
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
useful	O
Words	O
,	O
whose	O
Spelling	O
or	O
Sense	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
mistaken	O
.	O
Also	O
Christian	O
Names	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
J.	O
P.	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
fifth	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
.	O
Price	O
9	O
d.	O
The	O
Greatness	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Unspeakableness	O
of	O
the	O
Loss	O
thereof	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Causes	O
of	O
the	O
Losing	O
it	O
.	O
First	O
preached	O
in	O
Pinners-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
enlarged	O
,	O
and	O
published	O
for	O
good	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Bunyan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Shop	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Sold	O
to	O
all	O
Stationers	O
and	O
School-masters	O
in	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
,	O
Pieces	O
for	O
Christmas	O
,	O
Easter	O
and	O
Whitsunide	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
wholesale	O
and	O
retale	O
,	O
curiously	O
engraved	O
on	O
Copper-plates	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
King	O
George	O
the	O
II	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Jerusalem	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Temple	O
of	O
Solomon	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Geometry	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Haman	O
hanged	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Hunting-Piece	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Grammar	O
and	O
Writing-School	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Christ	O
's	O
Burial	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Show	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
Moses	O
in	O
the	O
Ark	O
of	O
Bull-rushes	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
History	O
of	O
Tobit	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Christ	O
's	O
Ascension	O
.	O
14	O
The	O
seven	O
Sciences	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
Dorastis	O
and	O
Fawnis	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
History	O
of	O
Judith	O
and	O
Holosernis	O
.	O
17	O
The	O
four	O
Evangelists	O
.	O
18	O
Stool-Ball	O
.	O
19	O
Joseph	O
flying	O
into	O
Egypt	O
.	O
20	O
Crucifixion	O
;	O
And	O
many	O
others	O
in	O
whole	O
Sheets	O
and	O
half	O
Sheets	O
:	O
Likewise	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
an	O
Elegiac	O
Poem	O
in	O
Commemoration	O
of	O
his	O
lare	O
Most	O
Second	O
Majesty	O
K.	O
George	O
,	O
engraven	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Also	O
Gospel	O
Mystery	O
Emblematically	O
illustrated	O
,	O
engraven	O
on	O
a	O
large	O
Copper-plate	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
CATO	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Cash	O
and	O
History	O
of	O
Self-Murder	O
,	O
argu	O
'd	O
and	O
Display	O
'd	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Principles	O
of	O
Reason	O
,	O
Justice	O
,	O
Law	O
,	O
Religion	O
,	O
Fortitude	O
,	O
Love	O
of	O
ourselves	O
and	O
our	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
Example	O
;	O
A	O
Solution	O
of	O
this	O
Problem	O
,	O
whether	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Sense	O
,	O
Goodness	O
,	O
and	O
Courage	O
,	O
ever	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
can	O
,	O
Kill	O
Himself	O
?	O
Particularly	O
calculated	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
Nation	O
:	O
Occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Stabbing	O
Himself	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instances	O
.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Lecture	O
,	O
deliver	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Oratory	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
Field	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Henley	B-pers
,	I-pers
M.	I-pers
A	I-pers
.	I-pers
Publish	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Hearers	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
J	O
.	O
Marshal	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
New-gate	O
.	O
Street	O
.	O
A	O
speedy	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
ITCH	O
,	O
At	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George's-Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
is	O
Sold	O
.	O
A	O
WATER	O
which	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
ITCH	O
,	O
or	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
offensive	O
Scent	O
;	O
and	O
hath	O
been	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
Years	O
Experience	O
:	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
Prepared	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
.	O
Chymist	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
The	O
true	O
Essence	O
or	O
Spirits	O
of	O
SCURVY-GRASS	O
,	O
both	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
most	O
Excellent	O
in	O
all	O
Degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Great	O
Elixir	O
of	O
Lite	O
,	O
called	O
DAFFY	O
's	O
ELIXIR	O
,	O
truly	O
prepared	O
from	O
the	O
best	O
Ingredients	O
,	O
very	O
useful	O
in	O
all	O
Families	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Half-pint	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
Published	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
of	O
A	O
PRACTICAL	O
TREATISE	O
;	O
Or	O
,	O
Second	O
Thoughts	O
on	O
the	O
Consequences	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
On	O
the	O
Simple	O
Gonorrhoea	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
from	O
Venereal	O
Embraces	O
,	O
Self-pollution	O
,	O
improperly	O
called	O
Onanism	O
,	O
or	O
Natural	O
Impecility	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Virulent	O
Gonorrhoea	O
,	O
or	O
Clap	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Lues	O
,	O
or	O
Grand	O
Pox	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
plainly	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
exact	O
Degrees	O
of	O
Difference	O
;	O
with	O
their	O
Signs	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
Prognosticks	O
,	O
and	O
Cures	O
in	O
all	O
Cases	O
,	O
their	O
Beginnings	O
,	O
Progress	O
,	O
and	O
fatal	O
Periods	O
,	O
when	O
neglected	O
or	O
unskilfully	O
managed	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
their	O
absolute	O
Cure	O
,	O
without	O
Violence	O
or	O
Injury	O
,	O
is	O
compleated	O
.	O
With	O
proper	O
and	O
effectual	O
Remedies	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
several	O
Stages	O
,	O
prescribed	O
and	O
recommended	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
that	O
prepolterous	O
way	O
of	O
Venery	O
with	O
Machines	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Dangers	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
little	O
expected	O
)	O
which	O
attend	O
that	O
vile	O
practice	O
.	O
Also	O
many	O
other	O
useful	O
Discoveries	O
relating	O
to	O
Infections	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
not	O
before	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
annexed	O
,	O
a	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
practice	O
of	O
Salivating	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Whole	O
fitted	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
Patients	O
as	O
young	O
Practioners	O
.	O
By	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CAM	I-pers
.	O
M.	O
D.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-Church-Yard	O
;	O
also	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
E.	O
Midwinter	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
;	O
T.	O
Corber	O
,	O
at	O
Addison	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
;	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
Hodges	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
Price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
To	O
Distillers	O
,	O
Joathan	O
Pead	O
Chymist	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
in	O
New-street-square	O
,	O
between	O
Shoe-Lane	O
and	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
Prepares	O
and	O
Sells	O
a	O
true	O
Calcination	O
of	O
TARTAR	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
given	O
a	O
general	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
by	O
cleansing	O
Malt-Spirits	O
from	O
all	O
their	O
sortid	O
Flavour	O
,	O
rendering	O
them	O
soft	O
,	O
sweet	O
,	O
and	O
pleasant	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
any	O
Mixture	O
,	O
improving	O
every	O
Day	O
it	O
upon	O
Trial	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
answer	O
the	O
Money	O
shall	O
be	O
repaid	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
Six	O
Pounds	O
are	O
sufficient	O
for	O
a	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
require	O
but	O
one	O
Distillation	O
.	O
Price	O
Fourteen	O
Pence	O
per	O
Pound	O
.	O
Plantation-Office	O
,	O
kept	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Agent	O
for	O
Merchants	O
,	O
Next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Cutler	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Castle-Alley	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
a	O
Board	O
of	O
Directions	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Several	O
hundreds	O
of	O
good	O
Countrymen	O
,	O
and	O
Servants	O
of	O
all	O
Trades	O
,	O
are	O
wanted	O
for	O
Jamaica	O
directly	O
,	O
Ships	O
will	O
Sail	O
every	O
Week	O
for	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
Good	O
able	O
Carpenters	O
,	O
Bricklayers	O
,	O
Wheelwrights	O
,	O
Blacksmiths	O
,	O
Sawyers	O
and	O
Coopers	O
,	O
shall	O
have	O
twenty-five	O
Pounds	O
yearly	O
Wages	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
all	O
Men	O
Servants	O
that	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
Jamaica	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
entertained	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Vivant	O
Rex	O
&	O
Regina	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
Masters	O
of	O
Ships	O
,	O
Country-Shopkeepers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
this	O
publick	O
Notice	O
is	O
given	O
.	O
THAT	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DICEY	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Conjunction	O
with	O
Mr.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
OKELL	I-pers
(	O
to	O
whom	O
a	O
Royal	O
Patent	O
is	O
granted	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COBB	I-pers
,	O
(	O
in	O
Right	O
of	O
ELIZABETH	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
late	O
Widow	O
of	O
Mr.	O
CLUER	O
)	O
and	O
ROBERT	B-pers
RAIKES	I-pers
,	O
continue	O
,	O
and	O
jointly	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
preparing	O
and	O
vending	O
,	O
both	O
Wholesale	O
and	O
Retail	O
,	O
that	O
excellent	O
Medicine	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Dr.	O
BATEMAN	O
's	O
PECTORAL	O
DROPS	O
,	O
at	O
their	O
Warehouse	O
against	O
the	O
South	O
Door	O
of	O
Bow	O
Church	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Church-Yard	O
from	O
Cheatside	O
,	O
London	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Place	O
(	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
)	O
Retailers	O
may	O
be	O
furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
good	O
Allowance	O
for	O
Profit	O
,	O
by	O
directing	O
for	O
or	O
sending	O
to	O
WIL	B-pers
LIAM	I-pers
DICEY	I-pers
or	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COBB	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
These	O
DROPS	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
most	O
violent	O
Fever	O
,	O
if	O
taken	O
in	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Remedies	O
for	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
afflicted	O
with	O
the	O
present	O
Distempers	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Coughs	O
,	O
Colds	O
,	O
intermitting	O
Fevers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
gives	O
present	O
Ease	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
racking	O
Pains	O
of	O
the	O
Gout	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
brought	O
away	O
Gravel	O
and	O
Stones	O
almost	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
Horse	O
Beans	O
from	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
restored	O
Thousands	O
of	O
poor	O
Infants	O
to	O
their	O
Strength	O
and	O
Liveliness	O
,	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
reduced	O
to	O
meet	O
Skeletons	O
,	O
They	O
never	O
fail	O
giving	O
Ease	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
violent	O
Pains	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
and	O
Limbs	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Ailments	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Medicines	O
in	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Consumptions	O
.	O
Sold	O
at	O
One	O
Shilling	O
per	O
Bottle	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
is	O
contained	O
three	O
Doses	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
Gratis	O
,	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
Certificates	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
more	O
Cures	O
than	O
can	O
be	O
produc	O
'd	O
from	O
any	O
one	O
Medicine	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
first	O
Use	O
of	O
Physick	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
THIRD	O
EDITION	O
of	O
The	O
SPELING	O
DICTIONARY	O
;	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
common	O
Words	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
Tongue	O
,	O
carefully	O
compared	O
with	O
the	O
original	O
Languages	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
are	O
derived	O
,	O
and	O
mark	O
'd	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
pronounced	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
DYCHE	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Sold	O
by	O
R.	O
WARE	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Sun	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
Amen	O
Corner	O
.	O
Also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
large	O
House	O
Bibles	O
,	O
Folio	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Six	O
Maps	O
of	O
Sacred	O
Geography	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brief	O
Concordance	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
easy	O
finding	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Places	O
therein	O
contained	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Dow-NAME	O
,	O
B.	O
D.	O
Bound	O
in	O
Calf	O
Leather	O
1	O
l.	O
6.	O
s.	O
per	O
Book	O
.	O
And	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cuts	O
2	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
ditto	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
fine	O
Paper	O
with	O
Cuts	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
ditto	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Impartial	O
Churchman	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
fair	O
and	O
candid	O
Representation	O
of	O
the	O
Excellency	O
and	O
Beauty	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
an	O
earnest	O
and	O
affectionate	O
Address	O
to	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Diffenters	O
.	O
By	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WARREN	I-pers
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
price	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
.	O
Part	O
II	O
,	O
Teaching	O
a	O
Christian	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
How	O
to	O
grow	O
in	O
Grace	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
How	O
to	O
demean	O
himself	O
in	O
Sickness	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
How	O
to	O
prepare	O
himself	O
for	O
a	O
happy	O
Death	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
Advice	O
how	O
Visitants	O
and	O
Attendants	O
should	O
carry	O
it	O
towards	O
the	O
Sick	O
.	O
And	O
some	O
general	O
Considerations	O
that	O
may	O
induce	O
Relations	O
and	O
Friends	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Death	O
patiently	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Reverend	O
and	O
learned	O
Dr.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Chichester	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
A	O
Description	O
of	O
Three	O
Hundred	O
Animals	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Beasts	O
,	O
Birds	O
,	O
Fishes	O
,	O
Serpents	O
and	O
Insects	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Whale-Fishery	O
.	O
Extracted	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Authors	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
all	O
Capacities	O
,	O
especially	O
to	O
allure	O
Children	O
to	O
read	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
,	O
whereon	O
is	O
curiously	O
engraven	O
,	O
every	O
Beast	O
,	O
Bird	O
,	O
Fish	O
,	O
Serpent	O
or	O
Insect	O
,	O
described	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
Book	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
.	O
Tradesman	O
's	O
Guide	O
.	O
Containing	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Stage-Coaches	O
and	O
Carriers	O
;	O
with	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Fairs	O
and	O
Market	O
Towns	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Whereas	O
I	O
JOHN	B-pers
FREEMAN	I-pers
,	O
dwelling	O
in	O
Turn-wheel	O
Lane	O
,	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Beecher	O
,	O
Salter	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
10	O
Years	O
periodically	O
troubled	O
with	O
windy	O
Eructations	O
and	O
four	O
Belchings	O
;	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pain	O
that	O
pierced	O
through	O
my	O
very	O
Back	O
and	O
Loins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Loss	O
of	O
Appetite	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Faculty	O
of	O
Puysick	O
,	O
without	O
obtaining	O
any	O
lasting	O
Relief	O
,	O
at	O
length	O
