TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
1732	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1732	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lee	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newham	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humston	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gainer	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Noss	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sellers	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Broomhead	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burchett	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sopp	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Gregory	B-pers
Pember	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blow	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sidwell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goss	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reneer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Feline	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Ann	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
17	O
s.	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Ann	O
Peterson	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
Seven-night	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Mary	O
Elizabeth	O
Homls	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Leadenhall-Market	B-place
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
Money	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
in	O
your	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
But	O
pray	O
look	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
one	O
single	O
brass	O
Farthing	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
shew	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
Holms	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
your	O
own	O
Money	O
?	O
Peterson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Money	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Market	O
with	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pences	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
Mrs.	O
Holms	O
brought	O
her	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Basset	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Holms	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
prosecute	O
you	O
?	O
Peterson	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
Business	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
Tell	O
me	O
that	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Holms	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hassle	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
pick	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
old	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
Money	O
have	O
ye	O
got	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
says	O
she	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
felt	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
empty	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
goes	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Eye	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
)	O
you	O
bold	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
call	O
her	O
Bitch	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
true	O
)	O
you	O
have	O
pick	O
'd	O
this	O
good	O
Woman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
ye	O
speak	O
such	O
another	O
Word	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
an	O
Example	O
of	O
ye	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six	O
pences	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
made	O
just	O
17s	O
.	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
that	O
drop	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Struggle	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
Bitch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
pretty	O
handsomely	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
watch	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
Days	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Pick	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
would	O
prosecute	O
them	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
A	O
couple	O
of	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
not	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
felt	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
all	O
her	O
Money	O
there	O
.	O
Peterson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
wicked	O
Hussy	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Bellows-Maker	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
takes	O
in	O
Things	O
to	O
wash	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
Things	O
;	O
old	O
Things	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
comes	O
in	O
my	O
Way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
come	O
often	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
within	O
this	O
half	O
Year	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
lying	O
about	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
3.	O
Henry	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Garlick-Hith	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cask	O
of	O
Pearl-Ashes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plaisted	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Plaisted	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Henry	O
Taylor	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Labourer	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
for	O
about	O
15	O
Months	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
Christopher	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Manner	O
?	O
Plaisted	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
done	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
Christopher	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
watch	O
about	O
my	O
Door	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
hir	O
'd	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
confess	O
Particulars	O
?	O
Plaisted	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
a	O
Cask	O
of	O
Pearl-Ashes	O
,	O
5	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Oyl	O
,	O
1	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Spirit	O
of	O
Turpentine	O
,	O
1	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Spirit	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
8	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Olive-Oyl	O
,	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Gun-powder	O
,	O
84	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Shot	O
,	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Allum	O
,	O
48	O
black	O
Links	O
,	O
40	O
Sacks	O
,	O
14	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Sackcloth	O
,	O
containing	O
about	O
290	O
Yards	O
,	O
10	O
Gross	O
of	O
Corks	O
,	O
1	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Whip-Cord	O
,	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Rand-Thread	O
,	O
1	O
Bag	O
of	O
Rape-Seed	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Bushel	O
,	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Powder	O
Blue	O
,	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Indico	O
Blue	O
,	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Starch	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Mustard-Seed	O
,	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Glue	O
,	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Salt-Petre	O
,	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Hemp-Cord	O
,	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Ground	O
Mustard-Seed	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
ask	O
Pardon	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4	O
,	O
5.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rose	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
4	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Peirson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Peirson	I-pers
.	O
Betty	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
3	O
Months	O
.	O
Her	O
Mother	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
Quilt	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Basingham	O
,	O
who	O
knowing	O
that	O
Betty	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Rose	O
Curry	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
Goods	O
of	O
mine	O
there	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Girl	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
Mother	O
in	O
o'Sundays	O
in	O
Sermon	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
those	O
times	O
her	O
Mother	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
Confession	O
in	O
Writing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Curry	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
surprise	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
Hand	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Basingham	I-pers
.	O
Rose	O
Curry	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
a	O
Quilt	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
leave	O
it	O
till	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Spouse	O
might	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
that	O
her	O
Daughter	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
suspicious	O
.	O
I	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Basingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Quilt	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
was	O
less	O
than	O
it	O
cost	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Looking	O
about	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
about	O
'em	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
ruin	O
of	O
her	O
Daughter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
John	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot-lid	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Salts	O
,	O
3	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Boar's-Head	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
over	O
a	O
Passage	O
which	O
leads	O
from	O
the	O
Street	O
to	O
other	O
Houses	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
Rogue	O
got	O
over	O
two	O
Fences	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
me	O
over	O
Fleet-bridge	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Pewter-pots	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
too	O
fast	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
5	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Night-house	O
in	O
George-Alley	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Winniat	O
's	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
in	O
Red-Lyon-Street	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Gallon-Pot	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
writ	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
at	O
the	O
Boar's-Head	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
And	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Word	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
George-Alley	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Snailes	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Snailehouse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
about	O
4	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Linen	O
Frock	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
led	O
my	O
Child	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
2	O
other	O
Women	O
took	O
off	O
its	O
Frock	O
and	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
strip	O
it	O
naked	O
,	O
but	O
somebody	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
prevented	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
.	O
A	O
Boy	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
away	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
Cold-Bath-Field	B-place
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Work-house	O
;	O
the	O
Child	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
it	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
Home	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
Home	O
drunk	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Frock	O
and	O
Stays	O
in	O
Cold-Bath-Field	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
off	O
its	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Dykes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kenstry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Lodging	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Sheets	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
9.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Cunnycut	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Parish-Church	B-place
of	I-place
Hendon	I-place
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Evening	O
,	O
Feb.	O
2.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
at	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
seen	O
sauntring	O
about	O
Hendon	O
:	O
Between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
drinking	O
till	O
near	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
looking	O
out	O
o	O
'	O
Window	O
,	O
saw	O
that	O
some	O
Lead	O
had	O
been	O
strip	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Church-Gallery	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Evening	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
,	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
Field	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
enter	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
towards	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
perceiving	O
that	O
Rudd	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
untrussed	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fit	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
looking	O
often	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Rudd	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Lead	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Church	O
.	O
Rudd	O
then	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
at	O
last	O
took	O
him	O
among	O
the	O
Boughs	O
of	O
a	O
stump	O
Tree	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
hide	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Box	O
for	O
Tea	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Kelar	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Briller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
Messieurs	O
Kelar	O
and	O
Briller	O
keep	O
a	O
Cabinet-maker	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
there	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
commonly	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
less	O
than	O
prime	O
Cost	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Pretence	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
Mahogony	O
Tea-box	O
was	O
missing	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ditch	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Polly	I-pers
for	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
whose	O
Shop	O
Mr.	O
Kelar	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Polly	O
described	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
soon	O
after	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kelar	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
more	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Henry	B-pers
Tilson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
2	O
Cows	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
1	O
Heifer	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Rosemary-Branch	O
,	O
in	O
Islington-Fields	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
Cows	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
driving	O
them	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
going	O
by	O
my	O
Door	O
with	O
2	O
Cows	O
:	O
Says	O
I	O
to	O
Harry	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
Green-yard	O
Business	O
.	O
And	O
say	O
Harry	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
I	O
'll	O
run	O
and	O
stop	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
)	O
gave	O
him	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
drive	O
'em	O
to	O
the	O
Green-yard	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
till	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
then	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
3	O
Cows	O
from	O
the	O
Common	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
away	O
at	O
Kingsland-Road	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Green-yard	O
gave	O
him	O
Money	O
for	O
driving	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Gran	O
's	O
Horse-thither	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
again	O
The	O
Cow	O
that	O
got	O
from	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
Home	O
again	O
The	O
Day	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Cows	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
Horses	O
taken	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
to	O
the	O
Green-yard	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
pay	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
for	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Green-yar	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Boy	O
that	O
brought	O
my	O
Horses	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
Not	O
only	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
round	O
me	O
have	O
had	O
their	O
Cows	O
or	O
Horses	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Green-yard	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
Charge	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
are	O
forced	O
to	O
pay	O
extravagantly	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Green-yard	O
gives	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a-piece	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
brings	O
Beasts	O
thither	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
Encouragement	O
for	O
these	O
Vagabonds	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Fields	O
,	O
or	O
off	O
the	O
Common	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
being	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
12	O
,	O
13.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Foy	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
14	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
47	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Setree	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
together	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Setree	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Russel-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
Carrol	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
fine	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
several	O
Counters	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
pleas	O
'd	O
her	O
Foy	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
where	O
several	O
Papers	O
of	O
Stockings	O
lay	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Coats	O
were	O
tuck	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
Smith	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
without	O
taking	O
any	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Scotch-Cloth	O
to	O
line	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
a	O
Gown	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
:	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
haste	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Carrol	O
was	O
in	O
haste	O
too	O
:	O
He	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
please	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
both	O
were	O
very	O
difficult	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
engaged	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Son	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Foy	O
was	O
bustling	O
about	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
suspect	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Carrol	O
bought	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Irish-Linen	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
19	O
d	O
1/2	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
borrow	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Foy	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
Foy	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
observed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
2	O
large	O
Linen	O
Bags	O
,	O
or	O
Pockets	O
,	O
within	O
side	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
.	O
Then	O
Smith	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Linen	O
as	O
Carrol	O
had	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
21	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
follow	O
'd	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
his	O
Customers	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
Smith	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Canister	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
he	O
got	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
Carrol	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mason	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hosse	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
.	O
By	O
good	O
Luck	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
standing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hesse	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Mistress	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
Foy	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
just	O
now	O
?	O
I	O
,	O
at	O
your	O
Shop	O
.	O
Fellow	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
your	O
Shop	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
stands	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
secured	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Foy	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
In	O
pulling	O
off	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
two	O
odd	O
Stockings	O
were	O
some	O
how	O
thrown	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
Smith	O
pretended	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Foy	O
;	O
but	O
Foy	O
and	O
Carrol	O
were	O
drinking	O
hot	O
Pots	O
together	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Up-stairs	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Lyon	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
themselves	O
to	O
be	O
denied	O
to	O
every	O
Body	O
but	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Smith	O
left	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
-	O
Bowen	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
Half-a-Crown	O
the	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cloth	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hosse	O
(	O
to	O
whose	O
Lodger	O
Carrol	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
)	O
going	O
Up-stairs	O
,	O
found	O
2	O
odd	O
Stockings	O
hung	O
between	O
the	O
Banisters	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
fellows	O
to	O
the	O
2	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
behind	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Counter	O
when	O
Foy	O
was	O
searched	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Mr.	O
Hosse	O
found	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
under	O
the	O
Water-Tub	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
those	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
.	O
Smith	O
was	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
[	O
out	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
on	O
their	O
Trail	O
]	O
Foy	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
met	O
her	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
5	O
or	O
10	O
Guineas	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
as	O
much	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
them	O
for	O
compounding	O
a	O
Felony	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Russel-Street	O
)	O
Carrol	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Life	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
her	O
in	O
Charge	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
dear	O
Honey	O
White	O
,	O
my	O
Life	O
is	O
in	O
your	O
Power	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
hang	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
save	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Foy	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
when	O
Smith	O
came	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
heard	O
Smith	O
had	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
surrender	O
herself	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
White	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
Leadenhall-Street	O
.	O
Carrol	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
facing	O
and	O
robing	O
for	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
unlikely	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Carrol	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Foy	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
13	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Foy	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Munyard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Ann	B-pers
Holburt	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holburt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Free	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
8	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
15.	O
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
16	O
Pair	O
of	O
Girls	O
Kid-Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
8th	B-place
of	I-place
this	I-place
Instant	I-place
February	I-place
.	O
While	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
busy	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
reaching	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
took	O
the	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
observed	O
by	O
Edward	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
,	O
an	O
opposite	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Royal-Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rutty	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Tavern	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
thorow	O
Fare	O
)	O
take	O
the	O
Pot	O
which	O
stood	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
;	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
John	B-pers
Broadby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
15	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Colebrant	I-pers
and	O
Ralph	B-pers
Myer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
is	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Colebrant	O
the	O
Sugar-Baker	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Colebrant	O
's	O
Coachman	O
.	O
The	O
Butter	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Colebrant	O
's	O
Stables	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Firkin	O
to	O
several	O
Tallow-Chandlers	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
8	O
Firkins	O
to	O
Carter	O
(	O
he	O
that	O
sells	O
Candles	O
so	O
cheap	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Half-Moon	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
;	O
3	O
Firkins	O
to	O
the	O
Tallow-Chandler	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
over-against	O
Carter	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rivet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Windford-Street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
swear	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
this	O
Butter	O
from	O
a	O
Carman	O
?	O
Lightfoot	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
But	O
ah	O
!	O
you	O
threatened	O
my	O
Life	O
if	O
I	O
swore	O
it	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
,	O
Carter	O
's	O
Boy	O
.	O
Lightfoot	O
brought	O
some	O
Firkins	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Colebrant	O
.	O
We	O
lost	O
Butter	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
times	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
11	O
Months	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
constantly	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
my	O
Service	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
.	O
Lightfoot	O
was	O
my	O
Prentice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
wronged	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
Gentlemen	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
18.	O
John	B-pers
Tapper	I-pers
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
Right-pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rohan	I-pers
.	O
You	O
must	O
know	O
that	O
Tapper	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Cannon	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
both	O
lodged	O
at	O
Cannon	O
's	O
Mother	O
in-Law	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
Chandler's-shop	O
in	O
Gravel-Lane	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
thither	O
about	O
Noon	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Ware	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
Company	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
there	O
?	O
Rohan	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Cannon	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
;	O
and	O
Tapper	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
Jonny	O
;	O
and	O
-	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
-	O
Smith	O
and	O
Cotterl	O
,	O
and	O
Wilcox	O
.	O
Now	O
Wilcox	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
Cards	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Wilcox	O
won	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
had	O
better	O
buy	O
me	O
a	O
Smock	O
to	O
my	O
Back	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
some	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
some-body	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
miscarried	O
;	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
your	O
Wife	O
with	O
Child	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
more	O
than	O
yours	O
will	O
ever	O
be	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
ye	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Because	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tapper	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
tapp	O
'd	O
her	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Have	O
ye	O
so	O
?	O
says	O
Tapper	O
,	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tap	O
you	O
.	O
My	O
Back	O
was	O
towards	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
Discourse	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
the	O
Deceased	O
opened	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Wound	O
under	O
his	O
right	O
Breast	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Lo	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
sha	O
n't	O
pay	O
for	O
this	O
?	O
Council	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
all	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
had	O
ye	O
not	O
?	O
Rohan	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
And	O
were	O
you	O
not	O
all	O
got	O
Drunk	O
?	O
Rohan	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
Drunk	O
?	O
Rohan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
tell	O
ye	O
;	O
why	O
,	O
sure	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
persuaded	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
Drunk	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
drinking	O
together	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
?	O
Rohan	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
always	O
a	O
quarrelling	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
off	O
when	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
Rohan	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
Yards	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
given	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
paring	O
his	O
Nails	O
just	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
?	O
Rohan	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
no	O
mention	O
of	O
a	O
Whetstone	O
?	O
Rohan	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
live	O
after	O
the	O
Accident	O
?	O
Rohan	O
.	O
Eleven	O
Days	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coroner	O
sat	O
on	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
told	O
me	O
(	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Care	O
)	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
accidentally	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
as	O
to	O
stab	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
sorry	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
prick	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Creed	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
Magpye	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
stab	O
Mr.	O
Cannon	O
?	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
sorry	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ackers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Creed	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
telling	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
pay	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
'll	O
stab	O
him	O
[	O
Cannon	O
]	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
that	O
the	O
Jobb	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
the	O
Matter	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Creed	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
stabb	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
prick	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
will	O
set	O
him	O
upright	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Tapper	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
has	O
murder	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
expect	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
him	O
brought	O
to	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
may	O
suffer	O
himself	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
me	O
suffer	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Puncture	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
below	O
the	O
Right-pap	O
,	O
it	O
run	O
something	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Quarters	O
deep	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
tolerably	O
easy	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
Wound	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
muscular	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
Day	O
the	O
Wound	O
look	O
'd	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
blooded	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
then	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
aint	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Wound	O
all	O
along	O
digested	O
well	O
openly	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
I	O
(	O
with	O
another	O
Surgeon	O
)	O
opened	O
his	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Blood	O
and	O
Matter	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Thorax	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
spit	O
no	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Lungs	O
no	O
way	O
touched	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
perform	O
their	O
Office	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Thorax	O
which	O
was	O
penetrated	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Body	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Maphragma	O
,	O
might	O
cause	O
his	O
Urine	O
to	O
be	O
something	O
bloody	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
suddled	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
first	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Nurse	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
lie	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
sit	O
bolt	O
up	O
right	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
black	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
almost	O
strangled	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
seven	O
Pints	O
of	O
Blood	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Mother-in-Law	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Gravel-Lane	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
to	O
drink	O
and	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
play	O
'd	O
with	O
Wilcox	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
down	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Money	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
that	O
too	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
shelter	O
in	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
News	O
was	O
brought	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
miscarry	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
we	O
heard	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
bad	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Joaks	O
pass	O
about	O
Tapping	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
?	O
Cotterell	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
cutting	O
his	O
Nails	O
with	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
who	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
)	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
Whetstone	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Trowel	O
lies	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
whet	O
your	O
Knife	O
on	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Trowel	O
,	O
and	O
whetted	O
his	O
Knife	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
Uamn	O
the	O
Monkey	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
Noise	O
he	O
makes	O
with	O
whetting	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
bearing	O
what	O
any	O
Body	O
say	O
.	O
And	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Push	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
round	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
over	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
prick	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
own	O
fault	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
push	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
drunk	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
about	O
this	O
Accident	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
all	O
owing	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
Bitch	O
her	O
Mother	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rohan	I-pers
when	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
hurt	O
?	O
Cotterell	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
Wilcox	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Cotterell	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
for	O
staying	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
up	O
and	O
call	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Cards	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
won	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
last	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
play	O
'd	O
with	O
Wilcox	O
.	O
They	O
play	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Farthing	O
a	O
Game	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
lost	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
down	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
15	O
d.	O
and	O
lost	O
all	O
that	O
Money	O
too	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
stripp	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Dimitty-Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
his	O
Wife	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
more	O
need	O
fetch	O
my	O
Smock	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
beat	O
your	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Lane	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Table	O
to	O
pare	O
his	O
Nails	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Whetstone	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Trowel	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
whet	O
his	O
Knife	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
whetting	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
the	O
Fellow	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
Noise	O
he	O
makes	O
with	O
his	O
Knife	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shove	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
that	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
round	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
he	O
fell	O
backwards	O
against	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
quite	O
all	O
along	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
if	O
the	O
Table	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
fuddled	O
and	O
stagger	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
Bless	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
that	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
's	O
all	O
along	O
of	O
that	O
Bastard	O
Tapper	O
's	O
Nonsense	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
about	O
Tapping	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tapper	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
Word	O
;	O
if	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
had	O
been	O
spoke	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
won	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
won	O
it	O
again	O
from	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
bid	O
his	O
Wife	O
pawn	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
play	O
there	O
to	O
pawn	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
snatch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Cards	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
in	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Word	O
was	O
brought	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Midwife	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Her	O
Mother	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Thank	O
God	O
she	O
's	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
has	O
been	O
there	O
and	O
blooded	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
and	O
paring	O
his	O
Nails	O
at	O
a	O
Table	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Whetstone	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
who	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Trowel	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
whetted	O
his	O
Knife	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
over	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
then	O
no	O
quarrel	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
this	O
?	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
thin	O
Coat	O
without	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
Cold	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
he	O
blam	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
intended	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
first	O
prob	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Wound	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Little-Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
last	O
Sessions	O
[	O
January	O
14	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Accident	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
the	O
Bitch	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
never	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
minded	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whetting	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
against	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drinking	O
together	O
very	O
friendly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
poor	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
how	O
the	O
Wound	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
but	O
Damn	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
mind	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
drink	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
spoke	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shook	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
quiet	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
quarrel	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
many	O
hundred	O
Times	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
taken	O
even	O
blows	O
patiently	O
,	O
without	O
returning	O
the	O
ill	O
Usage	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Cannon	O
's	O
Death	O
was	O
accidental	O
.	O
19	O
,	O
20.	O
John	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sacks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
8	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sperinck	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21	O
,	O
22.	O
Lucy	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Lucy	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Pound	O
of	O
Whalebone	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shrigly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shrigly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
And	O
Hester	O
for	O
receiving	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Whalebone	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
23.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
24.	O
John	B-pers
Fife	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Boat	O
and	O
an	O
Anchor	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
25.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
John	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
17.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camblet	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
7	O
Ells	O
of	O
White	O
Tabby	O
,	O
value	O
44	O
s.	O
2	O
Ells	O
of	O
Black	O
Tabby	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Wingate	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19.	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
A	O
Motion	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
on	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
that	O
Charles	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
two	O
material	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Motion	O
was	O
over-rul	O
'd	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Tapster	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bass	O
at	O
the	O
George	B-place
Inn	I-place
on	I-place
Snow-Hill	I-place
,	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
(	O
Mr.	O
Rider	O
's	O
Clerk	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Watford	O
Carrier	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Pantry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
And	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
stop	O
her	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
acquainted	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
How	O
acquainted	O
?	O
Was	O
she	O
a	O
Servant	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
rather	O
a	O
Mistress	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
Bass	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
inform	O
Mr.	O
Bass	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
aside	O
,	O
the	O
Landlord	O
had	O
distrain	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
acquaint	O
any	O
Body	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
our	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
William	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
Weeks	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
Dead	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rider	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Bass	O
and	O
his	O
People	O
carry	O
off	O
what	O
Goods	O
they	O
could	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
some	O
away	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
these	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
was	O
a	O
12	O
Month	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pantry	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
too	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
Goods	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
9	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Camblet	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
Ells	O
of	O
Tabby	O
,	O
some	O
Black	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
White	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
Papers	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Papers	O
open	O
'd	O
.	O
Powell	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
How	O
then	O
can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Colour	O
and	O
Quantity	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Papers	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rider	O
's	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Rider	O
find	O
the	O
Bill	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
at	O
any	O
Charge	O
in	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Hand	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cutting	I-pers
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Bass	O
was	O
under	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
he	O
conceal	O
'd	O
himself	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Stepney-Fields	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Taylor	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Camblet	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
she	O
brought	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tap-House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Brass	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
when	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Nurse	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
his	O
Goods	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
,	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Goods	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
but	O
Tom	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
(	O
taking	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
not	O
daring	O
to	O
appear	O
)	O
carried	O
off	O
20	O
Casks	O
of	O
Cyder	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cutting	I-pers
stole	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
great	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
28.	O
Charles	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Fleming	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
the	O
Ship	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Coach	O
or	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Robin	B-pers
Inwood	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Leg	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tript	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
my	O
Hat	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
swore	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
kick	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Mitre	O
Court	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
Hat	O
.	O
Rob	B-pers
Inwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
2	O
Yards	O
behind	O
Tom	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
.	O
[	O
Here	O
Inwood	O
repeated	O
the	O
same	O
Particulars	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Rain	O
'd	O
hard	O
;	O
my	O
Hat	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
against	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
seiz	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
stop	O
Thief	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
Boys	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
I	O
standing	O
still	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
ye	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
run	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Boys	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
ye	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Boys	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Lamps	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
passing	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Beaver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Plate	O
has	O
lain	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
no	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
take	O
ill	O
Courses	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
good	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
maintain	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
allow	O
'd	O
him	O
Pocket	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Cuthbert	B-pers
Peale	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Stumpy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Woolhead	I-pers
and	O
-	B-pers
Fatty	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
in	O
Squirrel-Alley	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
assaulted	O
Mary	B-pers
Aylesbury	I-pers
,	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Aylesbury	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
4	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
swore	O
,	O
Damn	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
that	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Dirt	O
,	O
in	O
Squirrel-Alley	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
but	O
one	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
stripp	O
'd	O
me	O
as	O
naked	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
fill	O
'd	O
my	O
Mouth	O
with	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
till	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
so	O
long	O
?	O
Aylesbury	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
there	O
till	O
Ten	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
?	O
Aylesbury	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
in	O
that	O
naked	O
Condition	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
take	O
away	O
all	O
your	O
Cloaths	O
?	O
Aylesbury	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
Rag	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
them	O
all	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
over	O
Soil	O
and	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
torn	O
to	O
Bits	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
touch	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
they	O
took	O
you	O
to	O
that	O
place	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Design	O
than	O
to	O
rob	O
you	O
-	O
to	O
Lie	O
with	O
you	O
-	O
Aylesbury	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
Design	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
stripp	O
'd	O
me	O
stark	O
naked	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
30.	O
Mary	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Papye	I-pers
,	O
Febr	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Modesty	O
not	O
suffering	O
him	O
to	O
appear	O
and	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
31.	O
Susan	B-pers
Elfe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
defrauding	O
Richard	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
of	O
three	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Pound	O
of	O
Starch	O
,	O
under	O
false	O
Colours	O
and	O
Pretences	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Grains	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
33.	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Feb.	O
25	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Burrard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
3d	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
return	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Son	O
in	O
March	O
was	O
12	O
Month	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
so	O
order	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
defrauded	O
his	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
by	O
false	O
Tokens	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
hearing	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
being	O
read	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
which	O
says	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
any	O
Person	O
order	O
'd	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
should	O
afterwards	O
he	O
found	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Dominions	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
the	O
Term	O
of	O
Years	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
for	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
suffer	O
Death	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
35.	O
John	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
and	I-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
Busby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
February	O
16	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36	O
,	O
37.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Faxton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
9d	O
.	O
Half-penny	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
William	O
Davis	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	B-place
Hackney	I-place
towards	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Moon	O
did	O
shine	O
as	O
bright	O
as	O
Day	O
;	O
O	O
law	O
!	O
thinks	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Rogues	O
!	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Faxton	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
!	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
Smith	O
a	O
Silver	O
Groat	O
,	O
and	O
5d	O
.	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
2d	O
.	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
I	O
met	O
Wingfield	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
)	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Oram	O
[	O
Oswald	O
]	O
with	O
2	O
great	O
Dogs	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
Wingfield	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
one	O
Dog	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
to	O
London-Field	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
[	O
Oswald	O
]	O
Oram	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Salmon	O
and	O
Ball	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
2	O
such	O
Men	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Faxton	O
,	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Pea	O
Jacket	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
short	O
Man	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
Coat	O
;	O
we	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
again	O
to	O
London-Field	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
Wingfield	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
by	O
Wingfield	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Oram	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Norris	O
,	O
Faxton	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Smith	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Groat	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Smith	O
said	O
to	O
Faxton	O
,	O
Ye	O
whiddling	O
Dog	O
,	O
now	O
you	O
have	O
hang	O
'd	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
cut	O
your	O
Throat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Oram	O
.	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
finding	O
Company	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
with	O
.	O
Wingfield	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
Foot-Pads	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
his	O
Service	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
a	O
Dog	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
2	O
Men	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Pea	O
Jacket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
short	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
Coat	O
.	O
Says	O
Wingfield	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
those	O
are	O
the	O
Rogues	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
answer	O
the	O
Description	O
.	O
We	O
stepp	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Faxton	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
he	O
trembled	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
Wingfield	O
seiz	O
'd	O
Smith	O
.	O
We	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
Faxton	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
Guilty	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
you	O
take	O
us	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
Smith	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
fight	O
the	O
2	O
brightest	O
Men	O
in	O
Hackney	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Buffaloe's-Head	O
,	O
in	O
Hackney	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
we	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Room	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
fixt	O
his	O
Eye	O
upon	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Says	O
some	O
Body	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
He	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
pointing	O
to	O
Faxton	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
Mittimus	O
was	O
making	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
advised	O
Faxton	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Smith	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
Smith	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
shall	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
too	O
.	O
Wingfield	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Oram	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
related	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Faxton	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Smith	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
Smith	O
then	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
then	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
now	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
one	O
to	O
hang	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
Smith	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
'll	O
go	O
to	O
Oswald	O
's	O
Window-shutters	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
the	O
Silver	O
Groat	O
that	O
I	O
thrust	O
in	O
there	O
last	O
Night	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
the	O
Window-shutters	O
were	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
fallen	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
.	O
When	O
Faxton	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
confess	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
Smith	O
had	O
on	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Loop	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
put	O
on	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
scarce	O
spoke	O
when	O
Smith	O
doubling	O
his	O
Hands	O
together	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
precious	O
Eyes	O
and	O
Limbs	O
!	O
that	O
Word	O
has	O
Hang	O
'd	O
us	O
both	O
!	O
but	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
alone	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
stick	O
ye	O
thus	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
before	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Smith	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
Faxton	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
Silver	O
Groat	O
in	O
the	O
ledge	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Oswald	O
's	O
Shutters	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Father	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Smith	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Old	O
Man	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
four	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
the	O
Silver	O
Groat	O
is	O
.	O
So	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Oswald	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
I	O
changed	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Groat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Silver	O
Groat	O
was	O
found	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Directions	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
bended	O
King	O
William	O
's	O
Groat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Hat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Norris	O
.	O
Fallum	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
voluntary	O
.	O
Smith	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Rage	O
and	O
Fury	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
should	O
die	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
look	O
on	O
the	O
Hat	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
looked	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Loop	O
is	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lamb-Alley	O
,	O
without	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
Bolognia	O
Pudding	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Trade	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
Smith	O
's	O
Aunt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
Sea	O
several	O
Years	O
;	O
his	O
Mother	O
makes	O
Sausages	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sells	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
38.	O
John	B-pers
Shaccoy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldersgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
16	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
-	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
in	O
Bride-lane	O
,	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
Ann	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk-Damask	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Quilted	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sam	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
21	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
40.	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Catherine	I-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldersgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Moidores	O
,	O
3	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Tin	O
Canisters	O
,	O
Value	O
18d	O
.	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
hir	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
at	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
weary	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Month	O
's	O
End	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
glad	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
pass	O
with	O
her	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
a	O
former	O
Servant	O
of	O
mine	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
without	O
a	O
Maid	O
,	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
my	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
my	O
Drawers	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
's	O
become	O
of	O
your	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
here	O
?	O
Became	O
of	O
'em	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
neither	O
Rings	O
nor	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
true	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
near	O
the	O
Compter-Gate	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Officer	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
7	O
Moidores	O
,	O
2	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
except	O
1	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
near	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
:	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
behind	O
the	O
Chest	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
persuade	O
her	O
Master	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
Money	O
and	O
these	O
Rings	O
,	O
wrapt	O
in	O
this	O
Rag	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
both	O
the	O
Jury	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
a	O
favourable	O
Report	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
.	O
41	O
,	O
42	O
,	O
43.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Tripland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Past	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Hatband	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
Scarf	O
.	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
And	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
being	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
.	O
At	O
Midnight	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
4	O
Fellows	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Rogue	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
uneasy	O
on	O
that	O
Account	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
could	O
hard-	O
be	O
so	O
abandon	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
pay	O
some	O
Regard	O
to	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
presume	O
to	O
attack	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
.	O
Encouraged	O
by	O
this	O
Reflection	O
,	O
I	O
past	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
up	O
Swan-Alley	B-place
,	O
when	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
2	O
Men	O
come	O
tripping	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
began	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
entertained	O
a	O
more	O
favourable	O
Opinion	O
of	O
them	O
than	O
they	O
deserved	O
:	O
I	O
mended	O
my	O
Pace	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
theirs	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
brought	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Thomas	O
Edwards	O
(	O
that	O
young	O
Lad	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
)	O
came	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
Knife	O
to	O
me	O
thus	O
-	O
and	O
bad	O
me	O
stand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Past	I-pers
(	O
that	O
down	O
looking	O
Fellow	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
next	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
then	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fright	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Pistol	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
been	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
clasp	O
'd	O
Knife	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tripland	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Back	I-pers
came	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
none	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
coming	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
slipt	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Scarf	O
:	O
They	O
swore	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
run	O
down	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
some	O
Persons	O
came	O
from	O
Rag-Fair	O
to	O
visit	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Swan-Alley	O
,	O
near	O
my	O
Brother	O
(	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prior	O
)	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
.	O
And	O
how	O
goes	O
Trade	O
your	O
Way	O
?	O
says	O
one	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
truly	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
so	O
,	O
says	O
another	O
;	O
but	O
Robbing	O
goes	O
forward	O
however	O
.	O
Robbing	O
?	O
says	O
a	O
third	O
.	O
Ay	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
pass	O
the	O
World	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
!	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
robb	O
'd	O
here	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
Clergyman	O
?	O
says	O
the	O
fourth	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
we	O
see	O
some	O
Fellows	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
with	O
a	O
Parson	O
's	O
Hat	O
?	O
And	O
so	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
The	O
Alehouse-Man	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
acquainted	O
my	O
Brother	O
with	O
what	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Moon-light	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Moon	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
clouded	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
under	O
such	O
Confussion	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
a	O
clasp	O
Knife	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Pistol	O
;	O
how	O
then	O
can	O
you	O
recollect	O
to	O
perfectly	O
that	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
very	O
Men	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
positive	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
Opinion	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
supported	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
more	O
positive	O
to	O
some	O
than	O
to	O
others	O
I	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
Past	O
and	O
Edwards	O
for	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
Tripland	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
Beck	O
's	O
Evidence	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
cautious	O
of	O
being	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
dirty	O
,	O
thick-set	O
short	O
Fellow	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
many	O
such	O
about	O
Town	O
.	O
Past	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
none	O
but	O
Edwards	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
indeed	O
,	O
that	O
Edwards	O
's	O
Countenance	O
struck	O
me	O
most	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
Edward	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
one	O
thing	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
observe	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
Providence	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
chang	O
'd	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
to	O
disguise	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Coat	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Coat	O
that	O
he	O
wore	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
or	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
.	O
About	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Edwards	O
,	O
and	O
Tripland	O
met	O
with	O
Past	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
My	O
Lads	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
Lay	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
upon	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
better	O
Business	O
than	O
stealing	O
Lead	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
but	O
a	O
foolish	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
;	O
you	O
had	O
much	O
better	O
stop	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
I	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Widegate-Alley	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
agreed	O
upon	O
Street-Robbery	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
stop	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Coachman	O
whipped	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
into	O
Hoxton-square	O
.	O
Going	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
,	O
Past	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Boys	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
Cock	O
!	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
mean	O
by	O
a	O
Cock	O
?	O
Beck	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Fire	O
!	O
Fire	O
!	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
let	O
him	O
pass	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
alarm	O
all	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
along	O
Old-street	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
,	O
without	O
doing	O
any	O
Business	O
:	O
But	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
,	O
Paste	O
called	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
Boys	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Smallcoal-man	O
;	O
let	O
us	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
wear	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Hats	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
A	O
Smallcoal-man	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
Beck	O
.	O
A	O
Parson	O
:	O
We	O
always	O
call	O
a	O
Parson	O
a	O
Smallcoal-man	O
,	O
because	O
their	O
Dresses	O
are	O
pretty	O
much	O
alike	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Parson	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
.	O
He	O
turned	O
down	O
Swan-Alley	O
,	O
when	O
Edwards	O
stept	O
forward	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
Whereof	O
another	O
Man	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
Past	O
said	O
,	O
Boys	O
!	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
a	O
swearing	O
at	O
the	O
Parson	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
swore	O
and	O
cursed	O
bloodily	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Half	O
pence	O
.	O
Then	O
Past	O
took	O
the	O
Parson	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Tripland	O
his	O
Scarf	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
poor	O
Parson	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Catherine-wheel	O
Alley	O
and	O
stole	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
off	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
new	O
Houses	O
that	O
are	O
unfinish	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
afterwards	O
all	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
Information	O
against	O
my	O
Companions	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Tripland	O
and	O
Past	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Edwards	O
many	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
stole	O
30	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
together	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Shop-door	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Beck	O
playing	O
the	O
Rogue	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
pushing	O
one	O
another	O
over	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
their	O
Looks	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
'em	O
.	O
Beck	O
had	O
got	O
on	O
a	O
great	O
flopping	O
Hat	O
,	O
without	O
Loops	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
does	O
that	O
great	O
Hat	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
that	O
Fellow	O
?	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
looks	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
Parson	O
's	O
Hat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Higginson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Notice	O
as	O
well	O
he	O
,	O
of	O
their	O
playing	O
the	O
Rogue	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
shabby	O
Fellow	O
as	O
Beck	O
should	O
wear	O
such	O
a	O
great	O
Hat	O
.	O
Rich	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Headborough	O
.	O
On	O
Jan.	O
30	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
sick	O
and	O
lame	O
in	O
Swan-Alley	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
to	O
his	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Alehouse-man	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
talk	O
'd	O
about	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
Robbing	O
there-a-way	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
Rogues	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Parson	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
they	O
rob	O
the	O
Cloth	O
?	O
And	O
says	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
4	O
Men	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Parson	O
's	O
Hat	O
among	O
'em	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
The	O
Alehouse-man	O
told	O
this	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prior	O
the	O
Brewer	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
we	O
knew	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
that	O
the	O
4	O
Men	O
were	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Yorkshire	O
Grey	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
seized	O
Past	O
and	O
Tripland	O
,	O
for	O
Edwards	O
and	O
Beck	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
.	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
'em	O
both	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
sent	O
Word	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prior	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Haydon	O
,	O
the	O
Parson	O
swore	O
downright	O
to	O
Edwards	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
Do	O
ye	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
you	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
know	O
you	O
better	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
observed	O
you	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
The	O
Parson	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Beck	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Byton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
in	O
Skinner's-street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Byton	O
directly	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
us	O
:	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Hat	O
.	O
Edw	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Beck	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
bid	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Rum	O
for	O
the	O
Hat	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
worth	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
to	O
Past	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Sweat	O
.	O
Past	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Skinner's-street	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
or	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Byton	I-pers
.	O
Tom	B-pers
Past	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
Hat	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Past	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Byton	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
an	O
Oath	O
was	O
a	O
tender	O
Thing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
verily	O
thought	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
knew	O
you	O
full	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
waved	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
for	O
the	O
Trouble	O
of	O
attending	O
the	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hancock	O
,	O
the	O
Headborough	O
,	O
in	O
Swan	O
Ally	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Discourse	O
happen	O
'd	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
related	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
the	O
Yorkshire	O
Grey	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
Past	O
and	O
Tripland	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Beck	O
and	O
Edwards	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
'em	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
we	O
collar	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
'em	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
[	O
Here	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
called	O
on	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
Defense	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Past	I-pers
.	O
I	O
own	O
myself	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Charge	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
dye	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
dye	O
.	O
But	O
Tripland	O
is	O
an	O
innocent	O
Man	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Beck	O
,	O
why	O
will	O
you	O
swear	O
against	O
Tripland	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
innocent	O
?	O
And	O
says	O
Beck	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
hang	O
Three	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
get	O
my	O
Discharge	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
confess	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
Tripland	O
is	O
Innocent	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tripland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
Back	O
till	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
we	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Tripland	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
no	O
disfame	O
of	O
his	O
Honour	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
bound	O
'Prentice	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Breed	I-pers
in	O
Strout	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
bound	O
himself	O
to	O
Sea	O
.	O
He	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Sea	O
in	O
Merchants	O
Service	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Lisbon	O
he	O
was	O
press	O
'd	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Edenburgh	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Chrisman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Ship	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Gravsand	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
left	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Sarah	O
Whittle	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Back	I-pers
.	O
Whittle	O
had	O
bought	O
Watches	O
and	O
Rings	O
of	O
Tem	B-pers
Past	I-pers
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Parson	O
's	O
Scarf	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
us	O
when	O
we	O
made	O
it	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
Question	O
?	O
Beek	O
.	O
She	O
meant	O
,	O
when	O
did	O
we	O
srea	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
last	O
Night	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
must	O
you	O
have	O
?	O
we	O
told	O
her	O
8	O
Shillings	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
afford	O
to	O
give	O
but	O
a	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
your	O
Lordship	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
all	O
your	O
Plate	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hanoak	I-pers
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
the	O
4	O
Men	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
ye	O
wake	O
up	O
the	O
Receiver	O
?	O
Who	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
Whittle	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Whittle	O
.	O
These	O
Men	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Scarf	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
buy	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Beck	O
(	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
)	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
against	O
Whittle	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
Black-guard	O
Bastard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
20	O
before	O
he	O
'd	O
hang	O
himself	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
Rag-fair	O
women	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Whittle	O
and	O
Tripland	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Past	O
and	O
Edwards	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
44.	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
