TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
1733	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1733	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXIII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
22d	O
,	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
1733	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lee	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plaston	I-pers
,	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Mussell	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hesky	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Middlebrook	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blow	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duns	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chisselholm	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Garnet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Grogram	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Cambrick	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Padusoy	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
December	O
21	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
Dec.	O
21.	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
Feb.	O
9.	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2	O
,	O
3.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cobb	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Linseed	O
Oil	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Rape	O
Oil	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
Dugal	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Norton	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
(	O
two	O
Black-Shoe	O
Boys	O
)	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stole	O
the	O
Oil	O
off	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
their	O
Baskets	O
(	O
which	O
they	O
clay	O
'd	O
within	O
side	O
)	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Currier	O
in	O
Blue-maid	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
on	O
three	O
Sunday-Nights	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Jays	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Martha	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tea-Tongs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
,	O
9.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Makepeace	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooksbanks	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Compton	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
Compton	O
Morris	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
printed	O
Linen	O
,	O
for	O
Robings	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
Customer	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pretty	O
many	O
Goods	O
lay	O
tumbled	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
those	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
more	O
than	O
she	O
should	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Hussy	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
stolen	O
something	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
threw	O
this	O
Linen	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Threshold	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
pester	O
'd	O
with	O
these	O
Vermin	O
in	O
our	O
Shops	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
vow	O
and	O
protest	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
living	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
above	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
by	O
them	O
since	O
last	O
Month	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Jane	B-pers
Judson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
6	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tea-Tongs	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
a	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
,	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
3	O
Broad-pieces	O
,	O
43	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
June	O
22	O
.	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
John	O
Crow	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cary-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Friends	O
in	O
Shropshire	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
between	O
the	O
22d	O
and	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
outward	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
being	O
broken	O
,	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
conceal	O
'd	O
till	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Family	O
were	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
jar	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
to	O
Shrewsbury	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
so	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
pursued	O
her	O
?	O
Crow	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
expected	O
her	O
up	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
saved	O
that	O
Trouble	O
and	O
Charge	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Oswistry	O
in	O
Shropshire	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
settle	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
saying	O
,	O
to	O
Shrewsbury	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
'em	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Jenny	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Where	O
's	O
your	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Hat	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
fetch	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Tea-Spoons	O
and	O
Tongs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
mark	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
those	O
Goods	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
next	O
Day	O
(	O
Sept	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
)	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Father	O
and	O
Brother	O
coming	O
to	O
intercede	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
those	O
Goods	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
(	O
while	O
her	O
Father	O
staid	O
)	O
her	O
Brother	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
too	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
June	O
14	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
June	O
21	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Leave	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
lye	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Inn	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
Carrier	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
ready	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
all	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Half-Sister	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
lye	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
Lodging	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
till	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
hurry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Pack-Horses	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
till	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
her	O
Box	O
before	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grimston	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White's-Alley	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Corbet	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
till	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Sister	O
Corbet	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
Coach	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
my	O
Maid	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
suppos	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Crow	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
their	O
Chamber	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
fasten	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
while	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gilby	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
bolted	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chester	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
first	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
(	O
June	O
23	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
standing	O
a-jar	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
pretended	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
miscarried	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquited	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Copeland	B-pers
Yoe	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
13.	O
Michael	B-pers
Allom	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
43	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
Great-Turnstile	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
43	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boys	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Feb.	O
5	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Boy	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Orders	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Stockings	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hancock	O
's	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Chequer-Ale-House	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
R.	O
Hancock	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Bays	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Chequer-Ale-House	O
,	O
and	O
exposed	O
the	O
Stockings	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Shilling	O
Earnest	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
thinking	O
them	O
too	O
dear	O
,	O
he	O
relinquish	O
'd	O
his	O
Bargain	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
Earnest	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
four	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
last	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
9	O
s.	O
per	O
Dozen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
for	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
Ray	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Attorney	O
at	O
Law	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
!	O
and	O
sold	O
Stockings	O
by	O
the	O
Dozen	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
?	O
Richard	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
three	O
Times	O
before	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
you	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Character	O
to	O
Hancock	O
.	O
Ray	O
.	O
My	O
Landlord	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Uncle	O
was	O
very	O
rich	O
,	O
and	O
dealt	O
in	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
have	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
I	O
stole	O
the	O
Stockings	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Something	O
very	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
your	O
Possession	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
had	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
an	O
Attorney	O
of	O
the	O
King's-Bench	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
Vicissitudes	O
in	O
Life	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
may	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
wholesale	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Stockings	O
too	O
?	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
those	O
Goods	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
the	O
Mischief	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
my	O
Unhappiness	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
prove	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Alice	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Shirts	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
Rowly	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Delly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
;	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Francis	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
n	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Rice	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Pranes	O
,	O
two	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Stone	O
Blue	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
d.	O
3	O
Farthings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
Near	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
on	O
Thursday	O
about	O
Whitsuntide	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Field	O
beyond	O
Marrybone	B-place
,	O
I	O
past	O
by	O
some	O
Fellows	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
missing	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Cocky	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
a-Clock	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
;	O
and	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Rogues	O
I	O
run	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
coming	O
close	O
after	O
me	O
swore	O
by	O
God	O
,	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
make	O
me	O
remember	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
Stick	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
another	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
does	O
he	O
resist	O
?	O
Kill	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
first	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
I	O
warded	O
off	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Blows	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
stunned	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
mighty	O
Cut	O
in	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Rice	O
and	O
Prunes	O
,	O
and	O
Stone	O
Blue	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
19	O
Pence	O
all	O
Copper	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Cag	O
of	O
Treacle	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
that	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Company	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
surrendered	O
myself	O
voluntarily	O
to	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
you	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
has	O
seen	O
me	O
with	O
them	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
?	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
we	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Father	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
Brick	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Simmonds	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
lying	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
hundred	O
times	O
.	O
Deily	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Brick	O
Fields	O
fifty	O
times	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robbed	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
beat	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Head	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
surrender	O
'd	O
himself	O
voluntarily	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Turner	O
in	O
the	O
Brick-Fields	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Stone-blue	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Sutton	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
)	O
with	O
some	O
Rice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
17.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Delavan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Guineas	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hick	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Hester	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
23	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Bees-wax	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19.	O
George	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
22	O
Pair	O
of	O
Childrens	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
woollen	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
January	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
my	O
Maid	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Shop	O
.	O
She	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
5	O
Minutes	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Canister	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Skinner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
I	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
his	O
Feet	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
As	O
young	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hitch	I-pers
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Sixty	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Lawn	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
Linen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Blow-Bladder-Street	B-place
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Dawson	O
was	O
my	O
School-Fellow	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
(	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Pancost	I-pers
standing	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Horse-Shoe	O
Alehouse	O
Passage	O
;	O
Dawson	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
for	O
haste	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
off	O
for	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
saw	O
us	O
run	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
run	O
after	O
us	O
your	O
self	O
?	O
Wheatly	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
our	O
Shop	O
Richard	B-pers
Pancost	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
thieving	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
one	O
Howard	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Baldwin	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Goods	O
we	O
stole	O
;	O
and	O
Howard	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
Hold	O
for	O
buying	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
at	O
Howard	O
's	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
Footman	O
hang	O
on	O
one	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
backwards	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dawson	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
while	O
we	O
stood	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
We	O
run	O
down	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
lost	O
Dawson	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
again	O
at	O
Howard	O
's	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
'em	O
all	O
to	O
Howard	O
's	O
Wife	O
for	O
22	O
s.	O
She	O
gave	O
us	O
12	O
s.	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
We	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
a-piece	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
cost	O
me	O
4	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
Dawson	O
says	O
he	O
is	O
but	O
14	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Parish	O
Books	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
appears	O
he	O
's	O
above	O
17	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Dawson	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
Hitch	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Hitch	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Feb.	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Ogleby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
John	O
Davis	O
.	O
About	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
White-lion	O
Street	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Quartern	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Brandy	O
in	O
a	O
Back-Room	O
by	O
our	O
selves	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
Clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
nothing	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
staying	O
to	O
count	O
my	O
Money	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
describ	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
abused	O
me	O
barbarously	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
well	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
for	O
having	O
a	O
Correspondence	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Assaults	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
beat	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
all	O
over	O
bloody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
them	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
at	O
Moll	O
Adams	O
's	O
in	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
true	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Clarety-Face	O
Hannah	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
his	O
old	O
Companions	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
Clarety-Face	O
Hannah	O
in	O
Castle-Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
hot	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
first	O
Six-pence	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
Three-pence	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
do	O
for	O
this	O
Money	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
-	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mohogony	O
Tea-Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint-Mug	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Harry	B-pers
Fowl	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Thread-Sattin	O
,	O
27	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lustring	O
,	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
White	O
Tabby	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
Yards	O
of	O
Groram	O
,	O
1	O
Yard	O
of	O
Damask	O
.	O
13	O
Yards	O
of	O
Crape	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Rasdegene	O
,	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sarcenet	O
,	O
106	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mantua	O
,	O
13	O
Yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
,	O
1	O
Yard	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Yard	O
of	O
Tabby	O
Brocade	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Fathergill	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
and	O
26.	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
7	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Sarcenet	O
,	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
and	O
23	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mantua	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
Harry	B-pers
Fowl	I-pers
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Goods	O
in	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
laid	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
than	O
what	O
I	O
found	O
again	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Honey-Lane	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
to	O
produce	O
.	O
When	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
restored	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
compared	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Quantities	O
with	O
the	O
Pieces	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
tallied	O
.	O
This	O
Piece	O
of	O
White	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
has	O
his	O
own	O
Mark	O
of	O
36	O
half	O
Yards	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and-this	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Piece	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
parted	O
,	O
makes	O
exactly	O
that	O
Measure	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
49	O
Quantities	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
make	O
169	O
Yards	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
7	O
Parcels	O
,	O
seal	O
'd	O
and	O
mark	O
'd	O
;	O
5	O
of	O
these	O
Parcels	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
,	O
my	O
Partner	O
knows	O
better	O
than	O
I.	O
Richard	O
Manning	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
and	O
Weavers	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
Honey-Lane	O
Market	O
,	O
the	O
Weavers	O
use	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
sell	O
their	O
Goods	O
to	O
other	O
Weavers	O
and	O
Macklers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Warehouses	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
lay	O
their	O
Goods	O
in	O
;	O
a	O
Porter	O
having	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
brought	O
several	O
Parcels	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
,	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
at	O
last	O
open	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
whole	O
Pieces	O
nor	O
Remnants	O
,	O
but	O
Quantities	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
several	O
Weavers	O
,	O
who	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
my	O
Boy	O
(	O
next	O
time	O
the	O
Porter	O
came	O
)	O
to	O
dog	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Biard	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Queen's-Arms	O
,	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Biard	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Porter	O
had	O
brought	O
9	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
that	O
Day	O
for	O
-	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Biard	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth-colour	O
'd	O
Mantua	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
several	O
Mercers	O
Shops	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
matched	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Fowl	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
within	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
while	O
we	O
staid	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
those	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Goods	O
by	O
the	O
Porter	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
for	O
Mr.	O
-	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
such	O
cut	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
Servant	O
?	O
You	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
as	O
many	O
left	O
for	O
you	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
1000	O
l.	O
It	O
's	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
paid	O
Fowl	O
above	O
100	O
l.	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
does	O
-	O
follow	O
?	O
Manning	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
Mackler	O
-	O
one	O
that	O
sells	O
Goods	O
for	O
the	O
Weavers	O
;	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
makes	O
Goods	O
himself	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
usual	O
for	O
Macklers	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
Mercers	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Weavers	O
?	O
Manning	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Fowl	O
;	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
how	O
Fowl	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Manning	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Fowl	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Sale	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Biard	I-pers
,	O
Porter	O
.	O
Fowl	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
10	O
Parcels	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
's	O
for	O
Mr.	O
-	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
handsomely	O
,	O
like	O
whole	O
Pieces	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Maynard	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Fowl	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Burean	O
,	O
found	O
these	O
49	O
Pieces	O
;	O
this	O
Parcel	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
-	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
rents	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
This	O
Parcel	O
we	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bullock	O
's	O
a	O
Piece-Broker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Raven	O
behind	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
other	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Waters	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Street	O
.	O
Bullock	O
and	O
Waters	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
such	O
Goods	O
of	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
usual	O
for	O
the	O
Piece-Brokers	O
to	O
buy	O
such	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Macklers	O
,	O
as	O
of	O
the	O
Weavers	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
.	O
We	O
found	O
these	O
Goods	O
in	O
Fowl	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
Bullock	O
's	O
and	O
Waters	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
other	O
2	O
Parcels	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
Fowl	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
set	O
up	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
met	O
with	O
Misfortunes	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
-	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
general	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
sell	O
Remnants	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
whole	O
Pieces	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
one	O
who	O
they	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Mercer	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
Parcels	O
which	O
were	O
not	O
Remnants	O
,	O
but	O
Quantities	O
cut	O
off	O
of	O
whole	O
Pieces	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
-	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
Fowl	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Sale	O
next	O
Week	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
another	O
(	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Weaver	O
)	O
that	O
sometimes	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
large	O
Piece	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
they	O
happen	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Case	O
it	O
was	O
common	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
tear	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Macklers	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Mercers	O
would	O
oblige	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
too	O
large	O
Abatements	O
for	O
such	O
Faults	O
in	O
their	O
Work	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fowl	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
L	O
P	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Vert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ewen	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Thin-slank	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shuter	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30	O
,	O
31.	O
Peter	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Buttock	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shuter	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fretwell	I-pers
*	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Madding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
d.	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Westminster	O
.	O
See	O
Sess	O
,	O
Paper	O
,	O
No	O
II	O
.	O
p.	O
48	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
6	O
d.	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
First	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Madding	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
8	O
Sheep	O
along	O
the	O
King's-Road	B-place
,	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
Chelsea-College	O
Slaughter-House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
spend	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
a	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
spend	O
a	O
Penny	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
spend	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
my	O
last	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
got	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
a	O
drawn	O
Knife	O
to	O
my	O
Left-Breast	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
give	O
them	O
what	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
'd	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
shortest	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
3	O
d.	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Hornsby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
robbed	O
this	O
Boy	O
of	O
3	O
Pence	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
King's-Road	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
Sheep	O
to	O
the	O
College	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Hornsby	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
about	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Madding	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
late	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
H.	O
These	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
Schoolfellows	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Rochester-Row	O
in	O
Tothill-Fields	O
to	O
Strutton's-Grounds	B-place
,	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
Men	O
.	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
followed	O
me	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
a	O
naked	O
Knife	O
to	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
began	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
roughly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
6	O
d.	O
indeed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Washing-tub	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Loaf	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
what	O
it	O
wou	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
die	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
back	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
?	O
Who	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
Knife	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
Hornsby	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Light	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
by	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Hornsby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
robbed	O
this	O
Woman	O
;	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Coach	O
Way	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Foot	O
Path	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Knife	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
Six-pence	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
Hornsby	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Gardiner	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Neat-house	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Hornsby	O
.	O
A	O
Pipe-maker	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
33.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bottom	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Edgington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Iron	O
Pins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
,	I-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
and	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Den	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Short	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
3	O
Iron	O
Pins	O
and	O
Chains	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Drays	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
lost	O
16	O
within	O
these	O
3	O
Weeks	O
.	O
William	O
Hill	O
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
beating	O
the	O
Hour	O
in	O
Booth-street	O
,	O
(	O
facing	O
Princes-street	O
)	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
clinking	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
(	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
Moon-light	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
seemingly	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
made	O
towards	O
him	O
he	O
brushed	O
off	O
;	O
this	O
must	O
be	O
some	O
Rogue	O
,	O
thought	O
I	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
ten	O
to	O
one	O
if	O
I	O
catch	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
made	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Hour	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
Rounds	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
hid	O
my	O
Lanthorn	O
under	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
out	O
of	O
Sight	O
.	O
Presently	O
my	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
I	O
pops	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Tho	O
'	O
you	O
're	O
the	O
Devil	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
who	O
you	O
be	O
.	O
Why	O
so	O
you	O
may	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
be	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Title	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
)	O
What	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
,	O
Tom	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
you	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
carry	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
Officer	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
made	O
you	O
shun	O
me	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
play	O
the	O
Pool	O
with	O
that	O
Woman	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
standing	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
hard	O
by	O
.	O
Now	O
I	O
always	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Rule	O
,	O
that	O
wherever	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
Mischief	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
3	O
Dray-pins	O
with	O
the	O
Chains	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
telling	O
this	O
long	O
Story	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
Of	O
one	O
Tom	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
from	O
a	O
Boy	O
;	O
here	O
he	O
stands	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
off	O
some	O
Pins	O
?	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Trueman	O
's	O
Brew-house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ring	O
'd	O
[	O
wrung	O
]	O
off	O
4	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Smith	O
in	O
Gravel-Lane	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
we	O
took	O
3	O
more	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
26th	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
stopt	O
me	O
with	O
them	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
stood	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
but	O
Robinson	O
and	O
that	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Trade	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
Robinson	O
?	O
R.	O
A	O
Weaver	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
work	O
'd	O
12	O
Years	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Coker	O
at	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
Business	O
does	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
?	O
R.	O
He	O
drives	O
Beasts	O
and	O
does	O
labouring	O
Work	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Nagshead-Alley	O
in	O
Winfred-street	O
,	O
Spittle-Fields	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
3	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
dark	O
or	O
light	O
Night	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
R.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
swears	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
for	O
whenever	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
wring	O
Pins	O
,	O
we	O
always	O
got	O
'em	O
and	O
sold	O
'em	O
long	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
him	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
right	O
Thigh	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
36.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Philip	B-pers
Honeywood	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Steel	O
Chain	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
and	O
a	O
Bath-metal	O
Seal	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Belfound	O
,	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
Randal	O
Parry	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
Master	O
General	O
Honeywood	B-pers
was	O
riding	O
in	O
his	O
Chariot	O
over	O
Hounslow-Heath	B-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Servants	O
were	O
attending	O
him	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
riding	O
towards	O
us	O
with	O
their	O
Faces	O
muffled	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Capes	O
of	O
their	O
Great	O
Coats	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
turn	O
'd	O
short	O
on	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
Michael	O
,	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
(	O
or	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
!	O
dismount	O
!	O
Michael	O
was	O
then	O
next	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
forward	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
draw	O
my	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Holster	O
.	O
I	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Postilion	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Off-side	O
of	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Pistol	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Holster	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Highway-man	O
rode	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
.	O
Do	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
shoot	O
.	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
fire	O
.	O
Fire	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ye	O
will	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
are	O
those	O
the	O
Men	O
?	O
Parry	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
positive	O
that	O
Bye	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
rode	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
so	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
dismounted	O
Michael	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
.	O
Now	O
as	O
Bye	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
presenting	O
our	O
Pistols	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
,	O
Shoot	O
,	O
and	O
Fire	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
somebody	O
,	O
step	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chariot	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Bye	O
withdrew	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
advancing	O
again	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
Bye	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
your	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
deliver	O
this	O
Minute	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
fire	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
mind	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Michael	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
ye	O
take	O
your	O
Horse	O
and	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
But	O
Michael	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
.	O
Says	O
Bye	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
12	O
Slugs	O
in	O
this	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
deliver	O
this	O
Minute	O
I	O
'll	O
fire	O
thro	O
'	O
your	O
Body	O
.	O
Still	O
my	O
Master	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
regard	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Michael	O
again	O
;	O
Michael	O
answer	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
Bye	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
my	O
Master	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Michael	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
Bye	O
was	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
Patience	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Body	O
should	O
suffer	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
Moment	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
directly	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
my	O
Master	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
hither	O
Parry	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
to	O
Bye	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
my	O
Master	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
illprobus	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
bring	O
them	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
immediately	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
then	O
my	O
Master	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Shelar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
Bye	O
rode	O
after	O
Parry	O
with	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
;	O
one	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Shoot	O
;	O
and	O
t'other	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Shoot	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
General	O
thinking	O
Parry	O
had	O
affronted	O
somebody	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
and	O
so	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
Bye	O
demanded	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
General	O
gave	O
it	O
Parry	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
to	O
Bye	O
,	O
but	O
Bye	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
General	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Bye	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Fellow-Servant	O
Parry	B-pers
;	O
and	O
Tims	O
stopt	O
Michael	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
Tims	O
?	O
Stanton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
Man	O
was	O
every	O
way	O
comportionable	O
with	O
Tims	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Cape	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Stanton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
he	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Stanton	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
Wall	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
there	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Distance	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Face	O
was	O
muffled	O
?	O
Stanton	O
.	O
I	O
actually	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
Michael	O
dismount	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
rusty	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
Bye	O
rode	O
by	O
the	O
Chariot	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
after	O
Parry	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
damn	O
ye	O
,	O
stand	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
.	O
Parry	O
turn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Postilion-Horse	O
,	O
but	O
rode	O
beyond	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
Off-side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Parry	O
drew	O
his	O
Pistol	O
.	O
The	O
General	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Bye	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
Tims	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
Part	O
of	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Stanton	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
beyond	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
Belfound	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Horses	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
ride	O
?	O
Stanton	O
.	O
Bye	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
brown	O
Mare	O
with	O
a	O
bay	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cut	O
Tail	O
;	O
and	O
Tims	O
had	O
a	O
bay	O
Gelding	O
with	O
a	O
swish	O
Tail	O
.	O
Tims	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Highwaymen	O
follow	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
or	O
meet	O
it	O
?	O
Stanton	O
.	O
They	O
follow	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
Egham	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
in	O
their	O
Talk	O
,	O
Tims	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
better	O
Nag	O
rid	O
than	O
his	O
was	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
Corns	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
says	O
Bye	O
,	O
my	O
little	O
Mare	O
is	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
match	O
him	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
70	O
l.	O
lately	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
100	O
l.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Horses	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
Egham	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
12	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
General	O
's	O
Chariot	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
and	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
One	O
,	O
or	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
riding	O
through	O
Hounslow	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
drive	O
;	O
my	O
having	O
heard	O
them	O
talk	O
about	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
more	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Tims	O
's	O
was	O
a	O
bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
swish	O
Tail	O
,	O
and	O
Bye	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
Brown	B-pers
Mare	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bay	O
or	O
Meally	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
cut	O
Tail	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
run	O
so	O
fast	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hinge	I-pers
.	O
Hinge	O
is	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
spell	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
read	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
's	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
a	O
Hinge	O
of	O
a	O
Door	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
Tims	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Egham	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
shaved	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
Bye	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Tom	O
!	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
see	O
I	O
'm	O
a	O
Shaving	O
?	O
says	O
Tims	O
;	O
Damn	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
Bye	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shave	O
some	O
Body	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
led	O
their	O
Horses	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
with	O
a	O
swish-Tail	O
,	O
and	O
t'other	O
a	O
brown	O
Mare	O
with	O
a	O
cut	O
Tail	O
.	O
Bye	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
'd	O
shave	O
some	O
Body	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
shav	O
'd	O
some	O
where	O
else	O
.	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
When	O
Bye	O
was	O
first	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Tims	O
could	O
tell	O
.	O
When	O
Tims	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Tims	O
the	O
same	O
Question	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Gelding	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
rode	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Bye	O
bought	O
the	O
Gelding	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Whatever	O
Tims	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Bye	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Defence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Publican	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Oakingham	O
,	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
,	O
Bye	O
is	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Rum	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Customer	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Horse	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
Chapman	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
deals	O
largely	O
in	O
our	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
fair	O
Dealer	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
Horse	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Wilmot	O
.	O
A	O
brownish	O
founder	O
'd	O
Gelding	O
with	O
a	O
swishy	O
Tail	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Egham	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
betwixt	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
at	O
Egham	O
.	O
They	O
eat	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
11	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
your	O
House	O
from	O
the	O
Powder	O
Mills	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
Miles	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
near	O
12	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stopt	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
Stains-Bridge	O
,	O
in	O
Egham	O
Parish	O
;	O
the	O
People	O
soon	O
after	O
came	O
from	O
Church	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
3	O
Miles	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
Belfound	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Miles	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
to	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
.	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Stains-Bridge	O
.	O
At	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
11	O
,	O
or	O
before	O
12	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
or	O
better	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
One	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
on	O
the	O
Clock	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
guess	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
by	O
the	O
Taunton	O
Coach	O
being	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bye	O
has	O
been	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Times	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
offer	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Rum	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
your	O
House	O
from	O
Gilbert	O
's	O
and	O
Sylvester	O
's	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
Mile	O
nearer	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
than	O
Gilbert	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Doors	O
from	O
Sylvester	O
's	O
,	O
nearer	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
.	O
My	O
Ostler	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stop	O
at	O
Sylvester	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
Tims	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
us	O
have	O
any	O
Arms	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stop	O
and	O
drink	O
at	O
Sylvester	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
3	O
Quarters	O
past	O
11	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
stay	O
'd	O
about	O
2	O
Hours	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Your	O
Mistress	O
swears	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
Knight	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
1	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Clock	O
.	O
Tims	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Arms	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
?	O
Knight	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
.	O
They	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
their	O
Great	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
danced	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Weekly	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
3	O
Quarters	O
past	O
2	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
the	O
Publick	O
Gateway	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Horses	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Gateway	O
too	O
.	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
neither	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
stay	O
'd	O
near	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Our	O
House	O
is	O
a	O
Mile	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dibby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
waited	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Lane	O
's	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
the	O
Taunton	O
Coach	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
what	O
Horses	O
they	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Bye	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Winchester	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
then	O
.	O
Eusebins	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
General	O
Honeywood	B-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lady	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
go	O
through	O
Stains	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Berlin	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
towards	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Church	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
twelve	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
[	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
]	O
4	O
Miles	O
distant	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
.	O
I	O
dined	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Taunton	O
Coach	O
was	O
then	O
there	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
General	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Berlin-Chariot	O
,	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
Stains	O
,	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
past	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
dined	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
to	O
Egham	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Taunton	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
Door	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sherburn	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Rachel	O
came	O
from	O
Brentford	O
Market	O
,	O
the	O
General	O
's	O
Coach	O
past	O
us	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
or	O
less	O
from	O
Belfound	O
,	O
these	O
two	O
Highwaymen	O
came	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
looking	O
behind	O
them	O
they	O
stopt	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
a	O
foot-pace	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Belfound	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
live	O
,	O
the	O
Parish	O
Clock	O
struck	O
12	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
Clock	O
went	O
right	O
?	O
Sherburn	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
went	O
very	O
right	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
Clocks	O
.	O
We	O
past	O
by	O
the	O
Coach	O
while	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
robbing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
rode	O
off	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
Tims	O
.	O
Are	O
we	O
the	O
two	O
Persons	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
?	O
Sherburn	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Men	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
View	O
of	O
them	O
twice	O
;	O
the	O
Capes	O
of	O
their	O
Coats	O
were	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
those	O
Men	O
were	O
taller	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Sherburn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
General	O
's	O
Coach	O
went	O
by	O
us	O
on	O
t'other	O
side	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
,	O
we	O
past	O
it	O
twice	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
went	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
brush	O
'd	O
my	O
Hamper	O
;	O
they	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Belfound	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
said	O
she	O
heard	O
it	O
strike	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
said	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
The	O
Men	O
came	O
from	O
London	O
Road	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
Way	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taller	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
or	O
anexst	O
the	O
same	O
Size	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Tannton	O
Coachman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Stains-Bridge	O
with	O
my	O
Coach	O
when	O
Bye	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
Bye	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
it	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
put	O
off	O
some	O
Brandy	O
or	O
Rum	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
One	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
left	O
'em	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Garner	I-pers
,	O
Exeter	O
Coachman	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Eleven	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
Eleven	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
with	O
the	O
Tannton	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
One	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Importer	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Bye	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
traded	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
deals	O
in	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Rum	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
him	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Wildstreet	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Business	O
will	O
maintain	O
him	O
handsomely	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
no	O
more	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
Import	O
Rum	O
and	O
Brandy	O
;	O
Bye	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
fair	O
Dealer	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
good	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
commonly	O
paid	O
me	O
ready	O
Money	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Foxcroft	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
3	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Wild-Court	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Room	O
for	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
Robberies	O
.	O
His	O
Horse	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
indifferent	O
scrubbed	O
Beast	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
3	O
Years	O
for	O
Rum	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
him	O
several	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
buy	O
one	O
above	O
50	O
Shillings	O
or	O
3	O
Pounds	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
most	O
4	O
Pounds	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
's	O
no	O
more	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
than	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
such	O
an	O
Opinion	O
of	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
100	O
l.	O
on	O
his	O
bare	O
Word	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
've	O
known	O
him	O
3	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
rents	O
his	O
House	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
pays	O
22	O
l	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Foxcroft	O
is	O
the	O
Ground	O
Landlord	O
.	O
Bye	O
's	O
Mare	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
scrubbed	O
Mare	O
not	O
13	O
Hands	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
no	O
Means	O
fit	O
for	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
last	O
Man	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
Bye	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
3	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
hired	O
Horses	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
as	O
fair	O
a	O
Character	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Bye	O
is	O
my	O
Landlord	O
;	O
I	O
rent	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
undertake	O
Funerals	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
thought	O
him	O
honest	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
trusted	O
my	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
that	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
on	O
such	O
an	O
Errand	O
would	O
rob	O
my	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Staton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Street	O
as	O
Bye	O
lives	O
in	O
5	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Rum	O
,	O
and	O
hired	O
Horses	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
keep	O
a	O
good	O
Horse	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Distiller	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
300	O
l.	O
of	O
Bye	O
in	O
3	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
Bye	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
13	O
Hands	O
and	O
an	O
Inch	O
high	O
,	O
a	O
dark	O
Bay	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brownish	O
Muzzel	O
,	O
a	O
bob	O
Tail	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Malander	O
on	O
the	O
Off-Foot	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
jump	O
over	O
a	O
Straw	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
her	O
for	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
2	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
poor	O
Man	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Senses	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
needs	O
no	O
more	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Shelvokt	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Tims	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
Governor	O
Feak	O
's	O
in	O
Bedford-Row	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
creditable	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Services	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
a	O
Butler	O
has	O
been	O
trusted	O
with	O
Plate	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
in	O
Devonshire-Square	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Rich	O
.	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
6	O
Months	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
2	O
Bay	O
Geldings	O
to	O
let	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
.	O
My	O
Horse	O
stands	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Stables	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bonham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
16	O
or	O
17	O
Years	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
Gentleman	O
he	O
served	O
was	O
Governor	O
Feak	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
come	O
from	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
4	O
Months	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
great	O
Charge	O
of	O
Plate	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Grocer	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Bedford-Row	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
several	O
times	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Service	O
.	O
John	O
Row	O
.	O
I	O
've	O
known	O
Tims	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ratcliff	O
in	O
Devonshire-Square	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
.	O
When	O
Tims	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Stables	O
to	O
let	O
out	O
Horses	O
.	O
Tims	O
.	O
When	O
Bye	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
Governor	O
Feak	O
's	O
Son	O
in	O
Court	O
-	O
if	O
he	O
pleases	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Feak	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
excus	O
'd	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Call	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servants	O
again	O
.	O
Officer	O
.	O
Here	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
be	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
Day	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
Parry	O
.	O
I	O
guess	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
12	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
past	O
.	O
Shelar	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
.	O
Stanton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
12	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
have	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
from	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
10	O
to	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
One	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
38	O
,	O
39.	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Curd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Greener	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
2	O
Girdles	O
,	O
3	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Mantle	O
,	O
24	O
Clouts	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
December	O
24	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Greener	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Currier	O
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
near	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
I	O
moved	O
from	O
that	O
Room	O
to	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
John	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
to	O
help	O
me	O
;	O
his	O
Mother	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
mine	O
.	O
My	O
Goods	O
were	O
all	O
safe	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Goods	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
A	O
Hair	O
Portmanteau-Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
2	O
Girdles	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
3	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Mantle	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
odd	O
Things	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
Husband	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
Name	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
John	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
this	O
Ring	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
gave	O
me	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
remove	O
her	O
Goods	O
from	O
one	O
Apartment	O
to	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Curd	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Coat	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
sain	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Who	O
lies	O
in	O
this	O
Room	O
to	O
Night	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
No-body	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
'twill	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Chance	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
take	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
For	O
any	O
thing	O
we	O
can	O
steal	O
we	O
call	O
a	O
Chance	O
-	O
)	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
too	O
near	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
we	O
met	O
again	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
we	O
use	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
again	O
about	O
this	O
Chance	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
persuaded	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
conveniently	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
not	O
enough	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
one	O
another	O
's	O
Shoulders	O
and	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
in	O
a	O
fresh	O
Hand	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
towards	O
Covent-Garden	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
West	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
us	O
from	O
New-street	O
to	O
Cecil-Court	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
We	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
too	O
early	O
to	O
do	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Curd	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
only	O
play	O
'd	O
the	O
Fool	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
a	O
Roguish	O
Design	O
to	O
betray	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
consented	O
.	O
West	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
lower	O
Shutters	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
one	O
Foot	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
upon	O
Curd	O
's	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Hook	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
above	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
I	O
broke	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Casement	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
ty	O
'd	O
my	O
Garter	O
to	O
the	O
Handle	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
round	O
hairy	O
Portmanteau-Trunk	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Sheet	O
and	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
.	O
In	O
less	O
than	O
an	O
Hour	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
whistled	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Bundle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
Curd	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
stand	O
under	O
it	O
because	O
his	O
Head	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
West	O
going	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ty	O
'd	O
a	O
Curtain	O
to	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
a	O
Walnut-tree	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
let	O
my	O
self	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Curtain	O
flying	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
I	O
bethought	O
myself	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
Hat	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
fearing	O
that	O
might	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
we	O
planted	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Curtain	O
,	O
found	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
same	O
Way	O
.	O
We	O
preserv	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Gin-shop	O
together	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
crying	O
,	O
Old	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
Sheet	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
Yes	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
,	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
:	O
Then	O
we	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bought	O
'em	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
for	O
50	O
s.	O
We	O
divided	O
15	O
s.	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
a	O
Crown	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
run	O
up	O
at	O
a	O
Gift-shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
West	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
same	O
Story	O
over-again	O
?	O
Smithson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
understood	O
that	O
the	O
Account	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
is	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
Invention	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
him	O
,	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
put	O
to	O
repeat	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
not	O
deny	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
consider	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Request	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
gives	O
a	O
different	O
Account	O
it	O
may	O
do	O
you	O
Service	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
repeats	O
all	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
without	O
Variation	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
strengthen	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
repeat	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
Smithson	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
Curd	O
wrong	O
'd	O
any	O
Body	O
;	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
'Prentice	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
Curd	O
is	O
my	O
Brother-in-law	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Butcher	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
Sea	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
Jobbs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
Errands	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
since	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
some	O
Way	O
astray	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
how	O
he	O
spent	O
his	O
Time	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
innocently	O
drawn	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nind	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nind	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
6	O
Cheeses	O
and	O
a	O
Bladder	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
my	O
Shop	O
Window	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Rathbourn	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Newport-Market	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Boys	O
at	O
Nind	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
past	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
they	O
came	O
along	O
,	O
each	O
with	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Curd	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Nind	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
Boys	O
went	O
;	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Curd	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Hays's-Court	O
.	O
Curd	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
Curd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
these	O
Cheeses	O
off	O
the	O
Shop-Board	O
in	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
we	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
40	O
William	B-pers
Allbriton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Devally	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41	O
Edward	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Sacks	O
and	O
12	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Barley	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42.	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43	O
,	O
44.	O
James	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sarcenet	O
Lining	O
of	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Chaffin	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Goodred	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sarcenet	O
Lining	O
of	O
a	O
Gown	O
to	O
dye	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Anne	B-pers
Chasins	I-pers
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
a	O
Sash	O
before	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
betwixt	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Wells	O
's	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
)	O
Shop	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
opposite	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wells	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Three	O
Kings	O
Entry	O
which	O
is	O
close	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
suspect	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Rogues	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
by	O
Mischance	O
.	O
But	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
,	O
Walter	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
broken	O
Pane	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sarcenet	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
:	O
Then	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
out	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
Walter	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
Hastings	O
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
white	O
Stockings	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
Walter	O
with	O
the	O
Sarcenet	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
Walter	O
came	O
up	O
toward	O
where	O
I	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Wells	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Silk	O
.	O
Another	O
pursued	O
Hastings	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
Hastings	O
threw	O
something	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
Window	O
;	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
white	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Pair	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Walter	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Bar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Goodred	O
's	O
Window	O
.	O
Walter	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
wrap	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
towards	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
on	O
Walter	O
.	O
Job	O
Hanks	O
.	O
Hastings	O
's	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Pains-taking	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
his	O
Mother	O
too	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burkitt	I-pers
.	O
His	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
towardly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
Mary	B-pers
Golby	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Golborn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
22	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
and	O
Linen	O
Check	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Heashfield	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
46.	O
Ann	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Strainer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
47.	O
Ann	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
six	O
Gross	O
of	O
Bath-metal-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sigerson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
49.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
50.	O
Mary	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Jane	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ordway	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
But	O
Jane	B-pers
Ordway	I-pers
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
51	O
,	O
52.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Budley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Hands	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Atterbury	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linsey	O
Woolsey	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
upper	O
Side	O
of	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Leonard	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
?	O
Hand	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
a	O
Lamp	O
that	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
my	O
Coat	O
with	O
his	O
Left-Hand	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Right	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
with	O
my	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taller	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
the	O
better	O
observe	O
his	O
Face	O
by	O
the	O
Lamp	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
aloud	O
,	O
Take	O
away	O
your	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
punching	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Pistol	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
had	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
(	O
who	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
other	O
Person	O
)	O
to	O
search	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
4	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Sixpences	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
'll	O
leave	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
any	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
bring	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
Butler	O
bid	O
me	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
a	O
Ball	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Breeches	O
were	O
cut	O
all	O
down	O
the	O
Side	O
;	O
I	O
gather	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Duke-street	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
'em	O
.	O
Amos	B-pers
Foss	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
complained	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Shillings	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
and	O
2	O
short	O
ones	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
cut	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Essex	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
near	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Duke's-Street	O
.	O
Butler	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
4	O
Shillings	O
and	O
2	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
cut	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
do	O
?	O
Essex	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Guard	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
?	O
Essex	O
.	O
I	O
surrender	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Justice	O
Mercer	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Essex	O
.	O
Ever	O
since	O
last	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Fair	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
you	O
kept	O
Company	O
together	O
?	O
Essex	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb	O
and	O
Horse-Shoe	O
,	O
in	O
George-Alley	O
,	O
which	O
goes	O
from	O
Shoe-Lane	O
to	O
the	O
Ditch-Side	O
.	O
The	O
City-Marshal	O
often	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
us	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
us	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
Carman	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
several	O
Times	O
seen	O
Essex	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
Doings	O
.	O
-	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
The	O
Lamb	O
and	O
Horse-Shoe	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
notorious	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
every	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
City-Marshal	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Butler	O
there	O
with	O
Essex	O
.	O
-	O
Jarvis	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Butler	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
3	O
Years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Currier	O
by	O
Trade	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
this	O
last	O
Year	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
within	O
these	O
3	O
Months	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
should	O
swear	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
;	O
what	O
you	O
heard	O
from	O
another	O
is	O
no	O
Evidence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
Butler	O
before	O
this	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
these	O
6	O
Months	O
past	O
.	O
Harris	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Cock-Founder	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
serve	O
his	O
Time	O
out	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
5	O
Years	O
with	O
a	O
Gunsmith	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
this	O
half	O
Year	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
53	O
,	O
54.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bag	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Harry	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
19	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
55.	O
William	B-pers
Stakepool	I-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Canister	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
and	O
56	O
Mary	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Mother	O
)	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Tea	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
57.	O
William	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
(	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
Richard	O
Hull	O
.	O
About	O
One	O
a-clock	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
behind	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
Sword	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
that	O
was	O
afterwards	O
publish	O
'd	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Jo	O
.	O
Lambert	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
published	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
Thief-Taker	O
by	O
Profession	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
Information	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
his	O
Endeavour	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
fired	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
me	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Powers	O
,	O
who	O
knows	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Powers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ackers	O
(	O
Dacres	O
)	O
who	O
keeps	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
over-against	O
the	O
King's-Bench	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
Dacres	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
my	O
Lodgers	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
58.	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
(	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Silk	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
work	O
'd	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
Linen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
