TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
1733	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BILLERS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1733	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXIII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
Sessions-Papers	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BILLERS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Jesson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
Stafford	B-pers
Briscoe	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rutty	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fidoe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Trueby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Elliot	B-pers
Percher	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Coleson	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Snee	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ackers	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Belline	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linen	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Nov.	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
William	B-pers
Crank	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Two-Quart	O
Pewter-Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Smith	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Prick	I-pers
.	O
About	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Walbrook	B-place
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Penn'orth	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
set	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
which	O
making	O
me	O
suspicious	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
'till	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
him	O
have	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
hua	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
consider	O
his	O
Grey-Hairs	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
Money	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
John	B-pers
Kempson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
of	O
Starch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Bridon	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Ann	B-pers
Trimlet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6	O
,	O
7.	O
John	B-pers
Shanks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Shanks	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
three	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
twelve	O
Napkins	O
,	O
seven	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
fourteen	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
six	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Dorothy	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
John	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ben	B-pers
.	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
26	O
.	O
Ben	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
About	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Compasses	I-place
against	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
three	O
Pints	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
by	O
ourselves	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hid	O
my	O
Watch	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
had	O
empty	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
Pint	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
W	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hazledine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
thither	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Clothes	O
,	O
we	O
concluded	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
private	O
Place	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
String	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
Place	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
easy	O
to	O
guess	O
at	O
without	O
naming	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
such	O
things	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
by	O
other	O
Gentlewomen	O
on	O
the	O
like	O
Occasion	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refusing	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hazledine	O
,	O
the	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
himself	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
any	O
such	O
sobb	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
undertook	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
assisted	O
in	O
holding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Close-Clipboard	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
King	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
superficial	O
Examination	O
would	O
signify	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
we	O
expected	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
search	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
Backside	O
to	O
her	O
Feet	O
while	O
they	O
made	O
the	O
Search	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
care	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
they	O
proceeded	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
venture	O
to	O
look	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
wip	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
had	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
wicked	O
Husband	O
that	O
had	O
abused	O
me	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
leave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
o	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Man	O
te	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
never	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
bare	O
two	O
Children	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
now	O
big	O
with	O
another	O
.	O
Will.	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Forever	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
overpersuaded	O
me	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
his	O
Will	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
stumbled	O
and	O
strumbled	O
,	O
and	O
trowd	O
me	O
about	O
till	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Matter	O
as	O
early	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
William	B-pers
Cammell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Robotham	I-pers
,	O
October	O
26	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robotham	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
in	O
a	O
Crowd	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Exchange	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
stood	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Pi	O
lory	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Irish	I-pers
As	O
I	O
stood	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
a	O
Pick-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
Water	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
leather	O
String	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
Somebody	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
pick	O
a	O
Pocket	O
!	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
and	O
presently	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Watch	O
stily	O
and	O
bove	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
String	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Catch	I-pers
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
's	O
see	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
Executioner	O
.	O
Faulkner	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
for	O
uttering	O
bad	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
attended	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
Gardner	O
and	O
I	O
stoop	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Gardner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Harper	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
his	O
Hand	O
might	O
be	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
But	O
he	O
never	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
any	O
manner	O
whatsomever	O
.	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Makepeace	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Gardner	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hold	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
Jack	B-pers
Catch	I-pers
presently	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
String	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
'Change-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Haberdasher	O
's	O
Shop	O
(	O
behind	O
a	O
carv	O
'd	O
blue	O
coat	O
Boy	O
that	O
stands	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
)	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Makepeace	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
a	O
Pick-pocket	O
;	O
Harper	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
held	O
up	O
a	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
has	O
lost	O
a	O
Watch	O
?	O
And	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Constable	O
!	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Hooper	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10	O
,	O
11.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lancake	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Pline	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
held	O
here	O
in	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
*	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Wigs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
,	O
June	O
17.	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Limcake	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
said	O
four	O
Hats	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Pline	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
said	O
two	O
Wigs	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Abraham	O
Gibson	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
VII	O
.	O
p.	O
184.	O
Susan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lankey	O
[	O
Lancake	O
's	O
]	O
Shop	O
in	O
Chick-lane	B-place
.	O
He	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Molly	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
For	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
Molly	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
my	O
Name	O
is	O
Sue	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
with	O
me	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
How	O
much	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
7	O
s.	O
He	O
laugh	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
meant	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Then	O
he	O
felt	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
measur	O
'd	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
more	O
at	O
the	O
George	B-pers
Alehouse	I-pers
in	O
Chick	O
lane	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
fetch	O
'em	O
directly	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
one	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
on	O
my	O
Head	O
;	O
he	O
blam	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
bringing	O
them	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
gaping	O
open	O
manner	O
;	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
broad	O
Brims	O
and	O
old-fashion	O
'd	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
new	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
these	O
were	O
little	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
wearing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
one	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
was	O
14	O
s.	O
he	O
laugh	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
meant	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
then	O
bid	O
me	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
came	O
to	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
more	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
Will	O
Newell	O
(	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
)	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
Lankey	O
,	O
who	O
paid	O
me	O
8	O
s	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
them	O
behind	O
his	O
Counter	O
.	O
Lancake	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Moon	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
Girl	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
's	O
hir	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
swear	O
this	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
seen	O
Sue	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
at	O
Lancake	O
's	O
Shop	O
a	O
selling	O
Hats	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
kept	O
ill	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
warn	O
'd	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
not	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
Hats	O
which	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
cost	O
me	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
16	O
s.	O
a-piece	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Easter	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
them	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
following	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
was	O
convicted	O
here	O
in	O
last	O
September	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
them	O
and	O
two	O
Wigs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Sue	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Newell	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
Newell	O
here	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
without	O
his	O
Evidence	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
see	O
how	O
you	O
will	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Hats	O
bought	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lancake	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Abraham	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Lancake	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
buy	O
the	O
Hats	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
his	O
Market	O
.	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Hat	O
he	O
wore	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
7	O
Hours	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
Bail	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
Lancake	O
's	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Dealers	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Way	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
cautious	O
in	O
buying	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
frequently	O
seen	O
him	O
strict	O
examine	O
People	O
that	O
brought	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
given	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Pline	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
12.	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
48	O
iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tomes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
October	O
19	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Tomes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
near	O
Cavendish-Square	B-place
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
several	O
large	O
Iron-bound	O
Casks	O
,	O
new	O
painted	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Distiller	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Casks	O
stripp	O
'd	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Hoops	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smithers	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
Oct.	O
13.	O
the	O
Watchman	O
knock	O
'd	O
my	O
Mistress	O
Tomes	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
Lock	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Staple	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Casks	O
lying	O
at	O
Rack	O
and	O
Manger	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Hoops	O
knock	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
of	O
these	O
Hoops	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
Benj	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Lamb	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
a	O
Dozen	O
at	O
Gilbert	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Hoops	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
we	O
lost	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
are	O
painted	O
Green	O
,	O
have	O
no	O
Rivets	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
try	O
'd	O
'em	O
they	O
jump	O
'd	O
exactly	O
into	O
the	O
Places	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
try	O
them	O
well	O
enough	O
,	O
because	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Casks	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hoops	O
left	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
held	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
Gilbert	O
and	O
Harvey	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
Hoops	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
old	O
Hoops	O
that	O
came	O
off	O
some	O
Casks	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
a	O
Jobb	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
those	O
Hoops	O
of	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
was	O
,	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
.	O
14.	O
Mary	B-pers
Royley	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Judge	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Death	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
34	O
Yards	O
of	O
Check	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
November	O
17.	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
after	O
my	O
Daughter	O
Eleanor	O
Griffin	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Red-lion-square	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
presently	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Royley	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
.	O
Good	O
Woman	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
there	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
ha	O
n't	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
stepp	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowing	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
I	O
saw	O
Judge	O
on	O
the	O
Steps	O
,	O
and	O
Royley	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Counter-side	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
else	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
stood	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
Presently	O
Royley	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Atkinson	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Spher	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Check	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-hoop	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Judge	O
,	O
by	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
Theobald's-Row	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
100	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Royley	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Judge	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15	O
,	O
16	O
Henry	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jack-the-Hatter	B-pers
+	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Maxwell	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
19	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
November	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
that	O
Jack-the-Hatter	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
several	O
Felonies	O
in	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pray	O
'd	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
might	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
a-part	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Maxwell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
November	O
22	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Globe	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
;	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
Occasion	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
telling	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
do	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
I	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
received	O
some	O
Money	O
at	O
Stepney	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
safe	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
venture	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
with	O
it	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
26	O
l.	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
about	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
but	O
recollecting	O
that	O
I	O
still	O
had	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Moidores	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Side-pocket	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
Security	O
.	O
Coming	O
into	O
White-horse-lane	B-place
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
Baxter	O
,	O
pass	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
thick	O
short	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
Hand	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
me	O
put	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
Side-pocket	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Moidores	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Family-Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hop	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
keep	O
it	O
;	O
go	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
well	O
us	O
'd	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
another	O
Way	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Collingwood	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
them	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
came	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
Links	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
running	O
towards	O
us	O
;	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
says	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
Care	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Wits	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
wild	O
Bull	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
the	O
Devil	O
was	O
coming	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
loose	O
Fellows	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Collingwood	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
Robbery	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
Baxter	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
my	O
Master	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Collingwood	O
took	O
Care	O
of	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Stepney	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Fowl	O
upon	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Chickens	O
upon	O
t'other	O
.	O
We	O
provided	O
them	O
with	O
separate	O
Lodgings	O
for	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
and	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Macdonald	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
me	O
well	O
in	O
giving	O
me	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
hop	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Clerk	O
left	O
me	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Collingwood	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
stay	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Field	O
we	O
met	O
Baxter	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
running	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Wits	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
met	O
a	O
mad	O
Bull	O
;	O
we	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	O
at	O
Stepney	O
-	O
Baxter	O
confess	O
'd	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Collingwood	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
and	O
his	O
Clerk	O
,	O
two	O
Fellows	O
came	O
running	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
us	O
!	O
-	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
-	O
a	O
mad	O
Bull	O
!	O
-	O
the	O
Devil	O
!	O
-	O
has	O
frighted	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Wits	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Rogues	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
made	O
bold	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
.	O
We	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
taking	O
some	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
of	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Ressistance	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
me	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Family-Watch	O
,	O
and	O
hop	O
'd	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
again	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
well	O
used	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
round	O
by	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
3	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Field	O
again	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
frighted	O
by	O
a	O
mad	O
Bull	O
.	O
Rook	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Baxter	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
athurt	O
[	O
athwart	O
]	O
the	O
Path	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Baxter	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
Rook	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
It	O
appears	O
that	O
Macdonald	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
afterwards	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Rook	O
.	O
Baxter	O
.	O
What	O
Cloaths	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
we	O
had	O
on	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
red	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
short	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
Baxter	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
Rook	O
had	O
a	O
new	O
Coat	O
with	O
Buttons	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Baxter	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
we	O
meet	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
Baxter	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
Mary	O
Aldus	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
Gardens	O
near	O
the	O
Hog-house	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
Rook	O
.	O
Baxter	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
at	O
Low-Layton	O
,	O
from	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
'till	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
4	O
Miles	O
from	O
Stra'ford	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
Low-Layton	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
Aldus	O
's	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
.	O
Baxter	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
what	O
a	O
vile	O
Fellow	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
+	O
+	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
,	O
Will	O
.	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Fisherman	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Session-Paper	O
,	O
for	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
p.	O
124.	O
Mary	B-pers
Aldus	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Church-Lane	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
Baxter	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
then	O
sick	O
a-Bed	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
came	O
not	O
near	O
us	O
'till	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
for	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
too	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tindall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
Rook	O
last	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
Blue-Coat-Fields	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jack-the-Hatter	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
your	O
Name	O
Rook	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
Nor	O
Jack-the-Hatter	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
again	O
,	O
Pray	O
who	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
when	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	O
Rook	O
,	O
is	O
my	O
Son	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
from	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
'till	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
following	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
came	O
that	O
Day	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
by	O
what	O
Circumstance	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
?	O
Edward	O
Rook	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
constantly	O
at	O
home	O
from	O
Thursday	O
to	O
Monday	O
?	O
Edward	O
Rook	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
my	O
Labour	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
will	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
abroad	O
?	O
Edward	O
Rook	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Edward	O
Rook	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	O
Rook	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
Day	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
marry	O
'd	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
where	O
was	O
your	O
Husband	O
on	O
:	O
those	O
Nights	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
A-bed	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Company	O
a-Days	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
a-Nights	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
17.	O
Henry	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Sickwell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sick-Will	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Aldus	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Golden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Iron-Grates	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
an/	O
Iron-Jack	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Iron-Spits	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Faith	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spade	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Golden	I-pers
,	O
November	O
19	O
.	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Golden	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
these	O
Goods	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
9	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
Porter	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Bromley	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
lain	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
moving	O
to	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Grates	O
,	O
and	O
Spits	O
,	O
and	O
Jack	O
,	O
were	O
lent	O
me	O
y	O
my	O
Aunt	O
,	O
Faith	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Spade	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Damage	O
was	O
dn	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Cellar-Door	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
the	O
upper	O
Bolt	O
thrust	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bottn	O
Bolt	O
wrenched	O
off	O
.	O
Macdonald	O
being	O
taken	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
impeach	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
ay	O
is	O
Information	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Common-Sewer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Baxter	O
,	O
and	O
Sick	O
Will	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
this	O
House	O
uninhabited	O
,	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
some	O
Lead	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Grates	O
,	O
a	O
Jack	O
,	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Spits	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spade	O
,	O
we	O
contented	O
ourselves	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
more	O
than	O
we	O
could	O
carry	O
clear	O
off	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
we	O
planted	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
we	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Old-Gravel-Lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
The	O
High-Constable	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Betty	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
Sick	O
Will	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Church-Lane	O
,	O
whither	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
ly	O
Landlady	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Message	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
right	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
a	O
Dark-Lanthorn	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
Candles	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
Flint	O
,	O
Steel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
Tinder-box	O
full	O
of	O
Tinder	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Betty	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
Baxter	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
before	O
Justice	O
Priestly	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Macdonald	O
inform	O
'd	O
against	O
Sickwell	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
us	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
a-Bed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Sickwell	O
then	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
next	O
Day	O
being	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
this	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
read	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Then	O
Sickwell	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
taken	O
before	O
John	B-pers
Priestly	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Nov.	O
24.	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
He	O
therein	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
4	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Nat	O
.	O
Sparks	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Sanders	O
,	O
stole	O
two	O
Gowns	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
Baxter	O
,	O
Sanders	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
stole	O
some	O
Fowls	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
Oct.	O
15.	O
he	O
and	O
Baxter	O
stole	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Great-coat	O
in	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
Nov.	O
19.	O
about	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
Baxter	O
,	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
broke	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
by	O
Rogues-Well	O
,	O
near	O
Stepney	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Grates	O
,	O
a	O
Jack	O
,	O
2	O
Spits	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spade	O
.	O
Sick	O
Will	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
by	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
a-Bed	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Light-headed	O
when	O
I	O
made	O
that	O
Confession	O
-	O
Here	O
's	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Jurymen	O
knew	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
Bethnall-Green	O
.	O
Juryman	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Sick	O
Will	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
many	O
a	O
Joint	O
of	O
Meat	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Baxter	O
.	O
Macdonald	O
is	O
a	O
vile	O
Rogue	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Prison	O
but	O
four	O
Days	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
As	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
resident	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
this	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
Burglary	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Aldus	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Sick	I-pers
Will	I-pers
.	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Stepney	O
Parish	O
,	O
October	O
15	O
.	O
Christopher	O
Stacey	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Great-Coat	O
and	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Pork	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Justice	O
Priestly	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Aldus	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Aldus	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
light-headed	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Baxter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Aldus	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Aldus	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Alice	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
13	O
s.	O
Oct.	O
20	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
home	O
from	O
Leaden-Hall	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	B-place
,	O
forced	O
me	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
Thieves	O
!	O
and	O
Help	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
sake	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Thank	O
you	O
kindly	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
saved	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
wrapt	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Bosom	O
to	O
another	O
Paper	O
that	O
had	O
Tea-dust	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struggl	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Paper	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fright	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Mistake	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Paper	O
of	O
Tea-dust	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
sad	O
cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
Thieves	O
.	O
I	O
run	O
down	O
an	O
Alley	O
near	O
at	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Body	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
was	O
silent	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
;	O
but	O
turning	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
that	O
Alley	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Shrieking	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Sound	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
another	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Woman	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Arms	O
extended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
Hands	O
open	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
any	O
unseemly	O
Posture	O
,	O
I	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
sav	O
'd	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
her	O
Money	O
was	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
But	O
presently	O
finding	O
her	O
Mistake	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Paper	O
of	O
Tea-dust	O
!	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
then	O
be	O
in	O
vain	O
,	O
because	O
in	O
his	O
Way	O
thither	O
he	O
had	O
opportunity	O
enough	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
another	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
near	O
.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
Man	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
bar	O
barous	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
harm	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
a	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprize	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
We	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Court	O
(	O
before	O
the	O
Verdict	O
was	O
Recorded	O
)	O
inform	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Value	O
was	O
not	O
material	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
consider	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Woman	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
believed	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
were	O
doubtful	O
of	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
again	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
regard	O
the	O
Sum	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
to	O
Acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
19.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Seat	O
of	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Curtains	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
and	O
Giles	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
George	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mecham	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
James	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chileot	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
Oct.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Cullington	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Mendall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Sept.	O
17	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
four	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
Sept.	O
17.	O
William	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
Bow	B-place
and	O
Mile-End	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
capp	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
towards	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Pistols	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Great-coat	O
on	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Cape	O
button	O
'd	O
up	O
-	O
But	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Pistols	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Mounting	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rammers	O
being	O
broke	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
Cordel	O
Firebrass	O
's	O
Servants	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Felt	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
other	O
three	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
between	O
Sudbury	O
and	O
Melford	O
.	O
It	O
happen	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
dislocated	O
his	O
Neck	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
dismounted	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Neck	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
again	O
.	O
Some	O
Bullets	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
gave	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	O
Chapman	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
fir	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach-door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
immediately	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
half	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
his	O
Horse	O
curvetted	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
the	O
Pistol	O
had	O
frighted	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bury	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
those	O
five	O
Pistols	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
leave	O
them	O
there	O
for	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
24.	O
Mary	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
strangling	O
and	O
choaking	O
it	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
,	O
Midwife	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
something	O
(	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
)	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
with	O
that	O
which	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
signify	O
'd	O
nothing	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
a	O
Child	O
I	O
would	O
find	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Father	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Her	O
Father	O
coming	O
in	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Daughter	O
had	O
been	O
Deliver	O
'd	O
-	O
Deliver	O
'd	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Ay	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
has	O
-	O
of	O
a	O
Sir-Reverence	O
.	O
Those	O
were	O
his	O
Words	O
,	O
begging	O
your	O
Worship	O
's	O
Pardon	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
so	O
much	O
by	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
towards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Passages	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
short	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
Father	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Grandfather	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
her	O
himself	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
declar	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Father	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
any	O
other	O
Man	O
but	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
this	O
Note	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Curtain	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
among	O
some	O
Horse-litter	O
in	O
Tom	O
Turd's-Hole	O
(	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Nightmen	O
lay	O
their	O
Soil	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
bled	O
to	O
death	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
proper	O
Help	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
a	O
Male	O
Infant	O
(	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
born	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
)	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
Opinion	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
Still-born	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
external	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
proceeded	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Cavities	O
of	O
the	O
Thorax	O
and	O
Abdomen	O
.	O
The	O
Lungs	O
appear	O
'd	O
inflated	O
;	O
I	O
cut	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Lobes	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Vessel	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
it	O
floated	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
therefore	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
the	O
Infant	O
had	O
breathed	O
;	O
I	O
likewise	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Blood-vessels	O
in	O
general	O
were	O
empty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Navel-string	O
lacerated	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
ty	O
'd	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
Reason	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
proper	O
Help	O
was	O
wanting	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
might	O
bleed	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
her	O
Father	O
is	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
Washing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
always	O
behaved	O
herself	O
prettily	O
and	O
modestly	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
poor	O
Creature	O
,	O
she	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
call	O
for	O
Help	O
?	O
M	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
weak	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
under	O
any	O
Surprize	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Labour	O
came	O
so	O
suddenly	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
Time	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
Assistance	O
?	O
M.	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
those	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
proper	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Waistcot	O
Box	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
it	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
Father	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
from	O
her	O
-	O
poor	O
young	O
Creature	O
-	O
she	O
's	O
hardly	O
Sixteen	O
-	O
her	O
wicked	O
Father	O
has	O
ruin	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tindall	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
with	O
Directions	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
among	O
some	O
Sraw	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Hog-house	O
in	O
Tom	O
T	O
-	O
d's-fields	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Linsey-Woolsey	O
Curtain	O
-	O
Her	O
Father	O
is	O
in	O
Reading	O
Goal	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
good-natur	O
'd	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
,	O
modest	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
extreamly	O
startled	O
at	O
the	O
News	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
-	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
for	O
deluding	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
indeed	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
her	O
Father	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
more	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
on	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
bleed	O
to	O
death	O
thro	O
'	O
her	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
want	O
of	O
proper	O
Help	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Whitchurch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
sober	O
Girl	O
before	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Child	O
might	O
die	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Help	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
25	O
,	O
26.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stick-in-the-Mud	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Boot	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
October	O
16.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	B-place
;	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
was	O
lifted	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Boot	O
taken	O
away	O
-	O
I	O
afterwards	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
informing	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Baker	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
Shoes	O
you	O
lost	O
squaretoed	O
or	O
round-toed	O
?	O
Rayner	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
odd	O
Shoes	O
and	O
the	O
Boot	O
were	O
square-toed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
round	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
a	O
Brandy-	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Pall-M	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
St.	O
James's-Square	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
Baker	O
shov	O
'd	O
the	O
Sash	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
Anderson	O
shov	O
'd	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
higher	O
;	O
we	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
quick	O
Return	O
,	O
I	O
shov	O
'd	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
Turns	O
till	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
quite	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
roundtoed	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
square-toed	O
Boot	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
odd	O
Shoes	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
square	O
Toes	O
and	O
one	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
'em	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
stood	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Doors	O
off	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
we	O
shar	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
odd	O
ones	O
and	O
the	O
Boot	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Tyburn-Road	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
drank	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Cherry	O
Brandy	O
and	O
parted	O
.	O
Not	O
long	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
grew	O
wary	O
of	O
keeping	O
ill	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
clear	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
voluntarily	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
information	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Baker	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
transported	O
.	O
Wild	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
was	O
transported	O
*	O
about	O
twelve	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
my	O
Time	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Sea	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
honestly	O
till	O
lately	O
I	O
fell	O
again	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
.	O
*	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
in	O
April	O
1721	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Gascoyn	I-pers
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Ann	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
Wild	O
was	O
transported	O
for	O
was	O
committed	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
this	O
.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
come	O
acquainted	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Wild	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Months	O
ago	O
;	O
you	O
were	O
talking	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
Will	O
.	O
Isaacson	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
transported	O
in	O
a	O
Maryland	O
Ship	O
that	O
I	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
my	O
Time	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Time	O
I	O
met	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
you	O
again	O
with	O
Frank	B-pers
Ogliby	I-pers
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
[	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ryner	I-pers
's	O
]	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
I	O
did	O
in	O
your	O
Company	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Anderson	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
-	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
then	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wakins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
Lad	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
.	O
Daniel	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
's	O
above	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
27.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stick-in-the-Mud	B-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
with	O
Francis	B-pers
Ogleby	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
Stand	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
October	O
4	O
.	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pray	O
'd	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
might	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
a-part	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Rayner	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
in	O
Church-street	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
4th	O
or	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
at	O
what	O
Hour	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
News	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Fore-parlour	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
double	O
Shutters	O
to	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
broke	O
thro	O
'	O
;	O
the	O
Iron-bar	O
was	O
bent	O
thus	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
outer	O
Shutter	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
wrenched	O
open	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Goods	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Rayner	O
.	O
A	O
silver	O
pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
Stand	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Pepper-box	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Chejoy	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Shutters	O
fast	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
'em	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
the	O
Sashes	O
of	O
that	O
Window	O
that	O
was	O
open	O
stood	O
double	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
E.	O
Chejoy	O
.	O
The	O
under	O
Sash	O
was	O
thrown	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
upper	O
one	O
drawn	O
as	O
far	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boufet	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
calling	O
past	O
twelve	O
when	O
Baker	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
Anderson	O
and	O
Ogleby	O
by	O
Charing-cross	O
;	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
us	O
whither	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
?	O
we	O
said	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
tell	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
Talk	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Night-cellar	O
by	O
Privy-garden	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Privy-garden	O
!	O
Wild	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
Privy-garden	O
or	O
Spring-garden	O
,	O
but	O
its	O
over-against	O
the	O
Meuse	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Discourse	O
had	O
you	O
there	O
?	O
Wild	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
Here	O
's	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
but	O
one	O
Pot	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
go	O
towards	O
the	O
Tennis-court	O
,	O
says	O
Ogleby	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
two	O
Stalls	O
where	O
the	O
People	O
leave	O
their	O
Goods	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
mill	O
'em	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
break	O
'em	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
soon	O
agreed	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Anderson	O
wrench	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
there	O
that	O
was	O
worth	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
better	O
Chance	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
at	O
last	O
into	O
Church-street	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
pushing	O
against	O
a	O
Shutter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
we	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
Chissel	O
betwixt	O
the	O
two	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
hard	O
Wrench	O
,	O
forc	O
'd	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
Noise	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
it	O
would	O
alarm	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
we	O
retreated	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Event	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
all	O
safe	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
blew	O
out	O
the	O
Lamp	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Then	O
Anderson	O
stood	O
upon	O
my	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
upper	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
reaching	O
over	O
,	O
undid	O
the	O
inner	O
Shutters	O
.	O
Getting	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
push	O
up	O
the	O
under	O
Sash	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
Ogleby	O
try	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
rais	O
'd	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
clapping	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
under	O
,	O
forc	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
high	O
enough	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
enter	O
.	O
Anderson	O
stepp	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Lamp	O
,	O
lighted	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Dark-lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
while	O
we	O
stood	O
without	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Stand	O
for	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Pepper-box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
took	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
he	O
sunk	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
we	O
saw	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
Time	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
thence	O
to	O
Stocks-market	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
four	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
us	O
having	O
any	O
Money	O
left	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
Hat	O
to	O
Ogleby	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
upon	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Hand	O
facing	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
indeed	O
it	O
was	O
Morning	O
then	O
.	O
He	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
lend	O
us	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
said	O
we	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Gin	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Gin	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
but	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
suspicious	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
call	O
'd	O
Lightfoot	O
;	O
we	O
concluded	O
Light-foot	O
was	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
so	O
bidding	O
the	O
Man	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
we	O
made	O
haste	O
away	O
.	O
Anderson	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
Money	O
we	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
and	O
redeem	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
.	O
Thence	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
Court	O
or	O
Alley	O
in	O
Turnmill-Street	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
we	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Baker	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Plate	O
weigh	O
'd	O
;	O
we	O
waited	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
we	O
stepp	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
Baker	O
came	O
thither	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
Plate	O
weigh	O
'd	O
twenty	O
one	O
Ounces	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
before	O
Whitehead	O
follow	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
what	O
the	O
Plate	O
came	O
to	O
at	O
4	O
s.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
Anderson	O
,	O
we	O
shar	O
'd	O
it	O
equally	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a-piece	O
.	O
Ogleby	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
first	O
?	O
Wild	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
you	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
drank	O
with	O
you	O
since	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
.	O
Ogleby	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
prove	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
drank	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Wild	O
.	O
Do	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
And	O
where	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
saw	O
me	O
first	O
?	O
Wild	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
we	O
committed	O
together	O
.	O
Ogleby	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
England	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
we	O
committed	O
this	O
Transgression	O
?	O
Wild	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
.	O
Ogleby	O
.	O
And	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
Day	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Wild	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Execution	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
Ogleby	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
any	O
Robberies	O
that	O
I	O
committed	O
?	O
Wild	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Ogleby	O
.	O
Name	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
Wild	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
you	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
self	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Ogleby	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
hang	O
you	O
by	O
Report	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
made	O
your	O
Brags	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
snatch	O
'd	O
twenty	O
Pockets	O
in	O
a	O
Night	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
gold	O
Watch	O
once	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gascee	I-pers
wanted	O
Money	O
you	O
went	O
a	O
snatching	O
Pockets	O
together	O
.	O
Wild	O
.	O
And	O
just	O
now	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Company	O
.	O
Baker	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Wild	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
fell	O
in	O
your	O
Company	O
at	O
Buck	O
's	O
Brandy-shop	O
by	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
you	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
you	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
there	O
.	O
When	O
it	O
was	O
Dark	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
Pockets	O
till	O
past	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
meeting	O
with	O
Anderson	O
and	O
Ogleby	O
,	O
by	O
Charing	O
cross	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
28.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Flax	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Carlton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
November	O
7	O
.	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Carlton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
whole	O
Door	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
half	O
Door	O
?	O
Carlton	O
.	O
A	O
half	O
Door	O
.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
And	O
could	O
nobody	O
get	O
over	O
it	O
without	O
breaking	O
it	O
open	O
?	O
Carlton	O
.	O
Not	O
easily	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
high	O
from	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
I	O
reach	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
half	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
unbolted	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Bell	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
,	O
we	O
waited	O
till	O
a	O
Coach	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Anderson	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
how	O
giving	O
a	O
Thrust	O
with	O
his	O
Knee	O
,	O
forc	O
'd	O
the	O
Lock	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
upper	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Burglary	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Flax	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
William	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Tons	O
of	O
old	O
Cast-iron	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
27	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
lives	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
deals	O
in	O
old	O
Clothes	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
some	O
Goods	O
to	O
Dunkirk	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Returns	O
in	O
old	O
Cast-iron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Captain	O
Hammond	O
's	O
Ship	O
to	O
Iron-gate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Boat	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
at	O
St.	O
Saviour's-dock	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
Instructions	O
are	O
right	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
on	O
a	O
sleeveless	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
one	O
Darling	O
,	O
put	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
Iron	O
into	O
another	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Faulcon	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
World	O
of	O
Wrong	O
done	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
a	O
World	O
of	O
Wrong	O
,	O
indeed	O
!	O
I	O
bought	O
four	O
Tons	O
of	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
old	O
Rags	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
in	O
Captain	O
Hammond	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Iron-gate	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Juty	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Juty	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
upon	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
Iron	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Bray	O
's	O
Boat	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Bray	O
,	O
s	O
Boat	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
's	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
at	O
Savorie's-dock	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
from	O
Iron-gate	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
agreed	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Ton	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Iron	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Spencer	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Property	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
your	O
Property	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Property	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
's	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
it	O
's	O
true	O
indeed	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
my	O
honourable	O
Lordship	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
Bray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Iron	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
would	O
take	O
but	O
18	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
his	O
Purpose	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Sculler	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Sculler	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Juty	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
said	O
Spencer	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
18	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
with	O
Bray	O
,	O
unknown	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
Bray	O
,	O
unknown	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanting	O
a	O
Waterman	O
to	O
Savorie's-Dock	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
Waterman	O
to	O
Savorie's-Dock	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
Bray	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
for	O
Bray	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
Boat	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
says	O
Bray	O
,	O
Mister	O
Williams	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
Mister	O
Williams	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
fetch	O
'd	O
old	O
Rags	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
and	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
why	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
let	O
me	O
carry	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
makes	O
a	O
sad	O
Noise	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
letting	O
the	O
Iron	O
lie	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
pray	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
Council	O
.	O
Was	O
Spencer	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Water-side	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
Spencer	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
please	O
my	O
honourable	O
Lordship	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Spencer	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Bray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
Bray	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
Bray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
Pray	O
Mister	O
Spencer	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
I	O
carry	O
it	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
And	O
says	O
Mr	O
Spencer	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
a	O
Lighter	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
And	O
Bray	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
ready	O
by	O
the	O
Ship	O
's	O
side	O
by	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
Bray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hammond	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Bray	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Lighter	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
in	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hammond	O
's	O
Ship	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
till	O
four	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Bray	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Lighter	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
till	O
four	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
God	O
save	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
!	O
no	O
my	O
honourable	O
Lordship	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
four	O
a	O
Clock	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
wonder	O
'd	O
Bray	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
for	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
bless	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
to	O
think	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
sent	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
sent	O
another	O
Lighter	O
man	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Bray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Lighter	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Ship	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
Iron	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Bray	O
's	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
at	O
Savorie's-Dock	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
took	O
18	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
apprehend	O
it	O
,	O
here	O
was	O
a	O
Contract	O
for	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Delivery	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Spencer	O
's	O
Man	O
.	O
Spencer	O
refus	O
'd	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
that	O
was	O
sent	O
back	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
which	O
Bray	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
:	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
meaning	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Pardon	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
but	O
18	O
hundred	O
to	O
Spencer	O
;	O
but	O
Bray	O
took	O
my	O
Iron	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Spencer	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
before	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Ess	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
found	O
5	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Faulcon	O
;	O
ess	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
.	O
Tubs	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
as	O
Bray	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Spencer	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
Bray	O
,	O
Where	O
's	O
the	O
Tubs	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bray	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Bray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Iron	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Thames-Street	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Bray	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
Spencer	O
took	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
18	O
hundred	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
's	O
Recommendation	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Founder	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
us	O
understand	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
possible	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
Deliver	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Iron	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Ess	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
ess	O
,	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
three	O
Tons	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
to	O
Bray	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
Bridge	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Lighter	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
never	O
get	O
thro	O
'	O
Bridge	O
this	O
Tide	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
two	O
Men	O
to	O
aid	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
push	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
thro	O
'	O
for-the	O
Tide	O
was	O
so	O
strong	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
push	O
'd	O
us	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Boat	O
fast	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Bridge	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
did	O
get	O
thro	O
'	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Ess	O
,	O
ess	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
thro	O
'	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
make	O
some	O
Excuse	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
you	O
away	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
O	O
!	O
yes	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Excuses	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
quitted	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
with	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Boat	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
White-Bear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Iron	O
would	O
be	O
safe	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
in	O
Possession	O
of	O
the	O
Iron	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
Body	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
Possession	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
safe	O
as	O
so	O
much	O
Gold	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
Bray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
Bray	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Now	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
again	O
.	O
But	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
at	O
the	O
Bridge	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
Bray	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
Bray	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Bray	O
,	O
Bray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
Bray	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
5	O
hundred	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
a	O
Subpoena	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
excus	O
'd	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
excus	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
World	O
of	O
Wrong	O
,	O
of	O
Wrong	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
a	O
World	O
of	O
Wrong	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
a	O
World	O
of	O
Wrong	O
have	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
is	O
kept	O
back	O
by	O
this	O
Wood	O
,	O
the	O
Founder	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Hutchins	O
is	O
indicted	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
Rochester	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Condition	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
dangerous	O
Condition	O
indeed	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
Ann	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
threaten	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
kept	O
this	O
Man	O
from	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
Judgement	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
from	O
Justice	O
and	O
from	O
Judgement	O
.	O
Pray	O
consider	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
sad	O
Condition	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
sad	O
Condition	O
indeed	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
sad	O
Condition	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Monmouth-Street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
Bray	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
And	O
Will	O
.	O
Darling	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Bray	O
,	O
Now	O
you	O
can	O
be	O
here	O
at	O
your	O
Liberty	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Water-side	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
have	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
Praemunire	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
this	O
Iron	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
says	O
Bray	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
keep	O
up	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
And	O
says	O
Darling	O
,	O
You	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
your	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Answer	O
that	O
Bray	O
made	O
was	O
,	O
What	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
and	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
and	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
brought	O
five	O
iron	O
Balls	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
Supper	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Captain	O
down	O
to	O
Eriff	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
30.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gainer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Quart-pot	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gerish	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ran	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
four	O
Mobs	O
,	O
twenty	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
twenty-one	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Freeman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
her	O
Work	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
Shoemaker	O
's-Pegs	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
her	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
my	O
Drawers	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Cannon-Street	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Drawers	O
with	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
what	O
should	O
I	O
open	O
them	O
with	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
?	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
?	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
three	O
Guineas	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
33.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Price	O
Heb	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chaloner	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
one	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
made	O
of	O
mix	O
'd	O
Metal	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35.	O
George	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
36.	O
John	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Francis	B-pers
Curfoy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Garters	O
,	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Dated	O
Oct.	O
6	O
.	O
1733.	O
drawn	O
by	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
on	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
Payable	O
at	O
5	O
Days	O
sight	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Curfoy	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
31	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Curfoy	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
led	O
me	O
a	O
back	O
Way	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
wrong	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
thither	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
Bill	O
for	O
5l	O
.	O
9s	O
.	O
(	O
dated	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
Oct.	O
6	O
.	O
1733.	O
drawn	O
by	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
on	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
Payable	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
5	O
Days	O
sight	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Garters	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
my	O
Chest	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pockets	O
.	O
My	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
about	O
my	O
Neck	O
in	O
a	O
double	O
Knot	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
getting	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
strangled	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Fye	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
native	O
Land	O
!	O
A	O
Woman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chandler's-Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
pulling	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
good	O
Woman	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Farthen	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
Small-beer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
left	O
I	O
should	O
meet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
View	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
;	O
but	O
next	O
Morning	O
Tho	B-pers
Ovington	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Shadwell-Cage	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Wath	O
I	O
the	O
Man	O
ath	O
produthed	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
before	O
the	O
Juthtith	O
.	O
Curfoy	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Jane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
did	O
not	O
a	O
Fellow	O
that	O
wath	O
before	O
the	O
Juthtith	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thay	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Curfoy	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Wath	O
not	O
I	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
Bandy-thop	O
when	O
you	O
thaw	O
me	O
firtht	O
?	O
Curfoy	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
you	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
together	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Wath	O
nobody	O
elth	O
in	O
the	O
Thop	O
but	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
?	O
Curfoy	O
.	O
Nobody	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Wath	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
thober	O
?	O
Curfoy	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
small	O
Cup	O
of	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
winding	O
Silk	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Blue	O
-coat-fields	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
!	O
Its	O
a	O
sad	O
Thing	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Christian	O
Land	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Fellow-natives	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Stones	O
at	O
Brown	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
pulling	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosetor	O
's	O
Nose	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Water	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Farthing	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
Small-beer	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
lifted	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
sell	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
the	O
Damage	O
he	O
had	O
suffer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Small-beer	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
Dram	O
?	O
He	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
4s	O
.	O
but	O
hop	O
'd	O
his	O
Note	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
but	O
searching	O
farther	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
too	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
The	O
Houses	O
in	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
are	O
left	O
out	O
in	O
Tenements	O
to	O
Lodgers	O
;	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ovington	O
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
our	O
Street-door	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
let	O
'em	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
some	O
Fellows	O
that	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
wath	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prothecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Low-room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
afterwardth	O
lay	O
,	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
pray	O
wath	O
not	O
hith	O
Nothe	O
cut	O
then	O
?	O
Thorton	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
wath	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Cage	O
,	O
and	O
thith	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
thee	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
thaid	O
thee	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
.	O
Thornton	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
nigh	O
the	O
Cage	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ovington	I-pers
,	O
Beadle	O
.	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
Blue-coat-fields	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Thornton	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
got	O
out	O
backwards	O
;	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Alley	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
thus	O
-	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
.	O
John	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
Go	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Black-guard	O
