TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
of	O
January	O
1734	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	O
BILLERS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1734	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXIV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
Sessions-Papers	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BILLERS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Vezey	B-pers
Hoslefoot	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
Coles	B-pers
Fortry	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Shuckburg	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Petley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Ashburnham	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Brooker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tillier	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Power	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Quilter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dolphin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold-rings	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk-gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Bromfield	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Bell-Yard	O
in	O
King's-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
sell	O
Greens	O
and	O
Fruit	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Lower-part	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Use	O
,	O
and	O
lett	O
all	O
the	O
Rest	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
an	O
Apron	O
or	O
a	O
Cap	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
.	O
About	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Covent-Garden-Market	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Apples	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
,	O
my	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Silk-gown	O
,	O
and	O
Quilted-petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Gold-rings	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
expected	O
(	O
suspected	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Flannel-petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
again	O
'till	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
Tho	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tovey	O
stopt	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gold-rings	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bennet	O
,	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
three	O
Nights	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
Months	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
eat	O
nor	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
left	O
a	O
Serge-coat	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
Bread	O
,	O
and	O
Small-beer	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
told	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Wedding-ring	O
in	O
pawn	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
Use	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
as	O
cheap	O
as	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
as	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
who	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
whereof	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
16	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Ring	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
pawn	O
the	O
Ring	O
?	O
Bennet	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
your	O
Husband	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
ever	O
wrong	O
you	O
?	O
Bennet	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
-	O
some	O
call	O
it	O
Thieving-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
two	O
Nights	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
Quilted-Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
Victuals	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Sister	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Rowlatt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
South-Mims	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Check	O
,	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ticking	O
,	O
12	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
l.	O
74	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
46	O
Spanish	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
37	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
French	O
Gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sherrard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
White-Bear	O
at	O
Hadley	O
,	O
near	O
Barnet	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
thither	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
to	O
tell	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
shew	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
Sight	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
with	O
my	O
Eyes	O
.	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
twelve	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Guinea	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
;	O
from	O
another	O
Bag	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
several	O
other	O
Outlandish	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
Parcel	O
a	O
of	O
Guineas	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
opening	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
Diamond-ring	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
that	O
was	O
of	O
more	O
Value	O
than	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Purse	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
-	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
Silver	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Nottingham	O
,	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Country	O
with	O
Orders	O
to	O
receive	O
this	O
Money	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
more	O
likely	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
some	O
Robbery	O
,	O
or	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
Assistance	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
me	O
pay	O
for	O
stopping	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Journey	O
-	O
But	O
afterwards	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
East	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Smith	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
his	O
Examination	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Confession	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sherrard	I-pers
told	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
any	O
Man	O
might	O
take	O
a	O
Thief	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
,	O
Humphry	O
Buckle	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
my	O
Orders	O
from	O
my	O
Master	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Writing	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Hand	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
48	O
Guineas	O
,	O
12	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Doubloons	O
,	O
and	O
double	O
Doubloons	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
'em	O
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
(	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
)	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
by	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
White-Bear	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
East	O
of	O
that	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scratoir	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
White	O
Dimity	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
Mr.	O
East	O
lived	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
somewhere	O
in	O
London	O
near	O
the	O
Monument	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
forgot	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
wrote	O
this	O
Letter	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
came	O
down	O
that	O
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
write	O
the	O
Letter	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
writ	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
read	O
in	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Clerk	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
in	O
Coleman-Street	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Star-Tavern	O
,	O
These	O
.	O
'	O
Honoured	O
Master	O
John	B-pers
Fast	I-pers
I	O
have	O
taken	O
'	O
your	O
Money	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
Barnet	O
'	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
do	O
confess	O
it	O
without	O
any	O
'	O
more	O
dispute	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
ask	O
a	O
thousand	O
pardons	O
'	O
and	O
my	O
Kinsman	O
Christopher	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
'	O
shall	O
be	O
bound	O
for	O
my	O
making	O
you	O
amends	O
'	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
spent	O
but	O
very	O
Little	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
'	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
litle	O
while	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
'	O
but	O
pardon	O
me	O
and	O
not	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
Newgate	O
'	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
my	O
uncle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Countery	O
'	O
which	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
satisfy	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
'	O
will	O
have	O
But	O
a	O
little	O
paticence	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
ask	O
'	O
ten	O
thousand	O
pardons	O
and	O
pray	O
do	O
not	O
put	O
me	O
'	O
to	O
no	O
more	O
Trouble	O
for	O
your	O
money	O
is	O
'	O
very	O
safe	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
so	O
no	O
'	O
more	O
at	O
present	O
but	O
your	O
Servant	O
Thomas	O
'	O
Rowland	O
kinsman	O
Cistopher	O
I	O
do	O
desire	O
'	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
with	O
this	O
for	O
'	O
I	O
will	O
down	O
of	O
my	O
knees	O
and	O
ask	O
you	O
'	O
both	O
pardon	O
and	O
forgiveness	O
and	O
Pray	O
pray	O
'	O
go	O
with	O
this	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
and	O
Desire	O
him	O
'	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
fauerably	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
at	O
'	O
present	O
tho	O
I	O
do	O
Little	O
Dersue	O
it	O
and	O
pray	O
'	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
Let	O
'	O
it	O
cost	O
what	O
it	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
asoon	O
as	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
opertunity	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
my	O
Uncle	O
'	O
so	O
pray	O
come	O
without	O
fail	O
before	O
the	O
Come	O
'	O
with	O
me	O
pray	O
get	O
some	O
bonds	O
men	O
to	O
be	O
'	O
bound	O
for	O
my	O
apperince	O
at	O
the	O
Sises	O
if	O
my	O
'	O
Master	O
does	O
desire	O
it	O
But	O
pray	O
pasifie	O
him	O
'	O
if	O
you	O
Can	O
and	O
pray	O
desire	O
Mr	O
James	O
to	O
'	O
Come	O
to	O
my	O
asistance	O
if	O
he	O
Can	O
but	O
do	O
'	O
me	O
the	O
fauer	O
for	O
if	O
my	O
Master	O
should	O
take	O
'	O
away	O
my	O
life	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
him	O
no	O
good	O
so	O
'	O
pray	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
with	O
this	O
with	O
faile	O
'	O
and	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
Easy	O
as	O
he	O
Can	O
'	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
I	O
lie	O
at	O
his	O
Breast	O
now	O
If	O
he	O
'	O
plesses	O
to	O
spare	O
my	O
Life	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
for	O
'	O
Ever	O
bound	O
to	O
pray	O
for	O
him	O
as	O
Long	O
as	O
'	O
he	O
Lives	O
Tho	O
Rowlatt	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
3.	O
Susan	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callimanco-Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silk-hood	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ticking	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saint	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4,5.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Iverson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
January	O
6	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Iverson	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
a	O
se'n-night	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Exeter-street	O
,	O
I	O
slipt	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
'em	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Distiller	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
call	O
for	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'd	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
very	O
well	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
hardly	O
sensible	O
.	O
The	O
Distiller	O
not	O
liking	O
the	O
Company	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
Watch	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
should	O
lose	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
able	O
enough	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Distiller	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Jones	O
,	O
but	O
Clark	O
got	O
of	O
.	O
Jones	O
told	O
us	O
Clark	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Six-pence	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
ill	O
Company	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
Watch	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
taking	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
my	O
dear	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
brought	O
you	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
you	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
thinking	O
they	O
might	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
standing	O
close	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
again	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
warrant	O
ye	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
that	O
myself	O
;	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
cunning	O
indeed	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
can	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
You	O
shall	O
see	O
how	O
safe	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
but	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Fob	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
.	O
Hah	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
gone	O
already	O
!	O
Upon	O
that	O
the	O
Women	O
both	O
took	O
to	O
their	O
Heels	O
,	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
Jones	O
but	O
Clark	O
escaped	O
then	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
by	O
Jones	O
's	O
Direction	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
again	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
7.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wetherly	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Knee-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
William	O
Dixon	O
.	O
Between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
fuddl	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
straddl	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Road	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
in	O
Blue-Coat-Fields	B-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
Joint-stool	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Rug	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
lye	O
down	O
any	O
where	O
.	O
They	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
'em	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
'd	O
let	O
me	O
lye	O
quiet	O
till	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
my	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
my	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Slumber	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
myself	O
,	O
nor	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
fuddl	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Fault	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
them	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
Things	O
alone	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
never	O
regarded	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
blew	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
secretly	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
must	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
8.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter-tankard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
William	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
Evers	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Laurence	O
Evers	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
Moor-Fields	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
my	O
Maid	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
below	O
Stairs	O
)	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Beds	O
-	O
The	O
Cup	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Moor-Fields	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Morpeth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Tom	O
.	O
Dun	O
went	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Tenters	O
,	O
in	O
Moor-Fields	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Chance	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
could	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
't	O
is	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
hard	O
by	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
farthest	O
End	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
Pallisades	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Chance	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
cou	O
'd	O
get	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
soon	O
contrived	O
a	O
Way	O
.	O
They	O
two	O
hoisted	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Pallisades	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Airey	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
listed	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
lately	O
been	O
washing	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
Sheets	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
the	O
Maid	O
would	O
come	O
down	O
and	O
surprize	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
handed	O
the	O
Cup	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
tall	O
enough	O
to	O
reach	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
,	O
he	O
rais	O
'd	O
himself	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
leaning	O
over	O
the	O
Pallisades	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
haul	O
'd	O
through	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Bars	O
Dun	O
helpt	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
covering	O
the	O
Linnen	O
with	O
his	O
Great-coat	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Vinegar-field	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
bring	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
the	O
Linnen	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cotterel	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Brandy	B-pers
Shop	I-pers
in	O
Moor-fields	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
waited	O
without	O
.	O
Dun	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Cotterel	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
Cotterel	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
look	O
like	O
well	O
dress	O
'd	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
drank	O
here	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
lend	O
you	O
a	O
Guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Dun	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
must	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
let	O
you	O
have	O
38	O
s.	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
redeem	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
yours	O
;	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
:	O
So	O
we	O
struck	O
a	O
Bargain	O
,	O
she	O
paid	O
us	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Dun	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
Dividend	O
,	O
each	O
Man	O
taking	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
discovered	O
the	O
Robbery	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
afterwards	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
another	O
Affair	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
Affair	O
was	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
knew	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
two	O
Informations	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
pass	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
for	O
a	O
Jeweller	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
you	O
appear	O
'd	O
pretty	O
well	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
your	O
Neck	O
in	O
danger	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
secure	O
your	O
old	O
Companions	O
,	O
you	O
made	O
this	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
slight	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Morpeth	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
first	O
at	O
a	O
Baudy-house	O
in	O
Swan-yard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
kept	O
by	O
Tom	O
.	O
Dun	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
Ebenezer	O
Dun	O
was	O
convicted	O
in	O
December	O
,	O
1732	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
when	O
Will	O
.	O
Byram	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
Numb	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Page	O
8	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Pallisades	O
are	O
not	O
so	O
high	O
that	O
I	O
needed	O
to	O
raise	O
myself	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
look	O
over	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
thieving	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
maintain	O
myself	O
very	O
well	O
by	O
my	O
Work	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Cane-Chair-Carver	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Father	O
(	O
in-law	O
)	O
is	O
a	O
Cane-Chair-Maker	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
.	O
Indeed	O
I	O
marry	O
'd	O
against	O
his	O
Consent	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
trusted	O
me	O
with	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Men	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gladstone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
,	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
Weeks	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
industrious	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
have	O
ruined	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
honest	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
Shop	O
open	O
(	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
all	O
Hours	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
ever	O
get	O
drunk	O
,	O
or	O
keep	O
ill	O
Hours	O
,	O
or	O
beat	O
my	O
Wife	O
?	O
Gladstone	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
One	O
Night	O
indeed	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
nothing	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
my	O
Brother-in-law	O
.	O
He	O
served	O
the	O
latter	O
three	O
Years	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
married	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
wild	O
indeed	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
good	O
Hours	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Phillips	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
(	O
whose	O
Daughter	O
he	O
married	O
,	O
three	O
Months	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
)	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
us	O
our	O
Wages	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
and	O
was	O
constant	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
first	O
Master	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Questy	O
)	O
's	O
where	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
idle	O
sometimes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Ratcliff-Highway	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
his	O
Father-in-law	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
Keeper	O
of	O
New-prison	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Morpeth	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
in	O
New-prison	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
another	O
Charge	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
detain	O
'd	O
.	O
10	O
Melchizedeck	B-pers
Kinder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bones	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
she	O
who	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Muslin-hoods	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
damask-gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Frying-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
Dec.	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tisden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Doroy-coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Dec	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13,14.	O
William	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Smoaky	I-pers
Jack	I-pers
,	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Payton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth-coat	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
a	O
Razor	O
,	O
a	O
Silk-handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Linen-handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
pray	O
'd	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
might	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
a-part	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
.	O
W.	B-pers
Peyton	I-pers
I	I-pers
have	O
some	O
Notion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
'em	O
positively	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
five	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	I-place
from	I-place
Buckingham-House	I-place
,	I-place
hard	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
King's-Head	I-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
lying	O
under	O
a	O
Hay-rick	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Horse-road	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
benighted	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
safely	O
lie	O
there	O
too	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Rick	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
my	O
self	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
About	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Man	O
(	O
like	O
Simmonds	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket-book	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Coat-pocket	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
awake	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
had	O
my	O
Nap	O
out	O
.	O
Aha	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
for	O
?	O
And	O
catching	O
up	O
my	O
Stick	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Skull	O
with	O
some	O
Weapon	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Pistol	O
by	O
the	O
Brightness	O
,	O
but	O
Fidzar	O
,	O
their	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
says	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Cafe-Knife	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
my	O
Stick	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
a	O
Knock	O
,	O
when	O
Fidzar	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Smoaking	O
Jack	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Stick	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
beating	O
and	O
mauling	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
like	O
Simmonds	O
,	O
kept	O
pushing	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Dog	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
resent	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
wounded	O
me	O
so	O
that	O
my	O
Skull	O
might	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
five	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
blinded	O
with	O
the	O
Blood	O
that	O
run	O
down	O
my	O
Face	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
self	O
over	O
power	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
Life	O
:	O
You	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
speak	O
another	O
Word	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
stabb	O
'd	O
the	O
Knife	O
against	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Stroke	O
falling	O
upon	O
the	O
Button	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
no	O
hurt	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
C	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
a	O
Razor	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
wanted	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Waist	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
be	O
the	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
beating	O
and	O
kicking	O
me	O
again	O
and	O
believe	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Fidzar	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Knife	O
from	O
Simmonds	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
Horse-road	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Moon	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Full	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Shade	O
of	O
the	O
Hay-rick	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
their	O
Faces	O
so	O
plain	O
as	O
certainly	O
to	O
know	O
'em	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
for	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
Steel	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
old	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
beat	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Eyes	O
and	O
Mouth	O
,	O
to	O
hinder	O
me	O
from	O
speaking	O
or	O
seeing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
-	O
Besides	O
what	O
I	O
mentioned	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
a	O
particular	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
kept	O
secret	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
Body	O
but	O
myself	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Thing	O
Fidzar	O
describ	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
so	O
exactly	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
he	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
turn	O
'd	O
Stick	O
for	O
a	O
Snuff-Mill	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fidzar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Simmonds	O
at	O
Buck	O
's	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
against	O
St.	O
Giles's-Church	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
there	O
all	O
Day	O
.	O
Towards	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
Steel	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
together	O
;	O
says	O
Simmonds	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
to	O
Night	O
?	O
Ay	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
Who	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
says	O
Simmonds	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
smoaky	O
Jack	O
-	O
That	O
's	O
a	O
Nick-name	O
that	O
Steel	O
goes	O
by	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
together	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
They	O
let	O
me	O
to	O
Hide-	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
behind	O
Buckingham-Wall	O
:	O
Now	O
,	O
says	O
Simmond	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
cross	O
to	O
that	O
Hay-cock	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
led	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Hay-cock	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
lying	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
Damn	O
says	O
Simmonds	O
,	O
Who	O
's	O
here	O
?	O
And	O
prese	O
took	O
a	O
Pocket-book	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
Smoaky	O
Jack	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
se-	O
verely	O
;	O
when	O
his	O
Wig	O
was	O
off	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
bald	O
headed	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
middle	O
Man	O
.	O
Simonds	O
push	O
'd	O
a	O
Knife	O
at	O
him	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Knife	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
bent	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
toss	O
'd	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
Rail	O
into	O
the	O
P	O
;	O
but	O
Smoaky	O
Jack	O
still	O
kept	O
beating	O
,	O
and	O
kicking	O
,	O
and	O
abusing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
They	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sham-Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
turn	O
'd	O
Stick	O
that	O
we	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
to	O
make	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
my	O
Hands	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Smoaky	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
'em	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
was	O
any	O
Mo-	O
ney	O
they	O
sunk	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coat	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
getting	O
under	O
the	O
Rail	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
turn	O
back	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
Simmonds	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
coming	O
to	O
a	O
high	O
Bank	O
,	O
we	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
two	O
of	O
us	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
over	O
without	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
a	O
third	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
help	O
'd	O
each	O
other	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
Hedge	O
and	O
Ditch	O
,	O
'till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Ditch	O
too	O
wide	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Hay-	O
cock	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Buck	O
's	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
by	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
wash	O
'd	O
the	O
Blood	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Simmonds	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
Smoakey	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Buck	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
.	O
They	O
two	O
toss	O
'd	O
up	O
for	O
their	O
share	O
in	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
Simmonds	O
won	O
Smoakey	O
's	O
part	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
sham	O
Shirt	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
;	O
the	O
Wig	O
I	O
sold	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Hat	O
(	O
which	O
we	O
valu	O
'd	O
at	O
10	O
d	O
)	O
I	O
kept	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
wear	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
us	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
Sutton	O
and	O
Stick-in-the-Mud	O
*	O
and	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
frequented	O
Buck	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Buck	O
's	O
,	O
expecting	O
Simmonds	O
would	O
meet	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
Sutton	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Mary-bone-Fields	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stick-in-the-Mud	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
convicted	O
of	O
two	O
Burglaries	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
1.	O
pag	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
here	O
,	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
your	O
Company	O
at	O
Buck	O
's	O
?	O
Fidzar	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
us	O
were	O
misfortunate	O
People	O
like	O
ourselves	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
Moon	O
light	O
Night	O
?	O
Fidzar	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Full-Moon	O
.	O
Smoaky	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
three	O
Times	O
already	O
.	O
You	O
deal	O
with	O
the	O
Thief-catchers	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
Trade	O
of	O
taking	O
Men	O
's	O
Lives	O
away	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Jail	O
,	O
for	O
Want	O
of	O
Sureties	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
this	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
inform	O
against	O
me	O
before	O
now	O
?	O
Fidzar	O
.	O
This	O
Robbery	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
'till	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
+	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
you	O
intended	O
to	O
make	O
yourself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
surrender	O
'd	O
myself	O
voluntarily	O
.	O
+	O
John	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
last	O
Sessions	O
against	O
Henry	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Sickwell	I-pers
,	O
See	O
their	O
Trials	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Part	O
I.	O
p.	O
5.7.	O
Edward	B-pers
Crafts	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Cook's-shop	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
Parish	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
Fidzar	O
and	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
dine	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
Fidzar	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
impeached	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Travers	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Moco	O
Jack	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Beans	O
++	O
.	O
++	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Travers	O
and	O
Cotterel	O
below	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
15.	O
John	B-pers
Asdell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shew-glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Lemon-peel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Barley-sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
L'Equeve	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Mary	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
two	O
Sheets	O
,	O
four	O
Curtains	O
,	O
two	O
Sauce	O
-pans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wishart	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
Diaper	O
Clouts	O
,	O
five	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
,	O
three	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
five	O
Bibs	O
,	O
one	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Caps	O
;	O
in	O
all	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Elizabeth	O
Wishart	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
August	O
4	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
for	O
apprehending	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
~	O
for	O
Dear-stealing	O
;	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
was	O
lawfully	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
by	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Burley	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Assistant	O
:	O
He	O
the	O
said	O
Turner	O
did	O
assault	O
the	O
said	O
Burley	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
feloniously	O
rescued	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
at	O
large	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hood	O
and	O
Burley	O
,	O
and	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
~See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Johnson	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
1	O
Part	O
II	O
.	O
p.	O
40	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
acquit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
18.19.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
Distance	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Molden	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
17	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Molden	O
.	O
Having	O
parted	O
with	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
-Door||	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
they	O
sold	O
good	O
Beer	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
did	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
:	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Distance	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
:	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
drank	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Discourse	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
sit	O
by	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
their	O
Familiarity	O
.	O
Then	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
had	O
an	O
ill	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
think	O
I	O
would	O
bear	O
with	O
ill	O
Usage	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
expos	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
fast	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bad	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
for	O
my	O
Gold-watch	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Villain	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
restore	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
raise	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
of	O
ill	O
Consequence	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
try	O
what	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
?	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
requir	O
'd	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
5	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
reply	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
unreasonable	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
insist	O
upon	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
helping	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Watch	O
when	O
he	O
knew	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
2	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
consult	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
aside	O
into	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
near	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
10	O
Minutes	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
lay	O
down	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
:	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Watch	O
first	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Curtain	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
sprung	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
my	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
re-	O
proach	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Usage	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
his	O
returning	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
laid	O
Hands	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
drag	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
imminent	O
Danger	O
,	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
them	O
towards	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Says	O
Distance	O
,	O
He	O
'll	O
be	O
too	O
hard	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
throw	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
This	O
added	O
to	O
my	O
Surprize	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
hop	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
upon	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
again	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
alarm	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
And	O
indeed	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Necessity	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
and	O
Thieves	O
!	O
when	O
by	O
God	O
's	O
Mercy	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
being	O
upon	O
his	O
Rounds	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
but	O
Stanley	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
||	O
The	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Echenham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
receiving	O
Plate	O
stolen	O
from	O
Col.	O
Des	B-pers
Romaine	I-pers
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Part	O
II	O
.	O
p.	O
35.	O
William	B-pers
Greenham	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Nan	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
came	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
2	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
Bit	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
run	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Screeking	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
so	O
close	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thrust	O
my	O
Staff	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
my	O
Way	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Stanley	O
with	O
his	O
Knuckles	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Face	O
was	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
your	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
lie	O
with	O
Betty	B-pers
Distance	I-pers
before	O
our	O
Faces	O
.	O
He	O
shook	O
Hands	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Jack	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
five	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
answer	O
'd	O
.	O
Go	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
20.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Elliston	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
James	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
Dec	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Partridges	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
Fowls	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
,	O
Nov.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Peter	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
*	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dav	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
*	O
Peter	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Dan	O
.	O
Tipping	O
,	O
in	O
July	O
1732	O
.	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
p.	O
160	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
himself	O
in	O
September	O
following	O
for	O
a	O
street-Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Numb	O
.	O
VII	O
.	O
Part	O
II	O
.	O
p.	O
210	O
.	O
His	O
Sister	O
Kate	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
Transported	O
.	O
Numb	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Part	O
II	O
.	O
p.	O
43	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24	O
,	O
25.	O
Edward	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Godhurt	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Dec.	O
31	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26.	O
George	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bains	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Kitching	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Barrels	O
of	O
Anchovies	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
Nov.	O
20	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Kitching	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Oyl-Shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John's-Street	I-place
.	O
My	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
were	O
made	O
fast	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Cellar-window	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
plank	O
was	O
split	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Barrels	O
of	O
Anchovies	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fidzar	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
*	O
in	O
Bit-Alley	O
in	O
Turnbull-street	O
-	O
Her	O
Husband	O
is	O
a	O
Watch-maker	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
thence	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Chance	O
,	O
'till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
There	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Chissell	O
and	O
split	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar-window	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
raising	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Anchovies	O
that	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
stood	O
so	O
close	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
another	O
,	O
without	O
pulling	O
up	O
the	O
remaining	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
plank	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Trouble	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
shift	O
to	O
manage	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
another	O
Barrel	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
then	O
have	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Barrels	O
rolling	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
let	O
them	O
lie	O
'till	O
Day-light	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
in	O
Charter-house-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
upon	O
Account	O
of	O
receiving	O
some-Plate	O
that	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
We	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
Anchovies	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
poor	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
much	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
7s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Noise	O
about	O
her	O
having	O
,	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
safe	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Anchovies	O
-	O
I	O
forget	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
her	O
Jenny	O
-	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
wrap	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
and	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Blue-Boar	O
,	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Walk	O
towards	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
People	O
talking	O
about	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Coming	O
back	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
Jenny	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
She	O
gave	O
us	O
4s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
Whitehead	O
could	O
get	O
-	O
I	O
surrender	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
January	O
2	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Claxton	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
two	O
more	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
Justice	O
Ribe	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
more	O
of	O
Whitehead	O
in	O
the	O
Trials	O
of	O
Stephen	O
Partridge	O
,	O
Robert	O
Tanner	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Cecil	O
,	O
in	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
1733	O
.	O
Numb	O
.	O
VI	O
p.	O
162	O
,	O
163	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
this	O
Fellow	O
Fidzar	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
Fidzar	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
acquitted	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
We	O
lodg	O
'd	O
but	O
a	O
Work	O
at	O
White-head	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
often	O
under	O
a	O
Cloud	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
By	O
Fidzar	O
's	O
Direction	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
his	O
Favour	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
Fidzar	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
Life	O
away	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
a	O
Lighterman	O
;	O
indeed	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
lately	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
Misdemeanor	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Chandler's-Shop	O
in	O
Rosemary-	O
Lane	O
,	O
in	O
October	O
and	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
visited	O
him	O
every	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Landlord	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Work	O
at	O
7	O
every	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
after	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
part	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
.	O
His	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
not	O
living	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
broke	O
up	O
House-keeping	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
quitted	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
partly	O
by	O
Consent	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Ducket	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pumps	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Nov.	O
17	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Ducket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Pewter-platter-Inn	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Street	O
.	O
My	O
Windows	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
at	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
and	O
about	O
9	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Plank	O
of	O
my	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
an	O
Instrument	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Curb	O
and	O
the	O
Flap	O
.	O
The	O
Bolts	O
that	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
Curb	O
were	O
forced	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
'em	O
since	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fidzar	I-pers
.	O
Some	O
Days	O
before	O
we	O
to	O
the	O
Anchovies	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
'd	O
about	O
'till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Pewter-platter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Chissel	O
between	O
the	O
Plank	O
and	O
the	O
Frame	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bolts	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Plank	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Tinder-box	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
the	O
Box	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
again	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
and	O
lighted	O
a	O
Candle	O
below	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
carried	O
Candles	O
and	O
Matches	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
Tinder	O
-box	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
down	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
staid	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Lay	O
hold	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
two	O
charming	O
Great-coats	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cape	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
blue	O
Rug	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
'em	O
on	O
a	O
Bulk	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
handed	O
up	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pumps	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Splatter-casnes	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
natural	O
Wig	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
these	O
with	O
the	O
Great-coat	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
pat	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Great-coats	O
,	O
under	O
which	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
us	O
bring	O
the	O
Great-coats	O
to	O
Taylor	O
's	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
we	O
shar	O
'd	O
betwixt	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Coats	O
were	O
worth	O
18	O
s.	O
but	O
we	O
must	O
not	O
have	O
less	O
than	O
16	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
she	O
brought	O
us	O
14s	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
too	O
little	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Coats	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
shared	O
it	O
equally	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
harboured	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
house	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
lay	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
another	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
the	O
the	O
Sun	O
and	O
Wheathead	O
.	O
We	O
can	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
constantly	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
never	O
rightly	O
settl	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Fidzar	O
's	O
Wife	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
Yesterday	O
A	O
ye	O
Rogue	O
!	O
my	O
Husband	O
bug	O
you	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
Reward	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'll	O
off	O
and	O
sell	O
cheeese	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
27.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Tiller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waple	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
29.	O
Henry	B-pers
Tilson	I-pers
,	O
*	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Werrel	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Worrel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
five	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
thirteen	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Quality-binding	O
,	O
thirteen	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Tape	O
,	O
six	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk-Ferrit	O
,	O
eighteen	O
Dozen	O
of	O
silk	O
Laces	O
,	O
two	O
Caps	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
girdle	O
Buckles	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chfield	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
3	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Tilson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Feb.	O
1733	O
,	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Page	O
82	O
Mary	B-pers
Chipperfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Haberdasher	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Rooms	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Kingsland-Road	B-place
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
Doors	O
fast	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
about	O
12	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
disturbed	O
again	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Manner	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
myself	O
about	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Pin	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shutters	O
was	O
thrust	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
These	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Lump-Sugar	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lay	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
like	O
Quantity	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
in	O
my	O
Drawer	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
This	O
Quality-	O
binding	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
by	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
William	B-pers
Docray	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
George-street	O
,	O
Spittle-fields	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Tilson	O
's	O
Sister	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tilbury	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Tilbury	O
Fort	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
his	O
Majesty	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Consession	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Tilson	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
'd	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
handcuff	O
'd	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
confess	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
'em	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
And	O
Tilson	O
told	O
us	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
Bed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Docray	I-pers
.	O
Tilson	O
's	O
Sister	O
pawn	O
'd	O
these	O
Goods	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linnel	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
At	O
past	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
's	O
Shutters	O
were	O
close	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
4	O
I	O
found	O
'em	O
open	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
'till	O
I	O
wak	O
'd	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chipperfield	I-pers
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
12	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
call	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
together	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
body	O
hid	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
And	O
so	O
thinking	O
the	O
Door	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
carelesly	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
,	O
without	O
observing	O
that	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Window-matter	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shop	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
a.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
some	O
Lodging	O
Houses	O
of	O
ill	O
Repute	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
At	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Houses	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
three	O
Lumps	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Lads	O
in	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
that	O
Bed	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
11	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
Time	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
:	O
However	O
we	O
took	O
these	O
two	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
there	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
passed	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
happened	O
to	O
see	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
goes	O
Tilson	O
and	O
Worrel	O
!	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
'em	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
Tilson	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
hid	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Brick-field	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
(	O
which	O
had	O
no	O
Shutter	O
)	O
and	O
so	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
Worrel	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
They	O
returned	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
out	O
the	O
Pin	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
back	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
to	O
Worrel	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
-	O
Worrel	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
drunk	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
30	O
,	O
31.	O
William	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
(	O
not	O
he	O
who	O
was	O
tryed	O
with	O
Smoaky	O
Jack	O
)	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Stay	O
,	O
2	O
silk	O
Skirts	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Remnant	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
3	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
2	O
Dimity-coats	O
,	O
3	O
Caps	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
5	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen-Frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Oct.	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
high	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Window-shutters	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
shut	O
down	O
close	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
there	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
'em	O
about	O
7	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Sash	O
open	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
lay	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
*	O
.	O
Between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
and	O
setting	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Sash	O
.	O
A	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
reached	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
Silk	O
Skirts	O
or	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stay	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
handed	O
down	O
;	O
Peters	O
went	O
up	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
out	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Ells	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
some	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
odd	O
Things	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
stood	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
below	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
We	O
pack	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Bundle	O
by	O
Turns	O
,	O
to	O
Sam	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
's	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
kept	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
retired	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Havard	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
deal	O
with	O
Strangers	O
He	O
brought	O
us	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
we	O
divided	O
them	O
equally	O
.	O
Thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Moulton	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
last	O
Sessions	O
against	O
Whitlock	O
and	O
Brown	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Col.	O
des	O
Romaine	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moulton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
used	O
my	O
House	O
together	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
Mitchell	O
drank	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
.	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
-	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Pot	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
indeed	O
he	O
would	O
commonly	O
sit	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Table	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
talk	O
jocosely	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Times	O
sitting	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
little	O
Daniel	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
their	O
Characters	O
,	O
I	O
forbid	O
'em	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
.	O
That	O
little	O
Daniel	O
is	O
a	O
Thief	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
to	O
Simmonds	O
,	O
You	O
black	O
guard	O
Dog	O
,	O
d'you	O
see	O
how	O
tight	O
I	O
am	O
?	O
Simmonds	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
as	O
tight	O
as	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bristol	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
Peters	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
Fellow	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
two	O
Men	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
'em	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Euphanioe	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
three	O
Silver-Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ephanioe	O
Kendall	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Velvet-Manteel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick-hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cowgill	I-pers
A	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Clogs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Euphanioe	O
Kendall	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
12	O
with	O
my	O
Daughter	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
in	O
Princes-square	O
,	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
.	O
We	O
lay	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Window-shutters	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
wak	O
'd	O
about	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Drink	O
.	O
My	O
Drawers	O
rattl	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
Mother	O
?	O
Presently	O
I	O
heard	O
some-body	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Maid	O
.	O
Catherine	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
d'you	O
sit	O
sleeping	O
there	O
?	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
?	O
But	O
immediately	O
recollecting	O
myself	O
,	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
!	O
So	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Sash	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
move	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
off	O
as	O
my	O
Hand	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
Head	O
nor	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
a	O
Ladder	O
left	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Silver-tankard	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
manteel	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick-hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Clogs	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Ladder	O
.	O
Peters	O
went	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
down	O
a	O
silver-Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
went	O
up	O
then	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Manteel	O
,	O
a	O
Sarcenet	O
(	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
)	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Clogs	O
.	O
Somebody	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
making	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
down	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
we	O
cou	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Ladder	O
behind	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Sam	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
's	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
the	O
Manteel	O
,	O
Hood	O
,	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Clogs	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Havard	O
for	O
18s	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Spoons	O
to	O
Rodenham	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
we	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
equally	O
.	O
Peters	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
prosecute	O
last	O
Sessions	O
?	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
you	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Peters	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
sent	O
your	O
Wife	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
lay	O
to	O
my	O
Charge	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Harry	O
Whitesides	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
in	O
Custody	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Whitesides	I-pers
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
'em	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
32.	O
James	B-pers
Belford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Cambrick-mob	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
silk-Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
First	O
Indictment	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
from	O
hence	O
in	O
Tothil-street	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
Husband	O
from	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Ring	O
off	O
my	O
Finger	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
)	O
cut	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
three	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
off	O
my	O
Mob	O
(	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Hair	O
with	O
it	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
frighted	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
served	O
by	O
a	O
lusty	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Dray-man	O
's	O
Apron	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
plainly	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
in	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
almost	O
opposite	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lamp	O
that	O
was	O
hard	O
by	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Mob	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
No	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
your	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
your	O
Bulk	O
and	O
your	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Elkins	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
(	O
a	O
Distiller	O
's	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
forward	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
came	O
up	O
without	O
her	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
running	O
down	O
her	O
Arm	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
frighted	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Rogue	O
that	O
has	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
Cap	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Mob	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
a	O
Seal	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
then	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
No	O
I	O
stood	O
behind	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
.	O
Her	O
Cap	O
was	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Arm	O
bloody	O
from	O
her	O
Elbow	O
to	O
her	O
Fingers	O
.	O
Nanny	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
A	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
has	O
abused	O
me	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
Head-clothes	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
Murder	O
,	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Cry	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
behind	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Elkin	O
took	O
the	O
Mob	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Elkin	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
came	O
in	O
almost	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
lusty	O
Fellow	O
in	O
a	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
We	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
Gateway	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
about	O
forty	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
behind	O
a	O
Coach	O
that	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
Chequer	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
the	O
Broad-sentry	O
(	O
Sanchary	O
)	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
's	O
he	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
you	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Dray	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
lighted	O
Link	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Drew	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
lighted	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Drew	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
Ten	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whiteman	O
,	O
a	O
Brewer	O
in	O
Blackman-street	O
.	O
My	O
Fellow-Servant	O
had	O
the	O
Dray-horse	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
with	O
a	O
lighted	O
Link	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
's	O
very	O
likely	O
that	O
I	O
shou	O
'd	O
do	O
a	O
Robbery	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Fellow-servant	O
is	O
sick	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
down	O
Old-Tothill-Street	B-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Oyl-shop	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
jostl	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
squeez	O
'd	O
me	O
hard	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
hit	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Arm	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
burnt	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
under	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
if	O
I	O
resisted	O
.	O
I	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
Way	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
close	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Drew	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
a	O
Window	O
just	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
you	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
hit	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hit	O
you	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
swore	O
you	O
threw	O
me	O
over	O
a	O
Block	O
.	O
Mary	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
swore	O
you	O
fell	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
hang	O
another	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
he	O
had	O
good	O
Friends	O
that	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
-	O
At	O
what	O
a	O
Clock	O
did	O
I	O
knock	O
you	O
down	O
?	O
Mary	O
Allen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
Ten	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Mary	O
Allen	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
that	O
be	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
sent	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
by	O
11	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Dram	O
?	O
Mary	O
Allen	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Tool	O
had	O
I	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
to	O
knock	O
you	O
down	O
with	O
?	O
Did	O
not	O
a	O
Man	O
hold	O
the	O
Dray-Horse	O
?	O
Mary	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
neither	O
saw	O
Horse	O
nor	O
Dray	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lighted	O
Link	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
you	O
a	O
Slap	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	O
Allen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
lighted	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
you	O
were	O
hauling	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Coach	O
came	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Flambeau	O
.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
33.	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34	O
,	O
35.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tobias	B-pers
Budgen	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Sho	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Piddington	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
Edward	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
and	O
150	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
adjoining	O
to	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	B-pers
Hon.the	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Mayor	I-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Commonalty	I-pers
and	I-pers
Citizens	I-pers
of	I-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
Aug.30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
37.	O
Henry	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Dinah	B-pers
Fulner	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Eliz	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Snuff	O
,	O
24lb	O
.	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Junes	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug-coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
James	B-pers
Cleavar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
compound	O
distill	O
'd	O
Spirits	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Feutrell	I-pers
,	O
Dec.27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41	O
,	O
42	O
,	O
43.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Punderson	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
44.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stone-	O
bottle	O
,	O
a	O
Gallon	O
of	O
Rum	O
,	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Oct.1	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Younger	O
(	O
aged	O
12	O
)	O
My	O
Father	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Rum	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Black's-	O
Fields	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
from	O
Layton's-Yard	O
(	O
where	O
they	O
build	O
Ships	O
)	O
to	O
a	O
bye	O
Alley	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
a	O
Pond	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
Rum	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
and	O
run	O
off	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
too	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
County	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Boy	O
.	O
In	O
Farthing-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Jacob-street	O
,	O
on	O
t'other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
Prisoner.Then	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Surry	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
Basket	O
found	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
White	O
-Chapel	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
in	O
any	O
County	O
where	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
are	O
found	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Elder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
vile-Fellow	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
fill	O
'd	O
the	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Rum	O
,	O
and	O
tent	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
this	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brain	I-pers
.	O
At	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Chambers-street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
beneath	O
an	O
Officer	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Gailon	O
of	O
Rum	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Rum	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Basket	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
And	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hearing	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
her	O
the	O
Rum	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Basket	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Rum	O
from	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
agreeing	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
a	O
Drop	O
of	O
Rum	O
there	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
got	O
drunk	O
aboard	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
along	O
where	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
Bottle	O
to	O
rest	O
himself	O
.	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Maggoty	O
,	O
we	O
gave	O
the	O
Bottle	O
a	O
push	O
for	O
fun	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
it	O
fell	O
and	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
three	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Basket	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
left	O
the	O
Basket	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Mins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46.	O
Peter	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Connor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47.	O
John	B-pers
Travis	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Moco	I-pers
Jack	I-pers
*	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Firkins	O
,	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
*	O
Moco	O
Jack	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Macgrady	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
1732	O
.	O
Sessions-paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
VII	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thayer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Casks	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Box	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
27	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
First	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brick	O
Lane	O
,	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
.	O
At	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Door	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
About	O
7	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Stock	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
was	O
burst	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bolt	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Staple	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
our	O
of	O
my	O
back	O
Cellar	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fidzar	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
frequented	O
Mrs.Church	O
's	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
at	O
Salt-Peter-Bank	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
often	O
there	O
from	O
Morning	O
to	O
Night	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
New-Years	O
Day	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
attempted	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
hinder	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
I	O
wrenched	O
open	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
afraid	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
alarm	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
off	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Candle	O
being	O
soon	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
concluded	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
us	O
.	O
So	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
my	O
Tinder-box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
lighted	O
a	O
Candle	O
below	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
Matches	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
above	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
coming	O
by	O
past	O
11	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
lie	O
close	O
,	O
and	O
stepp	O
'd	O
aside	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
taking	O
no	O
notice	O
,	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
post	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
up	O
one	O
Firkin	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
set	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
taking	O
one	O
,	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Whitechapel-Mount	O
,	O
and	O
cover	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
Dung	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
knew	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
up	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
When	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
,	O
I	O
propos	O
'd	O
we	O
should	O
fetch	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
very	O
sleepy	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
another	O
Man	O
(	O
we	O
call	O
him	O
French	O
Peter	O
)	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
bring	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Peter	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
together	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Church	O
's	O
.	O
Where	O
they	O
stood	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
a	O
Chap	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
met	O
Sarah	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
(	O
who	O
buys	O
old	O
Clothes	O
in	O
the	O
Fair	O
)	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
They	O
tasted	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Firkins	O
,	O
we	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
Two	O
pence	O
Half-penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
us	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Firkins	O
weigh	O
'd	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Hundred	O
and	O
eight	O
Pounds	O
a-piece	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
not	O
proving	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Women	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
but	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
We	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
to	O
mend	O
our	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
consented	O
to	O
take	O
their	O
Money	O
:	O
Anderson	O
carry	O
'd	O
one	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
afterwards	O
directed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
Church	O
's	O
and	O
pay	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
eat	O
a	O
ha	O
'	O
p'orth	O
of	O
boil	O
'd	O
Potatoes	O
in	O
the	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
back	O
to	O
Church	O
's	O
I	O
met	O
Anderson	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
my	O
half	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
7	O
s	O
,	O
9	O
d.	O
for	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
Pots	O
of	O
Cherry-beer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Fidzar	O
-	O
Indeed	O
I	O
have	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
the	O
Fellow	O
at	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
ever	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
His	O
Creature	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Aye	O
you	O
Rogue	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
get	O
the	O
Reward	O
for	O
banging	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
'll	O
live	O
honest	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thayer	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
Brick-Lane	B-place
.	O
My	O
Cellar-window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Clamp	O
,	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
Frame	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plank	O
that	O
flaps	O
down	O
was	O
lifted	O
up	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Casks	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Cellar	O
-	O
The	O
empty	O
Casks	O
and	O
Box	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
behind	O
my	O
House	O
by	O
some	O
Workmen	O
William	B-pers
Fidzar	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
Church	O
's	O
Shop	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
light	O
on	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
Brandy-shop	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
in	O
Brick-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
flung	O
back	O
two	O
flat	O
Bolts	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
wrenched	O
the	O
Plank	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
my	O
Tinder-box	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
lighted	O
a	O
Candle	O
below	O
;	O
some	O
Butchers	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Hurricane	O
of	O
Marrow-bones	O
and	O
Cleavers	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
lie	O
snug	O
,	O
'till	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
by	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
Cask	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
another	O
Cask	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
behind	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
empty	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
our	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
's	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
empty	O
Casks	O
and	O
Box	O
behind	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Hot-pot	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
till	O
Day-light	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Boy	O
for	O
Tom	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
Goods	O
of	O
us	O
before	O
.	O
Tom	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
some	O
Tobacco	O
that	O
Trevis	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
we	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
two	O
Bags	O
weigh	O
'd	O
about	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
one	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
us	O
13	O
s.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
14	O
s.	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
Shilling	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
scrupl	O
'd	O
sometime	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
Bag	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
staid	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
brought	O
us	O
14	O
s.	O
We	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
pains	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
equally	O
-	O
Pattison	O
now	O
keeps	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
Fellow	O
with	O
my	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Fidzar	O
.	O
We	O
became	O
acquainted	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Long-Will	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Long-Will	O
-	O
And	O
some	O
others	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
Harry	B-pers
Whitesides	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
you	O
were	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
against	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
these	O
Thief	O
-catchers	O
,	O
who	O
make	O
it	O
their	O
Business	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
People	O
's	O
Lives	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
you	O
pretended	O
that	O
you	O
came	O
in	O
voluntarily	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
48.	O
James	B-pers
Macdowald	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Susan	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
hera	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
sixpence	O
,	O
Dec.	O
27	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bales	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
,	O
in	O
Dr.	O
Mead	O
's	O
Coach	O
from	O
Kensington	O
,	O
to	O
St.	O
Albans	O
-	O
Near	O
Kensington-Gravel-Pits	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Coachman	O
not	O
minding	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
Stand	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Coachman	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Coach-door	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
Money	O
and	O
Watches	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Fright	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
Sir	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
what	O
we	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
red	O
Silk-purse	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
that	O
Purse	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Purse	O
was	O
not	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
then	O
-	O
The	O
Coach	O
glass	O
was	O
half	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bid	O
us	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
demanded	O
our	O
Watches	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
neither	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
your	O
Watches	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
-	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
both	O
Ways	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Highwayman	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
's	O
Servant	O
rid	O
after	O
him	O
-	O
A	O
Ploughman	O
threw	O
his	O
Staff	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
soon	O
after	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
's	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
her	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
Horseback	O
before	O
the	O
Coach	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
rid	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
door	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
Bay's-Water	O
by	O
the	O
Gravel-Pitts	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
demand	O
their	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
my	O
Lady	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
-	O
When	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
they	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Brompton	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
quitted	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Farmer	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Garden	O
-	O
Indeed	O
my	O
Horse	O
tumbled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
just	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
dismounted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
Little-Chelsea	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
in	O
Christmas	O
Week	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
