TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
Country	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1734	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	O
BELLAMY	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1734	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXIV	O
..	O
bl	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BELLAMY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Petman	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Poynz	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fret	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crampthorn	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wetherington	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Langdon	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Aymes	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Coxhall	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Newham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cookery	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Francis	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
John	O
Brown	O
)	O
2	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
a	O
Tea	O
Table	O
,	O
5	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Carraway	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Hebert	O
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Nov	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stoneball	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matthew	O
Hebert	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
Nov	O
,	O
28	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hebert	I-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Younger	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Footman	O
for	O
about	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
's	O
Scrutore	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
mist	O
it	O
last	O
Thursday	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Bread-street	O
:	O
There	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
Mary	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Bread	O
street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
sent	O
my	O
Maid	O
to	O
the	O
Cook	O
's	O
for	O
6	O
Penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Veal	O
-	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
delivered	O
this	O
Ring	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
up	O
safe	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Matthew	O
Hebert	O
,	O
the	O
younger	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stonehall	O
(	O
who	O
lives	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
)	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Till	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
mist	O
Mony	O
before	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stonehall	O
put	O
some	O
more	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Till	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
he	O
mist	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
our	O
Family	O
.	O
William	O
Stonehall	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
3	O
Guineas	O
in	O
his	O
Stocking	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
3.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Thurmond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
October	O
19	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
Beer	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
presently	O
mist	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
escaped	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Tankard	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
offer	O
to	O
resist	O
or	O
run	O
away	O
when	O
you	O
stopt	O
me	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Eyles	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
upon	O
ye	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
short	O
Truncheon	O
under	O
your	O
Coat	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
In	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Truncheon	O
hid	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
Death	O
.	O
4	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
by	O
wilfully	O
and	O
maliciously	O
discharging	O
a	O
Musket	O
loaded	O
with	O
Gunpowder	O
and	O
a	O
Bullet	O
;	O
and	O
thereby	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Bullet	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
Ten	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
set	O
Sentinel	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Chappel	O
Door	O
,	O
at	O
Somerset	B-place
House	I-place
.	O
Hearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
some	O
outrageous	O
Facts	O
upon	O
his	O
Post	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
keep	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
your	O
Butcher	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
mischievous	O
Fellow	O
I	O
proceeded	O
no	O
farther	O
.	O
At	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Richard	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Corporal	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
Regular	O
Relief	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
answered	O
,	O
Relief	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
ye	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Piece	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clubbed	O
his	O
Firelock	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
these	O
Men	O
.	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
Irons	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
alone	O
on	O
his	O
Post	O
till	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
relieve	O
him	O
-	O
Here	O
's	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wastcoat	O
-	O
Here	O
the	O
Bullet	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
third	O
Button-hole	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
-	O
And	O
here	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
the	O
right	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
-	O
As	O
to	O
loading	O
my	O
Piece	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
particular	O
Order	O
-	O
Who	O
came	O
for	O
Relief	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
bring	O
7	O
Men	O
or	O
3	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
Three	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
,	O
Henry	O
Thomas	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	O
Godson	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
I	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Corporal	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
,	O
Pass	O
your	O
Relief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
crowded	O
in	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
strugling	O
my	O
Piece	O
went	O
off	O
-	O
Richard	B-pers
Godson	I-pers
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
relieve	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
Who	O
comes	O
there	O
?	O
The	O
Corporal	O
answered	O
Relief	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
stand	O
off	O
!	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
comes	O
to	O
oppose	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Corporal	O
bid	O
us	O
advance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
Piazza	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
turned	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Row	O
,	O
stand	O
off	O
!	O
or	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
his	O
Piece	O
went	O
off	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
about	O
the	O
Distance	O
of	O
two	O
Firelocks	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
wheel	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
.	O
The	O
Bullet	O
enter	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
Spot	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
club	O
'd	O
his	O
Firelock	O
,	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
honest	O
Man	O
?	O
Godson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
your	O
club	O
'd	O
Fire-lock	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
knock	O
my	O
Comrade	O
down	O
too	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
relieve	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
comes	O
there	O
?	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
Relief	O
.	O
God	O
damn	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
stand	O
off	O
with	O
your	O
Relief	O
-	O
or	O
Row	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
bid	O
me	O
recover	O
my	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
relieve	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
immediately	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
present	O
his	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
it	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clubb	O
'd	O
his	O
Piece	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
thrice	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
third	O
Blow	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Stock	O
of	O
my	O
Firelock	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Blow	O
had	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
Was	O
you	O
under	O
the	O
Piazza	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
Corporal	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
bide	O
in	O
my	O
Place	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Sentry	O
under	O
the	O
Gate-way	O
:	O
The	O
Relief	O
came	O
at	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
who	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answered	O
,	O
Relief	O
.	O
Pass	O
the	O
Relief	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
Piazzas	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
fire	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
bid	O
the	O
Men	O
rest	O
their	O
Firelocks	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bid	O
them	O
recover	O
their	O
Pieces	O
and	O
relieve	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Piece	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
with	O
any	O
Design	O
;	O
but	O
went	O
off	O
while	O
they	O
struggled	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Corporal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
5.	O
Peter	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Porringers	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Soup-Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Punch-Ladle	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
12	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
5	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
6.	O
Susan	B-pers
Strafford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Porringers	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Red	B-place
Lyon-Inn	I-place
at	I-place
Charing-Cross	I-place
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Hughs	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Hughs	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
my	O
Plate	O
always	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
:	O
My	O
Wife	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
Man	O
Hughs	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Closet-Door	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Strafford	O
once	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
suspected	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
I	O
might	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
hear	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
understanding	O
that	O
some	O
Lawyet	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
I	O
could	O
learn	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
sometimes	O
drank	O
a	O
Dram	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
advertised	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
Word	O
was	O
sent	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
after	O
Dinner	O
at	O
Richard	B-pers
Slaters	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Horse	O
shoe	O
and	O
Chequer	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Strafford	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Napkin	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Mrs.	O
Slater	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
some	O
Money	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
privately	O
advised	O
'em	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
2	O
Constable	O
and	O
Charge	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bains	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Landlord	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
next	O
Day	O
that	O
such	O
Plate	O
was	O
Advertised	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
Silk-Dyers	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Barns	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
thence	O
above	O
4	O
Months	O
We	O
went	O
away	O
thro	O
'	O
some	O
Back-Alleys	O
into	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
accidentally	O
met	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
.	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
ye	O
!	O
She	O
asked	O
what	O
Business	O
we	O
had	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
soon	O
be	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Earns	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
She	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
Pet	O
.	O
Hughs	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Crooked-Billet	O
,	O
hard-by	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
she	O
curs	O
'd	O
and	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Son-of-a-Bitch	O
for	O
bringing	O
her	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
Premunire	O
.	O
Peter	O
took	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Tea-Spoons	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
Peter	O
's	O
Lodging	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
.	O
Strafford	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Drawer	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
took	O
this	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
2	O
Porringers	O
and	O
a	O
Punch-Ladle	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
:	O
Then	O
we	O
all	O
took	O
Coach	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
Peter	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
Plate	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Peter	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Plate	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hands	O
.	O
Then	O
Peter	O
's	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
was	O
proved	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
there	O
in	O
confesses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Plate	O
[	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
]	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Charles	O
Sims	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Strafford	I-pers
,	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Strafford	O
had	O
been	O
offering	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Slater	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
to	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Slater	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
advertised	O
:	O
I	O
remembred	O
that	O
Strafford	O
had	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
(	O
I	O
forget	O
upon	O
what	O
Occasion	O
)	O
left	O
Word	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
a	O
Silk-Dyers	O
in	O
Slaughter-street	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
went	O
thither	O
;	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
from	O
that	O
Place	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
going	O
back	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
by	O
Chance	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
defy	O
'd	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
touch	O
her	O
Honour	O
.	O
Look	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
It	O
signifies	O
nothing	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
very	O
Plate	O
which	O
you	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Slater	O
is	O
advertised	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
By-God	O
?	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
Then	O
that	O
Rogue	O
Hughs	O
has	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
fine	O
Scrape	O
.	O
By	O
her	O
Directions	O
we	O
found	O
Hughs	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
5	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
by	O
Holborn	O
Bridge	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
some	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
a	O
moderate	O
Price	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fernell	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
2	O
Spoons	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Strafford	I-pers
.	O
When	O
Hughs	O
first	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Newnham	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Blue-Boar	O
in	O
High	O
Holborn	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
Plate	O
that	O
was	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
by	O
some	O
Relation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
where	O
his	O
Clothes	O
were	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
owed	O
Mr.	O
Newnham	O
some	O
Money	O
for	O
Drink	O
and	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
Mr.	O
Newnham	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
his	O
Box	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
next	O
Day	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
which	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
telling	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Newnham	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Shirt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
Means	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Spoon	O
unperceived	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
sold	O
the	O
Spoon	O
for	O
11s	O
.	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
wanted	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
was	O
hired	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
afterwards	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
Friends	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
Plate	O
to	O
me	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
him	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Necessaties	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
then	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brets	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Dyer	O
,	O
in	O
Slaughter-street	O
,	O
in	O
Spittle-fields	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
.	O
She	O
brought	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
Friends	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Carrier	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
20	O
l.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
refused	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
sometime	O
as	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
otherwise	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Peter	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
7.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Rug	O
,	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
1	O
Bolster	O
,	O
1	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
1	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
William	O
Salter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Lodger	O
;	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
without	O
giving	O
me	O
notice	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
Martha	O
Williams	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Privity	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
8.	O
Edward	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Knee-Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
4	O
Silver	O
Stock-Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Girdle-Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Sleeve-Buttons	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Liger	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
October	O
19	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Liger	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shew-Glass	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
Man	O
might	O
have	O
lent	O
'em	O
:	O
But	O
next	O
Morning	O
my	O
Man	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
Buckles	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Master	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
there	O
was	O
Confederacy	O
between	O
his	O
Servant	O
and	O
mine	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confessed	O
that	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
near-sighted	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
some	O
Buckles	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
my	O
Man	O
opening	O
the	O
Shew-Glass	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
at	O
twice	O
took	O
out	O
several	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
Cousin	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
ordering	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
some	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
some	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Mr	O
White	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Silver	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
villainous	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
encreased	O
my	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
a	O
Brewers	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
presented	O
their	O
Maid	O
with	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
worth	O
20	O
Guineas	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shew-Glass	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
My	O
first	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
together	O
.	O
Her	O
Apprentice	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
her	O
Shop	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Ned	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
A	O
Buckle	O
for	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
for	O
my	O
Stock	O
She	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
'em	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
Thirteen	O
Nights	O
in	O
Fourteen	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Gloucestershire	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ivell	O
.	O
Six	O
or	O
Seven	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
me	O
some	O
old	O
broken	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Ruben	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Fellow-'Prentice	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Burrier	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Day	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
besides	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Number	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
his	O
Number	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Above	O
his	O
Number	O
:	O
That	O
's	O
a	O
little	O
strange	O
!	O
James	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
2	O
Boys	O
were	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
have	O
drank	O
14	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
together	O
.	O
Mr.	O
White	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
invented	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Stories	O
about	O
junketting	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
they	O
have	O
run	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
46	O
Gallons	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Garman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Consider	O
this	O
young	O
Youth	O
-	O
Good	O
God	O
!	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
afore	O
a	O
Justice	O
my	O
Lordship	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
-	O
My	O
Lordship	O
should	O
consider	O
a	O
young	O
Youth	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
Four	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
honest	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
8.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Luelling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Seal	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
Nov.	O
4	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hankerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Gain	I-pers
,	O
November	O
4	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Bedford	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Mob	O
gathered	O
about	O
2	O
Men	O
who	O
were	O
fighting	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
'em	O
.	O
when	O
presently	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
Watch	O
drawn	O
cut	O
of	O
my	O
Fob	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
next	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Hand	O
quite	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
struggling	O
he	O
twisted	O
himself	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
conveyed	O
my	O
Watch	O
away	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
some	O
others	O
assisting	O
me	O
we	O
at	O
last	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
.	O
My	O
Watch	O
indeed	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
which	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gain	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
expect	O
me	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
.	O
Expect	O
ye	O
?	O
I	O
suspected	O
ye	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
found	O
your	O
Hand	O
under	O
my	O
Coat	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
Watch	O
drawn	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Fob	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
himself	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
only	O
discharge	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
beg	O
my	O
pardon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
7	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
Sutling	O
.	O
and	O
Lodging-house	O
at	O
White-hall	O
3	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
when	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
brought	O
me	O
14	O
l.	O
on	O
a	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Farthing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Greencase	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
my	O
Work	O
lay	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
le	O
Grand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
mist	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Ann	O
Dean	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
is	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
trusted	O
him	O
several	O
Hours	O
together	O
in	O
our	O
Garret	O
where	O
our	O
Work	O
both	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
never	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
does	O
he	O
follow	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
sometimes	O
works	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
as	O
a	O
spare	O
Man	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gain	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
feiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
a	O
violent	O
Resistance	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
to	O
thrust	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Constable	O
searched	O
him	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
Occasion	O
for	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
feeling	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'mist	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
found	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
it	O
is	O
stained	O
and	O
snuffy	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
-	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Constable	O
take	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gain	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
matcht	O
exactly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
Size	O
by	O
above	O
an	O
Inch	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gain	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
were	O
compared	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
in	O
every	O
particular	O
.	O
Mr.Hickman	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gain	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
stain	O
'd	O
with	O
Snuff	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gain	O
sent	O
for	O
three	O
more	O
which	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Size	O
and	O
Colour	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gain	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
that	O
Night	O
under	O
the	O
Piazza	O
's	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
it	O
but	O
two	O
Minutes	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Ignoramus	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
9.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Sarah	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
3	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
5	O
Moidores	O
,	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Pierce	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dunkerton	I-pers
,	O
October	O
26	O
.	O
Pierce	O
Clay	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Ostler	O
.	O
My	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Box	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
John	O
Dunkerton	O
's	O
House	O
-	O
This	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Box	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
who	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
appearing	O
to	O
have	O
more	O
Money	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
this	O
Girl	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
clear	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
how	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
wooden	O
Box	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
ample	O
Confession	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
broke	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Vault	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
deny	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
10.	O
James	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Beesly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
31	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Check	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
Octob	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
apart	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Weaver	O
by	O
Trade	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
a-cross	O
White-Chappel	B-place
Fields	I-place
to	O
King	O
David	O
's	O
Fort	O
in	O
Ratclif	O
Highway	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
who	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Check	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Men	O
had	O
made	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
middle	O
Field	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Ditch	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
Soil	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
young	O
Fellows	O
with	O
Pistols	O
,	O
they	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
collar	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
again	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
stand	O
still	O
ye	O
Dog	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
ye	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
searched	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
but	O
nine	O
Pence	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
nothing	O
but	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
Piece	O
of	O
Check	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
;	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
that	O
Casey	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
collar	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
who	O
search	O
'd	O
my	O
Pockets	O
was	O
this	O
Man	O
here	O
,	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
Men	O
at	O
King	O
David	O
's	O
Fort	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
'em	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
I	O
likewise	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
Sun-Tavern	O
Fields	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
out	O
upon	O
Duty	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
look	O
after	O
such	O
Fellows	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
describ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
the	O
Street	O
way	O
-	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
same	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Orange	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
joins	O
to	O
the	O
Field	O
were	O
I	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Description	O
there	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
who	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
afterwards	O
,	O
some	O
who	O
were	O
acquainted	O
with	O
my	O
Workmen	O
,	O
calling	O
at	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Orange	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Men	O
who	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
who	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
New-Goal	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
sure	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
enough	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
nine	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
Information	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Lade	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Companions	O
were	O
in	O
Custody	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Lade	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
When	O
Casey	O
's	O
Sister	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Macdonald	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
Compter	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
likewise	O
found	O
Beesly	O
,	O
who	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
us	O
-	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Macdonald	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
Beesly	O
before	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
two	O
Men	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
I	O
believe	O
were	O
Casey	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Justice	O
Lade	O
's	O
when	O
Macdonald	O
made	O
his	O
Information	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
from	O
thence	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
in	O
Bread-street	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
Beesly	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
came	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
presently	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
Casey	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
one	O
Company	O
.	O
Sutton	O
enquired	O
for	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
some	O
Jail	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
in	O
what	O
Jail	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
could	O
inform	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
Atkins	O
a	O
hint	O
that	O
I	O
fancied	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
Macdonald	O
's	O
Information	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
kept	O
them	O
drinking	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
sufficient	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
apprehended	O
them	O
all	O
Five	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
says	O
Jack	O
Sutton	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
almost	O
two	O
Load	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Birth-day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Dick	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Lane	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
Stepney	O
Fields	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
staid	O
drinking	O
till	O
past	O
seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
Tom-Turd-Man	O
's	O
Hole	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
along	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Beesly	O
,	O
act	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Path	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
who	O
comes	O
t'other	O
way	O
,	O
for	O
here	O
is	O
but	O
one	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
can	O
deal	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
Beesly	O
went	O
behind	O
a	O
Bank	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Stone	O
's	O
throw	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Casey	O
collar	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Six	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
Three	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Half-Pence	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
Trifle	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Check	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Beesly	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
.	O
Casey	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Emery	O
's	O
Garden	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
Beesly	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
kept	O
by	O
one	O
Leadbeater	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
we	O
measured	O
the	O
Check	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
31	O
Yards	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Casey	O
's	O
Sister	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
likewise	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
us	O
17	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Check	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
We	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
in	O
Victuals	O
,	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
Gin	O
;	O
except	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
a	O
Wig	O
-	O
We	O
lived	O
together	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Nurse	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dicks	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Lane	O
against	O
the	O
Blue-Anchor	O
.	O
About	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
remarkable	O
Day	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bonfire	O
before	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Purveyor	O
's	O
Door	O
-	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
-	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Red	O
Coat	O
[	O
pointing	O
to	O
Casey	O
]	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
so	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
Mrs.	O
Dicks	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
towards	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
Macdonald	O
has	O
drank	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Casey	O
twice	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
seeing	O
Beesly	O
there	O
before	O
that	O
one	O
Night	O
.	O
Casey	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
my	O
Name	O
mentioned	O
in	O
Macdonald	O
's	O
Company	O
?	O
Busby	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Casey	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
strange	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
never	O
call	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Name	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
got	O
my	O
Bread	O
honestly	O
by	O
working	O
as	O
Labourer	O
to	O
Bricklayers	O
,	O
and	O
Plaisterers	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Hod	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
Jack	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
in	O
Newgate	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
to	O
treat	O
him	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
great	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
neither	O
-	O
And	O
so	O
meeting	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
Jack	O
Macdonald	O
in	O
Prilon	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Pot	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
in	O
Bread-street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
Bread	O
-	O
He	O
commonly	O
earn	O
'd	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
in	O
the	O
Winter	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
-	O
He	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
,	O
the	O
Builder	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Beesly	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
know	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Savil	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Beesly	O
's	O
Aunt	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Carver	O
and	O
Gilder	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Master	O
failing	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
Labourer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Buckhold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Builder	B-pers
.	O
Beesly	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
Labouring-work	O
for	O
me	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
his	O
Character	O
in	O
general	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Buckhold	I-pers
.	O
When	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
his	O
Mother	O
have	O
1	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Wages	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Bricklayer	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
this	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bryne	I-pers
.	O
When	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
after	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Beesly	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Casey	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
11	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
November	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Derry	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
November	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Ell	O
of	O
Russia	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Novemb	O
.	O
12.	O
Alice	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
12th	O
Day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
my	O
Maid	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
she	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
Hand	O
take	O
the	O
Parcel	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
:	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Tims	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
Parcel	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop-Thief	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
Stick	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
hit	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
,	O
15	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
and	O
Rachel	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
*	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthias	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Huntley	I-pers
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
November	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Alias	O
Rachel	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
.	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Perkins	O
and	O
Macgredy	O
in	O
Sept.	O
1732	O
.	O
Sess	O
.	O
Pap	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
7.	O
.	O
Matth.ias	O
Huntley	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
Shop	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
'em	O
several	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
extreme	O
difficult	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
'em	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Eleanor	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
draw	O
it	O
gently	O
till	O
it	O
fell	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
the	O
Shelves	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
I	O
perceived	O
her	O
to	O
stoop	O
down	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
11	O
d.	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
just	O
without	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
'em	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	O
drop	O
'd	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Eleanor	O
drop	O
the	O
Piece	O
just	O
as	O
my	O
Master	O
turn	O
'd	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Rachel	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Eleanor	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Greathead	I-pers
,	O
October	O
21	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Greathead	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Snow-Hill	B-place
,	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Men	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
buffet	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
thus	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
towards	O
the	O
Conduit	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
within	O
about	O
10	O
Yards	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Hill	O
or	O
going	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Greathead	O
?	O
Witness	O
.	O
You	O
and	O
your	O
Companions	O
were	O
coming	O
up	O
and	O
met	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
twice	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Companions	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ah	O
Lord	O
!	O
ha	O
,	O
ha	O
,	O
ha	O
!	O
William	B-pers
Harmet	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Greathead	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
and	O
Confession	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Robberies	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Were	O
those	O
two	O
concerned	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
taking	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
says	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
reply	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
adds	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
is	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
t'other	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
therein	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
stole	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-street	O
-	O
a	O
Tuck	O
Sword	O
-	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
-	O
another	O
Sword	O
-	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
-	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
-	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
behind	O
the	O
Exchange	O
-	O
another	O
near	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
-	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
-	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
-	O
other	O
Watches	O
-	O
and	O
lastly	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
picked	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Greathead	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Mop-stick-maker	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camblet	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
,	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18	O
,	O
19.	O
John	B-pers
Stepney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Beckles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hasland	I-pers
,	O
October	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Mantuil	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
3	O
Cambrick	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
And	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Parsons	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Martha	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Meacham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Candle-sticks	O
,	O
3	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
1	O
Counterpane	O
,	O
2	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
China	O
Cup	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Banford	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
35	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
Octob	O
.	O
26.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Mary	O
Gordon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
both	O
my	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
House	O
about	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Window	O
;	O
I	O
looking	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
35	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Mary	O
Gordon	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
put	O
4	O
Shillings	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
betwixt	O
my	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sacking	O
Bottom	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
below	O
Stairs	O
-	O
Next	O
Day	O
,	O
a	O
Milk	O
Boy	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
Loss	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
notice	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
Bag	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
26	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Bag	O
-	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
's	O
what	O
's	O
left	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
in	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Dung	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
me	O
near	O
your	O
House	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Months	O
before	O
you	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
Abricots	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Whose	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
John	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
Why	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
my	O
Master	O
Herbert	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
sell	O
Potatoes	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
Boy	O
coming	O
in	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
at	O
Newington-Green	B-place
who	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
the	O
Drink	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
dropt	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
John	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
your	O
Money	O
.	O
Ay	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
lose	O
it	O
I	O
must	O
work	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Woolaston	O
's	O
Entry	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Dung-Cart	O
.	O
Fran	B-pers
Kempthorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
's	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
is	O
here	O
himself	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
receiv	O
'd	O
no	O
Money	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
when	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
convicted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
ago	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
.	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
Particulars	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
supposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
prepar	O
'd	O
to	O
answer	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
12	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
some	O
Time	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
drew	O
Beer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Backmaker	I-pers
.	O
He	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
:	O
Some	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
but	O
indifferent	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
Dung	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Woolaston	O
(	O
a	O
Cow-keeper	O
)	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
lying	O
a-cross	O
a	O
Path	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
besides	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
and	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
24.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tortoiseshell	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Rim	O
,	O
a	O
Patch	O
Box	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Girdle-Buckle	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pocket-Piece	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Copson	I-pers
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
October	O
27	O
.	O
Richard	O
Copson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Coachman	O
for	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Red-Lyon-Inn	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
Drawers	O
in	O
my	O
Bedchamber	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Wickham	O
with	O
the	O
Mayor	O
of	O
Wickham	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
missed	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
3	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
next	O
Day	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
in	O
Vine-Street	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
afterwards	O
having	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cummins	O
's	O
in	O
Queen-Street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Box	O
with	O
my	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
that	O
Box	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Thursday	O
about	O
the	O
Half-Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cipson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Door	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
opens	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
Passage	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
it	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
another	O
Key	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
minded	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
Lock	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Repeating	O
Watch	O
,	O
gilt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
for	O
a	O
Watch	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Watch-Case	O
and	O
5	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Fernandez	I-pers
Nunes	I-pers
,	O
October	O
9	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nunes	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
an	O
Errand-Boy	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
Sea	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
Letters	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
Dover	O
and	O
Harwich	O
describing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
advising	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Harwich	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Booth	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
Having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Bridle-House	O
in	O
Harwich	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
his	O
Shirt	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Ells	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linnen	O
,	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Check	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
,	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
John	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rolls	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
16	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
August	O
18	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Rolls	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
One	O
and	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Hinges	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
flung	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
my	O
Till	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
Half-penny	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Gin	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Buckle	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Stables	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
would	O
buckle	O
up	O
his	O
Shoes	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
Buckles	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
Brags	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
broke	O
my	O
House	O
open	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Hulls	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
off	O
the	O
Hinges	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
the	O
Bellman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
was	O
proved	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
He	O
therein	O
owns	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
before	O
Day-Light	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rolls	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
and	O
stole	O
some	O
Money	O
and	O
a	O
Quart	O
Bottle	O
of	O
distill	O
'd	O
Liquors	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheets	O
and	O
2	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
October	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pridmore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Martha	B-pers
Holcomb	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
and	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
November	O
5	O
.	O
And	O
28.	O
Charles	B-pers
Holcomb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Von	O
Night	O
ven	O
it	O
vas	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Olumb	O
,	O
to	O
de	O
Tree	O
Tun	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
.	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
no	O
go	O
vid	O
me	O
dare	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
go	O
vid	O
mine	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
de	O
Drawer	O
to	O
fesh	O
me	O
some	O
body	O
dat	O
will	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Loshing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bring	O
Mrs.	O
Olcomb	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
tell	O
a	O
me	O
dat	O
she	O
will	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
von	O
vary	O
good	O
Loshing	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
in	O
de	O
same	O
Street	O
-	O
dat	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
is	O
de	O
oder	O
Presonar	O
-	O
Vell	O
,	O
den	O
we	O
drink	O
some	O
Vine	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
she	O
call	O
for	O
de	O
Coash	O
and	O
we	O
go	O
togader	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
in	O
tree	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Olcomb	O
make	O
a	O
me	O
give	O
de	O
Coashman	O
Tree	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Velden	O
ve	O
go	O
up	O
deStair	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
ve	O
all	O
drink	O
togader	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
pay	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Shilling	O
for	O
mine	O
Loshing	O
and	O
de	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Mrs.	O
Olcomb	O
Ten	O
Shilling	O
for	O
her	O
Troubel	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
vid	O
mine	O
self	O
and	O
put	O
mine	O
Breeshes	O
in	O
de	O
Shair	O
and	O
mine	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
Guineas	O
was	O
den	O
in	O
mine	O
Pockate	O
,	O
and	O
de	O
Lequor	O
was	O
got	O
in	O
mine	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fall	O
asleep	O
till	O
5	O
o	O
'	O
de	O
Clock	O
in	O
de	O
Morning	O
.	O
Vell	O
,	O
den	O
Mrs.	O
Olcomb	O
come	O
into	O
de	O
Room	O
(	O
vor	O
de	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
all	O
de	O
Night	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
make	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
and	O
vake	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
Pray	O
you	O
Fellow	O
get	O
up	O
!	O
-	O
Vat	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
in	O
mine	O
Bed	O
?	O
So	O
,	O
I	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
take	O
mine	O
Breeshes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
feel	O
in	O
mine	O
Pockate	O
,	O
I	O
no	O
cou	O
'd	O
find	O
my	O
Snuff-Box	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
come	O
down	O
into	O
de	O
Room	O
;	O
den	O
I	O
dress	O
mine	O
self	O
and	O
go	O
avay	O
but	O
say	O
noting	O
of	O
vat	O
I	O
lose	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
knock	O
'd	O
on	O
dehead	O
,	O
till	O
de	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
de	O
Shustice	O
and	O
get	O
de	O
Varrant	O
for	O
de	O
Conestauble	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
de	O
two	O
Womans	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Olcomb	O
confess	O
before	O
de	O
Shustice	O
dat	O
she	O
take	O
2	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
mine	O
Pockate	O
,	O
and	O
dat	O
I	O
give	O
her	O
de	O
rest	O
.	O
And	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
was	O
bail	O
'd	O
.	O
Vell	O
den	O
Sharles	O
Olcomb	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
say	O
dat	O
if	O
I	O
no	O
prosecute	O
de	O
Vomans	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
de	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Note	O
for	O
tree	O
Guinea	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
no	O
vill	O
do	O
dat	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
de	O
Shustice	O
,	O
and	O
de	O
Shustice	O
commit	O
him	O
to	O
de	O
Bridevell	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rawlins	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Holcomb	I-pers
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
Snuff-Box	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
fetch	O
'd	O
away	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Chairman	O
,	O
and	O
plyed	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
Justice	O
Mitford	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
.	O
Charles	O
Holcomb	O
own	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
Woman	O
a	O
release	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Defeuce	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Holcomb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
-	O
I	O
call	O
him	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
's	O
only	O
my	O
Friend	O
-	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
when	O
the	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
drunk	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
drunk	O
together	O
,	O
a	O
Coach	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
we	O
drove	O
to	O
Catherine-street	O
where	O
we	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
drove	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
I	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
drank	O
3	O
three	O
Shilling	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Punch	O
and	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
:	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
more	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
and	O
promised	O
me	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
cured	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
me	O
a	O
new	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
keep	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
sake	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Go	O
ye	O
nasty	O
lying	O
Toad	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Holcomb	I-pers
.	O
As	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
about	O
leaving	O
his	O
Breeches	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
frightning	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
Indeed	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
oblige	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Heat	O
of	O
his	O
Passion	O
was	O
soon	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
vast	O
deal	O
of	O
Civility	O
passed	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Humour	O
.	O
C	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Holcomb	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
my	O
Door	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
'em	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Bowl	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Bowl	O
-	O
of	O
Arrack	O
Punch	O
,	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Jellies	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
.	O
And	O
indeed	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
-	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
go	O
out	O
about	O
her	O
Business	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
had	O
engaged	O
my	O
self	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
a	O
Doctor	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
there	O
alone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
in	O
Bow	O
street	O
.	O
He	O
Swore	O
and	O
Curst	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
B	O
-	O
but	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Loss	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
No-body	O
than	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
but	O
one	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Staton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Holcomb	O
offer	O
to	O
give	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Note	O
for	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
return	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
go	O
to	O
Jail	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
these	O
four	O
Years	O
;	O
she	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
;	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
civil	O
House	O
it	O
is	O
-	O
as	O
to	O
Robberies	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cleaver	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Tavern	O
and	O
serve	O
her	O
with	O
Wine	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
Civil	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
alone	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
our	O
Porter	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Porter	O
fetch	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Holcomb	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
Pint	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
They	O
ordered	O
the	O
Coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
bid	O
the	O
Porter	O
see	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
beyond	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
but	O
how	O
much	O
further	O
they	O
went	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Cope	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
-	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Years	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
principle	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
any	O
wrong	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
Edmond	B-pers
Holcomb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Charles	O
is	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Chairman	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
Bread	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
Wife	O
-	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Martha	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
may	O
call	O
him	O
Husband	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Avison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
15	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
in	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
29.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Copper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mac	I-pers
Creagh	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Going	O
about	O
Noon	O
from	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
thro	O
'	O
Colston	B-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
next	O
Wild-street	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
was	O
standing	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
prudent	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
the	O
Gold	O
from	O
the	O
Silver	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Guinea	O
in	O
this	O
Pocket	O
,	O
7	O
Shillings	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Pence	O
which	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
spend	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
Mouth	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
Hester	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
put	O
one	O
Hand	O
round	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
t'other	O
-	O
down	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Arm-way	O
about	O
my	O
middle	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
kissing	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
that	O
Pocket	O
where	O
the	O
Silver	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Hand	O
was	O
shut	O
when	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
my	O
7	O
Shillings	O
:	O
I	O
presently	O
examined	O
t'other	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Guinea	O
was	O
gone	O
too	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
young	O
one	O
got	O
that	O
-	O
What	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
Ye	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
old	O
one	O
,	O
Do	O
ye	O
breed	O
a	O
Riot	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
?	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
make	O
'em	O
suffer	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
,	O
take	O
your	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
rightly	O
serv	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
Business	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
a	O
Bawdy-house	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
practice	O
the	O
Law	O
-	O
't	O
is	O
What	O
I	O
was	O
bred	O
to	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Where	O
you	O
never	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
before	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Once	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Margaret	O
.	O
O	O
the	O
Villain	O
!	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
that	O
Day	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
-	O
He	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Obrian	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Macdonnel	I-pers
had	O
sworn	O
my	O
Husband	O
into	O
the	O
Fleet	O
for	O
100l	O
.	O
Now	O
this	O
Fellow	O
comes	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
Michaelmas	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Ye	O
Bitch	O
!	O
ye	O
Irish	O
Bawd	O
!	O
Do	O
you	O
maintain	O
that	O
Bug	O
your	O
Husband	O
?	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Whore	O
your	O
Niece	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
Day	O
to	O
this	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Margaret	O
keeps	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
which	O
I	O
kept	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
Tea	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Niece	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
slopping	O
Hat	O
-	O
this	O
Man	O
looks	O
something	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
Pimples	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
called	O
him	O
Tom	O
Graham	O
-	O
And	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
Provocation	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
them	O
and	O
beat	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
before	O
that	O
Day	O
Sen'night	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
both	O
the	O
Aunt	O
and	O
the	O
Niece	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Burbidge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Fruit-Cellar	O
under	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Macgray	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
abusing	O
them	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
your	O
Husband	O
in	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
you	O
ye	O
old	O
Baud	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Whore	O
your	O
Niece	O
in	O
Newgate	O
before	O
a	O
Week	O
's	O
at	O
an	O
End	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
Headborough	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Grocer	O
's	O
Shop	O
facing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Noise	O
or	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
very	O
modest	O
Women	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Peace-Officer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
one	O
Night	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
-	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
calling	O
all	O
to	O
naught	O
-	O
Bitch	O
and	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
Baud	O
-	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
'	O
em	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
stole	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Plate	O
-	O
But	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
fair	O
,	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
6	O
Years	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Love	O
with	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
30.	O
John	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brackerby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wast-coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
October	O
27	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7	O
,	O
1733	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Croft	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
November	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Mary	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wallaxhall	I-pers
,	O
October	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
John	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Cooms	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
l	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Annet	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
Jane	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
6	O
Napkins	O
,	O
2	O
Knives	O
,	O
3	O
Forks	O
,	O
4	O
Wine	O
Glasses	O
,	O
1	O
Mustard	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Vinegar	O
Crewet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goosetry	I-pers
,	O
November	O
27	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Devil	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	I-place
Temple-Bar	I-place
.	O
He	O
had	O
missed	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
informed	O
that	O
she	O
frequently	O
went	O
out	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Boy	O
to	O
watch	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
dogg	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
-	O
Barns	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
in	O
White's-Alley	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Newton	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
Confession	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tireman	I-pers
,	O
October	O
29	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tireman	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
my	O
Nephew	O
Dawson	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Change	I-place
and	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Day	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
hussel	O
'd	O
about	O
by	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Fellows	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
out	O
of	O
Breath	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Trunkmakers	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
CheapsideI	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
speaking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
a	O
tall	O
Fellow	O
in	O
a	O
Cape-Coat	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
towards	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
;	O
and	O
perceiving	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
about	O
the	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
Passage	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
forward	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
finding	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Fellows	O
that	O
hussl	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
he	O
hipp	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
There	O
goes	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
your	O
Watch	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Cape	O
Coat	O
and	O
red	O
Breeches	O
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
heard	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
presently	O
mended	O
his	O
Pace	O
,	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Nag's-head	O
Tavern-Door	O
.	O
Ye	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
where	O
's	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Presently	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
dropp	O
'd	O
and	O
Beck	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Here	O
is	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
catch	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
all	O
dirty	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Star	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
nothing	O
.	O
W.	O
Beck	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
my	O
Shop-Mates	O
by	O
the	O
Pastrycook	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Cheapside	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Show	O
,	O
a	O
Crowd	O
of	O
Men	O
came	O
thrusting	O
along	O
.	O
Says	O
my	O
Mate	O
,	O
That	O
tall	O
Fellow	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
Cape-Coat	O
looks	O
like	O
a	O
Pick-Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Mob	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
towards	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
too	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
crouded	O
into	O
the	O
Swan	O
Passage	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
thro	O
'	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Cape	O
Coat	O
.	O
I	O
pointed	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
others	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
they	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Joyner	O
's	O
Stand	O
.	O
We	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Nag's-head	O
Tavern	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
that	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Cape	O
Coat	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Man	O
close	O
by	O
who	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
hit	O
against	O
my	O
Foot	O
.	O
I	O
stoop	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Watch	O
fall	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
?	O
Beck	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
both	O
Cape	O
Coats	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
Left	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Right	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
held	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
fell	O
at	O
my	O
Right	O
Foot	O
a	O
Yard	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
likely	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
follow	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
stand	O
quietly	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
throw	O
it	O
away	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
nor	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
suspected	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Cape	O
Coat	O
and	O
red	O
Breeches	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
Men	O
husseled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Mr.	O
Tireman	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
one	O
Way	O
or	O
other	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tireman	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
said	O
those	O
Fellows	O
had	O
been	O
larking	O
about	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
,	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Beck	O
told	O
us	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
Door	O
;	O
my	O
Uncle	O
and	O
I	O
passed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
without	O
minding	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Beck	O
hipped	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
goes	O
the	O
Man	O
up	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
mended	O
his	O
Pace	O
.	O
We	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tireman	O
and	O
I	O
collered	O
him	O
;	O
Beck	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
was	O
near	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
Beck	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
indeed	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Hand	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Beck	O
stoop	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
up	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Legs	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
before	O
it	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
hundred	O
Mob	O
about	O
us	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
drop	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Tireman	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Beck	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
the	O
People	O
gathered	O
about	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
Star	O
Passage	O
,	O
where	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Fellows	O
would	O
have	O
rescued	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
made	O
'em	O
keep	O
off	O
.	O
[	O
Then	O
Beck	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Cape	O
Coat	O
stand	O
.	O
Beck	O
.	O
At	O
my	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Side	O
as	O
the	O
Watch	O
fell	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
else	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
dropt	O
?	O
Beck	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Mob	O
of	O
20	O
People	O
about	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
?	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
charge	O
him	O
?	O
Beck	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
then	O
?	O
Beck	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Star	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Cape	O
Coat	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tireman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Cape	O
Coat	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
body	O
near	O
us	O
when	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
dropt	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Beck	O
!	O
What	O
Business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
Beck	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Cabinet-maker	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
Baldwin	O
's	O
Gardens	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
Inn	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
sets	O
his	O
Horse	O
up	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
goes	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
buys	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Cloth-worker	O
by	O
Trade	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Years	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Copeland	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
Yorkshire	O
Cloth	O
-	O
the	O
last	O
Parcel	O
I	O
bought	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
Lady	O
[	O
Elizabeth	O
Johnson	O
's	O
]	O
House	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
14	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Prejudice	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
Cloth	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
20	O
l.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
38.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rogerson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
118	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Mayor	B-pers
,	I-pers
Commonalty	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Citizens	I-pers
of	I-pers
London	I-pers
.	O
November	O
9	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cheuit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Labourer	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Welch-hall	B-place
under	I-place
Guild-hall	I-place
;	O
we	O
stole	O
the	O
Lead	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
from	O
Welch	O
hall	O
.	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
William	O
Cockson	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
in	O
White-Cross-Street	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cockson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
Lead	O
of	O
Cheuit	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cockson	I-pers
,	O
They	O
both	O
brought	O
Lead	O
together	O
twice	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
blind	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
Cheuit	O
.	O
Col.	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
39.	O
John	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
27	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
Men	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
his	O
Hat	O
before	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
a	O
Whale-bone	O
with	O
Bird-lime	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
out	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
a	O
second	O
and	O
third	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
perceiving	O
then	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
his	O
Whale-bone	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Bird-lime	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Shillings	O
limed	O
together	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
these	O
two	O
Men	O
to	O
catch	O
Birds	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
Whale-bone	O
and	O
Bird-lime	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
George	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hamans	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
27.	O
John	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
another	O
Man	O
into	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
