TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	O
BILLERS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1734	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
,	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXIV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BILLERS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Hardwicke	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Comyns	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sambrook	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Winchester	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burkett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ellery	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Limmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Noah	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dusell	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Micklebourn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wildair	I-pers
,	O
Phil	B-pers
Blanchard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mountany	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prescot	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Malling	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Popping	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
French	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
2.	O
James	B-pers
Sword	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Christian	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
27	O
Pewter	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
Sept.	O
25.	O
Christian	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
About	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Pyed	O
Bull	O
,	O
in	O
May-Fair	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Pewter	O
Spoons	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
sell	O
such	O
Spoons	O
as	O
these	O
for	O
?	O
They	O
are	O
not	O
good	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
2	O
Dozen	O
and	O
2	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
Carnaby-Market	B-place
,	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
got	O
about	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
another	O
Spoon	O
from	O
me	O
there	O
Rolus	O
Bolus	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
People	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
forgotten	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
effegs	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wing	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assault	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Carnaby-Street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hung	O
by	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
May-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
one	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Basket	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
her	O
Spoons	O
were	O
bad	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
no	O
Power	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
a	O
Licence	O
to	O
hawk	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
Spoons	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
May-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
oblige	O
her	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Greenwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Spoon	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
Tin	O
sho	O
Door	O
in	O
Carnaby	O
Street	O
;	O
Mr	O
Wing	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
required	O
to	O
discover	O
his	O
Companion	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Woman	O
first	O
by	O
the	O
Turn-Stile	O
in	O
Band	O
street	O
she	O
sighed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Pyed	O
Bull	O
,	O
an	O
there	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
her	O
of	O
two	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Spoons	O
.	O
What	O
Spoons	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Dozen	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
good	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
Price	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
call	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Gin-shop	O
in	O
Carnaby-Market	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
goes	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
Authority	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
hawk	O
such	O
Goods	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rogues	O
that	O
sells	O
Buttons	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
flew	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
taking	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Spoons	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
See	O
here	O
,	O
you	O
Rogue	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
Spoon	O
,	O
I	O
neither	O
stole	O
it	O
nor	O
is	O
it	O
bad	O
Metal	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
has	O
such	O
a	O
Rogue	O
as	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
John	O
Wing	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
by	O
God	O
she	O
shall	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
Mob	O
gather	O
'd	O
about	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
part	O
more	O
than	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
says	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Spoons	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
touched	O
'em	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
meddled	O
with	O
none	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
Spoon	O
as	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
in	O
Carnaby-Market	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Claghan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
sold	O
two	O
Spoons	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
at	O
my	O
Cellar-door	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
old	O
Spoons	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
dear	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
I	O
stole	O
some	O
Spoons	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Basket	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Cullimore	I-pers
.	O
She	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Pyed-Bull	O
at	O
May	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
sworn	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
there	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Spoons	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
18	O
or	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Brasier	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
8	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
He	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
from	O
Midsummer	O
to	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gaskin	O
-	O
He	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
my	O
Service	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gaskin	I-pers
.	O
He	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
3	O
Months	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
mist	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hodgins	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
8	O
Years	O
in	O
Colonel	O
Skelton	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
likewise	O
served	O
Captain	O
Lendsey	O
,	O
Captain	O
Strode	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
Godard	O
;	O
who	O
have	O
all	O
trusted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
all	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
3.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
piece	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Cambletee	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Delahaze	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
privately	O
,	O
September	O
21	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Delahaze	I-pers
.	O
About	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
smoaking	O
my	O
Pipe	O
at	O
an	O
opposite	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Indian	B-place
Queen	I-place
in	O
Crispin-street	B-place
;	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
an	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Delahaze	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
Cambletee	O
for	O
a	O
Gown	O
:	O
We	O
agreed	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
cut	O
off	O
12	O
Yards	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
felt	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
with	O
her	O
left	O
Hand	O
for	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
fumbled	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
with	O
her	O
right	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
was	O
hiding	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Cambletee	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
Purse	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
laid	O
down	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
earnest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
for	O
her	O
Purse	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
presently	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Companion	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Cambletee	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
an	O
Entry	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
piece	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
that	O
Entry	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Everton	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
wash	O
our	O
Entry	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
behind	O
our	O
half	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
perhaps	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
Susan	O
Everton	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Gery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement-Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stone	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Doll	O
's	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Sattin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Gause	O
Handkerchief	O
embroider	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Sarcenet	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Par	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Shirts	O
and	O
one	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
6	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Par	O
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Par	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Nurse	O
to	O
my	O
Boy	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
4	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
3	O
Weeks	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
Sick	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
her	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Companions	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Wild-Court	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
that	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Thing	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
mine	O
which	O
I	O
claim	O
'd	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
yours	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
Things	O
which	O
you	O
little	O
think	O
of	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
had	O
been	O
Pledged	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
particular	O
a	O
little	O
Doll	O
's	O
Gold-Ring	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
Moidore	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
as	O
they	O
hung	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
tookout	O
a	O
Guinea	O
-	O
I	O
lost	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
l.	O
or	O
14	O
l.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
Door	O
.	O
My	O
Ware-house	O
is	O
up	O
Stairs	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
with	O
the	O
Nursery	O
.	O
When	O
a	O
Customer	O
comes	O
to	O
redeem	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
common	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Bag	O
in	O
which	O
are	O
several	O
sorts	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
empty	O
at	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
Door	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
what	O
we	O
want	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
have	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
carry	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
there	O
till	O
we	O
come	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
these	O
Opportunities	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Par	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
Son	O
John	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
Rose-Alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Wild	O
Passage	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
They	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Frederic	O
Lucan	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
and	O
Hook	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
Cornelian	O
Seals	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
1	O
Stone	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
I	O
Horn-handl'ed	O
Hanger	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Horn-handled	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
studded	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Shagreen	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frederic	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
,	O
September	O
25	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lucan	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
Things	O
being	O
missing	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
for	O
a	O
Character	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
none	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
the	O
next	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
word	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Red-lion	B-place
Street	I-place
in	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Coach	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
'Scritore	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Back	O
door	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
two	O
Feet	O
,	O
which	O
look	O
'd	O
as	O
if	O
some	O
Man	O
had	O
dropt	O
from	O
the	O
Garden	O
Wall	O
.	O
Near	O
the	O
Stable	O
Door	O
I	O
found	O
other	O
Footsteps	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
green	O
Purse	O
with	O
some	O
Gold	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
had	O
been	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
hurry	O
.	O
The	O
Bar	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
Window	O
was	O
forced	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
supposed	O
the	O
Rogue	O
made	O
his	O
way	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
thing	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
Cane	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
Window	O
.	O
The	O
Cane	O
was	O
remarkable	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
had	O
an	O
Iron	O
Thimble	O
upon	O
it	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
Ferril	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Coach	O
to	O
my	O
Friends	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
,	O
to	O
consult	O
with	O
them	O
what	O
Method	O
I	O
had	O
best	O
to	O
take	O
for	O
discovering	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
Daily	O
Post	O
.	O
But	O
about	O
Two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
Nobody	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
Candle	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
to	O
light	O
myself	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Back	O
Door	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Thomas	O
Brooks	O
,	O
a	O
Foot-boy	O
(	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Servant	O
)	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
all	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
Candle	O
.	O
Lord	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
Brooks	O
,	O
Call	O
your	O
Nanny	O
,	O
for	O
our	O
John	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
-	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
some	O
ugly	O
Tricks	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Draught	O
on	O
the	O
Bank	O
for	O
137	O
l.	O
besides	O
what	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
'Scritoire	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Marks	O
of	O
Feet	O
under	O
the	O
Garden	O
Wall	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
Door	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
propt	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cane	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
She	O
mist	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
for	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Back-door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
one	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Jobb	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
drawing	O
a	O
Hanger	O
upon	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
Things	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
3	O
Cornelian	O
Seals	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
some	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Case	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Shoe-Snuff-Box	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
pair	O
of	O
Steel	O
Tweezers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
of	O
Gunpowder	O
.	O
-	O
Other	O
Things	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Order	O
of	O
my	O
Beadle	O
Tim	O
.	O
Micklewright	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Micklewright	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
our	O
Watch-house	O
at	O
Holborn-Bars	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
stick	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
troublesome	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
Hand-cuffed	O
and	O
searched	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
this	O
Hanger	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
in	O
the	O
Handle	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
And	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
were	O
found	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Case	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
and	O
Hook	O
,	O
four	O
Seals	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
in	O
the	O
top	O
-	O
the	O
Haft	O
of	O
a	O
Knife	O
with	O
a	O
Nail	O
fastened	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
up	O
crooked	O
,	O
which	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
pick	O
Locks	O
with	O
;	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Tin	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Havanna	O
Snuff	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Gunpowder	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ingleton	I-pers
.	O
One	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Shop	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Assistance	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
drawn	O
a	O
Dagger	O
upon	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
big	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
help	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
Watchmen	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
-	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
Bob	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Watchman	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
What	O
d	O
'ye	O
call	O
'em	O
's	O
-	O
your	O
Trinkle-me-trankles	O
-	O
your	O
Thingumee	O
's	O
for	O
Ladies	O
,	O
[	O
the	O
Hook	O
and	O
Chain	O
]	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
four	O
Seals	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
'em	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
-	O
some	O
sort	O
of	O
Snuff	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
Devil	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
no	O
Snuff	O
,	O
but	O
Gun-powder	O
.	O
-	O
Marsh	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Snuff-shop	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
telling	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
frightened	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
was	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
unruly	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
Hand-cuff	O
him	O
.	O
Those	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
have	O
sworn	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
word	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Forsithe	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Snuff	O
Shop	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Landlord	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
along	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
being	O
aware	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
scratch	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dropt	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
knock	O
over	O
the	O
Shins	O
,	O
and	O
stooping	O
down	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Knife	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Gunpowder	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
Devally	O
Snuff	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Seymore	I-pers
.	O
About	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Forsithe	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
(	O
James	O
Francis	O
)	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Valuables	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
about	O
five	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
Three	O
half-pence	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
saw	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Times	O
were	O
much	O
mended	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
Hanger	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
flourished	O
o'er	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
shewed	O
us	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seals	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
for	O
such	O
Things	O
to	O
France	O
and	O
Spain	O
.	O
We	O
begun	O
to	O
question	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
appeared	O
very	O
much	O
ruffled	O
,	O
asked	O
us	O
what	O
Business	O
we	O
had	O
with	O
his	O
Way	O
of	O
Dealing	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
slice	O
of	O
his	O
Hanger	O
?	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
draw	O
in	O
earnest	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
danger	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Pistol	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
charged	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
Things	O
before	O
we	O
part	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
surprized	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Watchman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Forsithe	O
went	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
smoaking	O
a	O
Pipe	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Forsithe	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Forsithe	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Pinch	O
of	O
Snuff	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
return	O
shall	O
I	O
make	O
you	O
for	O
this	O
Favour	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
your	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
welcome	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
half-penny	O
Dram	O
.	O
There	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
Hanger	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
an	O
Appearance	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
such	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
charge	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
500	O
l.	O
value	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Kensington	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
must	O
provide	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
safety	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
load	O
his	O
Pistol	O
somewhere	O
else	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
frightening	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
desisted	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Seymour	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
suspected	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
shewed	O
us	O
all	O
his	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
treat	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
Quartern	O
.	O
Seymour	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
deals	O
with	O
for	O
those	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
Abroad	O
with	O
foreign	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
Why	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
those	O
are	O
English	O
Goods	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Words	O
he	O
grew	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Hanger	O
,	O
asking	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
slice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
prevented	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Chain	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Snuff-shop	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
6.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Bell-Metal	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Titus	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
William	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Violin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
3	O
Stock	O
2	O
Rollers	O
and	O
3	O
Shams	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cockram	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
12.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cockram	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
both	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
Room	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Whitfield	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	O
Devereux	B-place
Court	I-place
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Goods	O
locked	O
in	O
my	O
Trunk	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
my	O
Trunk	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Lock	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
again	O
with	O
new	O
Nails	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
(	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
)	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
1	O
of	O
my	O
Shams	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Rollers	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
's	O
(	O
another	O
Pawn	O
broker	O
's	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
2	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
Shams	O
and	O
a	O
Stock	O
.	O
-	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
Stone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pledged	O
these	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
Publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
our	O
Room	O
was	O
always	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
his	O
Trunk	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
then	O
in	O
Devereux	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
left	O
his	O
Trunk	O
locked	O
fast	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
perhaps	O
when	O
a	O
Friend	O
has	O
staid	O
late	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Lodger	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
leaving	O
my	O
House	O
I	O
removed	O
the	O
Trunk	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
light	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Head	O
was	O
so	O
full	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Affairs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
enquire	O
into	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
Witnesses	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
They	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
30	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Damaree	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Fir	O
Timber	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
August	O
13	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Piece	O
of	O
Fir	O
Timber	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Theobald	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Theobald	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Aug.	O
13	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Fir	O
Timber	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
August	O
13	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Carpenters	O
and	O
Joiners	O
Joint	O
Stock	O
.	O
Word	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
our	O
Compting-house	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Timber	O
was	O
in	O
Earle	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Pieces	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Mark	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Triangle	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
-	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Timber	O
from	O
Stangate	B-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Lambeth	B-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
'em	O
at	O
Earle	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
At	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
times	O
I	O
bought	O
about	O
Ten	O
Load	O
of	O
Timber	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Mark	O
was	O
disfigured	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
from	O
25	O
s.	O
to	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Load	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
of	O
Hammersmith	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kensington	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
about	O
14	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
much	O
more	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Theobald	I-pers
.	O
We	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Timber	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
some	O
Pieces	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
were	O
at	O
Earle's-Court	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
Piece	O
there	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
Smith	O
was	O
building	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
P	O
T	O
and	O
the	O
Mark	O
is	O
fair	O
to	O
this	O
Hour	O
.	O
We	O
bought	O
600	O
l.	O
worth	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
38	O
s.	O
a	O
Load	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Smith	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
25	O
s.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
some	O
Timber	O
at	O
White-hall	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
the	O
Green-house	O
at	O
Batter-sea-Field	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
of	O
that	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Pieces	O
at	O
Earle's-Court	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
L	O
P	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Marks	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
scratch	O
'd	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Letters	O
undistinguishable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
Discovery	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Smith	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Pieces	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Waterman	O
.	O
Looking	O
farther	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Theobald	O
's	O
Timber	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
In	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
the	O
Mark	O
was	O
cut	O
out	O
with	O
an	O
Adz	O
-	O
Mine	O
cost	O
me	O
31	O
s.	O
a	O
Load	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
29	O
s.	O
a	O
Load	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
Less	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
up	O
Timber	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
for	O
these	O
Gentlemen	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
these	O
Pieces	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Salt	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Marks	O
not	O
being	O
Plain	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Knives	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Francia	I-pers
,	O
October	O
13	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
belong	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
Abraham	O
Francia	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Wine	O
Merchant	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
good	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Rosanna	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Valiant-Trooper	O
in	O
Beer-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Why	O
upon	O
these	O
Plates	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Three-Tuns	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Quaker	O
's	O
Tavern	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
who	O
apprehended	O
her	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Francia	O
is	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
that	O
Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
put	O
another	O
Man	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Ann	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Porridge-pot	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hamp	I-pers
,	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hamp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	B-place
in	O
Featherstone-Street	B-place
,	O
in	O
Bunhill-Fields	B-place
;	O
the	O
Pri-had	O
worked	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
from	O
the	O
17th	O
to	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
my	O
Porridge-pot	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
about	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
after	O
my	O
Pot	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
12.	O
Ann	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
23	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
13.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Craig	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
14.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Lively	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Vane	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
commonly	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Vane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
last	O
Instant	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
Playhouse	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Piazza	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Lord	O
Vane	O
a	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Red	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Black	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
bidding	O
my	O
Lord	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
2d	O
Witness	O
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
the	O
Play-house	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
my	O
Lord	O
Vane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Piazza	O
's	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
desir	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Morgan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
marry	O
'd	O
into	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
ever	O
stept	O
upon	O
English	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Pepper-box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
Eliz	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
New-street	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
her	O
Mistress	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Name	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Orgars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
a	O
Knife	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Loft	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pellit	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Martin's-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
hurt	O
my	O
Ancle	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
Vinegar	O
,	O
to	O
bathe	O
it	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Bread	O
and	O
Butter	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
refus	O
'd	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
did	O
as	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
rub	O
my	O
Leg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Butter	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
supt	O
already	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
damning	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
ill	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Bitch	O
and	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
like	O
her	O
Sister	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
provoke	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
throw	O
something	O
at	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
Case-knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
struck	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
holding	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Betty	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
cut	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
?	O
He	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
!	O
you	O
have	O
cut	O
him	O
indeed	O
!	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Christ	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
!	O
-	O
His	O
Caul	O
hung	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
a	O
Watchman	O
call	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
came	O
and	O
dress	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
advise	O
with	O
another	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
some	O
Sage-Tea	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
Night	O
-	O
He	O
died	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marriot	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
fell	O
upon	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
contradict	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Abdomen	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
Inches	O
from	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
and	O
rather	O
below	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Orifice	O
was	O
so	O
large	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Portion	O
of	O
the	O
Caul	O
hung	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
very	O
Deep	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Intestines	O
and	O
large	O
blood	O
Vessels	O
were	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
vast	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
.	O
Between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
another	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
approv	O
'd	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
visited	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
again	O
at	O
11	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
about	O
5	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
Case-knife	O
-	O
'T	O
is	O
round	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
,	O
but	O
something	O
sharp	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
pointed	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Wound	O
exactly	O
answers	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Knife	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marriot	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
the	O
Wound	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Knife	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
you	O
made	O
the	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
present	O
but	O
you	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Loft	I-pers
,	O
besides	O
my	O
self	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
either	O
you	O
or	O
she	O
that	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Pellit	O
's	O
Book-keeper	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
when	O
the	O
accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
her	O
self	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
flung	O
the	O
Knife	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
what	O
reason	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
so	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
another	O
time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kindleside	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
was	O
then	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
offered	O
any	O
rudeness	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
often	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
commonly	O
the	O
aggressor	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
Insolent	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
something	O
that	O
displeased	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
gave	O
way	O
;	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
shutting	O
his	O
Door	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
Scolding	O
and	O
calling	O
him	O
names	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
Mischief	O
one	O
time	O
or	O
another	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
never	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
rude	O
?	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
No	O
-	O
Indeed	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
kiss	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
farther	O
-	O
Another	O
time	O
she	O
threw	O
an	O
Oystershel	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
cut	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
behind	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
bled	O
pretty	O
much	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kindleside	O
.	O
Between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
one	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Porter	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
Convulsions	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
will	O
you	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
O	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
fear	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
escape	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
she	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
twice	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
forced	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Chair	O
-	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Whore	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
no	O
rudeness	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
violent	O
passionate	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
often	O
threatned	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
question	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
aggravated	O
me	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Knife	O
(	O
that	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
)	O
among	O
the	O
foul	O
Knives	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
bloody	O
like	O
rust	O
,	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
rising	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
blade	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
conceive	O
how	O
such	O
a	O
Case	O
Knife	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
pointed	O
,	O
but	O
round	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
,	O
could	O
be	O
thrown	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
pierce	O
through	O
a	O
strong	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
far	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
:	O
Which	O
made	O
me	O
ask	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
about	O
that	O
particular	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
so	O
quick	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
whether	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
or	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
-	O
The	O
Girl	O
Ann	B-pers
Loft	I-pers
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
come	O
thither	O
without	O
the	O
leave	O
of	O
her	O
Friends	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Witness	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Mischief	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Lord	O
!	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
what	O
shall	O
I	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
Say	O
?	O
Replied	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
What	O
would	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Knife	O
as	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
here	O
me	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
I	O
say	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
because	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Whore	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
confused	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
every	O
word	O
that	O
past	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
that	O
I	O
threw	O
the	O
Knife	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Marriot	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kindleside	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
had	O
stabb	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
very	O
provoking	O
words	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
Knife	O
or	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Quarrell	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Business	O
-	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
5	O
Inches	O
from	O
the	O
point	O
Red	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
rusty	O
with	O
the	O
Blood	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
gone	O
so	O
deep	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
had	O
only	O
run	O
down	O
so	O
far	O
towards	O
the	O
Handle	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
streaks	O
of	O
Blood	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
so	O
far	O
been	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
drawn	O
through	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
pulling	O
it	O
back	O
through	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Coat	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Blade	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Blood	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
all	O
streak	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
?	O
Guy	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
part	O
intirely	O
Bloody	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
streaky	O
except	O
within	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
of	O
the	O
Handle	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Bloody	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
wet	O
Cloth	O
and	O
rubb	O
'd	O
off	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Red	O
streaks	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
pin	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
that	O
part	O
appear	O
'd	O
bright	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
though	O
the	O
Red	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
rust	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
rust	O
but	O
Blood	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
Dead	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
violent	O
Fits	O
,	O
which	O
held	O
her	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
for	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Hours	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
coming	O
downStairs	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
should	O
find	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
and	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
their	O
Man	O
had	O
cut	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
bleed	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
I	O
directed	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
in	O
Abchurch-lane	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
soon	O
after	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
confused	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
sure	O
enough	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
wo	O
n't	O
tell	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
pay	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
half	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
never	O
worse	O
.	O
Somebody	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
in	O
Bed	O
:	O
By	O
which	O
I	O
guest	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
how	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
my	O
Relation	O
.	O
About	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
a	O
Messenger	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
Kins-man	O
was	O
dying	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
Master	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
Church	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
How	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
by	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
?	O
Do	O
n't	O
ask	O
me	O
questions	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
some	O
words	O
happen	O
'd	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
But	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
catch	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
how	O
was	O
it	O
done	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Uncle	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
speak	O
.	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
Ann	O
Loft	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Knife	O
?	O
Ann	O
Loft	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
Yards	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
rise	O
from	O
the	O
Table	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
?	O
Ann	O
Lost	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
rise	O
up	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
cutting	O
Bread	O
and	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
I	O
too	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
she	O
strike	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
?	O
Ann	O
Lost	O
.	O
No	O
-	O
She	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
it	O
went	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
no	O
ill-will	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Braham	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
often	O
a	O
Quarrelling	O
-	O
One	O
time	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
with	O
some	O
Meat	O
from	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Table	O
,	O
she	O
pitch	O
'd	O
a	O
Knife	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
Servant	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
will	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Lockley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
Person	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
tending	O
to	O
Passion	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
often	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
exprest	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Tenderness	O
and	O
good	O
Nature	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
23	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
Passion	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
quiet	O
young	O
Woman	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Virtuous	O
modest	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
drinking	O
or	O
ill	O
Language	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
.	O
Of	O
a	O
very	O
orderly	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
Just	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
dutiful	O
to	O
her	O
Parents	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
She	O
kept	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
2	O
Sisters	O
from	O
starving	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
And	O
impoverish	O
'd	O
herself	O
by	O
her	O
kindness	O
to	O
her	O
Friends	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
12	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
of	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Temper	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
.	O
Ann	O
Loft	O
,	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
2	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
quiet	O
and	O
good	O
Natur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Passion	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
one	O
Person	O
kills	O
another	O
without	O
a	O
just	O
provocation	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
Murder	O
:	O
And	O
words	O
alone	O
are	O
not	O
a	O
just	O
provocation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
17.	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	O
Sh	O
ppard	O
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-woman	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Ann	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
2	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
2	O
Pillows	O
,	O
2	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Dish	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
hired	O
a	O
Room	O
ready	O
Furnish	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
and	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19	O
,	O
20.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tooly	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Varseller	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
2	O
Sauce-pans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
October	O
10	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
21.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
,	O
September	O
12	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
William	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Kid-Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
privately	O
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Linch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ansell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Eslip	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ansell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Fruit	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Eslip	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Albermarle-street	B-place
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
7	O
Guineas	O
in	O
my	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ansell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sat	O
at	O
my	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
to	O
sell	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
step	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
me	O
up	O
some	O
Walnuts	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
busy	O
with	O
a	O
Customer	O
He	O
staying	O
much	O
longer	O
than	O
was	O
necessary	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
of	O
Walnuts	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
brought	O
half	O
a	O
Bushell	O
in	O
less	O
time	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
somebody	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
kept	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
but	O
he	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Crumpton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Victualling-Cellar	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Meuse	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
hot	O
pint	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
fell	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
wet	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
new	O
Pair	O
.	O
One	O
Macdonald	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Robins	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drank	O
together	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
6	O
Guineas	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
He	O
spent	O
16	O
d.	O
Half-penny	O
in	O
Hot-pots	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
job	O
in	O
Nathan	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
's	O
Cellar	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drank	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Crown	O
by	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
-	O
for	O
he	O
drove	O
a	O
Wheel-barrow	O
with	O
Fruit	O
-	O
Then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
broke	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
planted	O
6	O
Guineas	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
we	O
'll	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
-	O
But	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
White-hall	O
to	O
receive	O
my	O
pay	O
-	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
old	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
new	O
Pair	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
6	O
Guineas	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
rich	O
Man	O
.	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
planted	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Robins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Crompton	O
's	O
Cellar	O
to	O
roast	O
my	O
Goose	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
almost	O
all	O
Night	O
and	O
had	O
planted	O
6	O
Guineas	O
at	O
the	O
Black-horse	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
new	O
Stockings	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Southwark-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
won	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
by	O
tossing	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Halfpenny	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Head	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
knowing	O
the	O
Secret	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
not	O
to	O
discover	O
it	O
-	O
But	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
won	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
Nine	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
up	O
Wal-nuts	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
to	O
shell	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Back-door	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
may	O
come	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Back-door	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
back	O
Stairs	O
that	O
comes	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
into	O
that	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
come	O
down	O
that	O
way	O
to	O
fetch	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
want	O
Water	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
back	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
never	O
open	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
bolted	O
within	O
side	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
24.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
2	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
August	O
30	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
hired	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Week	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
till	O
Bartholomew-tide	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
set	O
his	O
Wife	O
up	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Fair	O
to	O
sell	O
Gin	O
and	O
Black-puddings	O
.	O
But	O
some	O
body	O
stole	O
her	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
24	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
drunk	O
at	O
all	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
give	O
'em	O
Warning	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
their	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
his	O
Wife	O
coming	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
's	O
gone	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
new	O
Stock	O
of	O
Gin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
never	O
darkened	O
my	O
Doors	O
afterwards	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
his	O
Brother	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
must	O
not	O
take	O
such	O
things	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
25.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
October	O
14	O
.	O
Agnes	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
let	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
one	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
a	O
Person	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
After	O
my	O
Daughter	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Price	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
your	O
Daughter	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
where	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
's	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
sorry	O
Husband	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
enquire	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
this	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
Civility	O
Money	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
kind	O
usage	O
to	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
18	O
s.	O
for	O
loss	O
of	O
Time	O
and	O
Expences	O
;	O
and	O
God	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
pay	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
revenged	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
26.	O
Mark	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Carcase	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
27.	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dead	O
Goose	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Richard	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
swearing	O
William	B-pers
Ansloe	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
,	O
abuse	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
him	O
from	O
one	O
to	O
t'other	O
,	O
and	O
strike	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Shins	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pinched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kicked	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
Sinews	O
of	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
Lameness	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
threaten	O
'd	O
if	O
ever	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
live	O
.	O
Whereas	O
in	O
truth	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
assault	O
or	O
abuse	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
break	O
his	O
Shins	O
,	O
or	O
bruise	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
or	O
kick	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
Sinews	O
,	O
or	O
pinch	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
threaten	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
Mischief	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
p.	O
197.	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
p.	O
202	O
.	O
Transportation	O
11.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Isabel	B-pers
Gery	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Dammaree	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Lively	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
SPECIFICK	O
INJECTION	O
or	O
LOTION	O
,	O
Which	O
in	O
Nineteen	O
Years	O
private	O
Practice	O
has	O
cured	O
673	O
Gonorrheas	O
or	O
Claps	O
,	O
(	O
without	O
taking	O
any	O
Medicine	O
by	O
the	O
Mouth	O
)	O
and	O
has	O
kept	O
several	O
Hundreds	O
from	O
Clap	O
or	O
Pox	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convince	O
the	O
World	O
of	O
its	O
Efficacy	O
.	O
IT	O
intirely	O
destroys	O
and	O
carries	O
off	O
all	O
Venereal	O
Contagion	O
,	O
(	O
because	O
it	O
reaches	O
the	O
Cause	O
immediately	O
,	O
which	O
no	O
Medicine	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Mouth	O
can	O
do	O
,	O
being	O
liable	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Food	O
to	O
the	O
Alterations	O
made	O
upon	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Stomach	O
)	O
thereby	O
prevents	O
all	O
the	O
dismal	O
Attendants	O
of	O
impure	O
Embraces	O
,	O
as	O
Inflammation	O
,	O
Scalding	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
Cordee	O
,	O
Phymosis	O
,	O
Paraphymosis	O
,	O
Herniaveneris	O
,	O
or	O
swell	O
'd	O
schirrbous	O
Testicles	O
,	O
Buboes	O
,	O
Gleets	O
,	O
Shankers	O
,	O
dribling	O
of	O
Semen	O
at	O
Stool	O
or	O
Urine	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
,	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
the	O
Pox	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
it	O
saves	O
a	O
Constitution	O
which	O
is	O
too	O
often	O
tore	O
to	O
pieces	O
by	O
harsh	O
Drugs	O
,	O
ill	O
applied	O
by	O
ignorant	O
Dabblers	O
in	O
Sin	O
,	O
Mercury	O
,	O
and	O
Antimony	O
,	O
and	O
spares	O
the	O
nauseous	O
Trouble	O
of	O
swallowing	O
such	O
poisonous	O
Slops	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Confinement	O
those	O
rugged	O
Drugs	O
require	O
;	O
and	O
never	O
fails	O
acting	O
with	O
Safety	O
,	O
Secrecy	O
and	O
Ease	O
,	O
upon	O
Man	O
or	O
Woman	O
,	O
without	O
Confinement	O
or	O
Alteration	O
of	O
Diet	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
old	O
Claps	O
,	O
Shankers	O
,	O
nay	O
if	O
you	O
piss	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Holes	O
,	O
(	O
old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
careous	O
Ulcers	O
in	O
the	O
Uraethra	O
or	O
Prostatiae	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Weakness	O
from	O
Nocturnal	O
or	O
Self-pollution	O
,	O
and	O
Whites	O
in	O
Women	O
,	O
when	O
every	O
thing	O
else	O
is	O
left	O
off	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
long	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Cockburn	O
's	O
Opinion	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
publick	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
see	O
People	O
as	O
bold	O
in	O
Iniquity	O
as	O
ever	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequents	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
really	O
the	O
common	O
Methods	O
of	O
Cure	O
are	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
least	O
Punishments	O
attending	O
it	O
;	O
witness	O
the	O
vast	O
Numbers	O
of	O
fine	O
Youth	O
,	O
both	O
Male	O
and	O
Female	O
,	O
daily	O
ruin	O
'd	O
,	O
nay	O
rotten	O
before	O
ripe	O
,	O
who	O
seldom	O
or	O
never	O
recover	O
the	O
Injury	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
oftner	O
their	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Fault	O
than	O
the	O
Distemper	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
run	O
longer	O
without	O
hurting	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
than	O
when	O
stopt	O
by	O
violent	O
or	O
frequent	O
Purging	O
Pills	O
,	O
Bolusses	O
,	O
Electuaries	O
,	O
Balsamick	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
and	O
lastly	O
,	O
Astringents	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
not	O
.	O
Simple	O
Colds	O
breed	O
many	O
Diseases	O
,	O
and	O
simple-Claps	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
generally	O
managed	O
,	O
I	O
affirm	O
,	O
lays	O
not	O
only	O
a	O
Foundation	O
for	O
the	O
Pox	O
,	O
but	O
Gout	O
,	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Leprosy	O
,	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
King	O
's	O
Evil	O
and	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
whatever	O
People	O
think	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
:	O
Therefore	O
I	O
can	O
no	O
longer	O
prevail	O
with	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
with-hold	O
so	O
useful	O
a	O
Remedy	O
from	O
my	O
fellow	O
Creatures	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
daily	O
imposed	O
upon	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
publick	O
Prints	O
and	O
private	O
Practice	O
,	O
by	O
People	O
who	O
generally	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
a	O
human	O
Body	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Operation	O
of	O
Medicine	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
Patient	O
does	O
,	O
but	O
uses	O
such	O
or	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
,	O
because	O
their	O
Master	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
or	O
such	O
a	O
Book	O
taught	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
generally	O
so	O
unconscionable	O
are	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
with	O
killing	O
Men	O
by	O
a	O
longed	O
winded	O
Cure	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
must	O
entail	O
Misery	O
upon	O
Posterity	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
lose	O
their	O
unjust	O
Gain	O
.	O
To	O
convince	O
the	O
World	O
this	O
is	O
published	O
for	O
a	O
general	O
Good	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Rich	O
may	O
chuse	O
,	O
Desipiantur	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
sold	O
at	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
ample	O
Directions	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
's	O
,	O
a	O
Watch-maker	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Rummer	O
Tavern	O
James-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
where	O
any	O
Country	O
or	O
Seafaring	O
People	O
may	O
be	O
supplied	O
with	O
Quantities	O
,	O
sending	O
a	O
Line	O
directed	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
Post	O
paid	O
.	O
People	O
who	O
want	O
Help	O
,	O
or	O
are	O
tired	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Pox	O
and	O
Apothecaries	O
Slops	O
,	O
may	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
without	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Antimony	O
or	O
Salivation	O
:	O
One	O
Bottle	O
of	O
this	O
will	O
prevent	O
many	O
Claps	O
,	O
and	O
generally	O
cures	O
a	O
common	O
one	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
keep	O
many	O
Years	O
in	O
any	O
Climate	O
.	O
Ask	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wash	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
wrap	O
'd	O
and	O
seal	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
This	O
never	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
publick	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
could	O
I	O
have	O
rendered	O
it	O
so	O
extensively	O
useful	O
for	O
Mankind	O
without	O
publishing	O
.	O
A	O
Speedy	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
ITCH	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George	O
's	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
is	O
Sold	O
,	O
A	O
WATER	O
which	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
ITCH	O
,	O
or	O
Itching	O
Humours	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
offensive	O
Scent	O
;	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
approved	O
by	O
many	O
Years	O
Experience	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
Prepared	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
PLACE	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
The	O
true	O
Essence	O
or	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
both	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
most	O
excellent	O
in	O
all	O
Degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
great	O
Elixir	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
called	O
Daffey	O
's	O
Elixir	O
,	O
truly	O
prepared	O
from	O
the	O
best	O
Ingredients	O
,	O
very	O
useful	O
in	O
all	O
Families	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Half-Pint	O
.	O
