TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1735.	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
WILLIAMS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1735	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
M.DCC.XXXV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Stafford	B-pers
Briscoe	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Durnford	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
George	B-pers
Eden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tindall	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lutkins	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whiteway	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Truby	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Fonace	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
Dennis	B-pers
Morgue	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Duhammel	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hodgins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorowgood	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Errington	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
,	O
Bladwell	B-pers
Peyton	I-pers
,	O
1.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Sejourne	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
silk	O
Tissue	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
silk	O
Brocade	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
silk	O
Damask	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Lone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lowel	B-pers
Chessey	I-pers
.	O
October	O
9	O
.	O
and	O
3.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
silk	O
Tissue	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
October	O
,	O
24	O
.	O
Perrin	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
and	O
Wake	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
October	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Manly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Calico	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
November	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Peter	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
pair	O
of	O
Kid	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bunting	I-pers
,	O
November	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
7.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Guinea	O
Red	O
Wood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crosier	I-pers
,	O
November	O
11	O
.	O
And	O
8.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
twenty	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
in	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Guilty	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Pepper	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Tea	O
Tongs	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Damask	O
Shoes	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
three	O
Towels	O
,	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Pinners	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pumps	O
,	O
November	O
7	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cock-Lane	B-place
,	O
West-Smithfield	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
my	O
Closet	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
my	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
made	O
November	O
the	O
tenth	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
proved	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Alex	B-pers
Rathe	I-pers
broke	O
open	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Cock-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
(	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
)	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
Thomas	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
in	O
George-Alley	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
for	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Whitehead	O
melted	O
all	O
the	O
Plate	O
down	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Tea	O
Tongs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
Constable	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
-	O
A	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
having	O
had	O
his	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Williams	O
,	O
Isaacson	O
,	O
and	O
Gulliford	O
(	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
and	O
G.	O
Holderness	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
Enquiy	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
too	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
abed	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
in	O
Black-boy	O
Alley	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
.	O
We	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Women	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
Perceiving	O
a	O
loose	O
Board	O
in	O
the	O
Floor	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Wax	O
Candle	O
,	O
a	O
Tinder	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
Iron	O
Instruments	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Mills	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
open	O
any	O
Door	O
in	O
England	O
-	O
This	O
with	O
the	O
Claw	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
wrench	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
with	O
the	O
Round	O
Hole	O
is	O
to	O
put	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Bolt	O
to	O
force	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
Accomplices	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
had	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
but	O
one	O
Night	O
longer	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
milled	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
jamm	O
'd	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
Alexander	B-pers
Rathe	I-pers
.	O
Indeed	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
Friend	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
buried	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
done	O
for	O
two	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Lawrence	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
Room	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Keeper	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
Lawrence	O
carried	O
us	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
and	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
turn	O
Evidence	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
some	O
that	O
will	O
swear	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Mills	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
Room	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
whose	O
Evidence	O
John	B-pers
Chickley	I-pers
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
10.	O
Ann	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
alias	O
Walker	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baccett	I-pers
,	O
October	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baccett	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
Women	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
'em	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
like	O
a	O
Maid	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
dismist	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Hind-Court	B-place
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
soon	O
found	O
my	O
Mistake	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
trea	O
ed	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Tiff	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Landlady	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
another	O
Tiff	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
before	O
with	O
a	O
Captain	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
part	O
Owner	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
fell	O
a	O
Sleep	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
waked	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
to	O
Pay	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
Pay	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
true	O
enough	O
-	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
nothing	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
(	O
except	O
three	O
Pence	O
)	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Company	O
over	O
Night	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
She	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
merry	O
free	O
Girls	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
some	O
Gold	O
and	O
a	O
Gilt	O
Metal	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
fashion	O
'd	O
Tweezer	O
Case	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
'em	O
again	O
So	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Tiff	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
Advertise	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Tweezer-Case	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
the	O
Tweezer-Case	O
.	O
I	O
Advertis	O
'd	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
again	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
Woman	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
it	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
left	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Why	O
Madam	O
,	O
Says	O
I	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
laid	O
the	O
Money	O
down	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
your	O
Security	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
the	O
Tweezer	O
Case	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
another	O
Tiff	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
But	O
where	O
's	O
the	O
Case	O
Madam	O
?	O
-	O
What	O
Case	O
!	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
?	O
-	O
Aye	O
but	O
the	O
Tweezer-Case	O
,	O
Madam	O
-	O
Lord	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Tweezer-Case	O
-	O
Why	O
Madam	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
leave	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
the	O
Tweezer-Case	O
?	O
I	O
swear	O
Sir	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
meant	O
the	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
read	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
;	O
but	O
D	O
-	O
the	O
Bitch	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
shall	O
never	O
sting	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
her	O
bring	O
the	O
Case	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
truly	O
the	O
Case	O
was	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
.	O
Why	O
Madam	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Bite	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
give	O
ye	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
the	O
Case	O
!	O
-	O
Aye	O
,	O
but	O
Sir	O
I	O
paid	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
Watch-Case	O
.	O
Nay	O
Madam	O
if	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Case	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
far	O
off	O
as	O
ever	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
has	O
cost	O
me	O
three	O
times	O
more	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
Case	O
than	O
ever	O
the	O
Case	O
was	O
Worth	O
.	O
And	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
no	O
more	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
with	O
myself	O
I	O
might	O
chance	O
this	O
Woman	O
to	O
Eternity	O
,	O
about	O
my	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
afterwards	O
I	O
received	O
100	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
away	O
75	O
l.	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
a	O
Whim	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Head	O
to	O
call	O
once	O
more	O
for	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
goes	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Madam	O
mighty	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wondring	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
for	O
my	O
Case	O
,	O
Well	O
,	O
have	O
ye	O
got	O
it	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
Aye	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
but	O
shall	O
we	O
not	O
drink	O
first	O
-	O
With	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
have	O
a	O
Tiff	O
of	O
punch	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Punch	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
Maid	O
fetch	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
gave	O
Madam	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
Change	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
change	O
it	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
but	O
sha	O
n't	O
we	O
have	O
t'other	O
Tiff	O
.	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
No	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
yes	O
but	O
we	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
join	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
forward	O
to	O
join	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
in	O
another	O
Tiff	O
.	O
I	O
tasted	O
it	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
strong	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
all	O
Brandy	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
loved	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Stiff	O
it	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Cholic	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
stay	O
'd	O
so	O
long	O
that	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
leaning	O
over	O
my	O
Chair	O
with	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
She	O
pulled	O
her	O
hand	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Gold	O
in	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
parcel	O
of	O
Money	O
to	O
carry	O
along	O
the	O
streets	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
Night	O
.	O
Do	O
ye	O
think	O
I	O
'll	O
let	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
Gold	O
about	O
ye	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
-	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
fall	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
and	O
lose	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
think	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
it	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
must	O
bear	O
the	O
blame	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
you	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
But	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
a	O
Reason	O
for	O
Picking	O
my	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Why	O
Dovee	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
now	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
rob	O
you	O
of	O
this	O
Money	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
as	O
safe	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
assure	O
you	O
I	O
keep	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
House	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
-	O
One	O
Night	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
by	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
left	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
with	O
a	O
100	O
l.	O
Bank	O
Note	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Madam	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
but	O
ye	O
sha	O
n't	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
stay	O
much	O
longer	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
your	O
Watch	O
too	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
by	O
good	O
luck	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
Watch	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
I	O
continued	O
telling	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
threatned	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
that	O
should	O
silence	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
I	O
expected	O
some	O
Mischief	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
before	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
Soldier	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
when	O
People	O
would	O
not	O
conform	O
to	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
by	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
ha	O
n't	O
you	O
made	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
your	O
Punch	O
yet	O
?	O
get	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
?	O
And	O
so	O
she	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
tossed	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cane	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
disabled	O
with	O
Drinking	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
defend	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
very	O
sick	O
I	O
lay	O
a	O
Bed	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
again	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
within	O
her	O
Doors	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Tweezer-Case	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Parrot	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Slut	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Affair	O
with	O
him	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
one	O
to	O
offer	O
him	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
likewise	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
little	O
Baudy-Ken	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
Ale	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
the	O
Tweeser	O
Case	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
discover	O
all	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Eccleston	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Mistress	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
eighth	O
of	O
October	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
a	O
Woman	O
into	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
two	O
Tiffs	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Punch	O
was	O
out	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Hat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
But	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
Coffee-Room	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
nor	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
afterwards	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
Hind	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
forward	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
standing	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
Water	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cane	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
Nevil	O
's	O
Alley	O
in	O
Fetter	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
parting	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
one	O
thousand	O
Pound	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
that	O
Night	O
's	O
Work	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
the	O
honourable	O
Court	O
to	O
judge	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
does	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
keep	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
watch	O
without	O
Doors	O
and	O
not	O
within	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
Disturbances	O
-	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
-	O
once	O
indeed	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Trifling	O
Affair	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
's	O
losing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Reputation	O
has	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Hill	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
a	O
poor	O
Watchman	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
House-keeper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
trifling	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
Why	O
she	O
does	O
keep	O
a	O
-	O
Bawdy-house	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
-	O
at	O
Ratcliff-Cross	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
Boalled	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Proecutor	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
twenty	O
two	O
Guineas	O
with	O
her	O
last	O
Night	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
Alphonso	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
,	O
Ticket-Porter	O
in	O
Castle	O
Yard	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Gentlewoman	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
Oranges	O
and	O
Lemons	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wash	O
and	O
nurse	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
my	O
Bread	O
honestly	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
no	O
Disorders	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
lived	O
very	O
quiet	O
and	O
sedate	O
,	O
and	O
orderly	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
one	O
Door	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
occupy	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
paid	O
me	O
honestly	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Menick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
ago	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
for	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
Rum	O
,	O
and	O
Oyl	O
,	O
and	O
Soap	O
,	O
and	O
Vinegar	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Langford	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
She	O
keeps	O
a	O
common	O
notorious	O
Bawdy-house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
any	O
such	O
Disorders	O
there	O
?	O
Langford	O
.	O
I	O
speak	O
the	O
common	O
Report	O
;	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
me	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
a	O
Bawdy-house	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Charles	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Carcass	O
of	O
a	O
Goose	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
,	O
September	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	O
G	O
fford	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
twenty-five	O
Play-house	O
Tickets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
0	O
d.	O
November	O
12	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Plumb	I-pers
,	O
November	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Mary	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Trott	I-pers
,	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trott	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	B-place
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
one	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
throwed	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
fuddled	O
into	O
the	O
Bargain	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
nothing	O
but	O
one	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
for	O
my	O
fourteen	O
Shilings	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
15.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
pearl	O
Necklace	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Pound	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
October	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16	O
,	O
17.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Arabella	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Arabella	O
,	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18	O
,	O
19.	O
Ann	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
alias	O
Gough	B-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
fourteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Hardland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
November	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20	O
,	O
21.	O
Ann	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
October	O
18	O
.	O
Henry	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
Country-man	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
this	O
Town	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Quarters	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
meaning	O
no	O
harm	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
upon	O
these	O
two	O
Women	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Earl	B-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
,	O
in	O
Drury	B-place
lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
House	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fire	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
.	O
I	O
grew	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
coming	O
away	O
.	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
like	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
me	O
with	O
them	O
an	O
Hour	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
helped	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
disorderly	O
Dealings	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
did	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
took	O
up	O
their	O
Coverings	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
what	O
Ware	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
would	O
needs	O
examine	O
mine	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Punch	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
Drams	O
,	O
we	O
drank	O
three	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
Silver	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
Gold	O
in	O
my	O
Fob	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
knocked	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Landlady	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
pretending	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
my	O
Quarters	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
one	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
before	O
I	O
mist	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Fob	O
.	O
Landlady	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
People	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
sure	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
see	O
you	O
righted	O
.	O
But	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
a	O
contrary	O
way	O
to	O
lose	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Man	O
hearing	O
me	O
complain	O
of	O
losing	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Countryman	O
?	O
And	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
tumbled	O
down	O
,	O
near	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
swore	O
and	O
called	O
us	O
all	O
to	O
Naught	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
three	O
Women	O
all	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Maid	O
and	O
another	O
disorderly	O
Creature	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
Ann	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
asleep	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Hamburgh	O
Coffee	O
house	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
had	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
Allen	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
Allen	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
Bed	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
us	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Bed-fellow	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
Creatures	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
Searching	O
about	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
Four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
hid	O
between	O
a	O
Board	O
and	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
these	O
particulats	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
22.	O
William	B-pers
Mackenny	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Satcher	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
10	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Satcher	O
.	O
My	O
Horse	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Ground	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
lost	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
Harrow	O
on	O
the	O
Hill	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Horse	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hired	O
Grass	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Horse	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
23	O
George	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gatward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
7l	O
.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
Nov.	O
13th	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at-night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gatward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Milk-man	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Land	O
of	O
Promise	O
in	O
Hoxton	B-place
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
Ten	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Kingsland-Road	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
behind	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24	O
John	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
seventy	O
yards	O
of	O
Sarcenet	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Sirr	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
Nov.	O
18th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sirr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Sarcenet	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Hey	O
Master	O
!	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Channel	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
Joshua	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
behind	O
St.	O
Clements	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Running	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
throw	O
the	O
pieces	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
roll	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Offence	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
five	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
They	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
very	O
Honest	O
,	O
till	O
may	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
greatly	O
surprised	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
25.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Batley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sarchel	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
thirty	O
four	O
Guineas	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
17th	O
.	O
John	O
Watson	O
.	O
This	O
Thomas	O
Jordan	O
keeps	O
a	O
Lodging	O
House	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	B-place
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
at	O
Mr	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
told	O
Jordan	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
my	O
Bed	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
there	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
Jordan	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
Candle	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
that	O
I	O
undrest	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Breeches	O
under	O
the	O
Pillow	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
Bed	O
.	O
My	O
Money	O
was	O
sew	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Fob	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
pretending	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
grip	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
cryed	O
,	O
Let	O
go	O
ye	O
Old	O
Dog	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
your	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
pulled	O
them	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
Jordan	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Coat	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have-gone	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
I	O
that	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
ragged	O
ars	O
'd	O
Beast	O
before	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Su	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Jordan	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
five	O
Hours	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
squabbled	O
about	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
-	O
Next	O
Day	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Breeches	O
-	O
Jordan	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
drunk	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Jordan	O
is	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
poor	O
Man	O
he	O
is	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
knows	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Breeches	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
be	O
dead	O
hearted	O
,	O
poor	O
thing	O
!	O
For	O
when	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
hurt	O
ye	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Claymor	I-pers
alias	O
Climer	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
October	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sibbalds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gallon	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
Gallon	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Orlebar	B-pers
Gostelow	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
November	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Robert	B-pers
Swanell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hannah	B-pers
Baugh	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
December	O
3	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Baugh	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
this	O
Boy	O
,	O
James	O
Dun	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Toy-shop	O
in	O
Pall-mall	B-place
,	O
and	O
tore	O
off	O
my	O
Hood	O
and	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
snatched	O
off	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
James	O
Dun	O
.	O
This	O
Gentlewoman	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
Mistresses	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
King's-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
home	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
us	O
all	O
up	O
Spring	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Pallmall	O
he	O
snatched	O
off	O
her	O
Hood	O
with	O
his	O
Left-hand	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hat	O
with	O
his	O
Right	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
near	O
Hedge-lane	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Waters	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
her	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
them	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
Buckley	O
,	O
a	O
Chairman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
Chair	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Gate	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rush	O
by	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Pall-mall	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
black	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
toss	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
sprung	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Waters	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Malen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
near	O
the	O
Opera	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Baugh	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Hood	O
and	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
are	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Lappets	O
that	O
were	O
tied	O
under	O
my	O
Chin	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tore	O
the	O
rest	O
off	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Hat	O
close	O
at	O
his	O
Feet	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Hat	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
others	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Escape	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
take	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Thief	O
.	O
-	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
six	O
Years	O
ago	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
near	O
Dunstable	O
in	O
Bedfordshire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
then	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Sibly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
Husbandry	O
Business	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
these	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
late	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
Guards	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
30.	O
Burton	B-pers
Brace	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Peter	B-pers
Bardin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
five	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
December	O
2	O
.	O
Peter	O
Bardin	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
at	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
going	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
Lady	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
attacked	O
me	O
turning	O
out	O
of	O
Hemming	B-place
's	I-place
Row	I-place
.	O
Your	O
Money	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
quick	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Horses	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
Coach	O
-	O
Some	O
Silver	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
satisfied	O
,	O
demanded	O
what	O
I	O
meant	O
by	O
trifling	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
more	O
Money	O
.	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
some	O
Copper	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
swore	O
it	O
was	O
Silver	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
demanded	O
what	O
Money	O
the	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
That	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
a	O
Lady	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
she	O
sat	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
,	O
the	O
Window	O
being	O
drawn	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
by	O
light	O
distinguish	O
the	O
Sex	O
.	O
His	O
Companion	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
drew	O
that	O
Window	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
towards	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drove	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Bardin	O
.	O
Indeed	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Moon-light	O
:	O
But	O
opposite	O
to	O
us	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
clearly	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Face	O
.	O
A	O
Face	O
,	O
I	O
well	O
remembred	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
hundred	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
what	O
place	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
Dress	O
exactly	O
.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
next	O
Day	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Lyon	O
in	O
Russel	O
street	O
.	O
Thence	O
to	O
the	O
Theatre	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
singled	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
Sir	O
!	O
Then	O
a	O
Constable	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
himself	O
,	O
much	O
less	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
So	O
we	O
called	O
another	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
conveyed	O
to	O
Justice	O
Mitford	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
him	O
examined	O
.	O
Nothing	O
would	O
he	O
confess	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Devil	O
-	O
Then	O
I	O
recollected	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
Bullets	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vanbrackle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bardin	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
side	O
I	O
sat	O
,	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
drawn	O
up	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
pulled	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
three	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-Pence	O
,	O
or	O
five	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
I	O
forget	O
which	O
,	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bardin	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
where	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Player	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lady	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
Jealous	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
Rival	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
carried	O
on	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
slightly	O
at	O
the	O
Yellow-Lion	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Capt	O
.	O
Mitford	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Pistol	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
Gun-powder	O
and	O
two	O
Bullets	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
under	O
my	O
Arm	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
,	O
Coachman	O
.	O
Driving	O
along	O
Hermitage	O
Row	O
with	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Lady	O
in	O
my	O
Coach	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
hired	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
stop	O
Coach	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
ye	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
was	O
drawn	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
pulled	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Lyon	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
Four	O
Guineas	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
were	O
then	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
receive	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
they	O
kept	O
an	O
Eye	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
them	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Kings	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
followed	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
twelve	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Lyon	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
two	O
Persons	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
(	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
's	O
Steward	O
)	O
coming	O
in	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Bardins	O
Description	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Men	O
must	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Play-house	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Bardin	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
100	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
A	O
Message	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
Drury-lane	O
Play-house	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
be	O
bound	O
to	O
raise	O
him	O
100	O
l.	O
If	O
Mr.	O
Bardin	O
would	O
not	O
Prosecute	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
speak	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bardin	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
house	O
by	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Box	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
an	O
Hour	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
looked	O
wishfully	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
reaching	O
over	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
mistaken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Rose-Tavern	O
in	O
Bridges-street	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
from	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
till	O
Four	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
bett	O
with	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
go	O
to	O
King	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
there	O
between	O
Three	O
and	O
Four	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
sooner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
since	O
Michaelmas-last	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
an	O
Estate	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Ship	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
Houses	O
in	O
Walworth	O
)	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
John	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
nine	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
off	O
being	O
a	O
Drawer	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Goosetry	O
left	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
nine	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Oylman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
eighteen	O
Months	O
,	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
begun	O
with	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
purchasing	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Estate	O
.	O
Ralph	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Brother	O
in-law	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
bound	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
extreamly	O
well	O
in	O
that	O
Service	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
,	O
We	O
were	O
four	O
Years	O
Fellow-servants	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Goosetry	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Goosetry	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
Servant	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
better	O
Opinion	O
than	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
engaged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sea	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Woodford	O
,	O
a	O
Captain	O
of	O
an	O
India	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
on	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
31.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fortune	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wastcot	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Velvet	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Top	I-pers
,	O
October	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32	O
,	O
33.	O
Lydia	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
seven	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
Coat	O
,	O
two	O
other	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Punch	O
Ladle	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
fifteen	O
Plates	O
,	O
three	O
Water-plates	O
,	O
four	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Warming-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Fender	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
November	O
3	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
who	O
had	O
pawned	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Harrison	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-Broker	O
in	O
Mansel	O
street	O
,	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
went	O
to	O
Harrison	O
's	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
Harrison	O
refused	O
to	O
produce	O
them	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
paid	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
paid	O
two	O
Pound	O
,	O
sixteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pence	O
for	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Water-plates	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
then	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
Harrison	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
,	O
except	O
he	O
brought	O
more	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
obtained	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
taking	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shewing	O
Harrison	O
the	O
Warrant	O
,	O
he	O
notwithstanding	O
would	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
open	O
his	O
Drawers	O
,	O
nor	O
suffer	O
them	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
very	O
Goods	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
had	O
seen	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
35.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
alias	O
Blake	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sarcenet	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Heaters	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
36.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
two	O
pound	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
one	O
pound	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Goodridge	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
October	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
37	O
,	O
38.	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Pell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
alias	O
Richard	B-pers
Slee	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sambrook	I-pers
,	O
September	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
39.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seventeen	O
pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
fixt	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hawkswell	I-pers
,	O
October	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brine	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
November	O
8	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41	O
,	O
42.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hog	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Luke	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
alias	O
Gimblet	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
43.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
Charles	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
45.	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
seven	O
Pound	O
Leaden	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wetherell	I-pers
,	O
November	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46.	O
Frances	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Langborn	O
Tingge	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Earings	O
,	O
a	O
Callimanco	O
Gown	O
,	O
eleven	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
November	O
13	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
no	O
Persons	O
then	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
aged	O
fifteen	O
Years	O
,	O
by	O
shutting	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
cold	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Falkner	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Dyer	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
keeping	O
her	O
from	O
March	O
the	O
twenty	O
fifth	O
till	O
November	O
the	O
seventh	O
following	O
,	O
without	O
Fire	O
,	O
sufficient	O
Meat	O
,	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
necessary	O
to	O
nourish	O
and	O
preserve	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
which	O
Necessaries	O
,	O
she	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
twenty	O
fifth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
seventh	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
miserably	O
perished	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Falkner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Roll	B-place
's	I-place
Buildings	I-place
in	O
Fetter	B-place
lane	I-place
.	O
A	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
Lady-Day	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
three	O
Daughters	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
the	O
eldest	O
,	O
Charlotte	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
and	O
Anna	O
Maria	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
youngest	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
fifteen	O
Year	O
's	O
old	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
till	O
November	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
died	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Maid	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
miss	O
Victuals	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
it	O
went	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
Door	O
to	O
be	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
almost	O
starved	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
Wife	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
or	O
Butter	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
complained	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
no	O
Victuals	O
for	O
two	O
Days	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
Liver	O
.	O
I	O
willing	O
to	O
examine	O
into	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
peeped	O
through	O
a	O
Slit	O
in	O
the	O
Partition	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Miss	O
Dony	O
[	O
Dorothy	O
]	O
sitting	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
Miss	O
Charlotte	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
standing	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
trembling	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
Bread	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Meat	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
another	O
time	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
pickled	O
Pork	O
for	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Pork	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
cold	O
Liver	O
,	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
my	O
two	O
Fingers	O
.	O
When	O
her	O
Mother	O
gave	O
her	O
Victuals	O
,	O
she	O
commonly	O
used	O
to	O
eat	O
it	O
cautiously	O
;	O
but	O
eating	O
this	O
Liver	O
more	O
eagerly	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
knocked	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Hussy	O
!	O
how	O
you	O
cram	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
expostulate	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
using	O
her	O
Child	O
thus	O
?	O
Falkner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
once	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
lying	O
Scoundrel	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
such	O
an	O
Answer	O
,	O
for	O
excepting	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
civil	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
ever	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
-	O
The	O
Deceased	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Apothecary	O
to	O
attend	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
any	O
of	O
our	O
Family	O
called	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
was	O
-	O
Her	O
Mother	O
had	O
a	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
without	O
a	O
Bedstead	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
locked	O
in	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
?	O
Falkner	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
April	O
and	O
November	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
Carpet	O
,	O
or	O
Matt	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
?	O
Falkner	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Charlotte	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
?	O
Falkner	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
was	O
not	O
she	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
?	O
Falkner	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
help	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
the	O
Cloth	O
-	O
The	O
Deceased	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Beer	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
Water	O
-	O
When	O
she	O
first	O
came	O
she	O
looked	O
something	O
better	O
than	O
when	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
though	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
she	O
was	O
vastly	O
thin	O
,	O
and	O
emaciated	O
:	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
she	O
looked	O
like	O
an	O
Anatomy	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
Skin	O
drawn	O
over	O
her	O
Bones	O
-	O
I	O
looked	O
another	O
time	O
when	O
she	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cold	O
Cabbage	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
might	O
not	O
she	O
have	O
had	O
Meat	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
you	O
looked	O
?	O
Falkner	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Miss	O
Doney	O
dined	O
first	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
-	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
Charcoal	O
dust	O
Tub	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
her	O
Garret	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
this	O
Tub	O
my	O
Maid	O
used	O
to	O
hide	O
Victuals	O
for	O
her	O
-	O
One	O
Day	O
a	O
Roll	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
Iron	O
was	O
thrown	O
over	O
from	O
the	O
Roll	O
's	O
Buildings	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
Maid	O
to	O
butter	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Dust	O
Tub	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Girl	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
eat	O
it	O
greedily	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Children	O
work	O
?	O
Falkner	O
.	O
Doney	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Needle	O
,	O
but	O
Charlotte	O
did	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
House-work	O
.	O
Q	O
You	O
say	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
?	O
Did	O
not	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Week	O
before	O
her	O
death	O
)	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
Charlotte	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Shew	O
.	O
Falkner	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
time	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
Deceased	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
her	O
death	O
?	O
Falkner	O
.	O
My	O
Journey-man	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
dangling	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
hung	O
on	O
with	O
Wires	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Falkner	I-pers
.	O
In	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
asked	O
my	O
Maid	O
for	O
Victuals	O
-	O
Once	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
come	O
from	O
my	O
Closet	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Bread	O
-	O
We	O
used	O
to	O
put	O
Victuals	O
for	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
Dust	O
Tub	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
any	O
Victuals	O
did	O
she	O
eat	O
it	O
?	O
A.	O
Falkner	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
cram	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
would	O
she	O
have	O
done	O
so	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
ready	O
to	O
starve	O
.	O
A.	O
Falkner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
peeped	O
through	O
the	O
Crevice	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
give	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Beef	O
-	O
and	O
Pork	O
-	O
and	O
Cabbage	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
sufficient	O
.	O
Q	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
locked	O
up	O
?	O
A.	O
Falkner	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Miss	O
Dony	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Basket	O
Woman	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Meat	O
,	O
Miss	O
Charlotte	O
used	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
Door	O
while	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Expence	O
of	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
?	O
A.	O
Falkner	O
.	O
The	O
Parish	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
Parish	O
?	O
A.	O
Falkuer	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
Girl	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
Miss	O
Nanny	O
was	O
a	O
dying	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Funnel	O
who	O
likewise	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Miss	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Answer	O
,	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
dead	O
!	O
Mrs.	O
Funnel	O
,	O
clapt	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
ye	O
wicked	O
Devils	O
!	O
are	O
ye	O
not	O
ashamed	O
to	O
starve	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
death	O
?	O
The	O
Thing	O
was	O
soon	O
noised	O
about	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Searchers	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
their	O
Opinion	O
,	O
starved	O
to	O
death	O
-	O
The	O
last	O
Victuals	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
was	O
two	O
Months	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pinned	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
for	O
fear	O
her	O
Sister	O
should	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
-	O
The	O
Searchers	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Bed	O
was	O
very	O
clean	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
thick	O
enough	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
complain	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
of	O
her	O
keeping	O
the	O
Child	O
without	O
sufficient	O
Food	O
?	O
A.	O
Falkner	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Miss	O
,	O
looks	O
very	O
poorly	O
,	O
is	O
she	O
not	O
well	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
eats	O
more	O
than	O
Doe	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
begged	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
because	O
her	O
Mother	O
would	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
sometimes	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Miss	O
Nanny	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
Girl	O
.	O
and	O
if	O
your	O
Mother	O
beats	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
wonder	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
you	O
cry	O
.	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
my	O
Mamma	O
stuffs	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
Mouth	O
when	O
she	O
eats	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Falkner	O
We	O
mist	O
Victuals	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
was	O
locked	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
always	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
Victuals	O
whenever	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
put	O
Victuals	O
under	O
the	O
Dust	O
Tub	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
her	O
eat	O
it	O
greedily	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
peeped	O
through	O
the	O
Crack	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
her	O
standing	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Doee	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
with	O
boiled	O
Pork	O
,	O
and	O
Turneps	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
give	O
her	O
Turneps	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Pork	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
Meat	O
before	O
I	O
looked	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
hard	O
Roll	O
in	O
our	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Dust	O
Tub	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
eat	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Mother	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
her	O
Sisters	O
have	O
locked	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Mary	O
Scot	O
,	O
But	O
the	O
Girl	O
has	O
complained	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
starved	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
her	O
Mother	O
keep	O
the	O
Victuals	O
?	O
Mary	O
Scott	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
?	O
Mary	O
Scot	O
,	O
The	O
Kitchen	O
Door	O
was	O
-	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
not	O
the	O
Girl	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
?	O
Mary	O
Scott	O
Yes	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
to	O
wash	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
got	O
at	O
the	O
Victuals	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
durst	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
her	O
Mother	O
should	O
beat	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Son	O
Charles	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
(	O
between	O
thirteen	O
and	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
lock	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
too	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
complain	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
Bread	O
and	O
Water	O
.	O
Q	O
Why	O
did	O
she	O
lock	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Mary	O
Scott	O
Because	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
twice	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
a	O
Jeweller	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
I	O
nursed	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
other	O
Children	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
a	O
Month	O
old	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
above	O
thirteen	O
Years	O
Old	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
Healthful	O
.	O
When	O
their	O
Father	O
Sir	O
Geo	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
dyed	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
last	O
August	O
)	O
they	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
their	O
Mother	O
who	O
then	O
lived	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
High-Cross	O
-	O
Sir	O
George	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thorn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
lived	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
on	O
Twelfth-Day	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
.	O
Her	O
Mother	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
Eats	O
and	O
Drinks	O
and	O
Sleeps	O
Well	O
.	O
In	O
March	O
following	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
.	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Beggar	O
and	O
very	O
thin	O
and	O
Poor	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
healthy	O
plump	O
Girl	O
before	O
.	O
She	O
complain	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
nor	O
her	O
belly	O
full	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
Eat	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Starved	O
.	O
Q	O
Were	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Circumstances	O
reduced	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Sir	O
George	O
?	O
Sus	O
n	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
:	O
But	O
while	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
Children	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
then	O
behaved	O
as	O
a	O
Mother	O
should	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr	O
Elleker	O
,	O
who	O
married	O
a	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Sir	O
George	O
's	O
?	O
Susan	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
When	O
Charles	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
left	O
his	O
Mother	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
Boarded	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Elleker	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
paid	O
for	O
maintaining	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Buxton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Holloway	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Freake	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Freake	O
found	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Ounces	O
of	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Cordial	O
Draught	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holloway	O
.	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Body	O
much	O
distempered	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
might	O
proceed	O
from	O
Natural	O
Causes	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
from	O
want	O
Food	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
always	O
shewed	O
the	O
like	O
Favour	O
and	O
Affection	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
other	O
Sister	O
.	O
The	O
deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Food	O
as	O
we	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Victuals	O
was	O
never	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
lay	O
with	O
Charlotte	O
on	O
a	O
good	O
warm	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
warmest	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Indeed	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Bedstead	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
double	O
thick	O
Cloth	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
look	O
'd	O
thin	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
ill	O
Usage	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
F.	O
nor	O
his	O
Wife	O
complain	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
but	O
indeed	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
she	O
looked	O
thin	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
them	O
complain	O
of	O
her	O
pilfering	O
their	O
Victuals	O
till	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
Dead	O
-	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
was	O
my	O
Mothers	O
Husband	O
-	O
My	O
two	O
Sisters	O
lived	O
with	O
Nurse	O
Robinson	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Home	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Sir	O
George	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
reduced	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
had	O
always	O
Victuals	O
enough	O
.	O
The	O
deceas	O
'd	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
she	O
dyed	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Thursday	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
Limbs	O
.	O
My	O
Mamma	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
Mutton	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
some	O
Broth	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
eat	O
three	O
parts	O
of	O
a	O
Bason	O
full	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
we	O
had	O
Tea	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
Charley	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Cold	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Mother	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Ale	O
with	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Sugar	O
in	O
it	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
Ill	O
but	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
dyed	O
at	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Law-Suit	O
between	O
Sir	O
George	O
's	O
other	O
Children	O
and	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
Has	O
your	O
Mother	O
any	O
Estate	O
for	O
Life	O
?	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
We	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
till	O
the	O
Law-Suit	O
is	O
Ended	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
Depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
and	O
added	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
in	O
my	O
Conscience	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
suffered	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
Severity	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
were	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
dyed	O
.	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
my	O
Mother	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
dye	O
because	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
Subject	O
to	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
my	O
Mother	O
fell	O
into	O
Fits	O
when	O
she	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Freake	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Holloway	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
Years	O
in	O
Tottenham	O
;	O
she	O
visited	O
my	O
Family	O
in	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
modestly	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thorn	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
handsome	O
manner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
two	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
visited	O
by	O
Lord	O
Colrain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
most	O
indulgent	O
tender	O
Mother	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
see	O
a	O
more	O
sober	O
and	O
sedate	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
company	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
-	O
'T	O
is	O
an	O
unaccountable	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
Children	O
came	O
home	O
since	O
her	O
Husband	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Circumstances	O
being	O
then	O
reduced	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
more	O
privately	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
.	O
Since	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
lain	O
on	O
the	O
Commonside	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
reduced	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
Straits	O
rather	O
than	O
make	O
her	O
Case	O
known	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
often	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Friday-Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
hers	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
convers	O
'd	O
with	O
.	O
Her	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
drest	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
visit	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
at	O
nurse	O
,	O
and	O
drest	O
plainer	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
no	O
way	O
cruel	O
,	O
angry	O
,	O
or	O
hasty	O
;	O
but	O
meek	O
and	O
tender	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
believe	O
it	O
posible	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
starve	O
her	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Distinction	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
of	O
her	O
Children	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Husband	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
Minister	O
of	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
she	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
was	O
frequent	O
at	O
Divine	O
Offices	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Church	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
respected	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
unkind	O
to	O
her	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
believe	O
she	O
would	O
starve	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
was	O
mightily	O
supriz	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
such	O
a	O
Report	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Apothecary	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Children	O
have	O
been	O
under	O
my	O
Care	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
indulgent	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
sollicitous	O
in	O
enquiring	O
after	O
their	O
Health	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
small	O
Pox	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
partiality	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
discern	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
most	O
her	O
Favourite	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dormer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
twenty	O
Years	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
seventeen	O
Years	O
at	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
frequently	O
visited	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
one	O
Child	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
at	O
nurse	O
till	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Christmass	O
;	O
she	O
often	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
a	O
Concern	O
when	O
she	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
ill	O
-	O
One	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
poor	O
Nanny	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
bad	O
all	O
Night	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
Purging	O
-	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Red-Wine	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
unnecessary	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
48.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Refue	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lerougetell	I-pers
,	O
December	O
3	O
.	O
Edward	O
Lerougetell	O
.	O
Between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stooped	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
He	O
washed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
Business	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
Gun	O
Barrel	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
still	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
kept	O
me	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Countryman	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Jersey	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Green	O
Bank	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
under	O
my	O
Arm	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
slip	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	B-place
the	I-place
Half-moon	I-place
and	I-place
Star	I-place
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
Bible	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
two	O
went	O
to	O
Cards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
Cut	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
Cards	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
mind	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
they	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
Shilling	O
upon	O
the	O
Game	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
won	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
ventured	O
fourteen	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
grew	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
going	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Guinea	O
between	O
my	O
Fingers	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
husseld	O
my	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Guinea	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
jumpt	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Landlady	O
shut	O
the	O
Fore-door	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
should	O
leave	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
accordingly	O
left	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
in	O
Nightingale	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fearing	O
some	O
mischief	O
,	O
shriek	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
Guinea	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lerougetell	I-pers
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Landlady	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
secure	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Woman	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Change	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
's	O
drink	O
to	O
my	O
Reformation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
first	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Landlady	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
drink	O
to	O
his	O
Reformation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
49.	O
Jane	B-pers
Miner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
value	O
four	O
Pound	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
value	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
John	O
Dickson	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
Ale	O
house	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
locked	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
welcome	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
Maid	O
's	O
Bed	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Bed	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
liked	O
that	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
without	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
she	O
undrest	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lie	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Bed	O
;	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
do	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
her	O
part	O
she	O
would	O
stay	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
remedy	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
awaked	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
my	O
Lady	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Breeches	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
them	O
:	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Yard	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
way	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
six	O
Months	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
my	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Mechlin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hallam	I-pers
,	O
by	O
thrusting	O
a	O
Stick	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
and	O
then	O
Died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
be	O
Numberer	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
of	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
Play-house	I-place
under	O
Mr.	O
Fleetwood	O
-	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
my	O
Accounts	O
in	O
the	O
Property-Office	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
at	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Scene-Room	O
where	O
the	O
Players	O
warm	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
-	O
Fronting	O
the	O
Fire	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
long	O
Screen	O
where	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
People	O
may	O
sit	O
.	O
The	O
Play	O
was	O
almost	O
done	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
making	O
Preparation	O
for	O
the	O
Entertainment	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
next	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
high	O
Words	O
rose	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
Stock-Wig	O
for	O
a	O
disguise	O
in	O
the	O
Entertainment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
play	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Wigg	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
for	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
What	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
my	O
Wig	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
more	O
a	O
Rogue	O
than	O
your	O
Self	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
Its	O
a	O
Stock	O
Wig	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
right	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Players	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Wigg	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
deceas	O
'd	O
having	O
found	O
another	O
Wig	O
,	O
he	O
fetched	O
the	O
Wig	O
in	O
dispute	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
your	O
Wig	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
like	O
better	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
begun	O
to	O
comb	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
begun	O
to	O
grumble	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
for	O
a	O
black	O
Guard	O
scrub	O
Rascal	O
,	O
How	O
durst	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
Impudence	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
Wig	O
?	O
The	O
Deceased	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
more	O
a	O
Rascal	O
than	O
your	O
self	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
started	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
full	O
Longe	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
the	O
Stick	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
he	O
looked	O
pale	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
Heel	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Stick	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
it	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
again	O
upon	O
his	O
Heel	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
through	O
his	O
Head	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sink	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
set	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
leaning	O
upon	O
his	O
left	O
Arm	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
Lord	O
!	O
cryed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
cut	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
feel	O
the	O
Ball	O
roll	O
under	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Young	O
Mr.	O
Cibber	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Coldham	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
shew	O
any	O
Concern	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Arne	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
utmost	O
Surprize	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
the	O
Stick	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
further	O
Concern	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
felt	O
of	O
the	O
Eye-Ball	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Dresser	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Comedy	O
player	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Fryday	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Comedy-Wig	O
to	O
play	O
Sancho	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fop	O
's	O
Fortune	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Wig	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Dresser	O
-	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
afterwards	O
waiting	O
in	O
the	O
Hall	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
answered	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
an	O
Impudent	O
Rascal	O
,	O
and	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
can	O
'd	O
for	O
your	O
Impudence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
acting	O
Juba	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
We	O
ca	O
n't	O
play	O
for	O
the	O
Noise	O
you	O
make	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
This	O
Rascal	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Wig	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
Hallam	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
impertinent	O
,	O
but	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
Hallam	O
still	O
refused	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
such	O
little	O
Rascals	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
example	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
drest	O
in	O
Shape	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
undrest	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodford	O
bid	O
me	O
bring	O
down	O
a	O
Scimitar	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Scene	O
Room	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
still	O
between	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
the	O
Settle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
Yards	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
starting	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
sudden	O
Longe	O
(	O
whether	O
stepping	O
or	O
running	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
)	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Reel	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
throwing	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
Settle	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
relent	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
came	O
first	O
into	O
the	O
Scene-Room	O
,	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
ill	O
about	O
a	O
Comedy-Wig	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
soon	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
ill	O
and	O
impertinently	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
that	O
Wig	O
-	O
They	O
went	O
out	O
separately	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fabian	O
,	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
a	O
Farce	O
to	O
be	O
acted	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
advised	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kitchin	O
the	O
Property	O
Man	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
better	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Wig	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
gave	O
another	O
Wigg	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
held	O
out	O
this	O
Wig	O
to	O
shew	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
lik	O
'd	O
it	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
you	O
saucy	O
impertinent	O
Rascal	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
wonder	O
how	O
such	O
a	O
litle	O
Scoundrel	O
dared	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Wig	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Dressing-Room	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Dresser	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
ye	O
prate	O
?	O
And	O
rising	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
Settle	O
,	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
stood	O
stock	O
still	O
,	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Settle	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
my	O
own	O
Eye	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
hurt	O
;	O
he	O
reel	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Who	O
does	O
the	O
Dressing	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
kept	O
,	O
belong	O
to	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
every	O
one	O
a	O
particular	O
Room	O
to	O
dress	O
in	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
who	O
drest	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Dresser	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wig	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Dresser	O
's	O
Name	O
is	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Scene-Room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
like	O
a	O
Pick-pocket	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Wig	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
fetch	O
him	O
the	O
Wig	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wig	O
:	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
another	O
Wig	O
;	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
this	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
change	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
better	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
for	O
taking	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
more	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
than	O
your	O
self	O
.	O
Some	O
other	O
Words	O
passing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rose	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
you	O
little	O
Dog	O
do	O
ye	O
prate	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Blow	O
.	O
He	O
clapt	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
to	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
O	O
'	O
Lord	O
!	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
Eye	O
is	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
fal'n	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
had	O
not	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
Lord	O
!	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
Eye-ball	O
is	O
shev	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
dressing	O
him	O
-	O
He	O
lived	O
'till	O
six	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
.	O
Ellis	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
Wig	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
liked	O
this	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
impudent	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shift	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
his	O
dressing	O
Place	O
)	O
-	O
No	O
more	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
than	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
for	O
calling	O
me	O
Ye	O
impudent	O
Rascal	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
prate	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
rising	O
up	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Longe	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Settle	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
hold	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
People	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
for	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
civil	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
have	O
attack	O
'd	O
me	O
like	O
a	O
Pick	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
lie	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
return	O
'd	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
lie	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
,	O
you	O
lie	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
made	O
one	O
Step	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
ye	O
little	O
Rascal	O
do	O
ye	O
prate	O
?	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Words	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
a	O
push	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
which	O
enter	O
'd	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
like	O
a	O
squashing	O
.	O
He	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
ran	O
down	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
he	O
totter	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
shock	O
'd	O
and	O
frighted	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
power	O
to	O
catch	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
Push	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
still	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
aim	O
at	O
any	O
particular	O
Place	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salway	I-pers
.	O
He	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
Passion	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
a	O
Stick	O
necessary	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Servant	O
?	O
Thomas	O
Salway	O
.	O
Yes	O
-	O
The	O
Deceased	O
stood	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
right	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Which	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
towards	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
pushed	O
?	O
Thomas	O
Salway	O
.	O
His	O
full	O
Face	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
What	O
a	O
passionate	O
Man	O
are	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
Mischief	O
?	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
answer	O
,	O
Good	O
God	O
!	O
What	O
will	O
not	O
a	O
Man	O
do	O
in	O
Passion	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
knows	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
?	O
Thomas	O
Salway	O
.	O
There	O
might	O
be	O
such	O
Words	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Coldham	O
.	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
drest	O
the	O
Deceased	O
-	O
He	O
died	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Stick	O
had	O
passed	O
through	O
the	O
thin	O
Bone	O
that	O
contains	O
the	O
Eye	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Brain	O
-	O
That	O
Bone	O
is	O
extream	O
thin	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
make	O
but	O
little	O
resistance	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
Blow	O
been	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
less	O
fatal	O
Effect	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
astonished	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
should	O
die	O
by	O
such	O
an	O
Instrument	O
-	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
attended	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shewed	O
much	O
Concern	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
all	O
possible	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
friends	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
plaid	O
Sancho	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wig	O
I	O
then	O
used	O
was	O
proper	O
for	O
the	O
