TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
1735.	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	O
BELLAMY	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1735	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BELLAMY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Head	I-pers
/	O
,	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Gowen	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Tunstal	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hoster	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Ann	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
two	O
Plates	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clear	I-pers
,	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Coleshill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sacking	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckels	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4.	O
John	B-pers
Stanning	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
6	O
,	O
7.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joshua	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Mourning	O
Ring	O
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Cellar-man	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
within	O
Bishopsgate	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
Family	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Nell	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
:	O
They	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Ale	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
;	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
Nell	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
is	O
open	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Daggers	I-place
Ale-house	I-place
in	O
Fore-street	B-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Freeman	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
us	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
together	O
till	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
says	O
Freeman	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
We	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
Funny	O
Wedding	O
,	O
You	O
shall	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Nell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Husband	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
lying	O
for	O
Transportation	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Wife	O
and	O
two	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
is	O
half	O
gone	O
with	O
another	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
Coach	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
Hornsey	O
,	O
and	O
Nell	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Freeman	O
and	O
one	O
Allington	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
Freeman	O
bid	O
the	O
Coachman	O
drive	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Sawyers	O
and	O
Hand-and-pen	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
;	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
It	O
signifies	O
nothing	O
talking	O
,	O
We	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
Funny	O
Wedding	O
.	O
To	O
make	O
short	O
of	O
my	O
Story	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
that	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
hardly	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
this	O
Mourning	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
It	O
has	O
tyed	O
us	O
so	O
fast	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
easily	O
untied	O
-	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Ring	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
Coach	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Daggers	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
rustical	O
,	O
and	O
Freeman	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
Hand	O
while	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Ring	O
off	O
my	O
Finger	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
is	O
this	O
what	O
you	O
call	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
?	O
Freeman	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
your	O
Character	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
Several	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Call	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
many	O
score	O
Pounds	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Daggers	O
Alehouse	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
self	O
on	O
a	O
Box	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
dozing	O
,	O
Nell	O
Byrom	O
snatched	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
;	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
mine	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Ring	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
again	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Husband	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
So	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
getting	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
Will	O
Byrom	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Billy	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
married	O
to	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
for	O
Love	O
or	O
Goodwill	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
get	O
what	O
I	O
can	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
it	O
will	O
serve	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
's	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
wants	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
time	O
goes	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
Clocks	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
better	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
occasion	O
for	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Eleanor	O
Byrom	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
courted	O
me	O
seven	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
me	O
that	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Daggers	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
be	O
married	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet	O
and	O
were	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
Doctor	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Wyat	O
.	O
Between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
married	O
this	O
Couple	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
drunk	O
?	O
Wyat	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
neither	O
drunk	O
nor	O
sober	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
brought	O
two	O
sober	O
Men	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Sober	O
!	O
They	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
all	O
Night	O
-	O
Did	O
you	O
perform	O
the	O
whole	O
Ceremony	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Rites	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
?	O
Wyat	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
repeated	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
Wyat	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Advice	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
or	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
as	O
they	O
might	O
think	O
proper	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
omit	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
omitted	O
in	O
several	O
Churches	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Man	O
capable	O
of	O
knowing	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
?	O
Wyat	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
him	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
the	O
odd	O
Six	O
pence	O
.	O
And	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
for	O
a	O
Certificate	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
very	O
well	O
approved	O
of	O
his	O
Choice	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
indicted	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Wives	O
-	O
Officer	O
,	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
Custody	O
-	O
The	O
Woman	O
too	O
may	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Husbands	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
Will	O
Byrom	O
has	O
been	O
dead	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
-	O
And	O
this	O
Will	O
Byrom	O
in	O
Newgate	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
Freeman	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
how	O
he	O
frequented	O
such	O
disorderly	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
such	O
ill	O
Company	O
.	O
8.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Manteuil	O
,	O
ten	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Fitch	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
August	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foxly	I-pers
September	O
2	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Girl	O
was	O
put	O
Apprentice	O
by	O
the	O
Parish	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
John	O
Easton	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
Ten	O
next	O
February	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
Months	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
first	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
the	O
Drawers	O
till	O
my	O
Wife	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
any	O
thing	O
then	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Drawers	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Easton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
twenty	O
nine	O
Pounds	O
in	O
a	O
Spice	O
Box	O
in	O
my	O
Drawers	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Foxley	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
only	O
the	O
Girl	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
my	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
all	O
Night	O
in	O
Moor-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
-	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
Woman	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Girl	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
10.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Duffel	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
,	O
September	O
6	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Getier	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
keeps	O
a	O
Sale-shop	O
,	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Master	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
old	O
Cloths	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
allow	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Ballance	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Master	O
not	O
being	O
there	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
several	O
other	O
Taverns	O
betwixt	O
there	O
and	O
Charing-Cross	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
him	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Chap	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
old	O
Clothes	O
again	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
new	O
ones	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
returned	O
together	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Zach	B-pers
Bohun	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
pretended	O
Master	O
was	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
contrived	O
this	O
Scheme	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
her	O
Clothes	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11	O
,	O
12.	O
Ann	B-pers
Maund	I-pers
and	O
Rachel	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
*	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bonamy	I-pers
,	O
September	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
Sessions	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Will	B-pers
King	I-pers
for	O
robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dearing	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Mob	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
Number	O
6	O
.	O
Page	O
98.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bonamy	I-pers
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
last	O
Friday	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
saying	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
met	O
Rachel	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
who	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
They	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
and	O
led	O
me	O
into	O
an	O
House	O
and	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
three	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
.	O
Then	O
Ann	O
Maund	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
forgot	O
my	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
Quartern	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
returned	O
me	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
hussel	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
thought	O
,	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
mist	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
took	O
Needham	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
Bess	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
said	O
,	O
that	O
Nan	O
Maund	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
bragged	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
the	O
Leather	O
Bag	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
one	O
Williams	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
thither	O
and	O
found	O
Taylor	O
and	O
Maund	O
alias	O
Boyns	O
;	O
Taylor	O
confest	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Maund	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Bag	O
into	O
Williams	O
's	O
Ashes	O
;	O
so	O
Taylor	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
brought	O
hither	O
.	O
Needham	O
.	O
The	O
Bag	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
tumbling	O
with	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Maund	O
.	O
So	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Carnal	O
Copulation	O
with	O
Nan	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
mind	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
upon	O
us	O
.	O
Nan	O
Taylor	O
is	O
more	O
in	O
favour	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
in	O
our	O
place	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
never	O
troubled	O
your	O
Court	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
now	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
never	O
shall	O
again	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
13.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Quentry	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Jane	B-pers
Leg	I-pers
*	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Slowrach	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Child	O
)	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Skirt	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
:	O
And	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
William	B-pers
Scarcity	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sail	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gaffney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
August	O
14	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Long-Acre	B-place
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Fire	O
happened	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
Croud	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Vine	O
Tavern	O
I	O
was	O
hussel	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
beset	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
.	O
My	O
right	O
Arm	O
was	O
held	O
up	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
close	O
behind	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
Hand	O
on	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
pushing	O
me	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
Watch	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Fobb	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Breeches	O
were	O
prodigious	O
tight	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
right	O
Hand	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
Skirts	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
my	O
Arm	O
down	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Hand	O
out	O
and	O
turned	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
that	O
posture	O
I	O
seized	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
your	O
Watch	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
Watch	O
.	O
Then	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
handed	O
it	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
your	O
Companions	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Character	O
as	O
your	O
self	O
-	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
raise	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
ye	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
readily	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
taunt	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
suffer	O
for	O
scandalizing	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
vertue	O
of	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
hand	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
speak	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Or	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
near	O
me	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Near	O
ye	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
prodigiously	O
crouded	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Watch	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Long	O
Acre	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Coat	O
was	O
then	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
the	O
Croud	O
,	O
I	O
buttoned	O
my	O
Coat	O
on	O
purpose	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
,	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
lost	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Vine	O
.	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Hand	O
under	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
seize	O
me	O
then	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
May	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Holditch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
Hand	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shoulder	O
pushed	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Do	O
not	O
squeeze	O
my	O
Legs	O
ye	O
B	O
-	O
;	O
presently	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
under	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coat	O
while	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Men	O
were	O
pushing	O
behind	O
.	O
I	O
whipt	O
off	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
at	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Croud	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
Capt	O
.	O
Brown	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Sea	O
)	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
Races	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
seized	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Huff	I-pers
,	O
Apothecary	O
in	O
New	O
Bond-street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
as	O
Journey-man	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
,	O
nine	O
Months	O
ago	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
pretty	O
well	O
-	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
his	O
Uncle	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
the	O
Army	O
-	O
Indeed	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
Papers	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Huff	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Scotland	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Eustace	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
ago	O
-	O
His	O
Family	O
were	O
very	O
credible	O
People	O
in	O
Dublin	O
-	O
But	O
for	O
the	O
nine	O
Months	O
last	O
past	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
I	O
live	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Neal	O
's	O
Yard	O
by	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
our	O
House	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
hurt	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
May	O
be	O
so	O
-	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
Maccray	O
come	O
with	O
him	O
sometimes	O
?	O
J.	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
always	O
came	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Maccray	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
nine	O
Months	O
?	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
Landlord	O
Mabson	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Cow-lane	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
lodged	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
such	O
a	O
notable	O
Surgeon	O
for	O
Maccray	O
?	O
*	O
*	O
Maccray	O
was	O
convicted	O
at	O
last	O
Kingston	O
Assizes	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Hammerton	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Gaffney	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
Maccray	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
Maccray	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
attended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Vomit	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
value	O
twenty	O
eight	O
Pound	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Phillip	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
And	O
17.	O
James	B-pers
Barthelemi	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shirley	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Hoop	B-place
Tavern	I-place
against	O
Beaufort	B-place
Buildings	I-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
twenty	O
ninth	O
of	O
June	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
Company	O
,	O
two	O
young	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
my	O
Passage	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Ground	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
my	O
self	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
turned	O
his	O
Face	O
aside	O
under	O
presence	O
of	O
wiping	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
laid	O
his	O
Head	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Red	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
carried	O
in	O
they	O
bid	O
the	O
Drawer	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
-	O
Do	O
they	O
take	O
this	O
for	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Do	O
they	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
my	O
while	O
to	O
keep	O
Servants	O
to	O
run	O
on	O
their	O
Errands	O
-	O
Let	O
them	O
walk	O
-	O
In	O
two	O
Minutes	O
my	O
Drawer	O
Giles	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
came	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Lisbon	O
for	O
a	O
Cool	O
Tankard	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
my	O
Customers	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
warrant	O
the	O
Tankard	O
should	O
be	O
safe	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
afterwards	O
ordered	O
twelve	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Beef	O
Steaks	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
set	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
to	O
keep	O
warm	O
for	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
whom	O
as	O
they	O
pretended	O
they	O
waited	O
for	O
.	O
They	O
bid	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
another	O
of	O
my	O
Servants	O
bring	O
them	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Oat	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
carried	O
in	O
another	O
Tankard	O
.	O
They	O
sent	O
my	O
Porter	O
on	O
three	O
Errands	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
with	O
both	O
the	O
Tankards	O
-	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
looking	O
out	O
-	O
The	O
large	O
Tankard	O
weighed	O
sixty	O
nine	O
Ounces	O
twelve	O
Penny-weight	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
cost	O
me	O
Ten	O
Pound	O
.	O
Gaffney	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
vertue	O
of	O
your	O
.	O
Oath	O
am	O
I	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Shirley	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ratcliff	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
the	O
twenty	O
ninth	O
or	O
thirtieth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hoop	O
Tavern	O
.	O
The	O
Room	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
was	O
a	O
Ground	O
Floor	O
on	O
the	O
Right-hand	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
with	O
Lemon	O
and	O
Sugar	O
for	O
a	O
Cool	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
brought	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
.	O
He	O
spoke	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Steaks	O
being	O
brought	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Oat	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
too	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
the	O
Porter	O
to	O
some	O
House	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
some	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
name	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Porter	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
Head	O
at	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
Tom	B-pers
King	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
way	O
was	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
Tankard	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Room	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
is	O
before	O
we	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
Information	O
before	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
.	O
Gaffney	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
was	O
catched	O
in	O
a	O
Capital	O
Offence	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
stolen	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swears	O
this	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
Ratcliff	O
was	O
indeed	O
taken	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
Tankards	O
?	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
I	O
sent	O
Frances	B-pers
Charnock	I-pers
with	O
the	O
least	O
Tankard	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Barthelemi	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
at	O
Charing-cross	B-place
.	O
She	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
six	O
Pound	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
thither	O
?	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
knew	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
Goods	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
without	O
asking	O
Questions	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
my	O
self	O
once	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
and	O
carried	O
a	O
Tankard	O
we	O
had	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Boar	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Tankard	O
was	O
melted	O
down	O
in	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Lumps	O
in	O
Gaffney	O
's	O
Room	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
Barthelemi	O
;	O
he	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
nine	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
nineteen	O
Shillings	O
more	O
.	O
He	O
reckoned	O
it	O
at	O
four	O
Shillings	O
and	O
nine	O
Pence	O
or	O
four	O
Shillings	O
and	O
ten	O
Pence	O
an	O
Ounce	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
ye	O
no	O
Questions	O
?	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
dealt	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
small	O
Wares	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Charnock	O
next	O
Day	O
for	O
the	O
nineteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
Barthelemi	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
first	O
Tankard	O
for	O
the	O
full	O
worth	O
-	O
As	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
brought	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
melted	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
weighed	O
but	O
forty	O
three	O
Ounces	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
being	O
well	O
drest	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
examined	O
Ratcliff	O
and	O
Charnock	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Barthelemi	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
I	O
read	O
Ratcliff	O
's	O
whole	O
Information	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
absolutely	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
out	O
Ratcliff	O
and	O
Charnock	O
to	O
confront	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Tankards	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
ten	O
Pound	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shirly	O
.	O
As	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Tankards	O
was	O
whole	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Refiners	O
-	O
And	O
when	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
prest	O
him	O
to	O
produce	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
marked	O
IER	O
for	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
of	O
the	O
Widow	O
Emery	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
Cardigan	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
frequented	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
the	O
Tankard	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
:	O
Besides	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Mark	O
and	O
the	O
Weight	O
which	O
was	O
set	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Advertisements	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
(	O
as	O
will	O
be	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
left	O
it	O
)	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Hours	O
before	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Charnock	I-pers
.	O
Gaffney	O
,	O
and	O
Ratcliff	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
all	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
home	O
together	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
twenty	O
ninth	O
or	O
thirtieth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
from	O
the	O
Hoop	O
Tavern	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Barthelemi	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
small	O
Tankard	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
And	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
lighted	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
no	O
Questions	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
without	O
asking	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
weighed	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
it	O
up	O
on	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
many	O
Ounces	O
it	O
weighed	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
much	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Ounce	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
both	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
remember	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
six	O
Pound	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
or	O
wanting	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
in	O
Holborn	O
-	O
I	O
then	O
lived	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn-lane	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
to	O
meet	O
some	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
me	O
so	O
far	O
homeward	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
farther	O
but	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Gaffney	O
.	O
Barthelemi	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Charnock	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
Word	O
.	O
Barthelemi	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
pass	O
for	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
one	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
a	O
Note	O
?	O
Charnock	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Barthelemi	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
said	O
your	O
Husband	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Law	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
you	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Tankard	O
-	O
What	O
Letters	O
was	O
it	O
marked	O
with	O
?	O
Charnock	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Barthelemi	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
Monday	O
that	O
you	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Produce	O
your	O
Books	O
and	O
contradict	O
her	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
,	O
by	O
shewing	O
a	O
regular	O
Entry	O
.	O
Barthelemi	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
no	O
Books	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
-	O
[	O
As	O
this	O
was	O
hardly	O
spoke	O
loud	O
enough	O
for	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
hear	O
him	O
distinctly	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
this	O
Pretence	O
and	O
said	O
]	O
-	O
I	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
so	O
in	O
my	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
six	O
Pound	O
nineteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Tankards	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
aside	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
matter	O
might	O
prove	O
very	O
troublesome	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
more	O
agreeable	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
easy	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
Words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
before	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
People	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
ashamed	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
bribe	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
-	O
was	O
only	O
his	O
Prayers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shirley	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
twenty	O
,	O
twenty	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
thirty	O
Guineas	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
-	O
Will	O
your	O
Lordship	O
please	O
to	O
ask	O
Charnock	O
about	O
her	O
selling	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Mug	O
that	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
by	O
GuildHall	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
enquire	O
into	O
particular	O
Facts	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
indicted	O
.	O
Barthelemi	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
five	O
Shillings	O
an	O
Ounce	O
for	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
will	O
you	O
needs	O
take	O
this	O
upon	O
your	O
self	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Holton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
Messenger	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Company	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
June	O
30.	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
Printed	O
Advertisement	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Tenour	O
as	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
at	O
Barthelemi	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
It	O
contains	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Tankards	O
,	O
the	O
Marks	O
,	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
Size	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
read	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Gaffney	O
to	O
Charnock	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
Ratcliff	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
by	O
his	O
Name	O
?	O
Charnock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Gaffney	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Tankards	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Shirley	O
.	O
Two	O
.	O
Gaffney	O
.	O
The	O
unfortunate	O
Dr.	O
Dunn	O
was	O
tried	O
here	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
these	O
Tankards	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
Servants	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Gaffney	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
be	O
but	O
Justice	O
to	O
bring	O
your	O
Servants	O
here	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
know	O
me	O
.	O
Shirley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
send	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Gaffney	O
.	O
Very	O
Good	O
!	O
Barthelemi	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mansfield	O
,	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
The	O
usual	O
Price	O
of	O
Old	O
Sterling	O
Tankards	O
when	O
melted	O
.	O
is	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
or	O
five	O
Shillings	O
one	O
Penny	O
an	O
Ounce	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
vast	O
deal	O
of	O
Sodder	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shirley	O
.	O
The	O
Tankards	O
were	O
both	O
New	O
Sterling	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mansfield	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
three	O
Pence	O
an	O
Ounce	O
more	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Laroch	I-pers
,	O
Silversmith	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
Mr.	O
Barthelemi	O
a	O
Tankard	O
at	O
a	O
Crown	O
an	O
Ounce	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
Old	O
Sterling	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pattison	O
,	O
a	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
Barthelemi	O
;	O
he	O
works	O
hard	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
from	O
Morning	O
to	O
Night	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
buy	O
Goods	O
publickly	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
thought	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
clandestine	O
way	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
lived	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
absconding	O
on	O
some	O
account	O
?	O
Pattison	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
an	O
Action	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
was	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
abroad	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Charges	O
.	O
Barthelemi	O
I	O
stopt	O
a	O
Maid	O
for	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
a	O
Tea-pot	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
.	O
German	O
Bonette	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Maid	O
came	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Maid	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
together	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
obliged	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
fair	O
Dealer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
knowingly	O
buy	O
Plate	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Gaffney	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
Barthelemi	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
.	O
18.	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
May	O
23	O
.	O
And	O
19.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	O
Short	B-place
's	I-place
Gardens	I-place
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
May	O
23	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Entrance	O
was	O
made	O
at	O
my	O
Window	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
Celler	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
three	O
Tankards	O
,	O
which	O
weighed	O
about	O
eighty	O
Ounces	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Lewis	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
committed	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bars	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
Bar	O
he	O
wrenched	O
up	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
standing	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Tankards	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
first	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Pritchard	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Brill	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
soon	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
,	O
in	O
Eagle	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
her	O
up	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Her	O
Husband	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
scrupulous	O
of	O
dealing	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
trouble	O
on	O
the	O
like	O
Account	O
.	O
*	O
Lewis	O
had	O
been	O
recommended	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
abroad	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
Thieving	O
.	O
)	O
though	O
she	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Glass	O
Blower	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
need	O
fear	O
no	O
harm	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
but	O
our	O
selves	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
the	O
same	O
(	O
Saturday	O
)	O
Morning	O
,	O
her	O
Son	O
fetched	O
some	O
Charcoal	O
to	O
melt	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
We	O
melted	O
it	O
below	O
Stairs	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
weighed	O
it	O
with	O
old	O
Leaden	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
forty	O
six	O
Ounces	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
reckoning	O
it	O
at	O
four	O
Shillings	O
an	O
Ounce	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
nine	O
Pound	O
odd	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
us	O
five	O
Guineas	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Remainder	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
-	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
Information	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
before	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
1733.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
alias	O
Hampton	O
,	O
in	O
December	O
,	O
1732.	O
Edward	B-pers
Post	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
Margery	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
)	O
for	O
apprehending	O
Lewis	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
help	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
desperate	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Jack	O
in	O
Dyot	O
Street	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
ajar	O
,	O
we	O
entered	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
abed	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Room	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
two	O
Hangers	O
,	O
a	O
Pick-lock-key	O
,	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
Pistols	O
,	O
Powder	O
and	O
Bullets	O
.	O
Davenport	O
.	O
This	O
Pick-lock-key	O
we	O
bought	O
of	O
Morris	O
's	O
Son	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
swears	O
they	O
sold	O
me	O
this	O
Plate	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Elwall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
four	O
Days	O
before	O
Whitsuntide	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Swan	O
Alley	O
in	O
Goswell	O
street	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Air	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
Days	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Elwall	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Lewis	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
Morris	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
.	O
20.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
for	O
turning	O
on	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Spoon	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Business	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
August	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
21.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Belmosset	I-pers
*	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
Belmosset	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Belmosset	I-pers
)	O
was	O
capitally	O
Convicted	O
in	O
December	O
,	O
1730	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
23.	O
David	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Wigmore	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
August	O
21	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
drunken	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
24.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
for	O
marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Katherine	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
John	B-pers
Violet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
New	O
Testament	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
26.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lamber	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
two	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
four	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
27	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
and	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
,	O
September	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Diaper	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Newsham	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tapper	I-pers
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Elby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sheet	O
and	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bold	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31.	O
Richard	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
four	O
Steel	O
Chapes	O
for	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
Pence	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32.	O
William	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pincers	O
,	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
a	O
Last	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
33	O
,	O
34.	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Immins	I-pers
,	O
August	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
five	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
August	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	O
George	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hayman	I-pers
+	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
August	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
+	O
Hayman	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
June	O
,	O
1733	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
like	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
,	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35	O
Ann	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
two	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
August	O
6	O
.	O
Steed	O
acquitted	O
and	O
Farrow	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
August	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10.	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
August	O
12	O
.	O
And	O
two	O
Pound	O
five	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
August	O
15	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ferrers	I-pers
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Callico	O
Print-Cutter	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
on	O
one	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Blank	O
Paper	O
,	O
three	O
counterfeit	O
Impressions	O
in	O
imitation	O
of	O
three	O
true	O
Sixpenny	O
Stamps	O
,	O
thereby	O
designing	O
to	O
diminish	O
the	O
Revenue	O
and	O
defraud	O
his	O
Majesty	O
of	O
the	O
Duties	O
of	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
granted	O
by	O
certain	O
Statutes	O
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
in	O
London	O
.	O
Elihu	B-pers
Bridoak	I-pers
.	O
In	O
July	O
1734.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
counterfeit	O
the	O
Stamps	O
on	O
Paper	O
so	O
exactly	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
distinguished	O
from	O
the	O
true	O
Stamps	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
half	O
the	O
Profits	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Office	O
for	O
two	O
treble	O
six	O
Penny	O
Stamps	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
fetched	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
By	O
these	O
he	O
made	O
counterfeit	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
not	O
convenient	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
by	O
his	O
Order	O
in	O
New-street	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
place	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
Press	O
and	O
Fly	O
and	O
Crucibles	O
and	O
Metals	O
and	O
other	O
Materials	O
for	O
coining	O
Guineas	O
and	O
stamping	O
Paper	O
.	O
We	O
stamped	O
several	O
Reams	O
of	O
Paper	O
which	O
I	O
distributed	O
,	O
some	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitworth	I-pers
of	O
Manchester	O
for	O
twenty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Quire	O
the	O
treble	O
six	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
seventeen	O
Shillings	O
the	O
double	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
thirty	O
Quire	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
;	O
some	O
to	O
Mr	O
Wheatly	O
(	O
or	O
Heatly	O
)	O
at	O
Chester	O
;	O
some	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Parsons	O
at	O
New	O
Castle	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
to	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
Stamps	O
on	O
these	O
five	O
blank	O
Sheets	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
these	O
were	O
not	O
done	O
in	O
New-Street	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Petty	O
's	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
hired	O
a	O
Garret	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
Nothing	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
Press	O
was	O
moved	O
thither	O
from	O
New	O
Street	O
except	O
the	O
Fly	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
new	O
Press	O
made	O
by	O
one	O
Boddington	O
.	O
When	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bowtell	I-pers
the	O
Stationer	O
was	O
apprehended	O
for	O
selling	O
counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
removed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
except	O
this	O
Fly	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
Press	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
.	O
The	O
new	O
Press	O
was	O
first	O
put	O
together	O
at	O
Bowtell	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
Bowtell	O
pulled	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
your	O
Tackle	O
.	O
The	O
Paper	O
we	O
stampt	O
for	O
Whitworth	O
,	O
Heatly	O
,	O
and	O
Parsons	O
,	O
was	O
doue	O
with	O
the	O
old	O
Press	O
.	O
Hearing	O
that	O
Bowtell	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
things	O
in	O
confusion	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
twenty	O
ninth	O
or	O
thirtieth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
arrested	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Bowtell	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
selling	O
Stamps	O
though	O
but	O
few	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
they	O
might	O
find	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
Bowtell	O
two	O
Quire	O
of	O
two	O
Shilling	O
and	O
three	O
Penny	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Quire	O
of	O
double	O
Penny	O
but	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Bowtell	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
As	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
may	O
be	O
turned	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
may	O
be	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
my	O
Life	O
is	O
worth	O
;	O
but	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
desire	O
him	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
to	O
hold	O
his	O
Tongue	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Life	O
depends	O
upon	O
his	O
Taciturnity	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
Presses	O
,	O
several	O
Stamps	O
,	O
Dies	O
and	O
Punches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Materials	O
for	O
Coining	O
and	O
Stamping	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Engraver	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
those	O
Punches	O
were	O
proper	O
for	O
repairing	O
Stamps	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
cast	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
had	O
been	O
searched	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
and	O
my	O
Hen	O
run	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
my	O
Hand	O
upon	O
this	O
Brass	O
Six	O
Penny	O
Stamp	O
,	O
marked	O
Y	O
.	O
This	O
Place	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
one	O
Watts	O
,	O
an	O
elderly	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
alone	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
before	O
the	O
search	O
-	O
This	O
Paper	O
was	O
found	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
-	O
Wagstaff	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
write	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
this	O
Writing	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Paper	O
was	O
read	O
;	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
March	O
.	O
6	O
qr	O
of	O
triple	O
3	O
qr	O
of	O
double	O
6	O
qr	O
of	O
prints	O
Ball	O
.	O
due	O
from	O
New	O
Cas	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
0	O
Mar	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
28	O
24	O
Indentures	O
12	O
Bonds	O
performance	O
1	O
qr	O
of	O
triple	O
12	O
bonds	O
April	O
7	O
4	O
qr	O
triple	O
1	O
double	O
13	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
0	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Pocket-book	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
-	O
Wagstaff	O
.	O
This	O
part	O
is	O
like	O
his	O
Hand	O
-	O
but	O
this	O
derogates	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
.	O
This	O
great	O
Press	O
I	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
alone	O
employ	O
you	O
?	O
Boddington	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
-	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Screw	O
of	O
that	O
other	O
Press	O
for	O
Bridoak	O
and	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Bridoak	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
liked	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
present	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
?	O
Boddington	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
fetched	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
Islington	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
rememberance	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Bridoak	O
swore	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
that	O
Press	O
from	O
Bowtell	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
little	O
House	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
Marsh	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wigley	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
clambered	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
into	O
a	O
Cock	O
Lost	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Gun	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
-	O
In	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
among	O
some	O
Bricks	O
and	O
Shavings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
Stamp	O
Paper	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
Pound	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Petty	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
Lady	O
Day	O
,	O
hired	O
my	O
Garret	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
and	O
lye	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
,	O
but	O
Bridoak	O
staid	O
longer	O
-	O
I	O
once	O
heard	O
a	O
thumping	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
.	O
On	O
January	O
29	O
,	O
1733	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
in	O
New-street	O
to	O
Bridoak	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
afterwards	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
France	O
-	O
On	O
Lady	O
Day	O
last	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
Key	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Furniture	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
White	O
House	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Bridoak	O
have	O
often	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
go	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
represented	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Furniture	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Bridoak	O
lodge	O
there	O
?	O
S.	O
Fell	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
carried	O
Drink	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
but	O
just	O
within	O
the	O
Door	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
Bedstead	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
owns	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
.	O
He	O
owns	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
himself	O
rich	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
poor	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
Law	O
Suit	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Sollicitor	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
recover	O
a	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
our	O
Acquaintance	O
begun	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
little	O
printed	O
Marks	O
to	O
copy	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
for	O
Daffy	O
's	O
Elixir	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
satisfying	O
him	O
this	O
way	O
for	O
managing	O
my	O
Law	O
Suit	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
most	O
of	O
these	O
Marks	O
had	O
Crowns	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
to	O
an	O
ill	O
use	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
would	O
meddle	O
with	O
none	O
but	O
Daffy	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
sell	O
my	O
Wig	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
this	O
Suit	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Pocket	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
a	O
Practice	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
reasonable	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
too	O
.	O
His	O
own	O
Terror	O
has	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Confession	O
:	O
He	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Secrets	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
should	O
discover	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
charges	O
me	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
himself	O
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
not	O
been	O
tryed	O
in	O
this	O
Place	O
,	O
*	O
and	O
convicted	O
at	O
Kingston	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
all	O
my	O
Tools	O
and	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
Suttle	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
thither	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
directed	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
at	O
what	O
House	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
been	O
informed	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
related	O
to	O
Coining	O
or	O
Stamping	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
*	O
In	O
April	O
1732.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
alias	O
Bodicoat	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Calf	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
his	O
Callicoe	O
Prints	O
,	O
three	O
Suits	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
odd	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Office	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
St	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
had	O
been	O
mine	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
likely	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
sent	O
them	O
away	O
too	O
-	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Writing	O
that	O
is	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
be	O
the	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Writing	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
counterfeited	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
a	O
Receipt	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
prove	O
by	O
Giles	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
who	O
proved	O
last	O
Sessions	O
that	O
Bridoak	O
was	O
concerned	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
Law	O
Suit	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
often	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Witness	O
is	O
not	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
-	O
Here	O
is	O
George	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
Brother	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Press	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
Bridoak	O
G.	O
Boddington	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
for	O
Bridoak	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edby	I-pers
.	O
That	O
House	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
to	O
old	O
Watts	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
in	O
Chymestry	O
there	O
-	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
kin	O
to	O
old	O
Watts	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Leather	O
Gilder	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
had	O
a	O
Ground	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Ground	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
Marsh	O
;	O
a	O
small	O
Ditch	O
parts	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Plank	O
lies	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
frequently	O
went	O
into	O
one	O
anothers	O
Ground	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
often	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
through	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
both	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
and	O
from	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
a	O
Secret	O
there	O
:	O
and	O
from	O
our	O
Ground	O
we	O
can	O
look	O
through	O
every	O
Window	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
gave	O
old	O
Wats	O
notice	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harbert	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
Bridoak	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
Watts	O
lodged	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
leave	O
a	O
Line	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
and	O
wrote	O
upon	O
it	O
thus	O
:	O
Mr	O
Dean	O
does	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
returns	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
that	O
Paper	O
into	O
Court	O
last	O
Sessions	O
:	O
I	O
understood	O
this	O
as	O
Caution	O
for	O
old	O
Watts	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Watts	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
twice	O
.	O
Then	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
They	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
inoffensive	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
41.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bowtell	I-pers
,	O
Stationer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
vending	O
one	O
Blank	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
having	O
on	O
it	O
three	O
Counterfeit	O
Impressions	O
resembling	O
three	O
Six-penny	O
Stamps	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
May	O
30	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
in	O
London	O
.	O
Elihu	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
Dean	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
seldom	O
a	O
Day	O
asunder	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Dean	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Butcher-hall-lane	B-place
,	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
fitted	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
Dean	O
and	O
I	O
removed	O
to	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
this	O
Press	O
thither	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
Press	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Dean	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
your	O
Tackle	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
stamped	O
this	O
Paper	O
-	O
One	O
Evening	O
,	O
Dean	O
,	O
Bacon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bacon	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
Friends	O
can	O
take	O
off	O
Stamps	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
use	O
you	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
you	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Months	O
Credit	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
Wood-Street	O
Compter	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
Dean	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Dean	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
proper	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
turned	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
his	O
Life	O
was	O
worth	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
own	O
Safety	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
mine	O
lies	O
on	O
his	O
being	O
secret	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
two	O
Quire	O
of	O
Two	O
and	O
Three-penny	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Quire	O
of	O
Double-penny	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
Dean	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
main	O
Bulk	O
of	O
Stamps	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
Dean	O
had	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
was	O
seized	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
Orders	O
to	O
remove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confest	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Stamps	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Trade	O
who	O
had	O
newly	O
left	O
off	O
the	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
Holland	O
Trader	O
-	O
Dean	O
dealt	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
once	O
sent	O
some	O
Paper	O
by	O
me	O
to	O
Dean	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Dean	O
knew	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Dean	O
deliver	O
a	O
Sheet	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
see	O
me	O
sell	O
a	O
Sheet	O
?	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
Dean	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rutland	I-pers
On	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
these	O
ten	O
printed	O
Stamps	O
and	O
these	O
eleven	O
Blanks	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
in	O
Tower	O
Street	O
for	O
three	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Paper	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
-	O
Jewks	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Office	O
.	O
-	O
Jews	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sell	O
these	O
for	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ream	O
of	O
Paper	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sydenham	O
deposed	O
that	O
these	O
were	O
Counterfeits	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Stationer	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
.	O
Sometime	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
twenty	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Treble	O
Six-penny	O
Stamps	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sydenham	O
deposed	O
that	O
these	O
were	O
Counterfeits	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wrench	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
seventeen	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Stamps	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Drawer	O
among	O
other	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
Name	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wrench	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
Letter	O
Y	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
Stamp	O
that	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
counterfeited	O
by	O
Dean	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Constable	O
Here	O
are	O
about	O
ten	O
Quires	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Drawers	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
Chamber	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
Attorney	O
.	O
In	O
April	O
or	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Dean	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
met	O
.	O
This	O
Business	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Suit	O
to	O
compel	O
one	O
Wigley	O
to	O
specify	O
performance	O
of	O
an	O
Agreement	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
betwixt	O
him	O
and	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
the	O
Suit	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
expensive	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
my	O
Paymaster	O
.	O
Sometime	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
Stamps	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Stamps	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Pound	O
;	O
the	O
chief	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
Stationer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
Counterfeit	O
Six-penny	O
,	O
marked	O
O	O
and	O
T.	O
Mr.	O
Bacon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
committed	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
what	O
Stamps	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
begun	O
to	O
write	O
on	O
the	O
Leaf	O
of	O
a	O
Pocket-book	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
finished	O
,	O
he	O
tore	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
would	O
clear	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
Events	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
blame	O
on	O
himself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
own	O
you	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
then	O
as	O
guilty	O
as	O
I	O
?	O
You	O
may	O
say	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
Rent	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
part	O
in	O
Stamps	O
.	O
March	O
twelve	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
Pound	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Treble	O
Six-penny	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Pence	O
in	O
Paper	O
.	O
May	O
the	O
twenty	O
eighth	O
Twelve	O
Double	O
Six-penny	O
-	O
six	O
Quire	O
of	O
Double	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
Six	O
Treble	O
Six-penny	O
Bonds	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
three	O
Pound	O
eighteen	O
Shillings	O
and	O
seven	O
Pence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
worth	O
in	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
them	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
I	O
threatened	O
to	O
strain	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
his	O
Wife	O
paid	O
me	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Rent	O
except	O
nine	O
Pence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
all	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
sold	O
the	O
Stamps	O
now	O
produced	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Bridoak	O
at	O
the	O
full	O
price	O
.	O
Abel	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
,	O
Book	O
binder	O
,	O
in	O
Bishop	O
's	O
Gate	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
about	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Bridoak	O
sell	O
him	O
a	O
Quire	O
of	O
Treble	O
Six	O
Penny	O
Stamps	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
paid	O
three	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
him	O
any	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
saw	O
this	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Master	O
settle	O
an	O
Accompt	O
with	O
Bridoak	O
for	O
two	O
Pound	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
gave	O
my	O
Master	O
a	O
Quire	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Treble	O
Six	O
Penny	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
gave	O
him	O
five	O
Shillings	O
to	O
ballance	O
.	O
The	O
Account	O
was	O
for	O
Work	O
and	O
Goods	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
He	O
binds	O
Books	O
in	O
Vellum	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bound	O
some	O
Pocket	O
Books	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
New	O
Castle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
twenty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
no	O
usual	O
for	O
Book-binders	O
to	O
have	O
many	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
them	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Dean	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Dran	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
making	O
four	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
Brass	O
,	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Base	O
Metals	O
in	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
Guineas	O
,	O
May	O
27	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Elihu	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
In	O
December	O
,	O
1733.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
make	O
Dies	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
present	O
Coin	O
.	O
He	O
finished	O
them	O
in	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
New	O
Street	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
Coin	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
thither	O
the	O
Bellows	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Materials	O
.	O
He	O
built	O
the	O
Furnace	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
up	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
provided	O
Gold	O
,	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
Copper	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Guineas	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
distributed	O
some	O
hundreds	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
Gold	O
in	O
each	O
as	O
was	O
worth	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
We	O
continued	O
Coining	O
till	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
stamping	O
Paper	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
these	O
two	O
Guineas	O
were	O
of	O
his	O
making	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
pick	O
them	O
out	O
from	O
a	O
Number	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
particular	O
Mark	O
.	O
The	O
Difference	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Lips	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
easily	O
distinguished	O
by	O
a	O
cursory	O
View	O
.	O
Mr.	O
North	O
.	O
When	O
Bridoak	O
gave	O
me	O
Information	O
of	O
these	O
Guineas	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Lips	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
pick	O
them	O
out	O
from	O
good	O
ones	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Maddoches	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
to	O
procure	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
.	O
Their	O
Out	O
tellers	O
got	O
four	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
mixt	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
with	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
ninety	O
six	O
good	O
ones	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
turned	O
them	O
over	O
and	O
picked	O
out	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
Officer	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Assay	O
of	O
their	O
real	O
value	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
North	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
tried	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Assay	O
Office	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
worth	O
about	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
a-piece	O
.	O
Brodoak	O
's	O
picking	O
out	O
the	O
four	O
Guineas	O
from	O
two	O
Hundred	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
Mrs.	O
Fell	O
of	O
New	O
Street	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knows	O
Watts	O
,	O
or	O
has	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Fell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
on	O
old	O
Man	O
named	O
Watts	O
:	O
They	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
.	O
He	O
mended	O
my	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Watch	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
then	O
in	O
Stone	O
Cutters	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
All	O
these	O
Materials	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
Bridoak	O
took	O
this	O
House	O
in	O
New	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
on	O
the	O
Design	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
42.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nurse	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
August	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Fans	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
44.	O
Ann	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Sauce	O
Pans	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lions	I-pers
,	O
August	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tyers	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sarah	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Stew	O
Pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46.	O
John	B-pers
Lattimore	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Graves	B-pers
Akin	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47.	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Printed	O
Cotton	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Cheesman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
August	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
and	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
July	O
31	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	O
Hall	O
,	O
July	O
31	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
fixt	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	O
Hall	O
.	O
July	O
31	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
49.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Benjafield	I-pers
+	I-pers
alias	O
BenderField	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
three	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
four	O
Towels	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
+	O
Benjerfield	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
September	O
,	O
1732.	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
Number	O
7	O
,	O
Part	O
2	O
.	O
Page	O
212	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
Mary	B-pers
Savory	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
51.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tea	O
Tongs	O
,	O
two	O
Pinners	O
,	O
eight	O
Mobs	O
,	O
five	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Trigg	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Poplin	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Noise	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rush	I-pers
,	O
September	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Workman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Grinoe	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Waggoner	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
53	O
,	O
54	O
George	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
seventeen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
August	O
22	O
.	O
Bird	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Allen	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
55.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
September	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
56.	O
Philip	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
Walpole	O
's	O
Bricklayer	O
about	O
eleven	O
Years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Pantry	O
amongst	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
for	O
being	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
mistrust	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gilpin	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
by	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
Back	O
Gate	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
produced	O
this	O
Escallop	O
'd	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
.	O
Seeing	O
a	O
Crest	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
the	O
Plate	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
satisfy	O
me	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
soon	O
fetch	O
one	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
Mr.	O
Stafford	O
from	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Office	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stafford	O
told	O
me	O
who	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
-	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
the	O
Crest	O
was	O
like	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Chandos	O
's	O
.	O
But	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
Walpole	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
owned	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
again	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Salver	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
's	O
Pantry	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
57.	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Sheep	O
Skins	O
and	O
two	O
Buck	O
Skins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bullock	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
July	O
26.	O
and	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bristol	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
Bullock	O
of	O
Colebrook	O
keeps	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
here	O
in	O
Town	O
which	O
I	O
look	O
after	O
.	O
He	O
employs	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
wants	O
a	O
Hand	O
he	O
sends	O
to	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
ninth	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1	O
heard	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Skins	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
but	O
though	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
no	O
farther	O
trouble	O
-	O
They	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Stamp	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
two	O
Bundles	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
those	O
Bundles	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
I	O
could	O
let	O
him	O
lye	O
there	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
for	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
wicked	O
Houses	O
about	O
Town	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
sober	O
Man	O
could	O
hardly	O
find	O
a	O
Place	O
to	O
lay	O
his	O
Head	O
in	O
-	O
At	O
Night	O
my	O
Maid	O
lighted	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wondered	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
that	O
strange	O
Man	O
lay	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
though	O
he	O
pretended	O
so	O
much	O
Godliness	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
rude	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
his	O
Hand	O
up	O
her	O
Coars	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
examined	O
his	O
Bundles	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
wet	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
Skins	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
Beadle	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Skins	O
were	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Stamps	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
refused	O
to	O
rise	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Bundles	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
however	O
that	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bullock	O
,	O
at	O
Colebrook	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bullock	O
had	O
a	O
Ware-house	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
sent	O
for	O
King	O
who	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
.	O
J.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Master	O
Bullock	O
's	O
Skins	O
by	O
the	O
Marks	O
,	O
for	O
each	O
of	O
his	O
Men	O
marks	O
his	O
own	O
Work	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
Fault	O
we	O
may	O
know	O
who	O
to	O
blame	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
left	O
my	O
Master	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Wickedness	O
of	O
his	O
Workmen	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
given	O
to	O
drink	O
Gin	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
who	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
my	O
self	O
with	O
Sobriety	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
that	O
pernicious	O
Practice	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Skins	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Colebrook	O
,	O
and	O
considering	O
with	O
my	O
self	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
belong	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
I	O
resolved	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Ware-house-keeper	O
there	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
was	O
my	O
Design	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
Word	O
and	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
for	O
Mercy	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Heaven	O
.	O
But	O
for	O
Christ	O
's	O
Sake	O
!	O
for	O
the	O
Lord	O
Jesus	O
Sake	O
!	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
Punishment	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
58.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Judith	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
one	O
Shilling	O
and	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
August	O
2	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
peeping	O
thro	O
'	O
some	O
Wooden	O
Pallisadoes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
Silver	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Huswife	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
that	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
-	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
over	O
a	O
Field	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
some	O
People	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
-	O
She	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Tools	O
.	O
J.	O
Saunders	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
stab	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
.	O
Hearing	O
of	O
several	O
Robberies	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
in	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Norris	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
in	O
Writing	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Norris	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
near	O
Grove	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
her	O
of	O
one	O
Shilling	O
and	O
three	O
Halfpence	O
and	O
that	O
Richard	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
,	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lurked	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
while	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
59.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Pickup	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
by	O
assaulting	O
and	O
fixing	O
both	O
his	O
Arms	O
and	O
Hands	O
about	O
her	O
Waste	O
and	O
squeezing	O
and	O
pressing	O
her	O
divers	O
times	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
Loins	O
and	O
Sides	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
her	O
several	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
August	O
2.	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
This	O
Deposition	O
on	O
Oath	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Mouth	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
as	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
at	O
Kensington	O
Gravel	O
Pits	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
eighth	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
August	O
following	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
following	O
purpose	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
Pickup	O
a	O
Brewer	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Races	O
were	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
being	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
alone	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
back	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
proposed	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
seized	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
her	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
his	O
Violence	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
ravish	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
apprehended	O
he	O
broke	O
something	O
within	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
her	O
Kidneys	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
felt	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
attempt	O
to	O
ravish	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
force	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
believes	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
further	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
Judgment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dying	O
Woman	O
,	O
in	O
great	O
Pain	O
and	O
Misery	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
rational	O
Answers	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
all	O
imaginable	O
Veracity	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
eighth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hounslow	O
Races	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Wife	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
the	O
reason	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
left	O
alone	O
any	O
more	O
:	O
That	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
her	O
Water	O
,	O
which	O
war	O
bloody	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
troubled	O
with	O
the	O
Stone	O
and	O
Gravel	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
no	O
Complaint	O
of	O
that	O
nature	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
well	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
Home	O
.	O
That	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Pickup	O
the	O
Brewer	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
alone	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
:	O
And	O
when	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
threw	O
his	O
Arms	O
round	O
her	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
ravish	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
half	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pulled	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
a	O
Cellar	O
full	O
of	O
Beer	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
why	O
he	O
had	O
abused	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
him	O
some	O
Two-penny	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Evidence	O
returned	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mosely	O
,	O
and	O
huffed	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
why	O
he	O
sent	O
back	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
:	O
You	O
Villain	O
how	O
dare	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
abuse	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Voice	O
,	O
called	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Villain	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
if	O
his	O
Wife	O
might	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
heard	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
cryed	O
out	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assaulted	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
struggled	O
with	O
her	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
breath	O
:	O
He	O
added	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
attended	O
in	O
her	O
Ilness	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Beaufort	O
,	O
Dr.	O
Bloxham	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
cross-examined	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
his	O
Wife	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Doctors	O
how	O
her	O
Disorder	O
began	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
thought	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
they	O
tell	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sheham	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
seventeen	O
Days	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
violent	O
Fit	O
of	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
by	O
eating	O
Beans	O
and	O
Bacon	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Evidence	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Gravel	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Beaufort	O
About	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Pain	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
a	O
total	O
suppression	O
of	O
Urine	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
proceeded	O
from	O
the	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
as	O
for	O
a	O
suppression	O
of	O
Urine	O
.	O
I	O
visited	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
complained	O
of	O
receiving	O
any	O
Bruises	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Disorder	O
about	O
her	O
Kidneys	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
if	O
taking	O
a	O
Woman	O
round	O
the	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
struggling	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
could	O
bruise	O
her	O
Kidneys	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
felt	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
so	O
doing	O
could	O
have	O
such	O
an	O
Effect	O
.	O
Being	O
farther	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
Stone	O
in	O
the	O
Kidneys	O
might	O
not	O
by	O
Violence	O
be	O
removed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
cause	O
that	O
suppression	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
any	O
Violence	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
used	O
in	O
hugging	O
and	O
squeezing	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Bloxham	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
attended	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
March	O
or	O
April	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
severe	O
Vomiting	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Stone	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
directed	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
his	O
Direction	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
voided	O
a	O
little	O
Stone	O
.	O
That	O
