TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1736.	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
WILLIAMS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1736	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXVI	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stanfield	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Ryal	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Tattershall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Philpott	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gresham	I-pers
,	O
Dean	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gogan	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chishall	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hasewittle	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grimboldson	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Issac	B-pers
Turbot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Allhallows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Birtwell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-house-Key	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
this	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
.	O
'T	O
is	O
my	O
Business	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Watchmen	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
night	O
over	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
loitering	O
about	O
some	O
Hogsheads	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Hogsheads	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
Quantity	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Simon	B-pers
Trevilian	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
.	O
Ashton	B-pers
Broad	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
January	O
the	O
24th	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
of	O
a	O
Ware-house	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
on	O
Cox	B-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Door	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
of	O
Sugar	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
weigh	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
half	O
a	O
Hundred	O
,	O
and	O
22lb	O
.	O
missing	O
;	O
we	O
compared	O
what	O
we	O
took	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
answered	O
directly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
Mr.	O
Broad	O
's	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
this	O
Sugar	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
broke	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Sugar	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tin	O
Christmas-Box	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
30s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
.	O
Sherwin	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Feb.1	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Jack	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
do	O
ye	O
know	O
where	O
your	O
Christmas-Box	O
is	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
your	O
Master	O
has	O
put	O
it	O
by	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
Customers	O
Names	O
that	O
had	O
put	O
Money	O
in	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Calculation	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
3l	O
.	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Apothecary	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
know	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
cleared	O
himself	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Silver	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
was	O
produced	O
that	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Henry	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Checqu	O
'd	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
T.	O
A.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Linnen-Draper	O
's	O
Shop	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
behind	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
Checque	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
and	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
in	O
five	O
Minutes	O
Time	O
.	O
His	O
Friends	O
have	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
since	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
informing	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
sent	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
dread	O
his	O
coming	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Grace	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Dun	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Strahan	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
a	O
Leather	O
Watch	O
String	O
,	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
and	O
2	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
.	O
John	O
Strahan	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
and	O
tumbled	O
down	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
:	O
Well	O
Woman	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
civil	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
'll	O
have	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
-	O
was	O
there	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
?	O
Strahan	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
Dram-shop	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
I	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
asleep	O
?	O
Strahan	O
.	O
I	O
wak	O
'd	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
my	O
Watch	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Landlord	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Scotchman	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
unacquainted	O
with	O
such	O
ways	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
you	O
Villain	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
pay	O
your	O
Reckoning	O
and	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
threw	O
down	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Drams	O
came	O
to	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
fetched	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
out	O
all	O
the	O
Candles	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
could	O
do	O
nothing	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
fled	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Wife	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
me	O
aside	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Bosom	O
;	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
found	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Zaccheus	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
at	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Brocas	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
keeps	O
this	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
Grace	O
Williams	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
her	O
at	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Brandy-shops	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
or	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
sell	O
Sheeps-heads	O
and	O
Drams	O
,	O
in	O
Moses	O
and	O
Aaron	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
:	O
She	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
2	O
Seals	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Diaper	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Chints-	O
Curtains	O
,	O
1	O
double	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
6	O
Drinking	O
Glasses	O
,	O
2	O
China	O
Chocolate-cups	O
,	O
2	O
China	O
Tea-cups	O
,	O
2	O
Saucers	O
,	O
3	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Laced	O
double	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Daffey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
,	O
9.	O
Grace	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Diana	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Diana	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Daffey	O
.	O
About	O
Christmas	O
last	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
above	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
14	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
depend	O
upon	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
liv	O
'd	O
any	O
where	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
worth	O
a	O
thousand	O
Pounds	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
that	O
Security	O
for	O
her	O
honesty	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
our	O
Service	O
required	O
a	O
trusty	O
Servant	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
honest	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
may	O
depend	O
upon	O
you	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
his	O
Character	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
above	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
double	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
7	O
l.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Daffey	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Pilferer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
without	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
must	O
therefore	O
watch	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
(	O
for	O
ought	O
I	O
know	O
)	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
Confession	O
sign	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
2	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
6	O
Glasses	O
,	O
2	O
Chocolate-cups	O
,	O
2	O
Tea-cups	O
,	O
2	O
Saucers	O
,	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
an	O
Earthern	O
Flower-pot	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
double	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
taken	O
this	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
single	O
Woman	O
,	O
confesseth	O
and	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
her	O
Service	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
5	O
Weeks	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
stole	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Daffey	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Table-cloaths	O
,	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Chints	O
Curtains	O
,	O
2	O
Chocolate-cups	O
,	O
2	O
Tea-cups	O
,	O
2	O
Saucers	O
,	O
some	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Daffey	O
took	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
one	O
Chints	O
Curtain	O
,	O
one	O
Pillow	O
,	O
a	O
Flower-pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
double	O
Ruffle	O
,	O
which	O
this	O
Examinant	O
stole	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
and	O
Trunk	O
at	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Daffey	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Williams	O
directly	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
Sister	O
Grace	O
had	O
convey	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
away	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Acton	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Daffey	O
's	O
the	O
Night	O
that	O
Williams	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
well	O
to	O
recommend	O
a	O
Thief	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
blam	O
'd	O
Mary	O
Hughes	O
for	O
behaving	O
so	O
wrong	O
:	O
They	O
whisper	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
not	O
a	O
Word	O
then	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
which	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
we	O
know	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
things	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
'till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
were	O
Boxes	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
Mary	O
's	O
Sister	O
had	O
gutted	O
them	O
by	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
when	O
Grace	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
assisted	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Duke's-Place	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
Grace	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Williams	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Daffey	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rutter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Daffey	O
at	O
Sir	O
William	O
Billers	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
Mary	O
had	O
brought	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
back	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
Grace	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
away	O
at	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
present	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
open	O
'd	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Daffey	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
;	O
we	O
advis	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
Grace	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Boxes	O
and	O
Goods	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Daffey	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
-	O
Thomas	O
.	O
Mary	O
Hughes	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Williams	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
Body	O
,	O
a	O
Country	O
Woman	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
newly	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
from	O
Chester	O
.	O
I	O
believed	O
Williams	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
on	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
found	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Town	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
saucy	O
impudent	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
things	O
while	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
any	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
threatned	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Law	O
if	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
cautious	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
5	O
Weeks	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Daffey	O
's	O
that	O
Evening	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
carrying	O
Mary	O
Hughes	O
away	O
;	O
Williams	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
meet	O
them	O
at	O
Sir	O
William	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
any	O
Goods	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
Boxes	O
and	O
a	O
Trunk	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Daffey	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
stripp	O
'd	O
;	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
lodged	O
some	O
other	O
Boxes	O
and	O
enquire	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Mary	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Williams	O
's	O
House	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
Williams	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Mary	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
her	O
in	O
Barnaby-Street	O
;	O
Williams	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Daffey	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
Grace	O
Hughes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Daffey	O
claim	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Daffey	O
.	O
Mary	O
Hughes	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
Boxes	O
,	O
full	O
of	O
other	O
things	O
at	O
Williams	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
Mary	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
Grace	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Mary	O
Hughes	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
and	O
Grace	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
expected	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinson	O
of	O
Hackney	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
appearing	O
for	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Hughe	O
's	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
giving	O
Williams	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
by	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Perukes	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Ambrose	O
Reason	O
.	O
On	O
Twelfth	O
Day	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
he	O
lay	O
out	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
my	O
Shop	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
4	O
Perukes	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
worth	O
15	O
l.	O
-	O
About	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
even	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Barnes	O
's	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
knowing	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
resort	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
Perkins	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Perukes	O
was	O
at	O
Barnes	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
-	O
Crisp	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Wig	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Barnes	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Reason	O
.	O
This	O
very	O
Wig	O
I	O
made	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Dutch	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
5	O
Guineas	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barnes	O
.	O
He	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
Wigs	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
Friends	O
Account	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
the	O
Wigs	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
shewn	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
Man	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
told	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crisp	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Penniworth	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
,	O
but	O
Perkins	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
25s	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Reason	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
telling	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
it	O
should	O
happen	O
so	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherine-Creedchurch	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
About	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
Aldgate	B-place
alone	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
twice	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
;	O
another	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
between	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
my	O
Hat	O
was	O
whipt	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
then	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Check	O
Shirt	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Great	O
Coat	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
slipt	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
up	O
an	O
Alley	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	O
street	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
jumpt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Coat	O
:	O
Give	O
me	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
assaulting	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
that	O
Night	O
:	O
Next	O
morning	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Brocas	O
committed	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
my	O
Hat	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
my	O
Hat	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Willcox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
belonging	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
call	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
snatch	O
'd	O
my	O
Staff	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
from	O
my	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Noise	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
Coat	O
upon	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
My	O
Partner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
out	O
comes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Coat	O
:	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Hat	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
Hat	O
;	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
you	O
struck	O
me	O
twice	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
:	O
and	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
afterwards	O
,	O
another	O
Watchman	O
going	O
round	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Basket-man	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Tuck	O
about	O
9	O
Inches	O
long	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
this	O
Tussle	O
.	O
-	O
Groom	O
,	O
another	O
Watchman	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Kings	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
his	O
Elbow	O
so	O
violently	O
into	O
my	O
Side	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
ran	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
:	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Stroke	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
resented	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Bustle	O
and	O
Tussle	O
his	O
Hat	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
tore	O
my	O
Coat	O
off	O
my	O
Back	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
against	O
Angel-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Watchman	O
's	O
Stand	O
in	O
that	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Alley	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Cooper	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Coat	O
;	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Coat	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
without	O
Opposition	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
his	O
Hat	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
acquitted	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Power	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
now	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
know	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Security	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
live	O
:	O
He	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
in	O
Mincing-Lane	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
disturb	O
the	O
Family	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Clerk	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Promise	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
next	O
Day	O
at	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Brocas	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mincing-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
they	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Landlord	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
brush	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Fore-room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
unhandsome	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
committed	O
on	O
your	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
you	O
swerve	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
very	O
unhandsome	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
very	O
troublesome	O
prosecuting	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
by	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
only	O
commit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
wronging	O
any	O
Body	O
:	O
He	O
would	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
lye	O
out	O
o'Nights	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
February	O
23	O
.	O
Joshua	O
Thompson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Cloaks	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
at	O
first	O
for	O
a	O
Cloath-colour	O
'd	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
Scarlet	O
:	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
try	O
'd	O
on	O
several	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
parted	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
Mr.	O
Turcan	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
perceiving	O
,	O
she	O
slept	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
throwing	O
the	O
Cloak	O
into	O
an	O
Entry	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
throw	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Edge	O
of	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
had	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
busie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turcan	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Customers	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
trying	O
on	O
the	O
Cloaks	O
:	O
When	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
red	O
hang	O
down	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
below	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cloak	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
any	O
Thing	O
red	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
behind	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
Landlady	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Shop	O
:	O
She	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
See	O
here	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
need	O
we	O
go	O
any	O
further	O
?	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
Cloak	O
lies	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
up	O
comes	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
swear	O
it	O
downright	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
promised	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
only	O
till	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Jayl	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Delaney	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yard	O
,	O
of	O
spotted	O
Lawn	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Mary	O
Pickering	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
perceived	O
they	O
wanted	O
none	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
stooping	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Body	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Hint	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
:	O
They	O
bought	O
a	O
Quarter	O
and	O
Nail	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
immediately	O
the	O
spotted	O
Lawn	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
my	O
Mother	O
saw	O
them	O
turn	O
down	O
the	O
next	O
Court	O
,	O
yet	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
:	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
to	O
desire	O
them	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
one	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
and	O
the	O
Lawn	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Dress	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lawn	O
was	O
very	O
remarkable	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Darns	O
in	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
value	O
the	O
Lawn	O
at	O
40	O
s.	O
John	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Lawn	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
,	O
to	O
inform	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Lawn	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
secured	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
Francis	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Bell	O
Mettle	O
Mortar	O
,	O
weighing	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Goleburn	I-pers
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
And	O
15	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Goleburn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
my	O
Mortar	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Leather-Lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
,	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Goleburn	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
:	O
We	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
half	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Mortar	O
:	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Whitehead	O
for	O
37	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Pope	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Brass	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Iron	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
proved	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
it	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Whitehead	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
bought	O
what	O
we	O
stole	O
;	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
George-Alley	B-place
,	O
at	O
Fleet-Ditch	B-place
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
Pope	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
.	O
-	O
Partridge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
one	O
Evening	O
and	O
Cockran	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
Whitehead	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
fetched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Mortar	O
:	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Chap	O
:	O
She	O
returned	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
Mortar	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
Whitehead	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Peaton	O
's	O
:	O
She	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
what	O
she	O
gave	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
Whitehead	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
Pope	O
and	O
Cockran	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
a	O
Crime	O
?	O
You	O
are	O
on	O
your	O
Oath	O
:	O
Was	O
she	O
not	O
a	O
Receiver	O
of	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
She	O
paid	O
Pope	O
for	O
this	O
Mortar	O
,	O
in	O
Black-Boy-Alley	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
London	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
5th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	O
,	O
marry	O
'd	O
Amy	B-pers
Amos	I-pers
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Old	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
he	O
marry	O
'd	O
Anne	B-pers
Appletree	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
;	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
Davis	O
being	O
arrested	O
for	O
the	O
Felony	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
7	O
Table-Cloaths	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Window-Curtains	O
,	O
1	O
Coral	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
1	O
Quilt	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
brass	O
Candlesticks	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Appletree	I-pers
.	O
John	O
Appletree	O
.	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Knights	B-place
bridge	I-place
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
being	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
committed	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
my	O
Daughter	O
Anne	B-pers
Appletree	I-pers
.	O
About	O
6	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Yeoman	O
in	O
the	O
Guards	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
between	O
other	O
People	O
's	O
Business	O
and	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
often	O
from	O
Home	O
:	O
But	O
one	O
Night	O
coming	O
Home	O
from	O
Duty	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
Daughter	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Knights-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Daughter	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Blue-ball	O
and	O
Horse-shoe	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
:	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
neither	O
sold	O
nor	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
under	O
her	O
Care	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
on	O
Friday	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
got	O
another	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
first	O
Wife	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
padlock	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
told	O
his	O
new	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
too	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
secur	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
to	O
enable	O
him	O
to	O
disannul	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Padlock	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
Warrant	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
a	O
Padlock	O
on	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
every	O
Thing	O
safe	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
all	O
into	O
my	O
Custody	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
they	O
are	O
.	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
Woman	O
swore	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
deposited	O
by	O
her	O
Father	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Knights-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
feloniously	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Appletree	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
single	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
were	O
married	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
removed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
safe	O
under	O
his	O
Care	O
,	O
as	O
mine	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Father	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Custody	O
:	O
He	O
refused	O
indeed	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
against	O
my	O
Consent	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
present	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Trial	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
she	O
informed	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
apprehended	O
her	O
Life	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
declared	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
Blood	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
he	O
gave	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Michael	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
2	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Brass	O
Seal	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
.	O
George	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
to	O
Knights	O
bridge	O
on	O
Monday	O
Se'nnight	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Constitution-hill	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Grimes	O
hit	O
me	O
with	O
an	O
Oaken	O
Stick	O
,	O
made	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Teeth	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
my	O
Gum	O
:	O
The	O
Moon	O
shone	O
upon	O
the	O
Snow	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
very	O
light	O
:	O
Grimes	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
Grimes	O
led	O
me	O
about	O
100	O
Yards	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
Things	O
,	O
rifled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ty	O
'd	O
my	O
Hands	O
and	O
my	O
Legs	O
together	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
Garters	O
:	O
They	O
left	O
me	O
sitting	O
within	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
Pond	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Wilderness	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
either	O
release	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
or	O
bring	O
me	O
more	O
Company	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
with	O
some	O
Difficulty	O
,	O
and	O
jumped	O
along	O
to	O
the	O
Keeper	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
unty	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
Discovery	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Papers	O
occasion	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
They	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
Grimes	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
always	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
Grimes	O
.	O
otherwise	O
Graham	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
my	O
Circumstances	O
he	O
knew	O
were	O
low	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
from	O
Time	O
to	O
Time	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
seduce	O
me	O
to	O
these	O
Courses	O
:	O
He	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
nights	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Success	O
in	O
our	O
Way	O
.	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Sunday	O
we	O
took	O
nothing	O
but	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
we	O
went	O
round	O
Hyde-Park	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
nothing	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
:	O
Come	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
down	O
Constitution-Hill	O
,	O
perhaps	O
we	O
may	O
make	O
something	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
met	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
:	O
The	O
Seals	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
Buckles	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Knives	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
I	O
who	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
Stick	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
behind	O
in	O
order	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
to	O
conceal	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
attack	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Stroke	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
with	O
my	O
Stick	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
Rusty	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
towards	O
the	O
Pond	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Accomplice	O
Grimes	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
when	O
another	O
Man	O
brought	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
4	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
his	O
Size	O
.	O
Grimes	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
very	O
Night	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
:	O
Upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
Grimes	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
will	O
come	O
whom	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
take	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
Grimes	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Mitford	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Information	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
When	O
Grimes	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
O	O
Mr.	O
Grimes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
!	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
Things	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
at	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Knife	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
this	O
Knife	O
and	O
some	O
Gun	O
Powder	O
and	O
some	O
Flints	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pockets	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
O	O
Mr.	O
Grimes	O
!	O
have	O
you	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
at	O
last	O
!	O
Alexander	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
prove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Grimes	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
;	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
3	O
Nights	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick	O
Shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
sell	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
Graham	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
sell	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
,	O
whether	O
Grimes	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
supplied	O
with	O
Money	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
had	O
Money	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
Grimes	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
he	O
was	O
starving	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Laundress	O
.	O
and	O
live	O
by	O
Golden-square	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
behalf	O
On	O
last	O
Monday	O
Se'nnight	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
write	O
me	O
out	O
a	O
Bill	O
for	O
Washing	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Supper	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
almost	O
10	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
Monday	O
Se'nnight	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
wanted	O
the	O
Bill	O
to	O
be	O
wrote	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
Bill	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
One	O
Mr	O
Sale	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
Date	O
to	O
that	O
Bill	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
was	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
produce	O
that	O
Bill	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
unlucky	O
;	O
because	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Sale	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Reputation	O
,	O
this	O
Circumstance	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
Weight	O
.	O
-	O
Pray	O
where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Humphrey	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Cheesemonger	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
from	O
6	O
to	O
10	O
.	O
Pray	O
does	O
any	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Humphrey	O
's	O
People	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Entry	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Shop	O
is	O
shut	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
through	O
:	O
When	O
a	O
House	O
is	O
full	O
of	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
they	O
seldom	O
take	O
notice	O
who	O
comes	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
here	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
but	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
washed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Linnen	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
served	O
the	O
Lord	O
Southwell	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Holland	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Lady	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Princess	O
of	O
Orange	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Place	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
his	O
Constitution	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
England	O
.	O
Another	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
speak	O
nothing	O
but	O
Truth	O
:	O
This	O
young	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Room	O
from	O
6	O
to	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Monday	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
provided	O
the	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
Child	O
at	O
this	O
Instant	O
of	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
Anderson	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
Lord	O
Southwell	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
from	O
Holland	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Character	O
to	O
two	O
Places	O
.	O
Luttwich	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Goodhall	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
when	O
Grimes	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
smoke	O
a	O
Pipe	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Graimes	O
called	O
him	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
.	O
Grimes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Goodhall	O
's	O
Parlour	O
;	O
when	O
one	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
wink	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Good-hall	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
charge	O
him	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
Pint	O
and	O
my	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
Grimes	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Grimes	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
.	O
Luttwich	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
Rascal	O
,	O
have	O
not	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
often	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
frequent	O
such	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
mention	O
the	O
Powder	O
nor	O
Flints	O
.	O
You	O
Villain	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
have	O
not	O
I	O
desired	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Chapel	O
and	O
hear	O
Mass	O
,	O
and	O
warned	O
you	O
against	O
such	O
Company	O
?	O
Luttwich	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
meet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
gone	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
serve	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
Beer-house	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
said	O
any	O
Thing	O
about	O
the	O
Flints	O
and	O
the	O
Powder	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
Men	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
a	O
Question	O
or	O
two	O
apart	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
withdraw	O
.	O
Q.	O
T	O
,	O
Morpan	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
for	O
Supper	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Morg	O
.	O
Breast	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
Turnips	O
,	O
and	O
Broth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
Supper	O
ready	O
?	O
Morg	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
doing	O
till	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
?	O
Morg	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
6	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
likewise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
drink	O
?	O
Morg	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
small	O
Beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
nothing	O
but	O
small	O
Beer	O
from	O
6	O
to	O
9	O
?	O
Morg	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
one	O
Bottle	O
of	O
small	O
Beer	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
,	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Supper	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
one	O
Bottle	O
of	O
small	O
Beer	O
?	O
Morg	O
.	O
Nothing	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
Bottle	O
of	O
small	O
Beer	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
any	O
Thing	O
till	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
withdraw	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
called	O
into	O
Court	O
.	O
2d	O
Woman	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
o'Night	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
Se'nnight	O
?	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
my	O
Partner	O
was	O
out	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
Woman	O
.	O
About	O
6	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
10	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
pass	O
the	O
Time	O
?	O
Woman	O
In	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Manner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Plain	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
reading	O
a	O
good	O
Book	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
drink	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Woman	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
strong	O
Beer	O
.	O
Q.	O
Whence	O
did	O
you	O
fetch	O
it	O
?	O
Woman	O
.	O
From	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
fetch	O
it	O
?	O
Woman	O
.	O
Not	O
till	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
Breast	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
Turnips	O
,	O
and	O
Broth	O
for	O
Supper	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
nothing	O
else	O
to	O
drink	O
all	O
this	O
Time	O
?	O
Woman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
drink	O
of	O
this	O
Strong	O
Beer	O
?	O
Woman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
tasted	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Small	O
Beer	O
?	O
Woman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
18.	O
John	B-pers
Pennelow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Drab	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
my	O
Lord	O
Cardgan	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
left	O
upon	O
the	O
Coach-Box	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	B-place
and	I-place
Horses	I-place
,	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
Hundred	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gammon	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hervieu	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Hester	B-pers
Dumontier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Matfelon	I-place
,	I-place
otherwise	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calimanco-Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19.	O
Jane	B-pers
Batteley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Quilter	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Street	O
,	O
in	O
Houndsditch	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Journey-woman	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
Work	O
at	O
the	O
Frame	O
last	O
Thursday	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
Coat	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
out	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
she	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
in	O
Half-Moon-Court	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
for	O
11	O
s.	O
Justice	O
Rickets	O
ordered	O
me	O
the	O
Coat	O
again	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
11s	O
.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Battiley	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
so	O
mean	O
Condition	O
;	O
when	O
so	O
many	O
Gentlemen	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
gets	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
Leave	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
make	O
Money	O
of	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
better	O
Apparel	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
;	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24,25.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Goose	O
,	O
one	O
Hen	O
Turkey	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Gurnell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
John	B-pers
Eagle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Knee-buckles	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baskerville	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Baskerville	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Hamlet	O
,	O
in	O
White-horse-street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
together	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
3	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
.	O
The	O
Buttons	O
were	O
on	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Buckles	O
in	O
my	O
Breeches	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Buttons	O
cut	O
off	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
a	O
Chair	O
close	O
to	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
lay	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
we	O
were	O
up	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
his	O
Mittimus	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
discharge	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
work	O
his	O
Finger-nails	O
off	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
amends	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Buttons	O
were	O
on	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Buttons	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Land-lord	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
3	O
who	O
lay	O
in	O
one	O
Bed	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Odey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Landlord	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Buttons	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Frock	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
my	O
Wife	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
go	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
three	O
Times	O
who	O
's	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
answer	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
Love	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
this	O
;	O
the	O
Door	O
is	O
open	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
ourselves	O
and	O
these	O
3	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Laytons	O
at	O
Redriffe	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
:	O
Suspecting	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
:	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
care	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27	O
,	O
28.	O
Martha	B-pers
Hoards	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Chess	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
32	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Change	O
at	O
Rag	O
fair	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Place	O
like	O
Exeter	B-place
Exchange	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
(	O
Chess	O
)	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
robb	O
'd	O
when	O
she	O
pass	O
'd	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
when	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
one	O
(	O
Hoards	O
)	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
Ribbon	O
;	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
not	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
from	O
my	O
Counter	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Allen	O
take	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
one	O
's	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
one	O
ran	O
away	O
Barbara	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
take	O
One	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
another	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
:	O
The	O
two	O
Allens	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
young	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
Cock-eye	O
(	O
the	O
old	O
one	O
)	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
might	O
take	O
Cock-eye	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
her	O
being	O
taken	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Night	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
O	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
Cock-eye	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
for	O
safety	O
'till	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Hoards	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Chess	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Clemency	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Napkin	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Towel	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
William	O
Bull	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
a	O
Lodging	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Linnen	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
privately	O
left	O
her	O
Lodging	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
return	O
them	O
when	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
Money	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
lodge	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
went	O
to	O
Wapping	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Friends	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
my	O
Pails	O
,	O
Yoaks	O
and	O
Strainers	O
;	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
4	O
Caps	O
and	O
2	O
Flannel	O
Petticoats	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
and	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
is	O
only	O
out	O
of	O
Spight	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
has	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
help	O
that	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Croaker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
2	O
Shirts	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Wright	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Hackney-writer	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
in	O
December	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
I	O
redeemed	O
them	O
,	O
hoping	O
he	O
would	O
mend	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
January	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
Money	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Places	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
this	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
Chambers	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fly	O
for't	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Directions	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
say	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
hard	O
usage	O
lay	O
'd	O
him	O
under	O
this	O
Temptation	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
hir	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
frequently	O
employ	O
him	O
in	O
Business	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
constantly	O
deducted	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pay	O
for	O
those	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
redeem	O
and	O
restore	O
them	O
when	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
rais	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Raphael	I-pers
de	I-pers
Silva	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Diamonds	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
.	O
Benjamin	O
Mumsord	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Polisher	O
,	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
these	O
Diamonds	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
to	O
Polish	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Liberty	O
to	O
work	O
them	O
either	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
he	O
absented	O
himself	O
longer	O
than	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
Sleep	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
Jewels	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
before	O
.	O
As	O
this	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Breach	O
of	O
Trust	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
32.	O
Richard	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
demanding	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
,	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Davis	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
John	O
Davis	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
behind	O
Hoxton	B-place
Chappel	I-place
-wall	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Boy	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
to	O
light	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
taken	O
the	O
Link	O
from	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
I	O
step	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
pass	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Good	O
Night	O
Gentlemen	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Link	O
but	O
miss	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
with	O
my	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Dick	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
alone	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Boy	O
some	O
little	O
Time	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
ran	O
for	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
presently	O
made	O
off	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fair	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Notion	O
have	O
you	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
?	O
Holt	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
speak	O
truth	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
Hell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
Uncles	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Burying	O
Ground	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Old-street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
light	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
3d	O
.	O
to	O
Light	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ivey-House	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
got	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
and	O
Goose	O
Door	O
we	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
bit	O
and	O
lighted	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
turning	O
into	O
another	O
Field	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
2	O
Men	O
coming	O
;	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
stood	O
up	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
pass	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
Good	O
Night	O
:	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
step	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
deliver	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
:	O
He	O
aim	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Head	O
but	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
bobb	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stick	O
lit	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Link	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Dick	O
Swift	O
let	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Minute	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
run	O
?	O
Damn	O
it	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
we	O
walk	O
along	O
the	O
Path	O
?	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
Green	O
Apron	O
on	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
the	I-pers
Elder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Father	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
charge	O
my	O
Son	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Master	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Boy	O
call	O
'd	O
;	O
Aye	O
says	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
Dick	O
Swift	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Green-Apron	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old-Street	O
,	O
almost	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Ask	O
's	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
my	O
Son	O
twice	O
that	O
Night	O
into	O
Field-Lane	O
;	O
He	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
he	O
returned	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
8	O
:	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
Time	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Woman	O
from	O
Fleet-Lane	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
33.	O
John	B-pers
Peter	I-pers
Scarinbone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
a	O
Salver	O
,	O
12	O
Spoons	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Rayne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Steal	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
inlay	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hulse	I-pers
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Hulse	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
Chancery-Lane-End	B-place
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Hurry	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Scabbard	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
my	O
Servant	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
some	O
Body	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
Sword	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Minute	O
between	O
my	O
losing	O
it	O
and	O
seizing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
swore	O
the	O
same	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Anne	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Busaglo	I-pers
.	O
21	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Barbery	O
Ducat	O
value	O
8	O
s	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Barbary	O
silver	O
Ducat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
Purse	O
.	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Moneys	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Busaglo	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Busaglo	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
both	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Church	B-place
Row	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
more	O
than	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
pray	O
come	O
Home	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
:	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Nurse	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Children	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
House-Maid	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
5	O
Months	O
Wages	O
and	O
wonder	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
going	O
without	O
her	O
Money	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
Home	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
every	O
Rag	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Trunk	O
empty	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
taken	O
something	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
left	O
her	O
Wages	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
miss	O
'd	O
nothing	O
there	O
;	O
upon	O
searching	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
my	O
Desk	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Lock	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
)	O
in	O
Hungerford	O
Market	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
3	O
Guineas	O
I	O
had	O
promis	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Reward	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Purse	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
carryed	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
who	O
returned	O
me	O
the	O
Purse	O
with	O
18	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Barbary	O
Coin	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
50	O
Pound	O
Bond	O
to	O
indemnify	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
this	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
false	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
show	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
she	O
assisted	O
in	O
finding	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Confession	O
before	O
me	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
twice	O
over	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Read	O
the	O
Examination	O
.	O
This	O
Examinant	O
voluntarily	O
confesseth	O
,	O
That	O
last	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
she	O
privately	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
writing	O
Desk	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Basaglo	I-pers
,	O
one	O
green	O
Purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
18	O
or	O
19	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
this	O
Examinant	O
faith	O
not	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
in	O
Hungerford	O
Market	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
above	O
10	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Maid	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
d	O
for	O
18	O
Pen	O
'	O
worth	O
of	O
Punch	O
;	O
while	O
it	O
was	O
making	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
so	O
late	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
she	O
might	O
lye	O
with	O
my	O
Maid	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
lye	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
before	O
my	O
Wife	O
or	O
I	O
were	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
Maid	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
an	O
honest	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
must	O
lose	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
They	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
2	O
Hours	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Tenant	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
late	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
them	O
lye	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
lye	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Bed	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
small	O
Table-bed	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
shift	O
to	O
pig	O
in	O
any	O
how	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
'till	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
expecting	O
her	O
Maid	O
again	O
)	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Purse	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
2	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
be	O
present	O
;	O
they	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
18	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Ducat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
when	O
she	O
made	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
kind	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
36	O
,	O
37.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lawn	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Vedast	I-place
,	I-place
Foster	I-place
lane	I-place
.	O
William	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Linnen-Draper	O
in	O
Cheap	B-place
side	I-place
;	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
White	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
Ell	O
of	O
Holland	O
:	O
Ann	O
Jones	O
came	O
in	O
immediately	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
White	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
half	O
Ell	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
likewise	O
a	O
Draper	O
,	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
and	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
would	O
search	O
her	O
:	O
He	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
and	O
held	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lawn	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
:	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
marked	O
in	O
the	O
End	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
shown	O
some	O
Lawns	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Pieces	O
Lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
discovered	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
clear	O
'd	O
my	O
Counter	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
nothing	O
near	O
them	O
.	O
White	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
followed	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
running	O
one	O
to	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
laid	O
5	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
.	O
White	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
tore	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
abruptly	O
going	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
back	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prevent	O
her	O
conveying	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
Arms	O
open	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
one	O
Hand	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Lawn	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
kick	O
and	O
spurn	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
to	O
White	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
Anne	O
Jones	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Mary	O
White	O
guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
defrauded	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
sent	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
for	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Isinglass	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ballard	O
and	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
had	O
secretly	O
marked	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
the	O
Money	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
acquit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Remedy	O
at	O
Law	O
for	O
a	O
Breach	O
of	O
Trust	O
.	O
39.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Visage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Sommerset	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gallon	O
Pewter	O
ot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Eschurchey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Holderness	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
offered	O
the	O
Pot	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
so	O
little	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
secured	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Pot	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Street	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Churches	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Pot	O
from	O
Jones	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
William	B-pers
Burbrook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
Bishop's-Gate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pint	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
January	O
16th	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
than	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
with	O
Beer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sawl	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
and	O
heard	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
and	O
I	O
cacht	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
Bailiffs	O
.	O
and	O
up	O
came	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
Officers	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
telling	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Tankard	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
shewing	O
my	O
Authority	O
,	O
the	O
Men	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
,	O
all	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Servant	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Tankark	O
at	O
my	O
Foot	O
and	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Assistance	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
half	O
Peck	O
Loa	O
and	O
passing	O
by	O
this	O
d	O
or	O
,	O
2	O
Men	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
Artillery-Lane	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
41.	O
Stephen	B-pers
otherwise	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Albert	B-pers
Nesbit	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Best	I-pers
.	O
I	O
serve	O
Mr.	O
Nesbit	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
laid	O
the	O
Cloath	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
according	O
to	O
Custom	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
4	O
Salts	O
,	O
four/Salt-Shovels	O
and	O
four	O
Spoons	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
dress	O
myself	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
mend	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Entry	O
dirty	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
for	O
something	O
for	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Salts	O
,	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Salt-shovels	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
House-keeper	O
,	O
a	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Buffet	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Plate	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Silversmith	O
who	O
made	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
the	O
Spoon	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Gilchrist	I-pers
.	O
After	O
Mr.	O
Nesbit	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
caused	O
Advertisements	O
to	O
be	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
two	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
and	O
no	O
Questions	O
ask	O
'd	O
:	O
About	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
as	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
gave	O
out	O
the	O
Bills	O
,	O
was	O
putting	O
one	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Newsome	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
stopt	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
us	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Newsome	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
brought	O
this	O
Spoon	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
valued	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
bring	O
somebody	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
appear	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
Cow	O
cross	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
a	O
Sea-faring	O
Man	O
:	O
He	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
;	O
I	O
play	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
won	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
a	O
Ring	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
play	O
against	O
that	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Gold	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
refused	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
Money	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
10s	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
won	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
worth	O
14s	O
.	O
and	O
wanted	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Value	O
:	O
why	O
then	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
live	O
but	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
entrust	O
you	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
't	O
is	O
worth	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
stopt	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
present	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Man	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
absconded	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
.	O
Gilchrist	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
told	O
by	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
her	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
about	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
a	O
Grubber	O
,	O
one	O
who	O
sweeps	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
heard	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
talking	O
of	O
Newgate	O
Nan	O
,	O
or	O
Pin	O
Nan	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
find	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Cow-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
New-gate	O
Nan	O
,	O
or	O
Pin	O
Nan	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
wanted	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
we	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Grubber	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
well	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
tidy	O
Fellow	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
spend	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Guineas	O
at	O
Cards	O
:	O
The	O
Constable	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Newgate	O
Nan	O
,	O
or	O
Pin	O
Nan	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Newgate	O
Nan	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Warrant	O
back	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
City	O
Constable	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
word	O
to	O
march	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
Liquor	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
march	O
:	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
says	O
Newgate	O
Nan	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
not	O
sir	O
,	O
till	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
's	O
worth	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
to	O
persuade	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
it	O
;	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
a	O
Word	O
to	O
the	O
Wise	O
is	O
enough	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Brandyshop	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
frequented	O
my	O
House	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
civil	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
drunk	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Chalkley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
right	O
against	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
an	O
Embroiderer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
followed	O
sometimes	O
Portering	O
,	O
sometimes	O
Coal-heaving	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
carrying	O
a	O
Basket	O
in	O
Newgate-market	O
for	O
his	O
Living	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
Sea	O
about	O
7	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
a	O
Talk	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
been	O
transported	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
glad	O
if	O
the	O
Man	O
I	O
won	O
the	O
Spoon	O
of	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
.	O
Q.	O
Aye	O
;	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
odd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
you	O
won	O
it	O
of	O
should	O
not	O
appear	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Newsome	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
won	O
the	O
Spoon	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
quick	O
Work	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
lost	O
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
Two	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
And	O
