TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
WILLIAMS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1736	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXVI	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
Matthias	B-pers
Prime	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jevon	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Cunnick	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Tunstall	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Calloway	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Munn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hosler	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Worral	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
Brass-Sliders	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
41	O
Brass-Heads	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Arundell	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
William	O
Arundell	O
.	O
I	O
make	O
Sliding-Heads	O
for	O
Tellescopes	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
70	O
Sliders	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Brass	O
Heads	O
;	O
35	O
Heads	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
work	O
secretly	O
with	O
an	O
Engine	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
counted	O
over	O
an	O
hundred	O
Dozen	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Dozen	O
of	O
them	O
wanting	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dolley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
being	O
Constable	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
small	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Arundell	O
pick	O
'd	O
these	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
prepared	O
the	O
Brass	O
for	O
the	O
Engine	O
to	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
this	O
Engine	O
,	O
I	O
slip	O
'd	O
in	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Pieces	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
prepar	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
cut	O
with	O
300	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
cut	O
them	O
without	O
discovering	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
bought	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
2.	O
William	B-pers
Caddy	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ackland	I-pers
,	O
August	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Pewter	O
,	O
value	O
33	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pewter-Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Soop	O
.	O
Dish	O
,	O
6	O
Pewter-Plates	O
,	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Sauce-boat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4	O
,	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
,	O
9.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
Isabel	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gutheridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Anthill	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Eavley	I-pers
,	O
August	O
16	O
.	O
Edward	O
Eavley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Black-Fryers	O
about	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Alice	B-pers
King	I-pers
in	O
Ludgate-Street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Cheapside	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
she	O
would	O
show	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Black	B-place
and	I-place
White-Court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Old-Baily	I-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
comes	O
to	O
6	O
d.	O
said	O
she	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
return	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
words	O
about	O
my	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
other	O
5	O
Women	O
came	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Hands	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
Do	O
n't	O
pick	O
my	O
Pocket	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
say	O
'd	O
they	O
;	O
but	O
Susan	O
Anthill	O
,	O
by	O
Violence	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
half	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
jump	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
about	O
me	O
at	O
once	O
;	O
One	O
had	O
her	O
Hands	O
about	O
my	O
Wast	O
;	O
another	O
unty	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Apron	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Porter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
Porter	O
do	O
very	O
wisely	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
these	O
Women	O
?	O
Alice	B-pers
Bunningham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
which	O
of	O
your	O
Mistresses	O
did	O
this	O
Man	O
charge	O
with	O
stealing	O
his	O
Watch	O
?	O
Bunningham	O
.	O
Susan	O
Anthill	O
ran	O
down	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
jump	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
she	O
went	O
directly	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Porter	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Anthill	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Bar	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Woman	O
and	O
that	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
make	O
haste	O
home	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Door	O
broke	O
,	O
my	O
Maid	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
a	O
Watch	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
told	O
my	O
Maid	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
New	O
Gown	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
transport	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
come	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
this	O
Maid	O
for	O
your	O
Evidence	O
?	O
Eavley	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Beadle	O
)	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Anthill	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
has	O
had	O
many	O
a	O
Shilling	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Beadle	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
Hubbub	O
at	O
Anthill	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
Anthill	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
suffer	O
'd	O
such	O
doings	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
soon	O
he	O
routed	O
away	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
my	O
impudent	O
Maid	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
stamping	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
we	O
were	O
admitted	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
:	O
We	O
made	O
them	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
4	O
Women	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
(	O
Anthill	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
)	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Frocas	I-pers
,	O
who	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
He	O
granted	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
Anthill	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
she	O
absconded	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
afterwards	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
last	O
Night	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
for	O
2	O
Guineas	O
.	O
They	O
keep	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
remove	O
them	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
removed	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Quantity	O
of	O
them	O
already	O
.	O
Anthill	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
64	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
a	O
velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
3	O
velvet	O
Girdles	O
,	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Gartering	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
silk	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
laced	O
with	O
Gold	O
;	O
one	O
Wastcoat	O
laced	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
August	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12	O
,	O
13.	O
Edward	B-pers
Row	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ratcliff	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
1735	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Gibson	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Time	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
my	O
Servant	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Bake	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Servant	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Thing	O
we	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
out	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Outcry	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
long	O
Pole	O
(	O
with	O
which	O
we	O
rub	O
the	O
Fire	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
Oven	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
Pole	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
fir	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
Breast	O
and	O
my	O
Arm	O
:	O
A	O
second	O
Pistol	O
wounded	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
backwards	O
:	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
their	O
Arms	O
and	O
laid	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Bake-House	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
brought	O
my	O
Man	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
Candles	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
ty	O
'd	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
him	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
:	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
over	O
us	O
while	O
the	O
others	O
robbed	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
according	O
to	O
our	O
Information	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
Information	O
,	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
executed	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
committed	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
sted	O
to	O
Ireland	O
,	O
but	O
Ward	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
the	O
Information	O
against	O
Row	O
and	O
Hampton	O
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
will	O
swear	O
to	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
will	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Eryan	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Bake	O
house	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
for	O
a	O
Scovel	O
which	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
Backside	O
of	O
the	O
Oven	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
Back	O
house	O
,	O
Row	O
and	O
his	O
Companions	O
rushed	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
surprized	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
were	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
they	O
presented	O
Pistols	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
Row	O
stood	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
to	O
guard	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
rest	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
discharge	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Flash	O
of	O
the	O
Powder	O
.	O
Row	O
afterwards	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Bake-house	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
my	O
Master	O
lie	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
:	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
stand	O
with	O
my	O
Face	O
to	O
the	O
Oven	O
's	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
own	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
about	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
rest	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
rifle	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
They	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
strong	O
Door	O
of	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
they	O
thought	O
proper	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Hampton	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
make	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ireland	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
Hall	O
and	O
Dillon	O
:	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
Bridgewater	O
.	O
Row	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
Dublin	O
last	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
over	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
Bridgewater	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
Ward	O
's	O
Confession	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
Ward	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
would	O
make	O
haste	O
and	O
get	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
Service	O
to	O
the	O
Town	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
his	O
Evidence	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
fuller	O
Discovery	O
than	O
Ward	O
had	O
done	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
might	O
recollect	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
more	O
merciful	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
than	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Rest	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
is	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Pain	O
.	O
Row	O
stood	O
as	O
a	O
Guard	O
,	O
and	O
Ward	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Row	O
was	O
indeed	O
more	O
merciful	O
.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Ward	O
and	O
Row	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Ward	O
and	O
Row	O
were	O
together	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
bought	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swore	O
that	O
Ward	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
another	O
Man	O
now	O
in	O
Custody	O
at	O
Dublin	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
brought	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
Hampton	O
may	O
appear	O
.	O
Ward	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Information	O
.	O
Row	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Hampton	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
14.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hornbrook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
of	O
a	O
wan	O
Colour	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Merry	O
.	O
My	O
Horse	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Church-yard	O
of	O
Yalling	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Huntingdon	I-place
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
cry	O
'd	O
at	O
St.	O
Ives	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
other	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
this	O
next	O
Witness	O
Mr.	O
Unwin	O
gave	O
me	O
Information	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Unwin	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Well-street	O
,	O
near	O
Well-Close-Square	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
2	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
one	O
was	O
enough	O
for	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
sit	O
for	O
a	O
Saddle	O
or	O
a	O
Chaise	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
wan	O
Gelding	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
worth	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Guineas	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
him	O
at	O
any	O
Price	O
.	O
The	O
Horse	O
was	O
in	O
very	O
bad	O
Condition	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
Onions	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
for	O
Onions	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Boy	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Information	O
.	O
Cox	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
swept	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
Laughing	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
laughed	O
at	O
;	O
why	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
Saddle	O
and	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
come	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Pannel	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
open	O
the	O
Gate	O
;	O
he	O
rode	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
came	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
13.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
divers	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Sides	O
;	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Green	O
did	O
languish	O
,	O
and	O
languishingly	O
liv	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
Green	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hathwell	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
on	O
other	O
Parts	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
which	O
with	O
a	O
Pleuretic	O
Fever	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Widow	O
:	O
He	O
dy	O
'd	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
seennight	O
before	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
bed	O
Condition	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Hurt	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
by	O
a	O
Blow	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Hurt	O
:	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
afterwards	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
bleed	O
him	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
continu	O
'd	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Pain	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
continu	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
:	O
It	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
uneasy	O
if	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
hurt	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
get	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
right	O
myself	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
2	O
of	O
their	O
Men	O
had	O
been	O
gaming	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
,	O
to	O
lend	O
the	O
Looser	O
:	O
Tom	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lent	O
his	O
Shirt	O
to	O
;	O
who	O
refusing	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Morris	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Blows	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bransbury	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
blooded	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
blooded	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
grew	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
lye	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
constantly	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
(	O
the	O
Day	O
he	O
dyed	O
,	O
)	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
Blow	O
Morris	O
gave	O
you	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
your	O
Death	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
say	O
'd	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
follow	O
the	O
Law	O
?	O
Do	O
what	O
you	O
please	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
he	O
deserves	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
forgiven	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bransbury	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
complaining	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
Shortness	O
of	O
Breath	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
very	O
uneasy	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
spit	O
Blood	O
,	O
or	O
made	O
bloody	O
Urine	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
blooded	O
twice	O
:	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
easier	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
his	O
Pain	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
lie	O
down	O
for	O
the	O
Shortness	O
of	O
his	O
Breath	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Decay	O
in	O
his	O
Constitution	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Bruises	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
complain	O
of	O
any	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
on	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Bruises	O
were	O
mortal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bransbury	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Adhesion	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
consumptive	O
Case	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
drank	O
hard	O
,	O
particularly	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
drink	O
Drams	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
formerly	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
off	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Bruises	O
had	O
occasion	O
'd	O
some	O
inward	O
mortal	O
Disorder	O
,	O
would	O
there	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Disorder	O
,	O
as	O
bloody	O
Urine	O
,	O
spitting	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
?	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Millaway	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
Skettles	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
play	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lost	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
play	O
for	O
his	O
Shirt	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
:	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
lend	O
his	O
Shirt	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
lost	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
losing	O
,	O
asked	O
the	O
Deceased	O
for	O
his	O
Shirt	O
;	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
growing	O
a	O
little	O
coldish	O
without	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
another	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
quarrelling	O
push	O
'd	O
one	O
another	O
against	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
broke	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sat	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
insisting	O
on	O
having	O
his	O
Shirt	O
again	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
above	O
6	O
Blows	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
observe	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
Blows	O
of	O
any	O
Consequence	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
over	O
:	O
after	O
this	O
they	O
sat	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
yellow	O
and	O
bad	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
fallen	O
from	O
a	O
Scaffold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Wood	O
15	O
Foot	O
long	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Ledger	O
fell	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bruis	O
'd	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
breath	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
John	O
Green	O
dy	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Consumption	O
.	O
15.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	O
Stevens	O
,	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
And	O
Mary	B-pers
Shropshire	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Finney	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	O
Stevens	O
,	O
July	O
21	O
.	O
And	O
Mary	O
Shropshire	O
and	O
Anne	O
Finney	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
owned	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Stevens	O
of	O
3	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
2	O
Women	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
Barrets	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
fetched	O
out	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Barret	O
.	O
Finney	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
pawned	O
this	O
Watch	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
Another	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawned	O
at	O
Haydon	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Finney	I-pers
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
John	O
Thomas	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
Finney	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
body	O
would	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
take	O
in	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Pawnbrokers	O
;	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
Barret	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
Account	O
Barret	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
hers	O
in	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
Finney	O
and	O
Shropshire	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
from	O
my	O
3	O
Infants	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Watch	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Haydon	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
's	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lent	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
my	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
Boy	O
.	O
July	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
(	O
Scott	O
)	O
brought	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
12	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Scott	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Watch	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
these	O
Watches	O
were	O
hung	O
in	O
a	O
Glass-Case	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
Thomas	O
told	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Case	O
open	O
one	O
time	O
;	O
another	O
time	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Key	O
hang	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
Gold	O
Watches	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
one	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Heart	O
misgave	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
.	O
John	O
Thomas	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Shropshire	O
and	O
Finney	O
,	O
Transportation	O
.	O
16	O
,	O
17.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dwyer	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
O	I-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Maintrew	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Tortoishell	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Stock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
.	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
31	O
st	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
32	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
7	O
Shillings	O
,	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Maintrew	I-pers
.	O
July	O
the	O
31st	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Horton	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	O
;	O
at	O
Beggars-bush	B-place
,	I-place
between	I-place
Acton	I-place
and	I-place
Kensington	I-place
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
Bridge	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Dunghill	O
and	O
a	O
Gate	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Bridge	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
a	O
black	O
Horse	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
their	O
left	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Truncheon	O
in	O
their	O
right	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
me	O
dismount	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
then	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
and	O
searched	O
my	O
Pockets	O
:	O
They	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
They	O
gagg	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
stripp	O
'd	O
me	O
quite	O
naked	O
;	O
my	O
Hands	O
were	O
ty	O
'd	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
left	O
Leg	O
fasten	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
right	O
Leg	O
lash	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
drew	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ditch	O
into	O
a	O
Furrow	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
'till	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Man	O
coming	O
by	O
released	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
their	O
Faces	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
'till	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
3	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Barns	O
.	O
Dwyer	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
he	O
desired	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
O	O
Neal	O
when	O
my	O
Beadle	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
too	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Slugs	O
which	O
I	O
drew	O
out	O
of	O
O	O
Neal	O
's	O
Pistols	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
at	O
the	O
Barr	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Stone-bridge	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Harrow	O
road	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
O	O
Neal	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Horse	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
Dwyer	O
lay	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
me	O
about	O
20	O
Poles	O
length	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
Under	O
a	O
Hedge	O
they	O
laid	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
O	O
Neal	O
took	O
7	O
Guineas	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
my	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
my	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Cloth	O
and	O
Buttons	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
:	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
Dwyer	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
O	O
Neal	O
pulled	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
my	O
Hands	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
Dwyer	O
got	O
upon	O
my	O
Horse	O
and	O
rode	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
O	O
Neal	O
bid	O
me	O
lye	O
still	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
bring	O
me	O
more	O
Company	O
presently	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
met	O
them	O
both	O
upon	O
my	O
black	O
Horse	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
riding	O
off	O
;	O
they	O
rid	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
they	O
thought	O
proper	O
,	O
then	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
Buckles	O
upon	O
O	O
Neal	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Buckles	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
'till	O
Thursday	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
from	O
Turnham	O
green	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
taken	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
such	O
Goods	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
O	O
Neal	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
Newman	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Paddington	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
:	O
We	O
drank	O
together	O
at	O
Halsden-green	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
2	O
Men	O
upon	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Horse	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
O	O
Neal	O
rid	O
hindmost	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
my	O
Maid	O
found	O
his	O
Whip	O
:	O
We	O
printed	O
Bills	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
Dwyer	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
being	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
The	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
James	O
's	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
Grosvener	O
square	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
dealt	O
in	O
Lace	O
and	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
Packs	O
about	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
They	O
lodged	O
about	O
9	O
Days	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Time	O
they	O
lay	O
out	O
4	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
2	O
Nights	O
successively	O
:	O
Once	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
they	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
and	O
fought	O
about	O
sharing	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Bed	O
:	O
My	O
People	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
charge	O
them	O
on	O
suspicion	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
without	O
a	O
Warrant	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
a	O
Justice	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
Dwyer	O
coming	O
to	O
a	O
Pawnbrokers	O
to	O
redeem	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
Dwyer	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Viel	O
,	O
who	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
two	O
several	O
Times	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
O	O
Neal	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
near	O
Brentford	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Brentford	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
:	O
O	O
Neal	O
was	O
now	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Hawkins	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
.	O
Dwyer	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
ill	O
or	O
hurt	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Dwyer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Buckles	O
upon	O
O	O
Neal	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Dwyer	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
O	O
Neal	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
Folly	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
Fever	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
dispute	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
18.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Balanger	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
12	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buck-skin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Dimity-Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Elenor	B-pers
Crouder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Pillow-biers	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Mazier	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Darby	B-pers
Bourk	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Kittel	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Chinnick	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
William	O
Chinnick	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Green	O
Grocers	O
Cellar	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Rose-Tavern	O
in	O
Russel-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
Cellar	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
within	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
full	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Lamps	O
:	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
Side	O
Pocket	O
:	O
the	O
Mob	O
gather	O
'd	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
so	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
comes	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
mow	O
him	O
down	O
like	O
Grass	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
3	O
Yards	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
Cellar-Door	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
a	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
Custom	O
)	O
for	O
my	O
Half-penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
Chinnick	O
down	O
;	O
Watch	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
ran	O
:	O
they	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
mow	O
down	O
like	O
Grass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
done	O
very	O
quick	O
:	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Company	O
came	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
yet	O
your	O
Money	O
was	O
snap	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
again	O
you	O
say	O
;	O
would	O
it	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
natural	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
have	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
then	O
?	O
Chinnick	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
swear	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
my	O
Money	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taken	O
?	O
Chinnick	O
.	O
About	O
7	O
Weeks	O
after	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Midford	O
for	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
only	O
to	O
an	O
Assault	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
squabble	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Chinnick	O
.	O
I	O
swore	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
happen	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Chinnick	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
Blows	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Watch	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
giving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
21.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ell	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Sign	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
William	B-pers
Jordon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
24.	O
Simon	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bois	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Hose	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Christial	O
Stone	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
Frances	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Porrage	O
Pot	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
a	O
flat	O
Iron	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Skiller	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
and	O
a	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Turbot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen-Apron	O
,	O
2	O
Linnen-sheets	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
flat	O
Iron	O
;	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
and	O
Heater	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
;	O
a	O
Muslin-Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick-Handkerchief	O
,	O
2	O
Damask-Clouts	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
August	O
19	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen-shirt	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthias	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
July	O
1	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30.	O
Susan	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckskin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen-Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Dimity-Mantle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lary	I-pers
,	O
August	O
17th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Plush	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
September	O
6th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32.	O
Mark	B-pers
Duree	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
called	O
Guineas	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Doleman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
sen.	O
August	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Doleman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
(	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Brown	O
's	O
House	O
)	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
lock	O
'd	O
:	O
but	O
upon	O
opening	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Bag	O
empty	O
;	O
14	O
Guineas	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
my	O
Landlady	O
(	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
abroad	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
enquired	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
no	O
body	O
:	O
some	O
body	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
is	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
Duree	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Son	O
John	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
both	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
my	O
Landlord	O
was	O
come	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
Mark	B-pers
Duree	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
rak	O
'd	O
about	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
10	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
at	O
Sheerness	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Chimney	O
Sweeper	O
.	O
The	O
Chimney	O
Sweeper	O
's	O
Brother	O
found	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
Mark	O
's	O
Mother	O
who	O
secreted	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
permit	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
without	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Place	O
appointed	O
was	O
the	O
Black-horse	O
in	O
Nightingale	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Mother	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
a	O
Millener	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
sometimes	O
1	O
Guinea	O
;	O
sometimes	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Son	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
follow	O
'd	O
this	O
Practice	O
for	O
6	O
Weeks	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
Key	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Happiness	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
Warrant	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
;	O
there	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
voluntarily	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
on	O
Oath	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
read	O
in	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
promised	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
Hair	O
on	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Son	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
always	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
turns	O
,	O
who	O
should	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
Doleman	O
's	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
where	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
his	O
Drawers	O
was	O
put	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Brother	O
who	O
is	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Chimney	O
Sweeper	O
on	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Hill	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
to	O
Sheerness	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
perswaded	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
Duree	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Son	O
took	O
Doleman	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Duree	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Child	O
is	O
unfortunate	O
,	O
in	O
falling	O
into	O
bad	O
Hands	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Case	O
before	O
your	O
lordship	O
,	O
Doleman	O
obliged	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
this	O
Boy	O
into	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
faithfully	O
promised	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Woman	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
being	O
at	O
present	O
under	O
a	O
Cloud	O
.	O
He	O
promised	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
that	O
Brown	O
's	O
Boy	O
or	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
concerned	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Duree	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lapine	I-pers
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
Mrs.	O
Duree	O
brought	O
her	O
Son	O
Mark	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
promis	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
hurt	O
him	O
:	O
Come	O
in	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
hurt	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
a	O
Constable	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Francis	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
23	O
Files	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Crander	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
34.	O
Elenor	B-pers
Higginson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
2	O
linnen	O
Caps	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Mary	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Glass	O
Bottle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Shrub	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
36.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Fagley	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
37.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Drysdell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Banyan	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
Cambrick	O
Stocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Rule	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bettrey	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Barr	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Child	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
marry	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
leaving	O
her	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Linnen	O
which	O
is	O
lost	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
who	O
lodged	O
and	O
boarded	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
He	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
nail	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
's	O
since	O
dead	O
at	O
Barbadoes	O
.	O
His	O
Name	O
was	O
Alexander	B-pers
Steadman	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
are	O
now	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Rule	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Executor	O
of	O
Steadman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
comes	O
on	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
Things	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
4	O
Shirts	O
and	O
a	O
Banyan	O
,	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
pawned	O
at	O
one	O
Davis	O
's	O
the	O
Week	O
before	O
Christmass	O
last	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
her	O
:	O
Ask	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Money	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
?	O
Bettrey	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
38.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rash	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hempen	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Massingale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
18	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Root	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Wager	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Cocky	O
Wager	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hasswel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Hasswell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
in	O
my	O
Chariot	O
,	O
July	O
23.	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Tottenham-Cross	B-place
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
Road	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
green	B-place
Lane	I-place
:	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
drove	O
above	O
a	O
Mile	O
,	O
before	O
2	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Faces	O
cover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Pistols	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
:	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
both	O
their	O
Faces	O
were	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
something	O
brown	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
Holes	O
for	O
their	O
Eyes	O
and	O
Nose	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
only	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
.	O
My	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Wager	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drove	O
Mr.Hasswell	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
back	O
6	O
or	O
8	O
Times	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Chariot	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
their	O
Face	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
Masks	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
2	O
Persons	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
and	O
expected	O
no	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Several	O
times	O
I	O
observed	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
Voice	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
he	O
speaks	O
thick	O
and	O
hastily	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
swearing	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
demanded	O
Mr.	O
Hasswell	O
's	O
Money	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
putting	O
on	O
his	O
Mask	O
behind	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
'd	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
,	O
shall	O
we	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
Coachman	O
has	O
got	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
stop	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
we	O
bid	O
him	O
Wager	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
Bonner	O
say	O
'd	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
Coachman	O
has	O
got	O
;	O
says	O
Wager	O
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
does	O
look	O
forward	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
(	O
Wager	O
)	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
delivered	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Bonner	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
Wager	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
left	O
us	O
and	O
went	O
2	O
or	O
300	O
Yards	O
towards	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
in	O
the	O
green	O
Lane	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
there	O
and	O
Bonner	O
came	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
Blood	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
he	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Gun	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Bonner	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
?	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
the	O
Gun	O
to	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
presented	O
the	O
Peice	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
have	O
you	O
.	O
Bonner	O
then	O
fell	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
clear	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
by	O
some	O
People	O
who	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
haunted	O
these	O
Lanes	O
for	O
some	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
both	O
him	O
and	O
Wager	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
Men	O
.	O
Bonner	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
if	O
he	O
knows	O
Wager	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
.	O
Bonner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
Wager	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
Affidavit	O
at	O
all	O
concerning	O
Wager	O
.	O
Bonner	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
he	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
to	O
be	O
Wager	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
but	O
by	O
intelligence	O
:	O
they	O
call	O
him	O
Cocky	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
the	O
Warrant	O
upon	O
Bonner	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
desperate	O
Fellow	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Spread-Eagle	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Pater	O
noster-Row	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Women	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Brocas	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
ready	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Alderman	O
could	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
hearing	O
:	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
uneasy	O
too	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
lusty	O
Carpenter	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Associates	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
more	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Bonner	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
``	O
have	O
you	O
``	O
brought	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Hangers	O
?	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
``	O
fall	O
to	O
,	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
:	O
''	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
Bonner	O
to	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
's	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
we	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
People	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
re-examin	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
Coachman	O
and	O
him	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
see	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
thousand	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
``	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
quick	O
Speech	O
.	O
''	O
Bonner	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Livery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Coachman	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
:	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Trouble	O
with	O
you	O
then	O
he	O
described	O
Wager	O
;	O
and	O
Cocky	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Waker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
Bonner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
desperate	O
Fellow	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
5	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Blackspread-Eagle	O
in	O
Paternoster-Row	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
up	O
comes	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
lusty	O
sturdy	O
Fellow	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
Bonner	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Hangers	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
fall	O
to	O
,	O
fire	O
and	O
away	O
;	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
a	O
Rescue	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Alderman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
for	O
a	O
farther	O
Hearing	O
.	O
Bonner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Black-spread-Eagle	O
,	O
with	O
Cocky	O
Wager	O
's	O
Sister	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Warrants	O
out	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
contriving	O
with	O
her	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
intimate	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
:	O
I	O
advised	O
Cocky	O
's	O
Sister	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
Call	O
Mr.	O
Well	O
's	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Well	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lyon	O
(	O
who	O
all	O
appearing	O
,	O
were	O
sworn	O
)	O
-	O
Wells	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Endfield	O
wash	O
,	O
am	O
a	O
Butcher	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
-	O
in	O
June	O
,	O
-	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
aye	O
in	O
July	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
Scholar	O
and	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Bullock	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
comes	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
says	O
he	O
?	O
How	O
do	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
bought	O
a	O
Bullock	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
says	O
I	O
?	O
Yes	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Bullock	O
of	O
a	O
Customer	O
I	O
deal	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
I	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
Wells	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Company	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
.	O
-	O
Story	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Butcher	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
Barr	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
drinking	O
there	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
come	O
you	O
to	O
remember	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
-	O
Story	O
.	O
Because	O
it	O
was	O
Market	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
are	O
other	O
Market	O
Days	O
,	O
are	O
there	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
Story	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
?	O
Story	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
that	O
Day	O
at	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
once	O
,	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Master	O
Wells	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Bullock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
luckily	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
Man	O
was	O
paying	O
for	O
the	O
Bullock	O
?	O
Bonner	O
was	O
there	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
?	O
Story	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
Bonner	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drinking	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Bullock	O
was	O
paid	O
for	O
?	O
Story	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
paid	O
to	O
?	O
Story	O
.	O
Master	O
Wells	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Farmer	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
Foiler	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
but	O
once	O
since	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
'till	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
was	O
drinking	O
there	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
other	O
Reason	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
on	O
Friday	O
July	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Reason	O
to	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
Husband	O
pay	O
'd	O
Money	O
that	O
Day	O
:	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
off	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
your	O
Husband	O
pay	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
take	O
a	O
Receipt	O
?	O
Susan	O
Well	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
Foiler	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
deals	O
with	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
bring	O
him	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
lock	O
was	O
bought	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Susan	O
Wells	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
matter	O
'till	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
else	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
brought	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Wells	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
Grey-hound	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
from	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Name	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
you	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
do	O
the	O
good	O
Office	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Tapsters	O
here	O
?	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
Essex	O
.	O
What	O
Character	O
does	O
Bonner	O
bear	O
?	O
-	O
Wells	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
:	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
him	O
Pork	O
and	O
Veal	O
in	O
Carcasses	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
(	O
Here	O
he	O
produced	O
Foiler	O
's	O
Receipt	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
this	O
John	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
that	O
witness	O
'd	O
this	O
Receipt	O
.	O
John	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
Business	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
Clerk	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
thence	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
this	O
Receipt	O
of	O
your	O
writing	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
follow	O
'd	O
since	O
you	O
were	O
discharged	O
from	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
the	O
same	O
Business	O
still	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
acted	O
in	O
the	O
Station	O
of	O
a	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Merchants	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
accidentally	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
when	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
and	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
there	O
.	O
These	O
People	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
thro	O
'	O
their	O
Persuasions	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
those	O
20	O
Years	O
.	O
Wells	O
can	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Bonner	O
's	O
Request	O
that	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
Receipt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
you	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
dated	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
:	O
Pray	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Foiler	O
before	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
after	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
accidentally	O
being	O
Bonner	O
's	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
you	O
staid	O
all	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
was	O
you	O
ever	O
at	O
that	O
House	O
before	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
serv	O
'd	O
the	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Bring	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Tapster	O
here	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
these	O
People	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
those	O
People	O
you	O
serve	O
now	O
?	O
(	O
to	O
Lyon	O
)	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
Business	O
for	O
the	O
South-Sea	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
India	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
several	O
Spanish	O
Merchants	O
in	O
Town	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
Business	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
at	O
the	O
London	O
Assurance	O
Office	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
wrote	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
a	O
Clerk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
else	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
,	O
particularly	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
is	O
all	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
serv	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
mention	O
:	O
if	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
Livelihood	O
by	O
being	O
a	O
Clerk	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
name	O
some	O
of	O
your	O
Employers	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
,	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
the	O
Ship	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
Street	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Bowsle	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
Place	O
did	O
you	O
write	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Business	O
you	O
did	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Lodging	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
him	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
private	O
Business	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
60	O
Folio	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
is	O
my	O
Relation	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
premited	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
an	O
Employment	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
use	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
London	O
Assurance	O
Office	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hasswell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Director	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
Man	O
there	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
's	O
Office	O
an	O
hundred	O
Times	O
.	O
(	O
Here	O
the	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
appear	O
'd	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Wells	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
?	O
Broughton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
If	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
that	O
any	O
such	O
Persons	O
as	O
these	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Foiler	O
of	O
Essex	O
?	O
Broughton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
by	O
my	O
Books	O
,	O
whether	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
paid	O
for	O
a	O
Bullock	O
:	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
Book	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Grasiers	O
:	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
themselves	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
Book	O
,	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
must	O
tell	O
me	O
who	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Bullock	O
of	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
4	O
People	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Broughton	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
any	O
Persons	O
sat	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
that	O
Day	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Hours	O
about	O
selling	O
a	O
Bullock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
know	O
Foiler	O
?	O
Broughton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.Maynard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Market	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
reputed	O
Highwayman	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Foiler	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
useth	O
the	O
Markets	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Broughton	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
Company	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
that	O
staid	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Hours	O
from	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
?	O
Broughton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Broughton	O
's	O
Man	O
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
.	O
(	O
Here	O
the	O
Books	O
from	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hostler	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Maynard	O
.	O
The	O
Way	O
of	O
paying	O
Money	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
is	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
Taker	O
receives	O
the	O
Debt	O
the	O
Master	O
does	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
Receipt	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
Taker	O
gives	O
it	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
set	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gives	O
the	O
Receipt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
Wells	O
)	O
Where	O
does	O
Foiler	O
live	O
?	O
Wells	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Hundreds	O
somewhere	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
jokes	O
are	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Broughton	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
2	O
Beasts	O
sold	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Book	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
's	O
none	O
of	O
Foiler	O
's	O
Name	O
.	O
A	O
Juryman	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Money	O
had	O
been	O
paid	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
should	O
you	O
have	O
enter	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
Book	O
?	O
Broughton	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
paid	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
who	O
takes	O
Money	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Burrough	O
,	O
Hostler	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
ever	O
since	O
Candlemas	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
People	O
before	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
Wells	O
I	O
am	O
inform	O
'd	O
harbours	O
these	O
Sort	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
publick	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
rising	O
Sun	O
,	O
at	O
Enfield	O
Wash.	O
Wells	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Story	O
and	O
Lyon	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Bonner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
40.	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
30	O
s.	O
August	O
21	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
41.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blakey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
August	O
31	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42	O
,	O
43.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leaden	O
Cistern	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
leaden	O
Pump	O
Head	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
August	O
19	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
John	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bureau	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
11	O
Chairs	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
Stove	O
Grate	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
18	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Culender	O
,	O
2	O
feather	O
Beds	O
,	O
3	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
6	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Stew	O
Pan	O
,	O
2	O
Pictures	O
,	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Tables	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Sayer	O
,	O
April	O
25	O
,	O
1734	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
,	O
April	O
20	O
,	O
1734	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1734.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
Yard	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
(	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
19	O
Years	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
expected	O
would	O
be	O
seized	O
by	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
some	O
Recognizances	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
(	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
)	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
2	O
Children	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Years	O
old	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
my	O
Bureau	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Law	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
or	O
get	O
50	O
People	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
of	O
40	O
l	O
and	O
5	O
Shirts	O
of	O
the	O
Orphans	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Pretence	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
for	O
this	O
?	O
Sayer	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
violently	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
he	O
arrested	O
me	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
140	O
l.	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Farthing	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
spunging	O
House	O
in	O
Grocer	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
he	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
sooner	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Custody	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Liberty	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Holland	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Pray	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
Coffee	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
live	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
?	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
both	O
receive	O
Money	O
of	O
your	O
Customers	O
?	O
Sayer	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
my	O
Lodger	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Name	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
At	O
whose	O
Expence	O
was	O
the	O
Coffee	O
House	O
fitted	O
up	O
?	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Sayer	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
pay	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Sayer	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
paid	O
any	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pass	O
for	O
your	O
Husband	O
?	O
Sayer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
in	O
Sheer	O
Lane	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
he	O
lodge	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
then	O
?	O
Sayer	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
to	O
screen	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
lodge	O
there	O
himself	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
whether	O
this	O
Quarrel	O
did	O
not	O
arise	O
from	O
his	O
reprimanding	O
you	O
about	O
your	O
Daughter	O
's	O
keeping	O
Company	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
sold	O
her	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Maiden-head	O
to	O
one	O
Major	O
Lewis	O
of	O
Deptford	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
She	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
even	O
her	O
own	O
Looking	O
Glasses	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
me	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
a	O
Bill	O
last	O
Sessions	O
as	O
a	O
Witnes	O
against	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
against	O
one	O
Drinkwater	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Drinkwater	O
has	O
charged	O
my	O
Wife	O
(	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
attending	O
on	O
me	O
here	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
by	O
one	O
Hicks	O
an	O
Officer	O
.	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Year	O
1734	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
Servant	O
for	O
about	O
6	O
Months	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Drawer	O
.	O
-	O
Hicks	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
Woman	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
attending	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Hicks	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
was	O
one	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
2	O
Men	O
and	O
2	O
Women	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Warwick	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Drinkwater	O
give	O
it	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Arm	O
.	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Drawer	O
at	O
Warwick	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Sheer	O
Lane	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
very	O
Disorderly	O
House	O
.	O
Sayer	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
advise	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
her	O
Administring	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
forged	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Will	O
of	O
any	O
bodies	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
by	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concerned	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
this	O
silly	O
Bitch	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
contrive	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
make	O
her	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
Good	O
by	O
Molly	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
from	O
you	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
's	O
Effects	O
from	O
the	O
Bitch	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Children	O
say	O
'd	O
she	O
:	O
I	O
'll	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
parted	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
rob	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
Drinkwater	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
his	O
Wife	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
attending	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Business	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
reprimanded	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
When	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
Joyce	O
and	O
Warwick	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
Joyce	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
Warwick	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
Porters	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
Baskets	O
and	O
Sheets	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
Boy	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
seen	O
me	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
this	O
Woman	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
Goods	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
once	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
seized	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Warwick	O
packing	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
Lock	O
from	O
Sayer	O
's	O
Street	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
;	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
else	O
where	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
scandalous	O
Story	O
.	O
Pray	O
what	O
Pretence	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shirts	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
's	O
?	O
Warwick	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
produce	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Rings	O
she	O
had	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
:	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
seized	O
them	O
on	O
an	O
Extent	O
;	O
a	O
Man	O
bought	O
them	O
afterwards	O
of	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
again	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Drinkwater	O
say	O
,	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Pen	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
to	O
get	O
Jack	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
hanged	O
or	O
transported	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
and	O
Sayer	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
so	O
:	O
nay	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
shewn	O
me	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Johnny	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Diamonds	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
she	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Johnny	O
as	O
we	O
ca	O
n't	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
Ring	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
alter	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
several	O
Workmen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
Warwick	O
had	O
Goods	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
's	O
Officers	O
had	O
seiz	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
again	O
of	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
's	O
Officers	O
for	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
but	O
Warwick	O
applying	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
never	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
Warwick	O
.	O
Ask	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
3	O
Guineas	O
for	O
the	O
Ring	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
Warwick	O
before	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Action	O
against	O
this	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
order	O
'd	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
spunging	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
Warwick	O
.	O
and	O
know	O
his	O
Demands	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
disbursed	O
Money	O
on	O
her	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
release	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
some	O
Debts	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
amounted	O
to	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
l.	O
She	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Lease	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
for	O
Security	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
this	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
take	O
Possession	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
accordingly	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
supposing	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
it	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
Warwick	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
down	O
;	O
some	O
were	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Warwick	O
told	O
me	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Authority	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
rather	O
than	O
I	O
would	O
dispute	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
48	O
s.	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
Warwick	O
and	O
Sayer	O
by	O
Water	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Horse	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
Grass	O
:	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
was	O
not	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
word	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
her	O
Daughter	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
was	O
very	O
kind	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
fret	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
should	O
wear	O
her	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
Daughter	O
's	O
)	O
'till	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
another	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Warwick	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
2	O
Years	O
ago	O
about	O
altering	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
Jackey	O
a	O
good	O
Watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
one	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
:	O
you	O
give	O
your	O
self	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
Sidley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
Warwick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Thief	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
45	O
.	O
*	O
Alexander	B-pers
Raitt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silk	O
Aprons	O
,	O
3	O
silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
Padesoy	O
,	O
1	O
Burdett	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
1	O
flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
1	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
6	O
Cambrick	O
ditto	O
,	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
,	O
5	O
Suits	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
with	O
sundry	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
a	O
Portugal	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Raitt	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
in	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
,	O
Page	O
138	O
,	O
Number	O
XXXVII	O
,	O
being	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Evidence	O
.	O
46	O
.	O
47.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
(	O
with	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Maldock	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Whitcher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
17	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Guy	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
(	O
A	O
Negro	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
paid	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Ship	O
Newcastle	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
along	O
Rosemary	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
between	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
met	O
2	O
Women	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Whitcher	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
Salmon	O
and	O
Punch	O
and	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
?	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
came	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
oldest	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
-	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Girls	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
,	O
that	O
8	O
Guineas	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
divided	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
swear	O
your	O
Money	O
on	O
another	O
Woman	O
?	O
Guy	O
.	O
Why	O
Mary	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
you	O
took	O
my	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Fulham	I-pers
.	O
These	O
2	O
Creatures	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
divided	O
8	O
Guineas	O
and	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
Whitcher	O
had	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Jones	O
said	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
who	O
had	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Black	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
and	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Black	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
48.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Camblet	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
49.	O
William	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Straps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
50.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gittings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
gilt	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Postlewaite	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
51.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pennicourt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
grey	O
human	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
2	O
Ounces	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
March	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
Bishop	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Bishop	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Mitchel	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
William	B-pers
Gunnel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
China	O
Punch	O
Bowl	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Delf	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
2	O
Prints	O
fram	O
'd	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
Quart	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Rum	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Madera	O
Wine	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dicker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
54.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
5	O
Wainscot	O
Boxes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Davis	O
,	O
September	O
7	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
55.	O
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
September	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
56.	O
Frances	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
silk	O
watered	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
57.	O
George	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
:	O
and	O
a	O
Damask	O
Napkin	O
,	O
4	O
Towels	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
some	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Shovell	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
58.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jessup	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cornish	O
Plane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
59.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linnen	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
an	O
iron	O
Key	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
60.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
September	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
61.	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
linnen	O
Clout	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
;	O
and	O
2	O
flaxen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
August	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
62.	O
David	B-pers
Wassereau	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tolley	I-pers
,	O
September	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
63	O
,	O
64.	O
John	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hasting	I-pers
,	O
August	O
28	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
65.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chesterman	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Betty	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
iron	O
Heater	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
66.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
64	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
67	O
,	O
68.	O
Diana	B-pers
Street	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Amy	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Mortar	O
and	O
Pestle	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Fletcher	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
69	O
,	O
70.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bryan	B-pers
Carney	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Burroughs	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Orr	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Carney	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
William	O
Orr	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
(	O
Reading	O
)	O
I	O
committed	O
the	O
Thing	O
to	O
writing	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
forget	O
any	O
Thing	O
material	O
,	O
nor	O
trouble	O
the	O
Court	O
with	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
was	O
trifling	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
did	O
when	O
the	O
Thing	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
not	O
usual	O
Sir	O
to	O
read	O
a	O
Testimony	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
use	O
your	O
Papers	O
to	O
refresh	O
your	O
Memory	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
the	O
Custom	O
for	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
give	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Viva	O
Voce	O
.	O
Orr	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
August	O
the	O
4th	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Hamburgh	B-place
Coffee	I-place
House	I-place
in	I-place
Drury	I-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
pretty	O
long	O
Walk	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Clare	O
Court	O
,	O
near	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
Coffee	O
House	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
to	O
refresh	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Punch	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
my	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
was	O
coming	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
grip	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
Dram	O
.	O
(	O
Reading	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
committed	O
my	O
Thoughts	O
to	O
writing	O
,	O
having	O
time	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
better	O
able	O
to	O
express	O
them	O
in	O
that	O
Light	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
humbly	O
conceive	O
(	O
my	O
Lord	O
)	O
it	O
will	O
set	O
the	O
matter	O
clearer	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Watch	O
upon	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
publick	O
Room	O
?	O
Orr	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
publick	O
Room	O
:	O
The	O
following	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
Declaration	O
,	O
will	O
shew	O
both	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
little	O
grip	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Girl	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Publick	O
Room	O
?	O
Orr	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
publick	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
scruple	O
of	O
