TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21	O
st	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
1736.	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
WILLIAMS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1736	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXVI	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Cummins	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lee	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sindery	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Frewteril	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coombes	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Bockham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Worral	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Christial	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Grainge	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Southall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mazey	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Delahay	I-pers
,	O
Rich	B-pers
Knightsbridge	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Baugh	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Baugh	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
July	O
9	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Tavern	O
to	O
my	O
Chambers	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
middle	B-place
Temple	I-place
Gate	I-place
the	O
Duchess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Marlborough	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
her	O
Chariot	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
Minutes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Sword	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
swear	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
missing	O
my	O
Sword	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
-	O
Sword	O
lost	O
-	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
the	O
Mob	O
set	O
out	O
and	O
run	O
beyond	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
Tavern	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
given	O
it	O
any	O
Body	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
you	O
run	O
away	O
then	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
pretty	O
late	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
John	O
Smith	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
farther	O
Evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
often	O
been	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
middle	O
Temple	O
Gate	O
:	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
draw	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
have	O
detected	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
quite	O
drawn	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Man	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
I	O
suppose	O
)	O
clapp	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whose	O
Coach	O
that	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
turn	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
a	O
Chymist	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Houses	O
that	O
was	O
burnt	O
down	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
July	O
9.	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baugh	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
told	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
to	O
offer	O
me	O
my	O
Sword	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
Smith	O
,	O
Why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Baugh	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
ask	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
could	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
my	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
without	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
'till	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
so	O
far	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
discovered	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
mis-used	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
Home	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
:	O
He	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
Sir	O
William	O
Billers	O
's	O
Office	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baugh	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
under	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
spurted	O
good	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
into	O
Smith	O
's	O
Face	O
and	O
down	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
either	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
or	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
2.	O
Ann	B-pers
Weakley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
green	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Neve	I-pers
.	O
June	O
24	O
John	B-pers
Oldsworth	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
is	O
a	O
Haber-dasher	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
We	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
counted	O
the	O
Ribbons	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
the	O
Number	O
on	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
8	O
penny	O
Ribbon	O
.	O
I	O
served	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Minute	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
.	O
My	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pottinger	I-pers
.	O
My	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
counted	O
the	O
Ribbons	O
over	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
Witness	O
served	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Minute	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
green	O
Saxe	O
Gotha	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Little	O
Minories	O
Gate	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
Head	O
in	O
Bread	O
street	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
Master	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Directions	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
hid	O
behind	O
some	O
Shutters	O
,	O
which	O
stand	O
under	O
that	O
Gate-way	O
.	O
I	O
pushed	O
the	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Avis	B-pers
Nutton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Callicoe	O
Borders	O
for	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiseham	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Wiseham	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
April	O
5	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Customers	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
served	O
the	O
Ladies	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
printed	O
Borders	O
and	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
Trifle	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Beer	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
appeared	O
well	O
dress	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
glass	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
draw	O
her	O
some	O
Beer	O
;	O
she	O
met	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
stairs	O
,	O
drank	O
the	O
Beer	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
she	O
curt'sied	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
pleased	O
she	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Beer	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
without	O
buying	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
another	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Borders	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
particular	O
Things	O
which	O
none	O
in	O
England	O
have	O
besides	O
myself	O
D	O
-	O
her	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
the	O
Bitch	O
has	O
stollen	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Brother	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
Home	O
.	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
your	O
humble	O
Servant	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
mistaken	O
Sir	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
your	O
Shop	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
very	O
much	O
alike	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Pattern	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
.	O
Three	O
of	O
us	O
followed	O
her	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
see	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
lost	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
the	O
Week	O
following	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
for	O
some	O
Borders	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
were	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
Price	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Borders	O
that	O
hung	O
up	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
;	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
she	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
me	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
ruin	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Husband	O
sixteen	O
years	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
my	O
Borders	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Drake	O
of	O
Bow	O
,	O
who	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Nutton	O
.	O
The	O
Roll	O
I	O
lost	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Printer	O
's	O
but	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
Cambrick	O
was	O
worth	O
4	O
l.	O
10s	O
.	O
-	O
and	O
this	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
's	O
Evidence	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Toller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
once	O
with	O
two	O
Parcels	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Price	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
those	O
Things	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
herself	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Robeings	O
of	O
Gowns	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Kaywood	I-pers
confirmed	O
Toller	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
produced	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
Borders	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
six	O
yards	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
shilling	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Price	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiseham	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
very	O
Things	O
we	O
found	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Drake	O
's	O
.	O
Rice	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
fall	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
begged	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
what	O
the	O
Things	O
came	O
to	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
harsh	O
and	O
passionate	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
reputable	O
Woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4	O
,	O
5.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Sacks	O
of	O
Meal	O
and	O
Middlings	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
6.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
October	O
28	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
24	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	O
Robertson	O
,	O
September	O
20	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
September	O
18	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
sixth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	O
Robertson	O
,	O
June	O
22	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
seventh	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
June	O
12	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
eighth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
;	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
First	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	O
Thatcher	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
with	O
grey	O
Hairs	O
in	O
the	O
Flanks	O
,	O
four	O
white	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
blaze	O
down	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
from	O
Woolston	B-place
in	I-place
Berkshire	I-place
,	O
28th	O
of	O
Octob	O
.	O
last	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Common	O
Mead	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
1	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Brewer	O
in	O
Ealing	O
;	O
I	O
swear	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
Mare	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Haines	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Mare	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
Alhallontide	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Grosvenor-street	O
,	O
near	O
Grosvenor	O
square	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
her	O
again	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
a	O
Brewer	O
at	O
Ealing	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
about	O
4	O
Months	O
before	O
I	O
sold	O
her	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
for	O
8	O
l.	O
she	O
had	O
4	O
white	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Owner	O
Mr.	O
Thatcher	O
has	O
got	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Haines	O
was	O
Confederate	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
The	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
try	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
Indictment	O
.	O
7	O
,	O
8.	O
Rose	B-pers
Mahon	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Shepperd	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shepperd	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Mahon	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Seal	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Shepperd	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boniface	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mahon	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
July	O
4.	O
in	O
Windmill-street	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
to	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Coventry-Court	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	B-place
Hay	I-place
market	I-place
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Rose	O
Mahon	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Mahon	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
say	O
so	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
-	O
do	O
n't	O
tell	O
that	O
Lye	O
.	O
Gould	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Maxwell	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
satisfy	O
you	O
;	O
well	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
no	O
matter	O
for	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
she	O
thought	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
miss	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
immediately	O
to	O
opening	O
the	O
Waistband	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
O	O
says	O
she	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
nothing	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
please	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
picked	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Stairs	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
below	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
Daughters	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
waited	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
from	O
that	O
Time	O
'till	O
Eight	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Some	O
Time	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
in	O
came	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shepperd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
Mahon	O
's	O
Husband	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
been	O
at	O
this	O
House	O
before	O
?	O
Gould	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
?	O
Gould	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
keep	O
such	O
Women	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
Bawdy	O
House	O
?	O
Gould	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
?	O
Gould	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
what	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
,	O
yet	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
there	O
.	O
Gould	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
So	O
when	O
Shepperd	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
done	O
a	O
fine	O
Thing	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
pick	O
'd	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
says	O
Shepperd	O
,	O
what	O
Business	O
had	O
he	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
your	O
Wife	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
only	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Butcher	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Mahon	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
my	O
Lord	O
he	O
may	O
turn	O
his	O
Face	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
Vertue	O
of	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
insist	O
upon	O
going	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
Chamber	O
?	O
Whether	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
?	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Time	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
I	O
'll	O
not	O
go	O
Home	O
'till	O
I	O
've	O
seen	O
your	O
Apartment	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
;	O
you	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
why	O
,	O
said	O
you	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
this	O
Rosy	O
?	O
I	O
stepp	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Gould	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
never	O
declared	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
?	O
Gould	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
ever	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
without	O
asking	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Scrape	O
as	O
this	O
before	O
.	O
Mahon	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
9d	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
that	O
to	O
my	O
Maid	O
?	O
Gould	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
9	O
d.	O
herself	O
.	O
Mahon	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
Maid	O
your	O
9	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lyon	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
in	O
Coventry	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
comes	O
Joseph	O
Sheppard	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
his	O
Rosy	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
from	O
who	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
from	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Messenger	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
blue	O
Grey	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
white	O
Spatterdashes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
very	O
heavy	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
pawn	O
for	O
14	O
Spankers	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Maxwell	I-pers
.	O
That	O
Jo	O
.	O
Sheppard	O
took	O
the	O
Lodging	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Coventry	O
Court	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
'till	O
this	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
then	O
Sheppard	O
came	O
in	O
while	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
done	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Nose	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Discourse	O
with	O
Mr	O
Gould	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
Maxwell	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
all	O
Night	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
say	O
something	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
-	O
Council	O
He	O
says	O
it	O
was	O
10	O
.	O
Maxwell	O
.	O
God	O
bless	O
me	O
;	O
-	O
then	O
the	O
Bells	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
right	O
about	O
;	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
but	O
9	O
,	O
because	O
when	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
Watch	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
!	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
o	O
n't	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pity	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Maxwell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Nagg's-Head	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
Sheppard	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
his	O
Elbow	O
thus	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gould	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
Sir	O
,	O
what	O
Concerns	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
-	O
pray	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
Sir	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
15	O
d	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
9	O
d.	O
Sheppard	O
threatned	O
to	O
sue	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
something	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
returned	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonniface	I-pers
.	O
While	O
Mahon	O
was	O
examining	O
before	O
Col.	O
De	O
Viel	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
brought	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Gould	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Watch	O
I	O
declare	O
.	O
Mahon	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
a	O
Clock	O
my	O
Dear	O
says	O
he	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
this	O
Rosy	O
says	O
he	O
?	O
Yes	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
smiled	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
and	O
have	O
but	O
9	O
d.	O
else	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
and	O
drunk	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
that	O
to	O
my	O
Maid	O
,	O
so	O
up	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
the	O
9d	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
-	O
he	O
said	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
trust	O
to	O
my	O
Honour	O
,	O
my	O
Generosity	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
pay	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
owe	O
my	O
Landlady	O
10	O
s.	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
in	O
lieu	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
my	O
Bed-chamber	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
four	O
Guineas	O
:	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
is	O
in	O
Privacy	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
us	O
Ladies	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
known	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
Servant	O
into	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Case	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
saved	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
two	O
Guineas	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
would	O
you	O
be	O
willing	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
a	O
Lady	O
should	O
be	O
guilty	O
in	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
Case	O
known	O
to	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Sheppard	O
is	O
an	O
innocent	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
9.	O
Robert	B-pers
Folgey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
June	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Barnwell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
quilted	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hibbins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wotlrey	I-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Edwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
two	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Canning	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
James	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Frock	O
without	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
and	O
4	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cloth	O
cut	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
4	O
pieces	O
cut	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
Gent	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Seymour	O
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Woolen	O
Stuff	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Sagathy	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Six	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
First	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	O
Seymour	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Journey-man	O
.	O
The	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
out	O
a	O
Suit	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
finish	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
some	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
again	O
,	O
English	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Work	O
might	O
be	O
finish	O
'd	O
in	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
Man	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
work	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
my	O
Work	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
other	O
Man	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
English	O
had	O
carried	O
out	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Yarp	O
's	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Globe-Stairs	O
by	O
Ratcliffe-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Priestly	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
pay	O
himself	O
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
Wilson	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Chest	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
had	O
brought	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
:	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
going	O
to	O
New-England	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
Money	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
owed	O
me	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
hard	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Boston	O
,	O
to	O
leave	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
these	O
Things	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
Word	O
next	O
Day	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
gave	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
to	O
one	O
Mac	O
-	O
something	O
,	O
a	O
Newgate	O
Solicitor	O
,	O
to	O
manage	O
my	O
Cause	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
nothing	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Costecan	I-pers
,	O
had	O
employed	O
and	O
entrusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
found	O
Seymour	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
these	O
Irish	O
Villains	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Door	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Key	O
)	O
and	O
we	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
too	O
The	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
brought	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Pledge	O
for	O
four	O
Guineas	O
which	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
made	O
me	O
lend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
their	O
Design	O
of	O
running	O
away	O
together	O
to	O
New	O
England	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
England	O
Coffee-House	O
and	O
got	O
Intelligence	O
where	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
:	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
Waterman	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
us	O
leave	O
to	O
crop	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
his	O
Advice	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Justice	O
let	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
go	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Chest	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
very	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
his	O
Wife	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
on	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
He	O
half	O
starved	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
New	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Chest	O
of	O
mine	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
the	O
Robbery	O
against	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
above	O
knows	O
where	O
my	O
Wife	O
is	O
:	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
t'other	O
Irishman	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
14.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
June	O
21	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
Bacon	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
some	O
Behaviour	O
of	O
hers	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
better	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
her	O
into	O
Hungerford-Market	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Cheese	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
mark	O
'd	O
,	O
GB	O
x	O
LH	O
.	O
Def	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
Man	O
's	O
Shop	O
for	O
Bacon	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Mistress	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
with	O
Child	O
?	O
Yes	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
Why	O
then	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
feel	O
your	O
great	O
Belly	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Groaning	O
Cheese	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
3	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
lye	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
God	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
required	O
farther	O
Favours	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
grant	O
him	O
.	O
Customers	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
John	B-pers
Maxworth	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Paddy	B-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Parliament	B-pers
Jack	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Blackerby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
of	O
June	O
19	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
handled	O
Knives	O
,	O
2	O
silver	O
handled	O
Forks	O
,	O
one	O
large	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
2	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Stock	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
fast	O
and	O
secure	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
first	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
a	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
2	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
great	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
.	O
We	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
unknown	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Servants	O
to	O
run	O
of	O
Errands	O
and	O
to	O
clean	O
Knives	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farewell	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
voluntarily	O
signed	O
it	O
.	O
Justice	O
Farewell	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Examination	O
and	O
Confession	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maxworth	I-pers
,	O
taken	O
before	O
me	O
Richard	O
Farewell	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
County	O
and	O
Liberty	O
of	O
Westminster	O
,	O
this	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1736.	O
Who	O
upon	O
Examination	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
Plate	O
being	O
stollen	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
o	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Blackerby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
confesseth	O
and	O
saith	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
on	O
a	O
Shed	O
in	O
Cotton	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Coal	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Blackerby	O
on	O
Saturday	O
June	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
thence	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
what	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
opened	O
,	O
by	O
turning	O
the	O
Brass	O
Knobb	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Crest	O
was	O
,	O
a	O
Blackmoor	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
Lawrel	O
Branches	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
Pinchbeck	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
took	O
2	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
Study	O
Door	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Parlour	O
and	O
the	O
Drawing	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
cut	O
of	O
the	O
Laundry	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
a	O
Stock	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coltman	I-pers
:	O
That	O
the	O
Cane	O
was	O
sold	O
at	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
:	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
said	O
Coltman	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Blackerby	O
's	O
:	O
Being	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
told	O
Coltman	O
of	O
his	O
Intention	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Robbery	O
before	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
inform	O
her	O
of	O
his	O
Intention	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Laundry	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
went	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
2	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
Parlour	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
using	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
Errands	O
and	O
clean	O
Knives	O
we	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Former	O
Witness	O
,	O
(	O
our	O
House-keeper	O
)	O
to	O
Bed	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Door	O
was	O
latch	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Study	O
Door	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
Evidence	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
young	O
Fellow	O
,	O
But	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
trusted	O
by	O
several	O
People	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
Money	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Stagg	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
and	O
have	O
always	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
Shopkeepers	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Matter	O
I	O
did	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Tortoise-Shell	O
Snuff-Box	O
with	O
silver	O
Rims	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
Pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Deards	I-pers
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Batty	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
he	O
also	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
16.	O
Francis	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Venetian	O
Wool	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Highmore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
18.	O
Robert	B-pers
Corff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
GERARD	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Bernardiston	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
worked	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Twinbrough	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
unseen	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
talking	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
an	O
opposite	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Constance	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Moneys	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dutch	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vennimore	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
July	O
8	O
.	O
William	O
Vennimore	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
Water-lane	B-place
to	O
make	O
Water	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
-	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
she	O
thrust	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Dutch	O
halt	O
Crown	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
directly	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
had	O
been	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
her	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
released	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
charged	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
of	O
searching	O
her	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
Gown	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
see	O
no	O
other	O
in	O
black	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
Whereof	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
Pockets	O
inside	O
out	O
;	O
whereof	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
me	O
a	O
Full-pot	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
strip	O
'd	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Goal	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
Elenor	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cambrick	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-clothes	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Ann	B-pers
Buzel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Calimanco	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
Gowns	O
and	O
two	O
Aprons	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
July	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Mary	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
Edward	O
Berry	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
clapped	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Chair	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
10th	O
or	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
Wife	O
would	O
have	O
look	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
forgot	O
it	O
.	O
Some	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
she	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
100	O
l.	O
up	O
Stairs	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Bag	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
heard	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
merry-making	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
so	O
my	O
Wife	O
challenged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
these	O
Guineas	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
several	O
different	O
Stories	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
concluded	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
took	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Chapman	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Hands	O
being	O
grease	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
to	O
wash	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Bed	O
was	O
making	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
tried	O
by	O
a	O
pick	O
Lock	O
Key	O
to	O
open	O
my	O
Drawers	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
doing	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
whole	O
Bunch	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
all	O
they	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
in	O
my	O
Hearing	O
she	O
took	O
six	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Owen	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
Guineas	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
June	O
12	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Eleven	O
and	O
One	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
for	O
Lodging	O
and	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Return	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
He	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
my	O
Hearing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26	O
Ruth	B-pers
Surry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
laced	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Freeman	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Mob	O
and	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Odam	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
John	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Winston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Winston	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
yesterday	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
from	O
Gloucestershire	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Cirencester	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Knights-bridge	B-place
,	O
near	O
Hyde	B-place
Park	I-place
Corner	I-place
,	O
three	O
Fellows	O
stopped	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
Money	O
,	O
Watches	O
and	O
Buckles	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Fellow	O
that	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
Person	O
gave	O
them	O
more	O
Silver	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
talked	O
of	O
taking	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
all	O
we	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
and	O
Justice	O
Ray	O
,	O
at	O
Hanover-Square	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bound	O
him	O
over	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
on	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Description	O
we	O
gave	O
of	O
the	O
Robbers	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
little	O
Fellows	O
,	O
young	O
,	O
and	O
unused	O
to	O
that	O
Way	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
very	O
civil	O
,	O
no	O
Oaths	O
nor	O
Swearing	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
deliver	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
take	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
but	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Winston	O
has	O
given	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
three	O
Foot	O
pads	O
,	O
one	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Speech	O
,	O
telling	O
us	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
us	O
an	O
Injury	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Necessity	O
obliged	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
pursue	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
his	O
Companions	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Coachman	O
drive	O
on	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Description	O
we	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
next	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Vestry-Room	O
,	O
in	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
past	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sud	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Foot-pads	O
had	O
stopped	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Checquer	O
'd	O
Shirt	O
,	O
dark	O
brown	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
flapped	O
Hat	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
other	O
Watchman	O
to	O
put	O
out	O
his	O
Light	O
,	O
thinking	O
if	O
they	O
saw	O
our	O
Lights	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
near	O
us	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
I	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
coming	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
Breast	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
attacking	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Turn-pike	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Coach	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Sissiter	O
(	O
Cirencester	O
)	O
Coach	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bell-Savage	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Coach	O
attack	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
described	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Description	O
)	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
these	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Instruments	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Stock	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
Coach	O
being	O
robbed	O
by	O
three	O
Foot	O
Pads	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
described	O
very	O
plainly	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
jumped	O
down	O
from	O
behind	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
stopped	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
at	O
the	O
Lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Park	O
Gate	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Shagreen	O
Cases	O
to	O
hold	O
Lancers	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Stock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Gold	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
beyond	O
my	O
Stand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ray	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Confession	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Parry	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Confession	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
signed	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
where	O
those	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
been	O
found	O
The	O
Examination	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Examination	O
of	O
John	O
Kelsey	O
taken	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
County	O
,	O
and	O
Liberty	O
of	O
Westminster	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
1736.	O
Who	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Winston	O
and	O
Hussey	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
them	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
near	O
Knight	O
's	O
Bridge	O
,	O
confesseth	O
and	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
Rigby	O
and	O
Cooper	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
with	O
them	O
'till	O
about	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
near	O
Queen	O
's	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
agreed	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
first	O
Coach	O
they	O
should	O
meet	O
,	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
they	O
stopped	O
this	O
Coach	O
,	O
that	O
Rigby	O
demanded	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
Buckles	O
of	O
the	O
Passengers	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Examinant	O
put	O
his	O
Hat	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pence	O
Half-penny	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Rigby	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
and	O
divided	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
saith	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
Road	O
again	O
,	O
were	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
this	O
Examinant	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
He	O
farther	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
last	O
Saturday	O
they	O
robbed	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
Coach	O
near	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Passengers	O
18	O
s.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Rigby	O
and	O
Cooper	O
in	O
robbing	O
the	O
Bury	O
Coach	O
,	O
in	O
Stratford	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
this	O
Examinant	O
had	O
9	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
.	O
Signed	O
John	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
Senses	O
when	O
I	O
made	O
that	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
frighted	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
whom	O
,	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
Cradle	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
swore	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kelsy	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
my	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
a	O
dutiful	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
lived	O
very	O
regularly	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
particular	O
Company	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
a	O
distressed	O
Widow	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
Rigby	O
,	O
nor	O
Cooper	O
,	O
-	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
my	O
Child	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
29.	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Daw	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Hopkins	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hog	O
's	O
Skin	O
Saddle	O
,	O
a	O
tann	O
'd	O
Leather	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Lamley	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
,	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
30.	O
Charles	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
Ann	B-pers
Eaves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
India	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
two	O
quilted	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
six	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Frock	O
without	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Adderson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
Adderson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
be	O
confined	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
22	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
discharged	O
3	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
this	O
very	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
entrusted	O
this	O
Woman	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
thinking	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
my	O
Things	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
was	O
absconded	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
her	O
'till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Dorman	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
,	O
two	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
here	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
swear	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dorman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
entrusted	O
by	O
Adderson	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
.	O
She	O
pawned	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Name	O
;	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
April	O
12	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
April	O
22	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
May	O
24	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
March	O
4	O
,	O
a	O
Cloak	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
April	O
16	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
17th	O
or	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Pinners	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
February	O
7	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
May	O
19	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
4	O
d.	O
May	O
15	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
8	O
d.	O
May	O
1	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
8	O
d.	O
April	O
28	O
,	O
five	O
Napkins	O
3	O
s.	O
May	O
12	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
6	O
d.	O
May	O
13	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
4	O
d.	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
a	O
Mob	O
8	O
d.	O
May	O
5	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
9	O
s.	O
May	O
20	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
May	O
24	O
,	O
a	O
Quilt	O
14	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
with	O
this	O
14	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
she	O
redeemed	O
two	O
Spoons	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Adderson	O
's	O
;	O
so	O
by	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
she	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
entrust	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
pawn	O
Goods	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Adderson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
commit	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
Custody	O
?	O
Adderson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
is	O
mistaken	O
in	O
his	O
Law	O
.	O
You	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
without	O
knowing	O
what	O
Authority	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
faulty	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
Dorman	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
List	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Addersons	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Name	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
any	O
Questions	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Name	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
check	O
'd	O
Apron	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
short	O
silk	O
Apron	O
for	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Remnant	O
of	O
new	O
Stuff	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Breadth	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Muslin	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
but	O
she	O
laid	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
that	O
receive	O
Goods	O
in	O
pawn	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
cautious	O
:	O
You	O
are	O
Nurseries	O
of	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
vent	O
for	O
stollen	O
Goods	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
them	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
Half	O
the	O
Felonies	O
committed	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
are	O
owing	O
to	O
this	O
Encouragement	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
of	O
an	O
Iron-grey	O
Colour	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Millet	O
.	O
My	O
Stable	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
July	O
6	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron-grey	O
Mare	O
,	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
were	O
stollen	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
pewter	O
Platter	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Mare	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Enmery	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
July	O
6	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
He	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
her	O
a	O
Feed	O
of	O
Corn	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Barley	O
Mow	O
,	O
near	O
Kent	O
street	O
Turnpike	O
.	O
I	O
unlocked	O
the	O
Stable	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
rid	O
60	O
Miles	O
since	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
last	O
Night	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
under	O
the	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
warm	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
heated	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
impossible	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
come	O
so	O
far	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
Bed	O
with	O
my	O
two	O
little	O
Children	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Children	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
them	O
down	O
Stairs	O
to	O
order	O
another	O
Feed	O
of	O
Corn	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Hostler	O
at	O
the	O
pewter	O
Platter	O
:	O
And	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Hostler	O
,	O
Hostler	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
take	O
my	O
Mare	O
:	O
I	O
rubbed	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
Mr.	O
Millet	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
very	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Millet	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
Mare	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
Operations	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Mare	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
nor	O
take	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Emmery	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Friends	O
this	O
17	O
Years	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
17	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
33	O
,	O
34.	O
Jane	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Buttock	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
weight	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Griffith	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
36.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Worsted	O
Cap	O
and	O
a	O
Felt	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Rowles	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
,	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
37	O
John	B-pers
Cisti	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Donnel	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
John	O
Donnel	O
.	O
The	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
stole	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
(	O
The	O
Willing	O
Mind	O
)	O
riding	O
off	O
the	O
Armitage	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
to	O
roll	O
some	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hold	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hold	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
Chair	O
in	O
the	O
Cabbin	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchmaker	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
his	O
Examination	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Examination	O
and	O
Confession	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cisti	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
before	O
me	O
Richard	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
said	O
Cisti	O
being	O
charged	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Donnel	I-pers
,	O
Master	O
of	O
The	O
Willing	O
Mind	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Cisti	I-pers
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cabbin	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Sloop	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	O
Donnel	O
;	O
he	O
confesseth	O
and	O
saith	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Major	O
Woolhead	O
in	O
Leadenhall	O
street	O
for	O
42	O
s.	O
and	O
farther	O
saith	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cisti	I-pers
.	O
Major	B-pers
Woolhead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
buy	O
this	O
Watch	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
:	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
fully	O
to	O
the	O
Description	O
in	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Maker	O
's	O
Name	O
is	O
advertised	O
(	O
W	O
A	O
Y	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Name	O
on	O
the	O
Watch	O
is	O
WISE	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
immediately	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sign	O
his	O
Confession	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38	O
Isabel	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
sixteen	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
39	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
5th-last	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Hardwick	O
.	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Cummins	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Justices	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
assigned	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
Goal	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Malden	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Morgan	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Smith	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
due	O
Form	O
of	O
Law	O
convicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
8	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Check-Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hilder	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Check-Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
And	O
by	O
a	O
certain	O
Jury	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
duly	O
impanneled	O
and	O
sworn	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
legally	O
tryed	O
and	O
convicted	O
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
Malden	O
otherwise	O
Morgan	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
so	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
attainted	O
and	O
convicted	O
;	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Shelton	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Malden	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
feloniously	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
house	O
,	O
lodge	O
,	O
comfort	O
,	O
maintain	O
and	O
harbour	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
Our	O
Soveraign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
his	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alston	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Malden	I-pers
escaped	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
after	O
Condemnation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
retaken	O
:	O
On	O
Whitson-Monday	O
Morning	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
again	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
Hold	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
our	O
People	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
search	O
we	O
could	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
retake	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
Court	O
to	O
receive	O
fresh	O
Judgment	O
.	O
After	O
several	O
Enquiries	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Germane	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Fetters	O
off	O
,	O
by	O
Shelton	O
:	O
she	O
confessed	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
harboured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
set	O
her	O
Name	O
or	O
her	O
Mark	O
to	O
her	O
Confession	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Caldwell	O
.	O
She	O
set	O
her	O
Mark	O
to	O
this	O
Examination	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
it	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Examination	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Shelton	O
s	O
,	O
taken	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
Williams	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Who	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
her	O
Servant	O
acquainted	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
Malden	O
had	O
again	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Curiosity	O
leading	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Malden	O
's	O
Room	O
which	O
joined	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
there	O
saw	O
him	O
eating	O
some	O
Pig	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
this	O
Examinant	O
,	O
applied	O
to	O
one	O
Germane	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
to	O
file	O
off	O
his	O
Fetters	O
,	O
who	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
an	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
returned	O
to	O
Malden	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
you	O
want	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
'till	O
I	O
am	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Irons	O
on	O
his	O
Legs	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
She	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
enquired	O
how	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
he	O
loosened	O
a	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
raised	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
of	O
his	O
Fetters	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
through	O
into	O
the	O
Funnel	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
Stone	O
fall	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stuck	O
fast	O
in	O
the	O
Funnel	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Difficulty	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Common	O
Shore	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shore	O
,	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
an	O
Engine	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
People	O
that	O
pursued	O
passed	O
by	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
Malden	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
?	O
Alston	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
her	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Whitsun-Monday	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Servant	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Malden	O
.	O
You	O
Blockhead	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
's	O
Story	O
:	O
No	O
Master	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
really	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
.	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
many	O
People	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
see	O
him	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Malden	O
's	O
Wife	O
's	O
Room	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
sitting	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Women	O
round	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
he	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
)	O
his	O
Trowsers	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
seems	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
sleeves	O
of	O
his	O
striped	O
Jacket	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
White	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whose	O
House	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Wive	O
's	O
:	O
The	O
Woman	O
they	O
call	O
Malden	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
lives	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
should	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Fetters	O
upon	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rivets	O
of	O
a	O
prodigious	O
Bigness	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
great	O
Links	O
of	O
the	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
great	O
Rivets	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
Shelton	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alston	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
very	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Woman	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
vastly	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
White	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Women	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
in	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
how	O
many	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
cautious	O
of	O
hurting	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
take	O
care	O
not	O
to	O
hurt	O
your	O
self	O
?	O
now	O
you	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
indeed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
occasion	O
'd	O
his	O
taking	O
up	O
his	O
Trowsers	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bravado	O
,	O
and	O
laugh	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Teeth	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
broke	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Several	O
People	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thinks	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
an	O
idle	O
Fellow	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
see	O
him	O
too	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
omitted	O
(	O
admitted	O
)	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
very	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Humphries	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
there	O
sometimes	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
-	O
here	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
the	O
Irons	O
on	O
his	O
Legs	O
in	O
a	O
Bravado	O
,	O
and	O
laugh	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
about	O
him	O
here	O
,	O
(	O
putting	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
his	O
Wast	O
)	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
seen	O
Malden	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apartment	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
told	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Wife	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
live	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
in	O
any	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Shelton	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
hers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
her	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alston	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Malden	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Shelton	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Shelton	O
live	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Next	O
Door	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
Malden	O
,	O
the	O
Houses	O
communicate	O
,	O
only	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
Row	O
of	O
Pales	O
between	O
.	O
Germane	O
.	O
On	O
Whitsun-Monday	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
White	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Shelton	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
privately	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
might	O
put	O
her	O
Life	O
into	O
my	O
Hands	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
shocked	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
?	O
Can	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
Malden	O
has	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
of	O
Jayl	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
Fetters	O
off	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
not	O
for	O
an	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
;	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
wrong	O
my	O
Conscience	O
,	O
my	O
King	O
,	O
nor	O
my	O
Country	O
.	O
She	O
found	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
answer	O
her	O
Ends	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
betray	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
away	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
not	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Temperance	O
Germane	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
above	O
Evidence	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
uses	O
Newgate-Market	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sad	O
Up	O
roar	O
;	O
for	O
Malden	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Pshaw	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
impossible	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
I	O
give	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
to	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
Children	O
while	O
I	O
am	O
out	O
,	O
comes	O
and	O
says	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
Malden	O
gone	O
up	O
Stairs	O
:	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
God	O
gives	O
me	O
Leave	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
eating	O
Pig	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
eat	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
eat	O
it	O
yourself	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
Oh	O
!	O
Daniel	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
loosened	O
a	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Fetters	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Funnel	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
stuck	O
;	O
but	O
God	O
brought	O
him	O
through	O
it	O
.	O
How	O
will	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
Irons	O
off	O
,	O
says	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
Germane	O
's	O
and	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
all	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
want	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
be	O
taken	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Irons	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
,	O
a	O
brown	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
brown	O
Shagreen	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
8	O
ruffled	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Shoe-buckles	O
,	O
two	O
large	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
coarse	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Vere	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Shoe-buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ditto	O
Knee-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bob-wig	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
:	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Shoe-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
Knee-buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gravener	I-pers
:	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Vere	O
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
John	O
Vere	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
joining	O
to	O
mine	O
.	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
Floor	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
Window	O
which	O
serves	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
that	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Lead	O
of	O
that	O
Window	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
taken	O
off	O
:	O
the	O
Sink	O
where	O
I	O
wash	O
myself	O
every	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
befoe	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
impossible	O
and	O
the	O
whole	O
family	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
his	O
Examination	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
a	O
back	O
Waiste	O
at	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nokes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lives	O
in	O
Bel-yard	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
or	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
empty	O
House	O
early	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Elis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Clerkenwell-green	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Shirt	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Parsons	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Markland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
Shirt	O
to	O
pawn	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Shirt	O
which	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
's	O
Maid	O
,	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Shirt	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
:	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Clerk	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banning	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shirts	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
Eight	O
of	O
these	O
Shirts	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
I	O
know	O
was	O
safe	O
that	O
Night	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12.	O
Rich	B-pers
Tabor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Shirt	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
Back	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Buckles	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Knee-buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
He	O
begged	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Jail	O
in	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gravener	O
swore	O
to	O
his	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pincers	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Ledge	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
supposed	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
untwisted	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robbed	O
the	O
House	O
dropped	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41	O
Robert	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Margaret	B-pers
Beauchamp	I-pers
.	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
June	O
13	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Sarah	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
Council	O
.	O
This	O
Prosecution	O
is	O
for	O
Bigamy	O
;	O
an	O
Offence	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
committed	O
in	O
marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
he	O
married	O
Sarah	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
married	O
Margaret	O
Beauchamp	O
:	O
We	O
shall	O
clearly	O
prove	O
both	O
Marriages	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Offence	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
produce	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
who	O
married	O
two	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
Robert	O
Hussey	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Seaton	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
co-habited	O
together	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Children	O
were	O
looked	O
on	O
as	O
the	O
legitimate	O
Issue	O
of	O
this	O
Marriage	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Gainham	O
.	O
The	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1733	O
.	O
I	O
married	O
a	O
Couple	O
at	O
the	O
Rainbow-Coffee-house	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
entered	O
the	O
Marriage	O
in	O
my	O
Register	O
.	O
As	O
fair	O
a	O
Register	O
as	O
any	O
Church	O
in	O
England	O
can	O
produce	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
last	O
Night	O
to	O
the	O
Fore-man	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Clerk	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
London	O
Punch-House	O
.	O
Reads	O
.	O
Robert	O
Hussey	O
,	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Westminster	O
,	O
Batchelor	O
;	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Setyon	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
fair	O
a	O
Register	O
as	O
any	O
Church	O
can	O
produce	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
all	O
my	O
own	O
Hand-writing	O
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
This	O
Certificate	O
is	O
all	O
my	O
Writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
these	O
People	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Gainham	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
gives	O
always	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Parishes	O
where	O
they	O
live	O
.	O
A	O
Spinster	O
,	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
say	O
a	O
single	O
Woman	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
ashamed	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
own	O
a	O
clandestine	O
Marriage	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
a	O
Court	O
of	O
Justice	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Gainham	O
.	O
(	O
Bowing	O
)	O
Video	O
meliora	O
,	O
deteriora	O
sequor	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
But	O
by	O
that	O
Paper	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Gainbam	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
to	O
my	O
Register	O
:	O
't	O
is	O
as	O
fair	O
a	O
Register	O
as	O
any	O
Church	O
in	O
England	O
can	O
show	O
you	O
.	O
This	O
Paper	O
is	O
a	O
Copy	O
from	O
my	O
Register	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
Register	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
on	O
your	O
Oath	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
you	O
never	O
enter	O
Marriages	O
in	O
that	O
Book	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
Marriage	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Gainbam	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
page	O
my	O
Book	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
altered	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Marriages	O
are	O
put	O
down	O
Alphabetically	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
very	O
readily	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Pray	O
who	O
directed	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
Paper	O
to	O
the	O
Fore-man	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
?	O
Gainham	O
.	O
My	O
own	O
common	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Sir	O
:	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
here	O
to	O
Day	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stallwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
often	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
her	O
Lyings	O
to	O
,	O
she	O
appeared	O
publickly	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
her	O
as	O
such	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Sarah	O
Hussey	O
's	O
Aunt	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
honest	O
Girl	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
lived	O
three	O
Years	O
together	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Frame-Guilder	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
many	O
and	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
supped	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
owned	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knows	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
lived	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
visited	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hussey	O
visited	O
me	O
:	O
They	O
passed	O
for	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
They	O
lived	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Whittle	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Brownlow-street	O
;	O
they	O
lived	O
there	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Year	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
no	O
one	O
made	O
any	O
Objections	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
once	O
I	O
was	O
abroad	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
behaved	O
as	O
other	O
Men	O
and	O
their	O
Wives	O
do	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
been	O
abroad	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
Mistress	O
?	O
Humphries	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
Man	O
use	O
his	O
Mistress	O
very	O
kindly	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Hussey	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
satisfied	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
,	O
else	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
question	O
them	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
any	O
Doubt	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Whittle	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Part	O
of	O
every	O
honest	O
Man	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Children	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
married	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
Dr.	O
Gainham	O
)	O
remembered	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Register	O
fair	O
and	O
clear	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Register	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
God-father	O
to	O
his	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Mouth	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
registered	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Such	O
Evidence	O
as	O
this	O
,	O
such	O
presumptive	O
Evidence	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
rejected	O
,	O
'till	O
the	O
Fact	O
be	O
established	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
this	O
last	O
Marriage	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
not	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
and	O
confess	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
to	O
bind	O
him	O
?	O
If	O
a	O
Man	O
confesses	O
himself	O
guilty	O
of	O
Bigamy	O
,	O
shall	O
not	O
that	O
be	O
Evidence	O
?	O
Council	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
only	O
presumptive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
admitting	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
dangerous	O
.	O
A	O
Parish	O
Clerk	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
two	O
Christenings	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Whittles	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
registered	O
two	O
Children	O
in	O
such	O
Names	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whittle	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
give	O
Directions	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Clerk	O
take	O
those	O
Directions	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
wicked	O
as	O
to	O
deceive	O
the	O
young	O
Girl	O
?	O
How	O
he	O
could	O
marry	O
her	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Wife	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
other	O
Woman	O
says	O
she	O
is	O
your	O
Wife	O
?	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Wickedness	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
wicked	O
as	O
you	O
imagine	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
married	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
(	O
Sarah	O
Hussey	O
)	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Wickedness	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
forgive	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
learned	O
Council	O
's	O
Opinion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
Seajeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
the	O
Marriage	O
with	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
;	O
another	O
Wife	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
Council	O
's	O
Opinion	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
hold	O
the	O
Woman	O
I	O
have	O
married	O
now	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
this	O
Discourse	O
at	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
It	O
must	O
be	O
granted	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
here	O
is	O
only	O
circumstantial	O
Proof	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Registring	O
of	O
Children	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
that	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
Marriage	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
for	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
this	O
Seaton	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
dye	O
,	O
till	O
6	O
Months	O
after	O
this	O
pretended	O
Marriage	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Our	O
Business	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
annul	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
punish	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
living	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
Woman	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
neither	O
de	O
Jure	O
,	O
nor	O
de	O
Facto	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brothers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
;	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Elenor	O
Brothers	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Tabernacle	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Father	O
gave	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
March	O
was	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
who	O
married	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Senses	O
since	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
16th	O
Day	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
her	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
dead	O
above	O
two	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
died	O
in	O
March	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
And	O
their	O
Marriage	O
was	O
in	O
September	O
1733	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
alive	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
live	O
with	O
this	O
Man	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Brothers	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
8	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
my	O
Daughter	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
(	O
Seaton	O
)	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
This	O
second	O
Marriage	O
broke	O
my	O
poor	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Senses	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
