TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
1736.	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
WILLIAMS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1736	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXVI	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Foddy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
Konst	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
Fleetwood	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Milliship	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boultby	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bellwood	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Timbrel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Luttman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blakesly	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Hipworth	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
++	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
++	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Gardell	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Isaac	O
Clark	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hameston	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Cramp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
Richard	O
Heather	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Cows	O
from	O
Woodford	B-place
in	I-place
Essex	I-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
drove	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Ground	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Edmd	B-pers
Pinfold	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Cows	O
;	O
an	O
ill	O
Thought	O
coming	O
into	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
by	O
Gaming	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Badger	I-pers
Welham	I-pers
,	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Charles	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
May	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Tea-strainer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
large	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
,	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
And	O
4.	O
Ann	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Astley	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Months	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Warning	O
;	O
when	O
her	O
time	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
several	O
Things	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
use	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
Three	O
large	O
Spoons	O
,	O
4	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
between	O
30	O
and	O
40	O
Shillings	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
these	O
were	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
examining	O
farther	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Linnen	O
gone	O
then	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
my	O
Business	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
we	O
found	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Curtis	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wybourn	O
's	O
on	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
;	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
and	O
another	O
Sheet	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Howards	O
;	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Franklin	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
Howard	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
lain	O
many	O
Nights	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
taken	O
all	O
Opportunities	O
to	O
wrong	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Curtis	O
's	O
,	O
Howard	O
's	O
and	O
Wybourn	O
's	O
;	O
when	O
Franklin	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Curtis	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
before	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
what	O
Things	O
Franklin	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Greenwood	O
had	O
brought	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbrokers	O
appear	O
'd	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
particular	O
Times	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Greenwood	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Franklin	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5	O
,	O
6.	O
James	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Macguineys	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Velvet	O
Coats	O
lac	O
'd	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
2	O
pair	O
Velvet	O
Breaches	O
,	O
2	O
Padesoy	O
Wastcoats	O
lac	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Hanger	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Belt	O
,	O
18	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
4	O
large	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	O
Cotes	O
,	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Cotes	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Bond-Street	B-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
May	O
10	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
wak	O
'd	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
2	O
Men	O
in	O
my	O
Chamber	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
my	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
snatch	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Gold	O
Repeating	O
Watch	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
but	O
they	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
Things	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Room	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
my	O
Chamber	O
;	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Velvet	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
one	O
Dove	O
Colour	O
,	O
embroider	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Chocolate	O
Colour	O
lac	O
'd	O
,	O
eighteen	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
;	O
a	O
Hanger	O
mounted	O
with	O
Silver	O
;	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Stockings	O
;	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Stocks	O
,	O
and	O
Padesoy	O
Wastcoats	O
to	O
the	O
Velvet	O
Coats	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
D	O
'd	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
your	O
Room	O
?	O
Baily	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
only	O
observe	O
that	O
one	O
was	O
taller	O
and	O
thinner	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
imperfect	O
Light	O
of	O
their	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
:	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
are	O
near	O
their	O
Size	O
and	O
Shape	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
?	O
Baily	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Cotes	O
's	O
Journeyman	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
made	O
any	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
the	O
Goods	O
?	O
Baily	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
have	O
recover	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Chocolate	O
Velvet	O
Suit	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
Lace	O
is	O
stripp	O
'd	O
off	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
one	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Short's-Gardens	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
of	O
my	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
Stockings	O
,	O
my	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Sword	O
and	O
Hanger	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
O'Henlon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Cotes	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Business	O
as	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
three	O
Months	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Macguineys	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Distemper	O
and	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
Cure	O
,	O
so	O
began	O
our	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
Macguineys	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
something	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
swear	O
never	O
to	O
discover	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
propose	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
propos	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
Time	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
another	O
Partner	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
.	O
I	O
condescended	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
leave	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
open	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
:	O
Macguineys	O
and	O
Scott	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
's	O
Chamber	O
directly	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
:	O
Macguineys	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Pistol	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
particular	O
Things	O
they	O
took	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
their	O
Burden	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
have	O
a	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
Sword	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
They	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
without	O
hindrance	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
Home	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
agreed	O
not	O
to	O
meet	O
for	O
twelve	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
to	O
avoid	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
Macguineys	O
House	O
next	O
Morning	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
before	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
Two	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
Days	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
before	O
Macguineys	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
alone	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
should	O
discover	O
:	O
I	O
assured	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
discover	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
consulted	O
People	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
can	O
hurt	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
keep	O
your	O
own	O
Counsel	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
Velvet	O
Suits	O
,	O
eighteen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
and	O
Hanger	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Repeating	O
Watch	O
,	O
three	O
large	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Spoon	O
and	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
assured	O
me	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
touch	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
two	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
two	O
Months	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
equally	O
divided	O
.	O
Scott	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
the	O
Discovery	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
eight	O
Days	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
discharged	O
before	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
Discovery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
after	O
you	O
was	O
discharged	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Macguineys	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Swallow-street	O
,	O
by	O
Appointment	O
,	O
four	O
Days	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
advised	O
me	O
right	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
own	O
Counsel	O
,	O
for	O
now	O
I	O
saw	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Shirt	O
and	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
's	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
Thing	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
assuring	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
touch	O
the	O
rest	O
for	O
two	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Scott	O
likewise	O
several	O
times	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
Days	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
dined	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
all	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Danger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
together	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
Macguineys	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
Crape	O
over	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
the	O
Discovery	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
At	O
Justice	O
De	O
Viel	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
accord	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
Macguineys	O
had	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
another	O
Patient	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Distemper	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
Possession	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
Shirt	O
and	O
the	O
Stockings	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
one	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Were	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
one	O
Savage	O
's	O
House	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Savage	O
I	O
let	O
into	O
the	O
Secret	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
wrong	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
Goods	O
divided	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Savage	O
a-again	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
direct	O
Savage	O
to	O
go	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
To	O
Macguineys	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
see	O
Savage	O
at	O
one	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Secret	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
Savage	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Stockings	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
Savage	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
Macguineys	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
Things	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Guiney	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
stript	O
the	O
Lace	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Suits	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Money	O
was	O
for	O
my	O
Part	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Maid	O
and	O
this	O
Fellow	O
:	O
the	O
Maid	O
I	O
committed	O
upon	O
strong	O
Circumstances	O
;	O
But	O
on	O
Re-examination	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
:	O
I	O
examined	O
this	O
Spark	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
prevaricated	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
to	O
commit	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
's	O
Shirts	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
supposed	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
before	O
me	O
the	O
2d	O
Time	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
this	O
Confession	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Short's-Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
before	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
now	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
acquainted	O
Savage	O
with	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
cheated	O
of	O
his	O
Part	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
Savage	O
as	O
a	O
proper	O
Person	O
to	O
secure	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
at	O
this	O
House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Hanger	O
,	O
Sword	O
,	O
Velvet	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Spoons	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
.	O
I	O
make	O
Oath	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Watch	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
five	O
Spoons	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robert	O
Cotes	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Spoons	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
May	O
9.	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
my	O
eldest	O
Son	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Dulwich	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Brother	O
and	O
Sister	O
;	O
we	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
Home	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	B-pers
Tyrawley	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Somerset-House	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
informed	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Fact	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Manner	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
has	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Spoons	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
Kitchens	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
O'Henlon	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Cotes	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
Months	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
Fault	O
with	O
,	O
-	O
Smith	O
.	O
O'Henlon	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Mother	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
I	O
doubted	O
the	O
Truth	O
o'n't	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Day	O
following	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Chairman	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
know	O
his	O
Haunts	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Places	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
;	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
Savage	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Savage	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Box	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
Savage	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
we	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
brought	O
Box	O
and	O
all	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
De	O
Viel	O
's	O
.	O
Davis	O
followed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
were	O
nine	O
Shirts	O
which	O
Savage	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Washer-woman	O
's	O
:	O
we	O
brought	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
wait	O
for	O
Savage	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
Discovery	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
O'Henlon	O
been	O
often	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Macguineys	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
Son	O
and	O
Daughter	O
kept	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
nine	O
Shirts	O
to	O
wash	O
from	O
Savage	O
himself	O
at	O
Davis	O
's	O
John	B-pers
Dobein	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shirts	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
whether	O
Macguineys	O
used	O
he	O
House	O
.	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
but	O
once	O
.	O
Macguineys	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
drank	O
with	O
O'Henlon	O
but	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q	O
Pray	O
how	O
come	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
?	O
Macguineys	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
Physick	O
before	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
given	O
the	O
Answer	O
,	O
we	O
wanted	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
.	O
Macguineys	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
in	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Room	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
and	O
Small	O
Beer	O
for	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
in	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Room	O
at	O
10	O
.	O
Scott	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
from	O
Sunday	O
to	O
Monday	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Jephson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Macguineys	O
's	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Macguineys	O
lay	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
at	O
six	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
O'Henlon	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
?	O
Jephson	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Bed	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
lay	O
in	O
had	O
blue	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
drawn	O
about	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
open	O
them	O
?	O
Jephson	O
.	O
A	O
n't	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
:	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Jephson	O
.	O
May	O
10.	O
it	O
was	O
Monday	O
.	O
O'Henlon	O
came	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Mother	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
above	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
before	O
:	O
young	O
Macguineys	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
ill	O
State	O
of	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
Physick	O
.	O
O'Henlon	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
tell	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
says	O
of	O
Macguineys	O
's	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
true	O
;	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Cotes	O
's	O
Maid	O
knows	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
our	O
Door	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
her	O
Name	O
is	O
Catherine	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
She	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
in	O
Short's-Gardens	O
;	O
Savage	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
there	O
:	O
O'Henlon	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
with	O
Savage	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Savage	O
lodged	O
with	O
us	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
much	O
Notice	O
of	O
People	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
O'Henlon	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
there	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Times	O
.	O
C.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
such	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
Davis	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
sober	O
and	O
serious	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Name	O
is	O
not	O
Macguineys	O
,	O
but	O
Mackenzie	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Savage	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Rogue	O
.	O
He	O
offer	O
'd	O
two	O
Shirts	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Dun	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Dealings	O
between	O
O'Henlon	O
and	O
Savage	O
but	O
once	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
time	O
Savage	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Deloni	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
,	O
Artbur	O
Hendrick	O
,	O
never	O
heard	O
ill	O
of	O
Macguineys	O
before	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Archdeacon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
Scott	O
up	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
Labouring	O
Work	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Soldier	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
subpoenaed	O
but	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Archdeacon	I-pers
.	O
May	O
Day	O
was	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Scott	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
us	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Obligations	O
known	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
where	O
to	O
get	O
Victuals	O
;	O
on	O
Sunday	O
May	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
chipping	O
Stocks	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
up	O
'till	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Key	O
by	O
my	O
Bedside	O
.	O
Susannah	O
But'cr	O
confirm	O
'd	O
Andercen	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	O
A	O
gin	O
spoke	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Mr.	O
Cotes	O
mov	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Council	O
for	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
Patrick	B-pers
O'Henlon	I-pers
,	O
might	O
be	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
such	O
Order	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
granted	O
.	O
7.	O
Mary	B-pers
Swann	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Black	O
silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Ticking	O
for	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Mary	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Forrest	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Pot	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Mallabar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
33	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
33	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
ditto	O
Edged	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
8	O
s	O
one	O
Holland	O
Mob	O
laced	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Airy	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
De	O
Viel	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
his	O
Confession	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Francis	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
Shirts	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Asbley	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
David	B-pers
Lacock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lbs	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pendall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Ship	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Generosity	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
May	O
4	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Pendall	O
.	O
I	O
shipp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Dieppe	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
Dieppe	O
to	O
Guernsey	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
stow	O
'd	O
about	O
70	O
or	O
80	O
Hogsheads	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
aboard	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Men	O
had	O
leave	O
to	O
Smoke	O
and	O
Chew	O
what	O
they	O
pleas	O
'd	O
but	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
Pocket	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
Biscuit	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
aft	O
into	O
my	O
Cabin	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cowdell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Bags	O
were	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Forecastle	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
toss	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
Bow	O
to	O
Ned	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
hand	O
the	O
Bags	O
to	O
Ned	O
Gill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
speaking	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
Shirt	O
,	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
with	O
Cambrick	O
Borders	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
made	O
first	O
my	O
Door	O
and	O
Windows	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Window	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
broke	O
,	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
peeping	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
His	O
Sister	O
liv	O
'd	O
up	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
Blood	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
!	O
come	O
up	O
Stairs	O
!	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
Things	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Manton	I-pers
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
as	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Barlin	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
swore	O
the	O
Boy	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Cotton	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
little	O
Boys	O
Sister	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
John	B-pers
Holburt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Daniel	B-pers
Macneal	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Peruke	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
silver	O
Stock-buckle	O
,	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Base-metal	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
April	O
20	O
.	O
1735	O
.	O
Macneal	O
.	O
Last	O
April	O
was	O
twelve	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
by	O
Well-close	O
Square	O
:	O
Holburt	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Malden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Box	O
:	O
Crossing	O
Salt-petre	B-place
Bank	I-place
in	O
my	O
way	O
Home	O
,	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Holburt	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stripp	O
'd	O
me	O
as	O
naked	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
'till	O
Daniel	O
Malden	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
Information	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
.	O
In	O
April	O
last	O
was	O
twelve	O
Month	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
my	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Evidence	O
stand	O
quaking	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
Condition	O
;	O
for	O
Christ	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
good	O
Christians	O
take	O
me	O
in	O
!	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
got	O
a	O
Blanket	O
and	O
put	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Wounds	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Couch	O
'till	O
twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
Home	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
Women	O
with	O
them	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Dallison	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
Time	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Blanket	O
and	O
Rug	O
and	O
cover	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
two	O
Men	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
had	O
dogg	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
stripp	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
near	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
express	O
himself	O
well	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
them	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
Macneal	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
be	O
then	O
lost	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
Jack	O
Holburt	O
's	O
Wife	O
brought	O
this	O
Coat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
Malden	O
having	O
made	O
his	O
Information	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
former	O
Witness	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
searching	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Coat	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
us	O
then	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
seems	O
she	O
has	O
since	O
recollected	O
her	O
Memory	O
.	O
Macneal	O
upon	O
the	O
first	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Jayl	O
,	O
knew	O
him	O
and	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
tuck	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
Fame	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
three	O
Informations	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
15.	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Iron	O
Harness-chains	O
,	O
a	O
Pitchfork	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
charged	O
him	O
with	O
picking	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Drawer	O
with	O
a	O
Whalebone	O
and	O
Bird	O
lime	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
17.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Plate-warmer	O
,	O
two	O
Black-horn	O
halfted	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
John	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Mortar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Storns	I-pers
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Saul	B-pers
Exel	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26	O
Saul	O
Exel	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
my	O
Child	O
and	O
it	O
's	O
Coral	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Child	O
home	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
without	O
it	O
:	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
frequently	O
take	O
the	O
Child	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Coral	O
was	O
sold	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Davenport	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davenport	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
Mother	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
4	O
s	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
full	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
Beer	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Coral	O
behind	O
our	O
Backs	O
in	O
Hog-Lane	O
;	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
Money	O
on	O
tour	O
Hackerey	O
Coach	O
men	O
.	O
Margety	B-pers
Pretty	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20	O
,	O
21.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Busco	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Casen	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Cousen	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Gondowin	I-pers
out	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calamanco	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
15d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
when	O
called	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Adler	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Sashes	O
glazed	O
with	O
Crown	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
John	O
Shepherd	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
24.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Bay	O
Stone	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Longhurst	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wollard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Horse	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
the	O
Widow	O
Longhurst	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
Leominster	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Sussex	I-place
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
lost	O
in	O
a	O
Stone-cart	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Highways	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Carter	O
put	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
long	O
Halter	O
of	O
my	O
Mistresses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Smith	O
field	O
leading	O
the	O
Horse	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
Horse	O
that	O
was	O
:	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
?	O
No	O
Matter	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Toll	O
House	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Cow	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
We	O
lost	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
the	O
7th	O
;	O
our	O
Stable	O
was	O
not	O
lock	O
'd	O
that	O
Night	O
only	O
hasped	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Friend	O
under	O
the	O
Heavens	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
but	O
God	O
and	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
no	O
Father	O
,	O
no	O
Mother	O
,	O
no	O
Friends	O
,	O
under	O
God	O
Almighty	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
that	O
Man	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Cook's-shop	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
direct	O
you	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Woollard	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
John	B-pers
Goswell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
live	O
Turkeys	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atterbury	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Moneys	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Row	I-pers
.	O
Mary	O
Row	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
poor	O
Creature	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Lodging	O
and	O
Victuals	O
for	O
nothing	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
more	O
than	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Days	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
one	O
Morning	O
about	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
my	O
Keys	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Keys	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
content	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgers	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bundling	O
up	O
their	O
Things	O
;	O
they	O
drew	O
the	O
Curtains	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
wak	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Spoons	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
;	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
laced	O
Head-cloaths	O
and	O
my	O
Stockings	O
too	O
.	O
This	O
Bundle	O
I	O
took	O
behind	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
:	O
Here	O
are	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
my	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
bundle	O
up	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
so	O
soon	O
?	O
Only	O
to	O
try	O
on	O
your	O
Wife	O
's	O
Head	O
(	O
says	O
she	O
)	O
and	O
down	O
Stairs	O
she	O
run	O
:	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
dropt	O
my	O
Landlady	O
's	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
untied	O
her	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
them	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
Landlady	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Things	O
:	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
two	O
Pewter	O
ones	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Landlady	O
's	O
Garters	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Shoes	O
with	O
silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Bundle	O
at	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Deborough	B-pers
Grasshous	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
check	O
'd	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Beere	I-pers
,	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Jack	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cogland	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
10	O
d.	O
++	O
28.	O
William	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Lining	O
for	O
a	O
Gown	O
in	O
two	O
Pieces	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
++	O
Dobson	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
P.	O
95	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Mob	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tonstall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Wallcot	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Robert	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Brass	O
Backs	O
for	O
Sconces	O
,	O
two	O
Sockets	O
,	O
two	O
Brass	O
Nossels	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Lamp	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Iron	O
Compasses	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bathmetal	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thresber	I-pers
,	O
May	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31	O
,	O
32.	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Daley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gerard	I-pers
,	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
William	O
Gerrard	O
.	O
My	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Fowls	O
stole	O
:	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
sent	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Witness	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Name	O
rightly	O
;	O
but	O
these	O
two	O
Men	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Fowls	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
we	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Esther	B-pers
Apple	I-pers
to	O
sell	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
but	O
they	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Farthing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Richard	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
76	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth-coloured	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
31	O
Yards	O
of	O
blue	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Crimson	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Yellow	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Mercery	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
And	O
34.	O
Elenor	B-pers
Cousen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
75	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
coloured	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
29	O
Yards	O
of	O
blue	O
ditto	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
became	O
my	O
Journeyman	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
since	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Cousens	O
had	O
carried	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
suspecting	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Baxter	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Cousens	O
brought	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Shagreen	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
Money	O
upon	O
two	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
piece	O
was	O
brought	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
Person	O
near	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
lend	O
Money	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
going	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Baxter	O
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
and	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Servant	O
whose	O
Name	O
was	O
Baxter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
discovered	O
the	O
Affair	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Baxter	O
immediately	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
charge	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
his	O
Master	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salt	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
Baxter	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
receiving	O
them	O
knowing	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
He	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Cousens	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
his	O
Arms	O
might	O
rot	O
off	O
his	O
Body	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
wrong	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
;	O
but	O
next	O
Day	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
Things	O
at	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
we	O
found	O
at	O
Pawnbrokers	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
excuse	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
this	O
Scrape	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Baxter	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
Cousens	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35	O
,	O
36	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
75	O
lbs	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
in	O
York-Buildings	B-place
,	O
Jan.	O
12	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
75	O
lbs	O
.	O
of	O
Brass	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lbs	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Jan	O
19	O
.	O
And	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Fourth	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
half	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mullalan	I-pers
.	O
In	O
January	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
house	O
:	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
made	O
the	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
in	O
his	O
Cellar	O
with	O
which	O
Baily	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
about	O
1/2	O
hundred	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
Tom	O
Smith	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Lombard-court	O
near	O
the	O
seven	O
Dials	O
at	O
9	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
per	O
hundred	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
About	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
we	O
enter	O
'd	O
again	O
and	O
got	O
as	O
much	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
we	O
sold	O
in	O
Dyott-street	O
for	O
11	O
s.	O
per	O
hundred	O
.	O
We	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
again	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Spindle	O
of	O
a	O
Brass-Cock	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Green	O
.	O
Tom	O
Smith	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
rob	O
there	O
these	O
seven	O
Years	O
and	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
out	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
consider	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
Irishman	O
.	O
Mullalan	O
.	O
So	O
are	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
he	O
will	O
swear	O
a	O
Cow	O
's	O
a	O
Horse	O
.	O
-	O
Hutchins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
concerd	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
York-Buildings	O
Company	O
:	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Service	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
;	O
but	O
missing	O
several	O
Things	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Some	O
little	O
Time	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
,	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
than	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Moon	O
,	O
you	O
sorry	O
Fellow	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
Mullalan	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Smith	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
several	O
Things	O
which	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
kindness	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
shy	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
Tom	B-pers
Fitz-Patrick	I-pers
for	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
.	O
O	O
you	O
Villain	O
!	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
me	O
before	O
?	O
Pray	O
my	O
Lord	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
Baily	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
drunk	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
troublesome	O
,	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
with	O
Money	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mullalan	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mullalan	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
Tom	O
Smith	O
's	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
then	O
,	O
you	O
Thieving	O
Dog	O
?	O
Edmund	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
for	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
Mullalan	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Cock-ey	O
'd	O
Charly	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Warrant	O
serv	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
Smith	O
's	O
means	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
cost	O
him	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
s.	O
that	O
Smith	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Smith	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
William	B-pers
Raitt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Alexander	B-pers
Raitt	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
two	O
silk	O
Aprons	O
,	O
three	O
silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
Padesoy	O
,	O
one	O
Burdett	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
two	O
Napkins	O
,	O
one	O
Table	O
Cloath	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
six	O
Cambrick	O
ditto	O
,	O
two	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
,	O
five	O
Suits	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Rufflels	O
,	O
with	O
sundry	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
a	O
Portugal	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6	O
Patrick	O
Smith	O
.	O
Sunday	O
May	O
16	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Walk	O
to	O
Pancras	O
,	O
leaving	O
all	O
fast	O
;	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
we	O
left	O
single	O
Lock	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
Mrs.	O
Raitt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
up	O
Stairs	O
should	O
let	O
herself	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
open	O
:	O
My	O
Wife	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
undress	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
ominated	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
gone	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Raitt	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
among	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Raitt	O
's	O
two	O
Sons	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Mrs.	O
Raitt	O
(	O
her	O
other	O
Son	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
)	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
bail	O
'd	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
has	O
made	O
herself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
Goods	O
at	O
Laurana	O
Ward	O
's	O
in	O
Crown-Court	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
'till	O
she	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
:	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
other	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
told	O
her	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
who	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Raitt	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
while	O
her	O
two	O
Sons	O
walked	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
two	O
bright	O
Keys	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
)	O
looking	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
somebody	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
still	O
;	O
then	O
walked	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Memory	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
either	O
go	O
in	O
or	O
come	O
out	O
:	O
but	O
Alexander	O
the	O
youngest	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
He	O
look	O
'd	O
both	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
somebody	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
put	O
her	O
Head	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
me	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
shy	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
Head	O
aside	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
cross	O
the	O
Kennel	O
by	O
herself	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
spake	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
her	O
only	O
by	O
her	O
living	O
with	O
Raitt	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Raitt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Oldcastle	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
younger	O
Brother	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
haste	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
Smith	O
's	O
Door	O
fast	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
is	O
gone	O
out	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
laughed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
their	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
their	O
Door	O
open	O
?	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
Fool	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
laughing	O
:	O
I	O
stept	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Lid	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Whiteness	O
of	O
the	O
Wood	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
or	O
cut	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
doing	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
?	O
They	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
trouble	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
for	O
both	O
the	O
Brothers	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Bundle	O
lie	O
upon	O
their	O
Mother	O
's	O
Couch-bed	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
discovered	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
for	O
themselves	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Bundle	O
to	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
Laurence	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
)	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
never	O
go	O
home	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ward	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bundle	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Coat	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table-Cloath	O
,	O
three	O
black	O
Hoods	O
,	O
two	O
Muslin	O
Hoods	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
Padusoy	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
open	O
Stocks	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
that	O
Sheet	O
now	O
it	O
is	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Midford	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
Discovery	O
.	O
Justice	O
Midford	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
first	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
enclined	O
to	O
make	O
herself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
?	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
say	O
nothing	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Friend	O
for	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Strangers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
advise	O
with	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Person	O
came	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
she	O
could	O
trust	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
trust	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Fellows	O
now	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
the	O
Discovery	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
now	O
,	O
almost	O
Verbatim	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
it	O
.	O
Laurena	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Cole	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
leave	O
the	O
Bundle	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
(	O
whereof	O
)	O
she	O
came	O
not	O
again	O
till	O
Monday	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
my	O
Place	O
was	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
must	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
an	O
empty	O
Trunk	O
,	O
(	O
whereof	O
)	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Things	O
.	O
From	O
Sunday	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
till	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
such	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
Those	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
all	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
at	O
Raitt	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Raitt	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Leach	O
a	O
Peruke-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Freeman	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
that	O
Sunday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Father	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
and	O
Sister	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
this	O
Woman	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
my	O
Sister	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
two	O
at	O
Dinner	O
.	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
new	O
Rails	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
nine	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
my	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
stop	O
my	O
Son	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Brother	O
was	O
sent	O
away	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
Morning	O
,	O
then	O
his	O
Master	O
came	O
and	O
fetched	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Smith	O
told	O
me	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
he	O
might	O
stay	O
here	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
dined	O
together	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
after	O
Dinner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
can	O
there	O
be	O
no	O
Mischief	O
done	O
without	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Gin	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
or	O
ending	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
What	O
Hour	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Box	O
broke	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
Between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
entering	O
into	O
Russet-street	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
;	O
we	O
only	O
said	O
your	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
on	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
about	O
five	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Hatton-Garden	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
six	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mitchen	I-pers
,	O
Archibald	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ailsbury	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Cambden	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
general	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
38.	O
James	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
divers	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
with	O
a	O
Mopstick	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
Neck	O
,	O
Stomach	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
Thighs	O
,	O
Knees	O
and	O
Legs	O
;	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
he	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
:	O
And	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
his	O
Work	O
better	O
,	O
he	O
beat	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
(	O
excessively	O
)	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Mercy	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Boy	O
cry	O
sadly	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
'till	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Peruke-Ribbon-Weaver	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
beat	O
you	O
no	O
more	O
with	O
my	O
Fist	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
beat	O
you	O
with	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
murder	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
vast	O
Cut	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blow	O
over	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
right	O
Ear	O
was	O
perfectly	O
lugg	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Skin	O
broke	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Plaister	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lewen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
Boy	O
between	O
13	O
and	O
14	O
Years	O
old	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
.	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
poor	O
Child	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
wash	O
'd	O
and	O
dress	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
the	O
Hurt	O
was	O
done	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Cut	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
another	O
on	O
his	O
Eyebrow	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
right	O
Ear	O
very	O
black	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
torn	O
with	O
Fingers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
run	O
from	O
his	O
Temples	O
about	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
wet	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
throwing	O
Water	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
blue	O
Marks	O
on	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
Shoulder	O
and	O
Stomach	O
,	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
my	O
Finger	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
beat	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Mopstick	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
broke	O
it	O
into	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
work	O
;	O
why	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
starv	O
'd	O
Child	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
should	O
you	O
work	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
he	O
starves	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
's	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
eat	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Fingers	O
stood	O
astrut	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
Blows	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Elbows	O
:	O
Then	O
the	O
Parish	O
Barrow	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Work-house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
walk	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Beadle	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
alive	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
heard	O
Noises	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
Words	O
,	O
nor	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
his	O
Face	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
cry	O
'd	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
you	O
Dog	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Occasions	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rumbling	O
Noise	O
.	O
One	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Face	O
was	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
this	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
.	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Work-house	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
large	O
Contusions	O
about	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
right	O
Temple	O
;	O
several	O
on	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
Wrists	O
,	O
Fingers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
one	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
Knee	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
emaciated	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
the	O
Abuse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Work	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
beat	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Mopstick	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Consumption	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Cough	O
,	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Diarrhea	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
must	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
be	O
worse	O
for	O
the	O
Bruises	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
must	O
hasten	O
his	O
Death	O
:	O
He	O
all	O
along	O
charg	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
with	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Balgay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
emaciated	O
;	O
nothing	O
but	O
Skin	O
and	O
Bone	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Temple	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
opening	O
the	O
Head	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
affected	O
the	O
Scull	O
;	O
The	O
Brain	O
was	O
clear	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
.	O
The	O
Bowels	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
Order	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
opening	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Lungs	O
adher	O
'd	O
so	O
strongly	O
to	O
the	O
Pleura	O
and	O
Ribs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
separate	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
little	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
skin	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
unfit	O
Subject	O
for	O
such	O
barbarous	O
Usage	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
immediate	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
might	O
hasten	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
liv	O
'd	O
much	O
longer	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
beat	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
declared	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
end	O
his	O
Days	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Face	O
bloody	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
stroke	O
given	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
flung	O
his	O
Shuttle	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
with	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
Nose	O
bleed	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
the	O
Bruises	O
might	O
come	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Spring	O
of	O
his	O
Battins	O
being	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Loom	O
to	O
mend	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Side	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
I	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
died	O
of	O
a	O
Consumption	O
.	O
39	O
Rosannah	B-pers
Swann	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
short	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Vanfrost	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Vanfrost	I-pers
.	O
I	O
loose	O
de	O
Cloke	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
dis	O
vor	O
Month	O
;	O
she	O
staul	O
'd	O
it	O
vrom	O
my	O
Rome	O
.	O
I	O
lordged	O
in	O
de	O
House	O
and	O
mine	O
Ausband	O
:	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
mine	O
Cloke	O
vas	O
gon	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Presonar	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
vold	O
not	O
sprack	O
vor	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
vill	O
tell	O
you	O
vat	O
,	O
I	O
vanted	O
Curtain	O
vor	O
de	O
Vindow	O
,	O
and	O
day	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
ve	O
vill	O
send	O
you	O
for	O
de	O
Shale	O
,	O
and	O
day	O
say	O
I	O
stole	O
dare	O
Blanket	O
vrom	O
de	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
de	O
gron	O
Shury	O
fine	O
de	O
Bill	O
vor	O
me	O
,	O
Husy	O
,	O
vor	O
vat	O
you	O
call	O
me	O
Newgate	O
Slut	O
,	O
vor	O
?	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
Water	O
in	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
cold	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
(	O
I	O
shall	O
call	O
)	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
two	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
borrowed	O
the	O
Dutch	O
Woman	O
's	O
Cloak	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
till	O
March	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Bedcloaths	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beamsley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
borrow	O
the	O
Dutch	O
Woman	O
's	O
Cloak	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
abed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
Maid	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
persuaded	O
Mrs.	O
Swann	O
to	O
borrow	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Maid	O
up	O
Stairs	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
over	O
her	O
Shoulders	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
Heater	O
and	O
Stand	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
December	O
24	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
41	O
,	O
42.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bullivant	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43.	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
George	O
Barker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Son	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
I	O
married	O
his	O
Mother	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Twelve	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Pannel	O
in	O
the	O
Shutter	O
cut	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
.	O
Esco	B-pers
Jacobson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
raised	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
seeing	O
his	O
Shutter	O
broke	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
.	O
Ursula	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
own	O
Mother	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
Words	O
about	O
some	O
Carr-Figures	O
which	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
.	O
Child	O
after	O
my	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
loose	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Child	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
abed	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
Husband	O
to	O
stay	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
unless	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
40	O
l.	O
Francis	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Fennel	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
44.	O
Joan	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Planes	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Mortois	O
Chissels	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hopper	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46	O
,	O
47.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Hannah	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowler	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Doland	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Bathmetal	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Bathmetal	O
Tea-Tongs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Boyde	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Hannah	I-pers
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Dowle	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Anvil	O
,	O
Weight	O
400	O
lb	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mabson	I-pers
,	O
September	O
4	O
1734	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Mabson	O
.	O
September	O
last	O
was	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Anvil	O
from	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
between	O
Night	O
and	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve-Month	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
several	O
Letters	O
from	O
one	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
telling	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
one	O
Letter	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
with	O
very	O
little	O
Trouble	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Woman	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Lodge	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
could	O
inform	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Anvil	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
unless	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
another	O
if	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Anvil	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
Coach-hire	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
's	O
Shop	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
secreted	O
,	O
any	O
Body	O
might	O
see	O
it	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
cost	O
me	O
two	O
Guineas	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
come	O
by	O
it	O
safely	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
without	O
Advice	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Advice	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
indict	O
him	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
grant	O
me	O
a	O
Warrant	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Anvil	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
without	O
prosecuting	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
the	O
Anvil	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
worth	O
6	O
l.	O
-	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
but	O
30	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
safely	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
Charge	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Trifle	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
(	O
30	O
s.	O
)	O
for	O
a	O
Thing	O
worth	O
6	O
l.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Anvil	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
a	O
Year	O
or	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Mahson	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
four	O
pence	O
half	O
penny	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
bid	O
three	O
pence	O
half	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
lose	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
Door	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
his	O
Door	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
offer	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Mabson	O
say	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
safe	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
two	O
Guineas	O
charge	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
you	O
in	O
one	O
sense	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Price	O
does	O
not	O
shew	O
it	O
;	O
For	O
the	O
Anvil	O
weighs	O
about	O
4	O
hundred	O
,	O
or	O
4	O
hundred	O
and	O
odd	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ince	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Anvil	O
brought	O
into	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Agreement	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
per	O
Hundred	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
half	O
Cash	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
in	O
Iron	O
Plate	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
afterwards	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
strong	O
Demand	O
for	O
more	O
Money	O
than	O
the	O
Agreement	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Iron	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Agreement	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
afterward	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Anvil	O
came	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
two	O
Hours	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
:	O
We	O
question	O
'd	O
whence	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
above-Bridge	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
necessity	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
Master	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
Price	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
any	O
Body	O
will	O
allow	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
2	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
Cash	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Difference	O
between	O
paying	O
in	O
Iron	O
Plate	O
and	O
Cash	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Mabson	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
somewhere	O
about	O
Golden-Lane	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
's	O
Foreman	O
:	O
This	O
Anvil	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
Shop	O
in	O
a	O
Wherry	O
:	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Men	O
to	O
heave	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
that	O
Necessity	O
drove	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Hundred	O
and	O
half	O
in	O
Plate	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
Master	O
's	O
Trade	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
Iron	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
?	O
Josiah	O
Roper	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
that	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Story	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
buying	O
2	O
stolen	O
Anvil	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mabson	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
claims	O
the	O
Anvil	O
:	O
well	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Mabson	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
either	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
Anvil	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
.	O
Why	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
says	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
swear	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
Advantage	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
For	O
he	O
demanded	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
Pocket	O
:	O
Let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
then	O
says	O
Mr.	O
Mabson	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
grant	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Anvil	O
was	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
him	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Time	O
:	O
You	O
'll	O
hardly	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
reputable	O
Man	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
has	O
been	O
Smith	O
to	O
me	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
is	O
a	O
general	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
and	O
just	O
Man	O
.	O
Justice	O
Cross	O
,	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
gave	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
just	O
,	O
and	O
reputable	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
49.	O
John	B-pers
Chidley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
May	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
51.	O
John	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Iron	O
Chains	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Nugent	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
William	B-pers
Pooley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ashburn	I-pers
,	O
March	O
5	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
54.	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
and	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Whitcher	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
55.	O
Phillis	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Pillow-biers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Udall	I-pers
,	O
from	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
56.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Doleman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Dodsley	O
'd	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dodsley	I-pers
,	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
Fleece	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	I-place
New-street	I-place
by	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
Bars	I-place
)	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Porrage-pot	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
we	O
shar	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Pot	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
my	O
Part	O
.	O
He	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Tenner-Row	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
the	O
14th	O
or	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
made	O
this	O
Discovery	O
,	O
because	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
to	O
Prison	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
laugh	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dodsley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Window-shutters	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
between	O
15	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Corner	O
Cupboard	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
Doleman	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shar	O
'd	O
no	O
more	O
with	O
me	O
than	O
36	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
Word	O
for	O
my	O
Share	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
before	O
we	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
we	O
poison	O
'd	O
his	O
little	O
Dog	O
with	O
Nux-Vomica	O
and	O
Butter	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
Morris	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Doleman	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Radwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
labouring	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
myself	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Russel	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Night	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Grace	O
Gee	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
behind	O
a	O
Stratford	O
Coach	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
He	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Whitechappel	B-place
Barrs	I-place
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Morris	O
stand	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Horse	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
were	O
not	O
twenty	O
Rods	O
before	O
me	O
before	O
Morris	O
got	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
Doleman	O
was	O
by	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Coach-Wheel	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
Morris	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Doleman	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
did	O
know	O
Doleman	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Doleman	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Nagg	O
's	O
head	O
Cellar	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Butts	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
57.	O
Delina	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Totley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton-Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
And	O
58.	O
Ester	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Pool	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Wyat	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
59.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anyon	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
60.	O
John	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
(	O
indicted	O
three	O
Times	O
yesterday	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
May	O
12	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bunting	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
another	O
Person	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Welston	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bunting	O
inform	O
'd	O
us	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
bolted	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Garden	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Backdoor	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Mullaly	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
them	O
but	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bunting	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
disaffected	O
Persons	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
gave	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Fore-door	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
went	O
round	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Back-door	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
six	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lead	O
of	O
the	O
Sink	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
-	O
Dansie	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mullaly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Tom	O
Smith	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
Bailey	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
Charles	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
got	O
six	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
brought	O
off	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Tom	O
Smith	O
's	O
Keys	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
before	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
we	O
bolted	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
round	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
61.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Careless	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time-indicted	O
for	O
attempting	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
62.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rawd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Half-peck	O
Loaves	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
twelve	O
Quartern	O
Loaves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pottinger	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
63	O
,	O
64	O
,	O
65.	O
George	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Yorkshire	I-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Hemming	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Heming	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
one	O
inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
)	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
May	O
17.	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
these	O
four	O
Years	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
Time	O
I	O
rid	O
with	O
him	O
was	O
last	O
March	O
four	O
Years	O
.	O
May	O
16.	O
three	O
Years	O
ago	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
William	O
Farrow	O
's	O
at	O
