TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	O
Barnard	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1737	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
1	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXVII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Three-Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARNARD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
PROBYN	O
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Rene	B-pers
de	I-pers
Boyville	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
PersHouse	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Colvel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Soden	I-pers
,	O
Herbert	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Lowner	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Thredgold	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
,	O
Owen	B-pers
Sainsbury	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boussier	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
1	O
,	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
dead	O
Geese	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
wicker	O
Pen	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back-Church	I-place
,	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
John	O
Williams	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Mary	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3	O
,	O
4.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Steppen	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
and	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
causing	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
and	O
forged	O
a	O
certain	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Words	O
following	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
unto	O
Jonathan	O
Jordan	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
Demand	O
for	O
Value	O
received	O
,	O
per	O
me	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Test	O
.	O
Robert	O
Steppen	O
.	O
With	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
,	O
Mariner	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
likewise	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
the	O
said	O
Jordan	O
and	O
Steppen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
10th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
did	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
they	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
Steppen	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
5.	O
John	B-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Bugden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
2	O
small	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
enamelled	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
Moidore	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Crown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
23	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
Francis	O
Brooks	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
!	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
against	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Nov.	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
from	O
my	O
Chamber	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
readily	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
-	O
Good-Morrow	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
drank	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
requested	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
with	O
him	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
Wine	O
was	O
like	O
Physic	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
mulled	O
Wine	O
and	O
a	O
Toast	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
Harm	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
Hall	O
,	O
who	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
acquainted	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Yarmouth	O
Vessel	O
now	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Smuggling	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
live	O
honestly	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
from	O
Yarmouth	O
to	O
the	O
Pool	O
with	O
his	O
Vessel	O
in	O
30	O
Hours	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Run	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
drowsy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wished	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
my	O
Cabbin-Coy	O
comes	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
stay	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
well	O
drest	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
my	O
Maid	O
Patience	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lodger	O
's	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
lay	O
such	O
a	O
Bed	O
straight	O
for	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
as	O
I	O
ordered	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
John	O
Burges	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Bed	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
up	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
in	O
my	O
Chamber	O
up	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
above	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
restless	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
true	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
in	O
my	O
Chamber	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
mourning	O
Rings	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
had	O
2	O
Sparks	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Cypher	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
likewise	O
three	O
Notes	O
of	O
Hand	O
for	O
about	O
25	O
l.	O
these	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
flung	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
I	O
lost	O
amounts	O
to	O
much	O
about	O
9	O
l.	O
I	O
no	O
sooner	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
but	O
I	O
requested	O
my	O
Customers	O
to	O
go	O
some	O
one	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
another	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
bad	O
Houses	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
2	O
Hours	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Mercy	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
two	O
Doors	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	O
Billers	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
my	O
Shirt	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
within	O
30	O
s.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
Promises	O
of	O
Favour	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
Confession	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
all	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
done	O
generously	O
.	O
Patience	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
)	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
lock	O
the	O
Lodger	O
's	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
my	O
Knee	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
fast	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
Bedcloths	O
smooth	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
above	O
Stairs	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
it	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
before	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Wall	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
Wapping	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Oars	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
them	O
here	O
to	O
produce	O
.	O
Burges	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
upon	O
his	O
Finger	O
which	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
7	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Watch	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
these	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Rings	O
:	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Mourning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
my	O
Son	O
's	O
.	O
This	O
French	O
Crown	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
from	O
France	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Things	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Shirt	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Back	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
made	O
abroad	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Fellow	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
now	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
Brooks	O
's	O
House	O
since	O
last	O
Summer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perfect	O
Stranger	O
to	O
all	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
6.	O
William	B-pers
Cudmore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoats	O
lac	O
'd	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Sagathy	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
19	O
silver	O
Tea-spoons	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Pepperbox	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Bottomley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
several	O
Things	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Sharp	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
Watson	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
my	O
sself	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
murder	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Stratagem	O
of	O
his	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
Sharp	O
what	O
Information	O
I	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
Suspicion	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
Sharp	O
's	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Black	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
Johnson	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
14	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
our	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
frequently	O
drank	O
together	O
o'Night	O
.	O
He	O
liv	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
about	O
9	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
,	O
Watson	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Two	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
's	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
Cudmore	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
come	O
every	O
Day	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
Watson	O
and	O
I	O
lodged	O
,	O
to	O
intreat	O
either	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
Watson	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
engaged	O
.	O
A	O
fortnight	O
afterwards	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
appointed	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee	O
House	O
by	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
agreed	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
resolv	O
'd	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
whoever	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
should	O
rob	O
it	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
my	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
About	O
5	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
Watson	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
being	O
abroad	O
)	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
within	O
Call	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
yet	O
.	O
About	O
6	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
a	O
Boy	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
Word	O
back	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
my	O
Master	O
would	O
come	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
Watson	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
lose	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
himself	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
our	O
robbing	O
my	O
Master	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
there	O
were	O
Goods	O
of	O
considerable	O
Value	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
particularly	O
2	O
Rings	O
worth	O
300	O
l.	O
which	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Business	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
all	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
need	O
not	O
stay	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
expos	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
our	O
Resolution	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Table-drawer	O
,	O
2	O
Chopping	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
He	O
,	O
Watson	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Chest	O
from	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
Then	O
with	O
the	O
Chopping	O
Knives	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Watson	O
and	O
I	O
hold	O
up	O
the	O
Lid	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Suits	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
set	O
the	O
Chest	O
in	O
it	O
's	O
proper	O
Place	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Suits	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
Black	O
and	O
other	O
Colours	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
Hurry	O
to	O
take	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Watson	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
down	O
Stairs	O
on	O
their	O
Arms	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Street	O
was	O
clear	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
near	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
behind	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
desired	O
Watson	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
a	O
clean	O
Shirt	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
accordingly	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Cudmore	O
had	O
pawned	O
one	O
Suit	O
for	O
46	O
s.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
following	O
:	O
My	O
Master	O
sent	O
me	O
then	O
,	O
to	O
Market	O
for	O
a	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
buying	O
some	O
Apples	O
,	O
Cudmore	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
now	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
so	O
how	O
could	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Am	O
I	O
(	O
say	O
'd	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
so	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Villain	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
use	O
that	O
Expression	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Sharp	O
,	O
and	O
Watson	O
brought	O
down	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
-	O
purely	O
out	O
of	O
Friendship	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Monmouth-Street	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
Second	O
hand	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
A	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
one	O
Flemming	O
,	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
for	O
Sale	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Fellow	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
old	O
Coats	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
old	O
Fashion	O
'd	O
Things	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
Black	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
bate	O
a	O
Farthing	O
of	O
4	O
Guineas	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
Some	O
Time	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Keat	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
any	O
Cloaths	O
at	O
the	O
Checquer	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
King-Street	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
immediately	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
-	O
Caddy	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
a	O
Pawn	O
broker	O
in	O
Wych	O
Street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
Cloaths	O
(	O
another	O
Parcel	O
)	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
45	O
Shillings	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bottomley	O
.	O
These	O
likewise	O
are	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
any	O
Ways	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
,	O
-	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
this	O
45	O
Shillings	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
upon	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Guinea	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Sharpe	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
really	O
did	O
lose	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Piazzas	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
Notion	O
of	O
the	O
Play	O
,	O
-	O
so	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
presently	O
.	O
I	O
humbly	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
,	O
and	O
transport	O
me	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
hang	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Caset	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
quiet	O
,	O
civil	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
7.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Stephen	O
Wallbrook	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
1	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
linnen	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
twelve	O
linnen	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
four	O
white	O
linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
Muslin	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
d.	O
eight	O
coarse	O
Towels	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
six	O
Silver	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tea-strainer	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
;	O
and	O
18	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
25	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
Silk	O
Tabby	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
22	O
yards	O
of	O
grey	O
Silk	O
Tabby	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Satchwell	I-pers
;	O
and	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Hannah	O
Allen	O
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
8.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
11	O
Napkins	O
,	O
4	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Towels	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	O
Allen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
yards	O
of	O
Tabby	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	O
Satchwell	O
,	O
she	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
October	O
21	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Buckler's-bury	B-place
;	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
the	O
Watchman	O
knock	O
'd	O
us	O
up	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
opens	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Errand-boy	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
Napkins	O
,	O
6	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Cambrick	O
and	O
Muslin	O
,	O
6	O
gilt	O
Tea-spoons	O
and	O
a	O
Strainer	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Aprons	O
.	O
The	O
Linnen	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
that	O
was	O
like	O
a	O
Seat	O
,	O
to	O
sit	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Some-body	O
that	O
knew	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
3	O
Weeks	O
or	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
advertis	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Midford	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
sign	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
Substance	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
(	O
whose	O
Name	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Pin	O
not	O
being	O
fast	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
then	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
Houses	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Linnen	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Whole	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Hen	B-pers
Mold	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
naughty	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Cole-yard	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
speak	O
'till	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
Dick	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
?	O
He	O
shook	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Sorrow	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
he	O
that	O
has	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
all	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
Williams	O
and	O
Humphries	O
would	O
come	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Sue	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
had	O
given	O
them	O
Notice	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Companions	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
at	O
one	O
Harbin	O
's	O
in	O
Leicester-street	O
,	O
by	O
Hockley	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
never	O
came	O
there	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
we	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
at	O
Harbin	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
Tabby	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Stockings	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Carter	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Midford	O
that	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Harbin	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
these	O
Men	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Allen	O
's	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Windows	O
and	O
Doors	O
were	O
fast	O
over	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
which	O
was	O
nail	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pumps	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
got	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Pumps	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Satchwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
left	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Tabby	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Allen	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
were	O
stole	O
with	O
her	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Hen	O
.	O
Mold	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
two	O
Companions	O
would	O
have	O
murder	O
'd	O
the	O
Maids	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mistress	O
too	O
.	O
Harbin	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
Sue	O
Chapman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Carter	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
for	O
my	O
Trouble	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
and	O
Humphries	O
,	O
coming	O
daily	O
after	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Stokes	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
some	O
part	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
Stokes	O
had	O
for	O
her	O
Trouble	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cook	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
safe	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
got	O
them	O
10	O
Miles	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
after	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
Cook	O
and	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
Humphries	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
Cook	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
Fools	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
got	O
150	O
l.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
then	O
have	O
disturb	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Cook	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
blown	O
all	O
their	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Bull	O
upon	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Carter	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
can	O
have	O
the	O
Assurance	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
?	O
He	O
and	O
Sue	O
Chapman	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fastned	O
my	O
Door	O
with	O
the	O
Poker	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Morris	I-pers
gave	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Carter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Cook	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
William	B-pers
Hardesty	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Painter	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Octob	O
25	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cade	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
clapping	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Bl	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
-	O
your	O
Money	O
.	O
Immediately	O
another	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
quickly	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
we	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
search	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
walk	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
swearing	O
if	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Court	O
that	O
was	O
no	O
Thorough-fare	O
:	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
down	O
White-cross-street	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
ran	O
past	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
never	O
attempted	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Beech-lane	O
this	O
little	O
Watchman	O
fell	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Staff	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
,	O
but	O
just	O
turning	O
the	O
Corner	O
.	O
My	O
Penknife	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
calling	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
toward	O
my	O
Stand	O
in	O
Beech-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
twice	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
indeed	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Pistol	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
naked	O
Fork	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
10.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
wrought	O
base	O
Metal	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d	O
Oct.	O
12	O
.	O
William	O
Haines	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Dobney	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
between	O
the	O
Pond	O
and	O
the	O
New	B-place
River	I-place
Head	I-place
,	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
my	O
Company	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
fired	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Company	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
Watch	O
and	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Knock	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Watch	O
but	O
he	O
searched	O
me	O
all	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
good	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
take	O
that	O
among	O
you	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
I	O
ran	O
back	O
to	O
Dobney	O
's	O
and	O
got	O
his	O
Man	O
to	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
with	O
me	O
with	O
two	O
Dogs	O
.	O
We	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
Sadler's-Wells	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Friends	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Critchley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Dobney	O
's	O
with	O
4	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
foremost	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Stile	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
each	O
Side	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Stile	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Bl	O
-	O
ds	O
deliver	O
this	O
Minute	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
behind	O
me	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
heard	O
another	O
Friend	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
fight	O
away	O
Boys	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
nothing	O
but	O
Powder	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
it	O
by	O
with	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
off	O
it	O
went	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
grasp	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Middle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
broke	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
with	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
'till	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
was	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
nor	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Haines	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
;	O
what	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Sadler's-Wells	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
us	O
there	O
,	O
his	O
Buckles	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
Business	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
abscond	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
impeach	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
likewise	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
rifle	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
the	O
Fellow	O
quitted	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
one	O
Pistol	O
fir	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
another	O
flash	O
;	O
that	O
Stevens	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Comrades	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
take	O
it	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Ball	O
from	O
this	O
Pistol	O
wounded	O
his	O
Brother	O
in	O
the	O
Cheek	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Blows	O
before	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Companions	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
fire	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
fired	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
run	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Forcer	O
's	O
(	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Wells	O
)	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
Men	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Holloway	O
they	O
proposed	O
robbing	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
dragged	O
me	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
Field	O
,	O
they	O
attack	O
'd	O
these	O
People	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Way	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
11.	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Nov.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Shirts	O
and	O
a	O
linnen	O
Stock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
John	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Copper	O
Coffee-Pots	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Toller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
John	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
a	O
linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
26	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Nov.	O
11	O
.	O
Ann	O
Porter	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Palmer	O
's	O
Green	O
from	O
Sunday	O
to	O
Friday	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
coming	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
nearest	O
Way	O
;	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
Hornsey-Wood	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Ring	O
from	O
my	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
my	O
Neck	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
run	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Thumb	O
under	O
the	O
Root	O
of	O
my	O
Tongue	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Fingers	O
upon	O
my	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
press	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
hard	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Nose	O
like	O
a	O
Tap	O
.	O
I	O
scream	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
up	O
came	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Prices	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
sent	O
out	O
2	O
Men	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
light	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Holloway	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
civil	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
Father	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Headborough	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
Charge	O
at	O
Mother	O
Redcap	O
's	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Headborough	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
at	O
Mother	O
Redcap	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
this	O
Knife	O
and	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Porter	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
When	O
his	O
Father	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Justice	O
Elliot	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mugg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
this	O
Girl	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Curnock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
Robbing	O
this	O
Girl	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
Handkerchief	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
at	O
Newington	O
;	O
but	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Wood	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Porter	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
Word	O
of	O
Matrimony	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
15.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
of	O
Harlington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
of	O
a	O
brown	O
Colour	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
Colour	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
Henry	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
Nov.	O
18.	O
from	O
Charwelton	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Northamptonshire	I-place
:	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blacksmith	O
at	O
Tocester	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
shod	O
such	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Gelding	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
at	O
Staines	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Staines	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Gelding	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
likewise	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
suppos	O
'd	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Mare	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Grounds	O
with	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
any	O
he	O
could	O
catch	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Samuel	O
Smith	O
when	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
Smith	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Horses	O
in	O
that	O
Stable	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
us	O
one	O
.	O
We	O
pitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
this	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
led	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
and	O
asked	O
14	O
Guineas	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
Badby	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Goodman	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
Mare	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Horses	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
,	O
-	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
come	O
at	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
from	O
Hilledon	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Northamptonshire	I-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Neighbour	O
Smith	O
had	O
found	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Stable	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
the	O
Horses	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Gelding	O
at	O
Dawley	O
Lodge	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
caught	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
by	O
pulling	O
some	O
Oats	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Rick	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
my	O
Horse	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Alderson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dealt	O
in	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Horse	O
of	O
a	O
Stranger	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
Harm	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
16.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Rickfield	I-pers
,	O
October	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Instrument	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rice	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
Nov.	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Jane	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
18	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s	O
24	O
Brass	O
Candle	O
sticks	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
2	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
3	O
Silver	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Damask	O
Napkin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
5	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
China	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
China	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
8	O
lbs	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Pillowbeer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19.	O
John	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
John	B-pers
Pomeroy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
blue	O
Yard-wide-stuff	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21	O
,	O
22.	O
Grafton	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tery	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Harry	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
chased	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
Oct.	O
21	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Abraham	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
October	O
21	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
4	O
Footpads	O
in	O
the	O
Enfield	O
Stage-Coach	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Enfield	B-place
.	O
Their	O
Persons	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
:	O
They	O
broke	O
the	O
wooden	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
rush	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
stood	O
without	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
civil	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
Purse	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fellow	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
more	O
from	O
such	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
unless	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Silver	O
.	O
He	O
damanded	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
my	O
gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
by	O
Force	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
what	O
Silver	O
I	O
'	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
attack	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Endfield	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
attack	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
by	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Footpads	O
:	O
They	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
remember	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
stepp	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
cut	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Guinea	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
besides	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
Watch	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
When	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Terry	O
Gerrard	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Robbery	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
.	O
Kirk	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wint	I-pers
.	O
The	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
and	O
I	O
,	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Endfield	O
Coach	O
,	O
between	O
Endfield	O
and	O
Edmonton	B-place
;	O
't	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
none	O
but	O
they	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
3	O
Horses	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
their	O
Heads	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
readily	O
find	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
Kirk	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
tear	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
or	O
cut	O
it	O
down	O
:	O
He	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
thus	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Gerrard	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
Kirk	O
's	O
Hat	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Man	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
Door	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
first	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
Gerrard	O
took	O
a	O
Pistol	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
stop	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
flourish	O
'd	O
his	O
Whip	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
still	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
burst	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
jump	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
stood	O
likewise	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
cock	O
'd	O
and	O
loaded	O
,	O
and	O
Gerrard	O
's	O
Pistol	O
was	O
loaded	O
too	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
directly	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
their	O
Companies	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
Robbery	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
'twill	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
we	O
shar	O
'd	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Fields	O
distant	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
we	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
sold	O
the	O
Saturday	O
afterwards	O
for	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Gerrard	O
and	O
Peirce	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
Moses	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
Coachman	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
4	O
Footpads	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Coat	O
as	O
this	O
Wint	O
has	O
now	O
on	O
,	O
held	O
the	O
Horses	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
the	O
Coach	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
burst	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
flourish	O
'd	O
my	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
whip	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Leaders	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
the	O
little	O
Man	O
that	O
jump	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wint	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Wint	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Brother	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
Peirce	O
and	O
Gerrard	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
took	O
Gerrard	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
in	O
Bethnal	O
Green	O
Hamlet	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
my	O
self	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
threw	O
off	O
the	O
Bed-cloaths	O
for	O
Fear	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
Fire	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Assistants	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gough	O
's	O
Watch	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
this	O
wo	O
n't	O
save	O
your	O
Brother	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
none	O
but	O
me	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
I.	O
Grafton	O
Kirk	O
is	O
in	O
Goal	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
Coat	O
hang	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
in	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
draw	O
'd	O
at	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
's	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Moreau	I-pers
gave	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
with	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Witness	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
Gerrard	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gough	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
for	O
others	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
that	O
deserv	O
'd	O
hanging	O
more	O
than	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
and	O
nam	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
House	O
in	O
Brick-lane	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
his	O
Ruin	O
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Lamskin	I-pers
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
proceeding	O
Evidence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Maggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
advertis	O
'd	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gough	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
Loyd	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
Loyd	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Jew	O
that	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Jew	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
Pawn	O
from	O
another	O
Jew	O
for	O
16	O
l.	O
I	O
paid	O
15	O
Guineas	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Jew	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
,	O
was	O
Solomon	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Fellow	O
with	O
one	O
Eye	O
,	O
that	O
goes	O
about	O
with	O
a	O
Bell-harp	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Perrimonie	I-pers
,	O
spake	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
Gerrard	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
before	O
related	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
a	O
pav	O
'd	O
Alley	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
for	O
6	O
Guineas	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistol	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Coat-pocket	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
down	O
Kennington-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
(	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
)	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
Highwaymen	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
were	O
?	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
me	O
but	O
my	O
Hanger	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
after	O
them	O
:	O
At	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
Sot	O
's	O
Hole	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
Hanger	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Turning	O
I	O
overtook	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
bid	O
me	O
Good-night	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
Thing	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seiz	O
'd	O
began	O
to	O
struggle	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Kirk	O
drew	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
fir	O
'd	O
it	O
full	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Shot	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
stunn	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Shot	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
recover	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
load	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
quitted	O
my	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
firing	O
upon	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
twice	O
over	O
the	O
Hands	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
him	O
quit	O
his	O
Pistol	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the-White-Hart	O
in	O
Kennington-lane	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Goal	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
shot	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gough	O
's	O
Affair	O
.	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Munns	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
Geo	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
Nathan	B-pers
Gaze	I-pers
,	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Thurtle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
spake	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
(	O
Kirk	O
's	O
)	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
Gerrard	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Terry	O
Gerrard	O
>	O
,	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Elliston	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
another	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Bathmetal	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Elliston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Parrimonie	I-pers
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
24.	O
William	B-pers
Hardesty	I-pers
,	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Piper	I-pers
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Octob	O
23	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
took	O
Coach	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Hardesty	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
James	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
walk	O
'd	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
by	O
the	O
Coach-side	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
.	O
Above	O
Holborn	B-place
bars	I-place
the	O
Evidence	O
James	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hardesty	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Horses	O
Heads	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
cock	O
'd	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
18	O
d.	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Pocket	O
by	O
it	O
self	O
to	O
pa	O
the	O
Coachman	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
likewise	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
demanded	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wrench	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Hardesty	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
another	O
Pistol	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
myself	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
snapp	O
'd	O
this	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
Watch	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
any	O
other	O
than	O
Hardesty	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Witness	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
Piper	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
Hardesty	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistol	O
:	O
Hardesty	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Piper	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
Pistol	O
?	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Discourse	O
with	O
Piper	O
that	O
was	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
the	O
Purpose	O
.	O
James	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
Holborn	O
by	O
the	O
Bars	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Piper	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
Heads	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
:	O
Hardesty	O
and	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
Piper	O
walk	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
Wind	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
drew	O
up	O
that	O
Window	O
.	O
James	O
.	O
Piper	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Horses	O
Heads	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
Hardesty	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
Pieces	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
dropp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
remain	O
'd	O
but	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
Pistols	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
which	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
has	O
produc	O
'd	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Piper	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
18	O
d.	O
was	O
shar	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
6	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
spent	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
facing	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Marks	O
that	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Pistol	O
before	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Hardesty	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Piper	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
John	B-pers
Stephen	I-pers
Flexmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
Gelding	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edmund	B-pers
South	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
walking	O
Stick	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pinchbeck	O
Metal	O
Head	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
South	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Pocket	O
Piece	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	O
South	O
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
Edmund	O
South	O
On	O
Monday	O
Night	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
to	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
two	O
Fellows	O
assaulted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
Pistols	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
(	O
Harrison	O
)	O
is	O
another	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
very	O
Moonlight	O
when	O
they	O
attack	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Harrison	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
Time	O
I	O
ever	O
engag	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Way	O
was	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
Night	O
-	O
we	O
had	O
10	O
s.	O
between	O
us	O
then	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
Grafton	O
,	O
Kirk	O
,	O
Terry	O
Gerrard	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
kept	O
Company	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
together	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
of	O
Captain	O
Gough	B-pers
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Adams	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
we	O
parted	O
Company	O
:	O
Kirk	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
meet	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
Islington	O
Church	O
yard	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Farthing-Pye	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Uproar	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
Informer	O
against	O
a	O
Seller	O
of	O
Gin	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
,	O
and	O
Grafton	O
Kirk	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
joined	O
Company	O
again	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
proceeded	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
South	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
while	O
our	O
Companions	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
two	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Cane	O
and	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoe	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Terry	O
Gerrard	O
came	O
running	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Shaw	O
began	O
to	O
rifle	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
prevented	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
by	O
presenting	O
his	O
Pistol	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
South	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
about	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
Islington	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
Harrison	O
and	O
Kirk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Sword	O
.	O
-	O
Whittle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
on	O
Horseback	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
some	O
Men	O
to	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
for	O
Information	O
about	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Jail	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
upon	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Directions	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
concerning	O
Mr.	O
South	O
's	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Harrison	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
generally	O
five	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
us	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
another	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
Mr.	O
South	O
's	O
Cane	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
12	O
Miles	O
-	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Holderness	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lade	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Dark	O
house-lane	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
Goal	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
,	O
why	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
Harrison	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robberies	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ought	O
to	O
suffer	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
an	O
hundred	O
People	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
29.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
dated	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
1736	O
,	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
sign	O
'd	O
James	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
,	O
payable	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
One	O
other	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
,	O
dated	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1737	O
,	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
sign	O
'd	O
Timothy	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
,	O
payable	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Wilson	O
.	O
One	O
other	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
,	O
dated	O
April	O
25	O
,	O
1737	O
,	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
sign	O
'd	O
William	B-pers
Dockwray	I-pers
,	O
payable	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Wilson	O
,	O
with	O
Interest	O
on	O
Demand	O
.	O
One	O
other	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
dated	O
Oct.	O
5	O
.	O
1737	O
,	O
for	O
10	O
l	O
1	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
sign	O
'd	O
Arthur	B-pers
Grainger	I-pers
,	O
payable	O
two	O
Months	O
after	O
Date	O
,	O
and	O
endorsed	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
John	B-pers
Wybourn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
said	O
respective	O
Sums	O
secur	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Notes	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
due	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Wilson	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Nov	O
23	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
quarter	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
27	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wilson	O
.	O
John	O
Wilson	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictments	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
my	O
Lodging	O
Room	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
seem	O
'd	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
push	O
'd	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
.	O
-	O
Mason	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Neighbourhood	O
;	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
some	O
Wood	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
was	O
shiver	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Fact	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
committed	O
by	O
some	O
Body	O
that	O
knew	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
one	O
Plew	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
a-bed	O
and	O
a-sleep	O
.	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Osborn	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
with	O
Plew	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
inform	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
This	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
farther	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Landlady	O
disputing	O
about	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
knew	O
something	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
her	O
Master	O
Wilson	O
's	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
Flung	O
the	O
Bolster	O
off	O
of	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
with	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
Guinea	O
,	O
2	O
half-Crowns	O
and	O
some	O
Farthings	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rising-Sun	O
in	O
Bishopgate	O
street	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Clark	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
denied	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Winford-Street	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
I	O
found	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
observ	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
fling	O
something	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Notes	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Room	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Chissel	O
that	O
(	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
)	O
Osborn	O
said	O
Clark	O
perswaded	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
the	O
Chissel	O
.	O
Clark	O
had	O
the	O
Chain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Osborn	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
was	O
Part	O
of	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchman	O
confirm	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Osborn	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
.	O
Clark	O
.	O
Osborn	O
put	O
the	O
Chain	O
about	O
my	O
Neck	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
30.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Udall	I-pers
,	O
May	O
27	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
.	O
Henry	O
Udall	O
.	O
The	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
10	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
walking	O
with	O
my	O
Child	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Air	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
I	O
told	O
over	O
my	O
Tankards	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
9	O
.	O
A	O
quarter	O
before	O
10	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
right	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
immediately	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cornhill	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
:	O
We	O
kept	O
it	O
till	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Brick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Udall	O
.	O
I	O
value	O
it	O
at	O
6	O
l	O
at	O
least	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
swears	O
against	O
me	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Udall	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
what	O
Company	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Barclay	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
know	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Business	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Philosophical	O
Instrument	O
Maker	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
then	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
since	O
;	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
Swear	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
the	O
Air	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
31.	O
Abel	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
evil	O
Disposition	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
knowingly	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
send	O
unto	O
Catherine	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
certain	O
Letter	O
without	O
Name	O
,	O
demanding	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
50	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
containing	O
divers	O
Threats	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Alderson	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
laid	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Demand	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Letter	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Damage	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Alderson	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
evil	O
Example	O
of	O
others	O
offending	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
knowingly	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
send	O
unto	O
Catherine	O
Alderson	O
,	O
one	O
other	O
Letter	O
,	O
signed	O
,	O
J	O
.	O
Brown	O
,	O
W.B	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Alderson	O
,	O
demanding	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
containing	O
Threats	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
if	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
not	O
laid	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Demand	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Councel	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Letter	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Area	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Alderson	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary-ax	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fasten	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
three	O
Bits	O
of	O
Sealing-wax	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
dabb	O
'd	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Brown	O
Paper	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Letter	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
Directed	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Alderson	O
.	O
Madam	O
,	O
Please	O
to	O
lay	O
50	O
Guineas	O
under	O
the	O
Stone	O
between	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
plug	O
and	O
your	O
Rails	O
,	O
before	O
your	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
Steps	O
,	O
near	O
your	O
own	O
Door	O
.	O
Let	O
it	O
be	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Comrades	O
will	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
fail	O
leaving	O
it	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Direction	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Play	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
Coach	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
Home	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
know	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
your	O
coming	O
Home	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
shall	O
make	O
no	O
more	O
Words	O
,	O
but	O
leave	O
the	O
Money	O
if	O
you	O
value	O
your	O
Life	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
set	O
any	O
Watch	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
Murder	O
them	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
.	O
Do	O
as	O
you	O
think	O
fit	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
value	O
your	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
Son	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
leave	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
receive	O
no	O
Harm	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Briar	O
.	O
This	O
Letter	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
Michaelmas-day	O
:	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
Sir	O
William	O
Billers	O
's	O
Office	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Mistress	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Letters	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
Nothing	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
write	O
his	O
Mind	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
took	O
Pen	O
,	O
Ink	O
,	O
and	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
and	O
wrote	O
this	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
Peice	O
of	O
Wax	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
dabb	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
fasten	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Thumb	O
.	O
The	O
sealing	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
was	O
so	O
like	O
those	O
found	O
in	O
our	O
Yard	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
immediately	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
Mind	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Letter	O
he	O
sent	O
by	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
.	O
Honoured	O
Madam	O
,	O
No	O
Man	O
did	O
induce	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
,	O
who	O
promis	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Reward	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
like	O
a	O
Fool	O
took	O
his	O
Advice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
your	O
Pardon	O
for	O
this	O
great	O
Fault	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
did	O
throw	O
the	O
Letters	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
New-gate	O
,	O
but	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
where	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
most	O
humble	O
Servant	O
to	O
command	O
,	O
ABEL	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brian	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Time	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
my	O
Mistress	O
not	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
against	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
whenever	O
she	O
pleas	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
too	O
many	O
bad	O
Things	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Mistress	O
to	O
release	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
were	O
my	O
Mistresses	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
to	O
sell	O
that	O
very	O
Day	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
2d	O
Letter	O
in	O
my	O
Mistresses	O
Yard	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Oct.	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Blanket	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Letter	O
was	O
read	O
)	O
To	O
Mrs.	O
Alderson	O
,	O
``	O
Madam	O
,	O
Since	O
you	O
deceiv	O
'd	O
us	O
we	O
will	O
try	O
you	O
one	O
other	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
come	O
some	O
Night	O
next	O
Week	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
well	O
for	O
your	O
self	O
and	O
Family	O
:	O
if	O
you	O
leave	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
do	O
as	O
we	O
told	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Letter	O
.	O
We	O
give	O
you	O
no	O
ill	O
Words	O
,	O
nor	O
bad	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
lies	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
Power	O
to	O
make	O
yourself	O
both	O
easy	O
and	O
happy	O
Think	O
not	O
to	O
escape	O
us	O
.	O
if	O
you	O
leave	O
not	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
shall	O
light	O
of	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
little	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
B.	O
W.	O
Brown	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Sir	O
William	O
Billers	O
's	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
Letter	O
she	O
carried	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brian	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
to	O
no	O
one	O
but	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
my	O
Mistress	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
Thurston	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
in	O
Leaden	O
hall	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
Mistress	O
wanted	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
no	O
Notice	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Thurston	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Lady	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
Thurston	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Thurston	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
of	O
the	O
Thing	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
Thurston	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Fact	O
for	O
10,000	O
l.	O
Mrs.	O
Alderson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
Stone	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
Letter	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
came	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
under	O
the	O
Stone	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
gave	O
me	O
however	O
,	O
a	O
bad	O
Opinion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
my	O
Servants	O
never	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Footman	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
Word	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
Thurston	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
one	O
whose	O
Name	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Footman	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Thurston	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
-	O
then	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Rascal	O
for	O
his	O
Pains	O
,	O
-	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
would	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
discharg	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
some	O
Bills	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
imagined	O
the	O
Hand-writing	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
bore	O
a	O
Resemblance	O
with	O
the	O
Letters	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Thurston	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Time	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
was	O
when	O
the	O
Lady	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mispley	O
about	O
these	O
Letters	O
.	O
They	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Place	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
that	O
Night	O
disguised	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
saying	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
Threatning	O
Letters	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Alderson	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Watch	O
set	O
,	O
both	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Curiosity	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
the	O
Watch	O
stood	O
:	O
I	O
own	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
kick	O
up	O
the	O
Stone	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
Lady	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
kick	O
up	O
the	O
Stone	O
indeed	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
3	O
Crowns	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
his	O
Lady	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
easy	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
any	O
Mistrust	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Footman	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
my	O
ordering	O
him	O
to	O
deny	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
Observation	O
of	O
the	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
rested	O
Night	O
nor	O
Day	O
since	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Thing	O
should	O
be	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Customers	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
foolish	O
Thing	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Thurston	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
privy	O
to	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
?	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
he	O
demurr	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
asked	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
consented	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
Thurston	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fuddled	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
William	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
Letter	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
some	O
Confusion	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
his	O
Opinion	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
promiss	O
'd	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
Truth	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
agreed	O
with	O
Thurston	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
his	O
Mistress	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
farther	O
Information	O
unless	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
sworn	O
.	O
Brian	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Alderson	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
Reason	O
to	O
mistrust	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
Harry	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
,	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Liquor	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
shuffle	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Alderson	O
's	O
two	O
Maids	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Rabbet-skins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ravener	I-pers
,	O
October	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
William	B-pers
Lavender	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
October	O
19	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farrier	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Wacket	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckskin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
a	O
dimmity	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Brogrove	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Oct	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
Alice	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ellory	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
John	B-pers
Goodhall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Drawer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
peice	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
December	O
5	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-rings	O
with	O
stone	O
Drops	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Longbottom	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Table	O
cloths	O
,	O
3	O
Sheets	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
William	B-pers
Furnell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
Ann	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
diaper	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
peice	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
September	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41.	O
William	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
42.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
3	O
Pillowbeers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cramphorn	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
29	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43.	O
John	B-pers
Grindley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Sherringham	I-pers
,	O
one	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Woodland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brownhill	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
Ann	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
dead	O
Fowls	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
dead	O
Geese	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Topping	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
Ellen	B-pers
Margetson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grogram	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Nov	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46.	O
Richard	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
11	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
4	O
Sheep-skins	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
1	O
Doe-skin	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
47.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
4	O
.	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spout	O
of	O
a	O
Tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
Tortoise-shell	O
Snuff-boxes	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Railton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
Nov	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckskin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
dimmity	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Menthorp	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Grumwell	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
49.	O
William	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nugent	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Check	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
Irish	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
1	O
quarter	O
yard	O
of	O
cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Nov	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
51.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Pumps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Arthurs	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trout	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Heneage	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
for	O
violently	O
ravishing	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
Sept.	O
4	O
.	O
And	O
Richard	B-pers
Fastnege	I-pers
,	O
for	O
aiding	O
,	O
abet	O
ting	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
said	O
Trout	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Fact	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Sept	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Hall	O
a	O
Pastry-Cook	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
