TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
12th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	O
Barnard	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1738	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXVIII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Three-Pence	O
.	O
)	O
N.B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
BARNARD	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Three-Pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
shall	O
coontain	O
the	O
usual	O
Quantity	O
sold	O
for	O
Six-Pence	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
past	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
Three-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARNARD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
REYNOLDS	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
CHAPPLE	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
COMMYNS	O
;	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Re	O
corder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pardo	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bittany	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rustat	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Morse	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
,	O
Bernard	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
:	O
Richard	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Basnett	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cullis	I-pers
,	O
Ignatius	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Cuthbert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bottomley	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
2.	O
William	B-pers
Moreland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
cloth	O
Coach-cushions	O
,	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Feathers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Temple	B-pers
Stinton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
3.	O
William	B-pers
Moreland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	O
Church	O
,	O
Spittlefields	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
David	B-pers
Nix	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Alley	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Smock	O
Alley	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
May	O
23	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Nix	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
from	O
Widegate	O
Alley	O
,	O
into	O
Smock	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
and	O
saw	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Fellows	O
standing	O
together	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Moonlight	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
little	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Austin	O
knock	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
off	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
caught	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Skirts	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
'till	O
the	O
Mob	O
subsisted	O
(	O
came	O
)	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
quitted	O
my	O
Hold	O
,	O
'till	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
.	O
His	O
Companions	O
seeing	O
me	O
hold	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
me	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
to	O
their	O
Heels	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
-	O
stop	O
Thief	O
too	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
The	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
together	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
not	O
being	O
set	O
,	O
we	O
dogg	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
into	O
Widegate	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
imagin	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
fuddl	O
'd	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Gingerbread	O
Baker	O
's	O
he	O
lighted	O
his	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
towards	O
Smock	O
Alley	O
;	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
our	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
Austin	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Smock	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Fellows	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Tenter	O
Grounds	O
,	O
in	O
Moorefields	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
(	O
Fellows	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
kept	O
all	O
Night	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
Horns	O
,	O
near	O
Shoreditch	O
Church	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Nix	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Morning	O
against	O
Austin	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
Information	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
rob	O
who	O
we	O
could	O
;	O
for	O
Austin	O
and	O
Moreland	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
together	O
a	O
whole	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
Night	O
and	O
Day	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
spent	O
and	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
all	O
we	O
had	O
to	O
live	O
upon	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
resolved	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
to	O
get	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
with	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
Information	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Justice	O
Booth	O
.	O
Austin	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
off	O
:	O
Miller	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
ran	O
from	O
us	O
toward	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
kick	O
his	O
Heels	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
some	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Thing	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Hat	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
Duke	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
too	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
.	O
Nix	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Austin	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Hat	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Heels	O
directly	O
;	O
then	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
knock	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Brick-bat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Officer	O
that	O
took	O
Moreland	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Miller	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Half-p'orth	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
seeing	O
him	O
pull	O
out	O
a	O
Handful	O
of	O
Silver	O
and	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
fuddled	O
,	O
they	O
resolved	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
and	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
they	O
dogg	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
Widegate	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Gingerbread	O
Baker	O
's	O
to	O
light	O
his	O
Pipe	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
Smock	O
Alley	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
this	O
to	O
say	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Evidence	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Black-Guard	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sorry	O
they	O
must	O
die	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
triffling	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
something	O
whereby	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
maintain	O
'd	O
themselves	O
in	O
Jail	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Keddit	I-pers
,	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Monday	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hat	O
fetch	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
in	O
Moreland	O
's	O
Name	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
A	O
Quarter	O
before	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Austin	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
stole	O
it	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
trip	O
up	O
my	O
Heels	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
lay	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Dennet	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
belonging	O
to	O
this	O
Officer	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
Austin	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
;	O
the	O
Officer	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
lay	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
,	O
that	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
trip	O
up	O
my	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Perrington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Three	O
Tun-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Austin	O
together	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
Jail	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
next	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
indeed	O
(	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Dennet	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Company	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
propos	O
'd	O
making	O
the	O
Matter	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
seem	O
'd	O
willing	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
with	O
Relation	O
to	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Austin	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
weave	O
rich	O
Brocades	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
great	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
Silver	O
and	O
Silk	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
while	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
quitted	O
my	O
Service	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
some	O
Words	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
his	O
Mistress	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Austin	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
4.	O
George	B-pers
Nock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
and	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watlington	I-pers
,	O
May	O
27	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
clean	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Room	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
a	O
Guinea	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Perry	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
her	O
Sweet	O
Heart	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
Confession	O
being	O
made	O
without	O
any	O
Promises	O
of	O
shewing	O
her	O
Favour	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quarter-Barrel	O
of	O
Raisins	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary-Hill	O
,	O
May	O
25	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
my	O
Cooper	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
came	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Quarter-Barrel	O
of	O
Raisins	O
from	O
Smart's-Key	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
thirty	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Barrel	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
it	O
seems	O
)	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
over	O
Board	O
.	O
The	O
Mark	O
upon	O
the	O
Barrel	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Property	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
nothing	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Money	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
had	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Symmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
past	O
Smart's-Key	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Barrel	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
Boat	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
tumbled	O
down	O
,	O
Barrel	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
.	O
My	O
Waterman	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Thief	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
shove	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
heav	O
'd	O
something	O
over	O
board	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
ashore	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Boat	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Barrel	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Raisins	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
Barrel	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
compar	O
'd	O
the	O
Pieces	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Breaches	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Barrel	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fitted	O
:	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Mark	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Pieces	O
,	O
which	O
flew	O
out	O
when	O
he	O
fell	O
with	O
the	O
Barrel	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Barrel	O
itself	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
comparing	O
this	O
Mark	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
's	O
Barrels	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Waterman	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Symmonds	O
.	O
Testimony	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
very	O
plainly	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
throw	O
the	O
Barrel	O
over-board	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
tumbled	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Barrel	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
shewn	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Boat	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
George	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Blackamoor	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Gravener	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver-bow	O
'd	O
Scissars	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spatula	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Probe	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Steel	O
crooked	O
Needle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d	O
a	O
Fish	O
skin	O
Case	O
with	O
Silver	O
Hinges	O
and	O
Clasps	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
Lancers	O
,	O
with	O
Tortoiseshell	O
Scales	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Gum	O
Lancet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
Shagreen	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
7	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gravener	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Endfield	B-place
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
attack	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
They	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
their	O
Clubs	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Horse	O
threw	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
150	O
or	O
200	O
Yards	O
towards	O
Islington	B-place
Town	O
,	O
but	O
happening	O
to	O
fall	O
in	O
a	O
Cart-rut	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Accomplice	O
overtook	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
likewise	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
seiz	O
'd	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Comrade	O
rifled	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
fell	O
from	O
my	O
Horse	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
so	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
rifled	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
Hat	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
guarding	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Reason	O
of	O
my	O
desiring	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
some	O
Body	O
might	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Black	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
walk	O
'd	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
Hat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gravener	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
(	O
to	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
)	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
his	O
Time	O
last	O
Monday	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Month	O
in	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
thence	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
Hospital	O
can	O
be	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
8.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Pocket	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Clancey	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
an	O
evil	O
Disposition	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
not	O
regarding	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1723	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
knowingly	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
send	O
a	O
certain	O
Letter	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
without	O
Name	O
or	O
Date	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Dolley	I-pers
,	O
demanding	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
containing	O
divers	O
Threats	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
burning	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Dolley	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Directions	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Letter	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Damage	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Dolley	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
evil	O
Example	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
William	O
Dolley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
(	O
Alice	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
)	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
haste	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Company	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
threatening	O
Letter	O
was	O
sent	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
within	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
slight	O
Glance	O
on	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
double-lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
Pistols	O
,	O
or	O
Knives	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
my	O
Hands	O
upon	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Pockets	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
who	O
were	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Jail	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
strongly	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
without	O
first	O
carrying	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
For	O
this	O
Reason	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
least	O
his	O
Comrades	O
should	O
be	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Elephant	O
and	O
Castle	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
wrote	O
this	O
Note	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
Friends	O
;	O
some	O
Persons	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
comparing	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Letter	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Hands	O
agreed	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
immediately	O
with	O
having	O
wrote	O
the	O
Letter	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
wrote	O
the	O
Letter	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
himself	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Poulson	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Confession	O
was	O
voluntarily	O
sign	O
'd	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner.	O
``	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
To	O
wit	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
of	O
John	O
``	O
Wright	O
,	O
taken	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
``	O
Who	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
``	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
``	O
William	B-pers
Dolley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
demanding	O
the	O
Sum	O
``	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
threatening	O
,	O
on	O
Refusal	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
``	O
said	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
reduce	O
his	O
House	O
``	O
to	O
Ashes	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
``	O
Word	O
thereof	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
proper	O
Hand	O
of	O
this	O
``	O
Examinant	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Letter	O
was	O
read.	O
``	O
To	O
Mr.	O
William	O
Dolley	O
,	O
Ironmonger	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
``	O
Warming-Pan	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
SIR	O
,	O
``	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
certain	O
``	O
Number	O
of	O
poor	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
without	O
present	O
``	O
Help	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
ruin	O
'd	O
:	O
Therefore	O
we	O
all	O
consent	O
``	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
four	O
able	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
like	O
yourself	O
,	O
``	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
that	O
old	O
Gold	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
lain	O
by	O
you	O
``	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
We	O
send	O
for	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
30	O
l.	O
``	O
which	O
you	O
can	O
spare	O
so	O
easily	O
.	O
So	O
for	O
your	O
own	O
``	O
Safety	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
refuse	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
``	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Bearer	O
.	O
Put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Box	O
;	O
cover	O
``	O
it	O
with	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
seal	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
``	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brings	O
you	O
this	O
``	O
Letter	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
refuse	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
make	O
any	O
``	O
Stir	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
kill	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
reduce	O
``	O
your	O
House	O
to	O
Ashes	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
imagine	O
we	O
``	O
are	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
Faces	O
of	O
any	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
positively	O
``	O
declare	O
we	O
will	O
murder	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
yours	O
,	O
``	O
as	O
sure	O
as	O
ever	O
you	O
were	O
born	O
,	O
either	O
riding	O
,	O
``	O
walking	O
,	O
or	O
sleeping	O
.	O
We	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
``	O
much	O
of	O
your	O
Riches	O
you	O
have	O
cruelly	O
and	O
unjustly	O
``	O
gotten	O
;	O
so	O
if	O
you	O
refuse	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
wash	O
our	O
``	O
Hands	O
in	O
your	O
Heart	O
's	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
burn	O
your	O
``	O
House	O
to	O
Ashes	O
,	O
therefore	O
we	O
command	O
you	O
to	O
``	O
send	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
Peril	O
of	O
your	O
Goods	O
,	O
Life	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
Habitation.	O
``	O
We	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
''	O
Mr.	O
Dolley	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinson	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
give	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
ago	O
,	O
on	O
much	O
such	O
an	O
Affair	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
(	O
for	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
's	O
House	O
)	O
in	O
April	O
Sessions	O
,	O
1737	O
.	O
Vide	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
for	O
that	O
Year	O
,	O
No	O
IV	O
.	O
p.	O
94.	O
Alice	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
Letter	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
an	O
Errand	O
Boy	O
,	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Dolley	O
,	O
and	O
required	O
an	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dolley	O
's	O
Partner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
thanked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
waited	O
for	O
an	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
my	O
Mistress	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprised	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
my	O
Friends	O
may	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cruikshank	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
and	O
always	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
seiz	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
rooted	O
melancholy	O
Desperation	O
.	O
Some	O
Time	O
or	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
either	O
of	O
November	O
or	O
December	O
1735	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
full	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
melancholy	O
desperate	O
Expressions	O
,	O
declaring	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
devoted	O
to	O
eternal	O
Destruction	O
,	O
and	O
abandon	O
'd	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
answer	O
all	O
his	O
unreasonable	O
Objections	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
some	O
good	O
Effect	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
his	O
old	O
Melancholy	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
was	O
occasioned	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
baptized	O
;	O
being	O
descended	O
of	O
Parents	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
call	O
'd	O
Quakers	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
he	O
mention	O
'd	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
his	O
Melancholy	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1735-6	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
baptized	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Holy	O
Communion	O
,	O
-	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
instructed	O
in	O
the	O
Principles	O
of	O
the	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
April	O
or	O
May	O
following	O
,	O
his	O
Melancholy	O
recurr	O
'd	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
two	O
Attempts	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
by	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
drown	O
himself	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
all	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
ease	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
succeeded	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
continually	O
in	O
a	O
melancholly	O
way	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
observe	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Attempts	O
of	O
Self-Murder	O
,	O
were	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
before	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Affair	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinson	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Months	O
of	O
April	O
and	O
May	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
receiving	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
That	O
Affair	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Cognizance	O
of	O
this	O
Court	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
his	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
express	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
off	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
the	O
Civil	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
Executioner	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
Affair	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
pretty	O
soberly	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
hopes	O
his	O
melancholy	O
Distemper	O
would	O
wear	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
recurr	O
'd	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
September	O
1737	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
high	O
Degree	O
,	O
as	O
appears	O
by	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Corse	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
judge	O
of	O
any	O
Man	O
's	O
Writing	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
judge	O
of	O
that	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
moral	O
certainty	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
that	O
't	O
is	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Penny	O
Post	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Letter	O
read	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
see	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
oddest	O
Expressions	O
that	O
ever	O
were	O
heard	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
moral	O
Reason	O
to	O
believe	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
a	O
rooted	O
,	O
desperate	O
Melancholy	O
.	O
Since	O
the	O
Writing	O
of	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
melancholy	O
Expressions	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
weary	O
of	O
Life	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
World	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
this	O
last	O
Spring	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
ascertain	O
the	O
particular	O
Time	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Lad	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
sober	O
;	O
never	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Immoralities	O
,	O
except	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
his	O
downright	O
Melancholy	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
for	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
Reason	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
kept	O
any	O
bad	O
Company	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Bamfield	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
just	O
Woman	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Brain	O
,	O
and	O
oftentimes	O
in	O
the	O
Spring	O
would	O
leave	O
his	O
Family	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Sister	O
this	O
last	O
Summer	O
confined	O
for	O
the	O
Disorder	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
raving	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Action	O
,	O
except	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinson	O
's	O
Affair	O
last	O
Summer	O
and	O
this	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
him	O
often	O
for	O
these	O
two	O
Years	O
;	O
once	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
among	O
other	O
young	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
certainly	O
damn	O
'd	O
and	O
ruin	O
'd	O
to	O
all	O
Eternity	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
use	O
these	O
Expressions	O
.	O
Another	O
Time	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
drown	O
himself	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Thought	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Telford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
intimately	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
Months	O
,	O
by	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
always	O
very	O
circumspectly	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
these	O
Flights	O
;	O
but	O
sometimes	O
he	O
would	O
fly	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
advise	O
him	O
to	O
throw	O
of	O
those	O
Flights	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
die	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
no	O
longer	O
carry	O
about	O
with	O
him	O
this	O
Body	O
of	O
Sin	O
.	O
Before	O
this	O
Accident	O
happened	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
blooded	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
a	O
Porringer	O
full	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
blooded	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lost	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
would	O
not	O
permit	O
it	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
Weeks	O
or	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
bad	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
his	O
Friends	O
know	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
(	O
foolish	O
)	O
kept	O
the	O
Secret	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
but	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
this	O
Letter	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
singing	O
a	O
Verse	O
of	O
the	O
138th	O
Psalm	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
I	O
could	O
sing	O
him	O
into	O
Heaven	O
with	O
that	O
Tune	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
weary	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
hang	O
himself	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
made	O
Shoes	O
for	O
me	O
near	O
a	O
Twelve-month	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
out	O
among	O
my	O
merry	O
Shoe-makers	O
to	O
divert	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
bear	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
tempted	O
to	O
destroy	O
himself	O
,	O
once	O
to	O
hang	O
himself	O
,	O
another	O
Time	O
to	O
drown	O
himself	O
?	O
then	O
to	O
starve	O
or	O
bleed	O
himself	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
me	O
Home	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
he	O
did	O
this	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Flights	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
he	O
was	O
capable	O
of	O
doing	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Forest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
solid	O
and	O
sober	O
,	O
except	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
those	O
Fits	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
express	O
despairing	O
Words	O
,	O
-	O
Words	O
of	O
deep	O
despair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
surely	O
perish	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
mind	O
his	O
Duty	O
to	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
concern	O
himself	O
so	O
much	O
about	O
sacred	O
Things	O
.	O
At	O
some	O
Times	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
glimmering	O
of	O
Hope	O
,	O
but	O
oftener	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
despair	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
.	O
Ivel	O
Northam	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
sometimes	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
request	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
Conversation	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
melancholy	O
,	O
and	O
afraid	O
of	O
his	O
Damnation	O
.	O
One	O
Sunday	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
better	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
off	O
all	O
Religion	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
scandal	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
good	O
Advice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hard	O
hearted	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
split	O
upon	O
the	O
Rock	O
of	O
Despair	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
as	O
you	O
stand	O
before	O
the	O
great	O
God	O
,	O
declare	O
on	O
what	O
Account	O
you	O
sent	O
this	O
Letter	O
;	O
was	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
No	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
to	O
hang	O
yourself	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
better	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
by	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
the	O
Land	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
murther	O
ones	O
self	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
Proof	O
have	O
you	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
damned	O
?	O
Because	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
he	O
that	O
believeth	O
not	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
damned	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
?	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
-	O
for	O
my	O
Sake	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Friend	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
only	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
an	O
Ironmonger	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
Friends	O
would	O
trouble	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
the	O
Law	O
have	O
its	O
Course	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
rejoice	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Tyburn	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
tempted	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
somebody	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
the	O
Work	O
effectually	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
could	O
say	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
Effect	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
Romish	O
Priests	O
,	O
that	O
are	O
disputing	O
about	O
Transubstantiation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Infalibity	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
great	O
Disorder	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
odd	O
Expressions	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
you	O
consider	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
Person	O
is	O
not	O
prejudic	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
Interest	O
into	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
Day	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
at	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
whether	O
his	O
Bill	O
was	O
rectify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
one	O
Bill	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
another	O
should	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
partial	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Prosession	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
he	O
has	O
so	O
many	O
Notions	O
running	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
about	O
the	O
Roman	O
Priests	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
he	O
goes	O
to	O
one	O
Place	O
,	O
sometimes	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Church	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Churches	O
beside	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
10.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
hoop	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
Manteel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hannah	I-pers
,	O
May	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
black	O
Geldings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
14th	O
Day	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
black	O
Geldings	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
common	O
Field	O
in	O
Gloucestershire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
this	O
Man	O
's	O
(	O
Davis	O
's	O
)	O
Possession	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
selling	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
Davis	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Hostler	O
at	O
the	O
Rose-Inn	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
another	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
another	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Star	O
in	O
his	O
Forehead	O
,	O
two	O
white	O
Heels	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
Foot	O
before	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
my	O
other	O
Horse	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
while	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
:	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
an	O
odd	O
Thing	O
you	O
should	O
take	O
my	O
Horses	O
away	O
!	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Word	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
sink	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
my	O
Stables	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
put	O
up	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
baited	O
him	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
Cart	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
with	O
but	O
one	O
Eye	O
.	O
The	O
Same	O
Day	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Stables	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
earnest	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
this	O
Horse	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
Wiltshire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
hardly	O
worth	O
his	O
while	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
such	O
Horses	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
my	O
Charges	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Smith-field	O
to	O
sell	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
Hinton	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
claim	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Horse	O
.	O
Benj	O
Taylor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
Davis	O
's	O
Stables	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Hedge	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Oates	O
,	O
a	O
Rack	O
full	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Penn'orth	O
of	O
Beans	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Corn	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Master	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bargaining	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
-	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
blind	O
of	O
an	O
Eye	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Hinton	O
's	O
Possession	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hinton	O
.	O
The	O
Horse	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Davis	O
's	O
Possession	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Rose	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
bait	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
little	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
rid	O
about	O
the	O
Market	O
accordingly	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hinton	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
other	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
claim	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
these	O
Horses	O
.	O
Hinton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
People	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
desire	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
13.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
,	I-place
London-Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Martha	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
yellow	O
Damask	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
grey	O
Damask	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Manteel	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Cambrick	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
Shifts	O
unmade	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saville	I-pers
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Acor	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Acroy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s	O
a	O
Straw	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
check	O
'd	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Mary	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
flower	O
'd	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
May	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Draper	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
Sale-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
carries	O
on	O
that	O
Trade	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Girl	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
bail	O
'd	O
out	O
by	O
Harris	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
in	O
Rose-Mary-Lane	O
,	O
a	O
Thief	O
Catcher	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
stole	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
more	O
;	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
Margaret	B-pers
Poland	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Irish	O
Peg	O
.	O
Phillis	B-pers
Weldon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
Irish	O
Peg	O
's	O
Lap	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Irish	O
Peg	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
Peg	O
gave	O
her	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
of	O
her	O
whatever	O
she	O
should	O
get	O
.	O
This	O
Accessary	O
is	O
out	O
upon	O
Bail	O
;	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Warrener	O
,	O
(	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
's	O
Clerk	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Thief-takers	O
would	O
never	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
bail	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Child	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
Child	O
,	O
only	O
she	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
this	O
Jade	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Father-in-Law	O
.	O
I	O
marry	O
'd	O
her	O
Mother	O
with	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lives	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
help	O
sometimes	O
to	O
break	O
up	O
Ships	O
;	O
sometimes	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Lath-bender	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
buy	O
my	O
Wood	O
at	O
the	O
best	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
it	O
out	O
into	O
Matches	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
sent	O
out	O
that	O
Day	O
to	O
sell	O
two	O
Bundles	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Her	O
Mother	O
is	O
a	O
Stay-Maker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Girl	O
as	O
ever	O
the	O
Sun	O
shin	O
'd	O
upon	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Girl	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
that	O
were	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
sober	O
Girl	O
.	O
Irish	O
Peg	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Girl	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Money	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
declar	O
'd	O
she	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Days	O
of	O
her	O
Breath	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Poland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
otherwise	O
Margaret	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mayfield	I-pers
;	O
otherwise	O
Margaret	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tweed	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Irish	O
Peg	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Margaret	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Margaret	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Poland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
having	O
stolen	O
a	O
flower	O
'd	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
May	O
29	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Poland	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
29	O
.	O
The	O
Record	O
of	O
Haley	O
's	O
Conviction	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Draper	O
deposed	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Trial	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
had	O
six	O
Gowns	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
describe	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Shop-keepers	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
delivering	O
the	O
Gown	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Hugger	O
Mugger	O
Manner	O
.	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
got	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
D	O
-	O
mn	O
your	O
Eyes	O
(	O
said	O
she	O
)	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Harris	O
,	O
the	O
Thief-taker	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
her	O
Bail	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
eating	O
with	O
Harris	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
'd	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
prove	O
against	O
her	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
(	O
says	O
she	O
)	O
can	O
you	O
prove	O
upon	O
me	O
now	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
beat	O
me	O
and	O
bit	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
unless	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
with	O
Harris	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
now	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
(	O
says	O
she	O
)	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Harris	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
lay	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
tearing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wiping	O
the	O
Table	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
what	O
she	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
Liberty	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Thief	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
that	O
Time	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
Girl	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
Children	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
Match-Girl	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
not	O
likely	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
Gown	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
fairly	O
,	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
common	O
Thieves	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
noted	O
Thief	O
,	O
one	O
Fosset	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
stole	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
two	O
Husbands	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
;	O
pray	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
many	O
Husbands	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
?	O
Draper	O
.	O
Not	O
so	O
many	O
Husbands	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
a	O
hundred	O
Fellows	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
two	O
but	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
.	O
Phillis	B-pers
Waldon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
fairly	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
Street	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
which	O
the	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Thieves	O
she	O
deals	O
with	O
,	O
frequent	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Fellows	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
have	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
was	O
worth	O
20	O
s.	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Shop	O
myself	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Gown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
upon	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
down	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
scruple	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
claim	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
them	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
lose	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
lose	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
beside	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Discharge	O
of	O
the	O
Warrant	O
.	O
The	O
Husband	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
beat	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
inform	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Law	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
arrested	O
me	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
I	O
got	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
upon	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Sturt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
bought	O
this	O
Gown	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
Place	O
to	O
buy	O
such	O
Things	O
in	O
.	O
She	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Girl	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
tell	O
her	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
said	O
't	O
was	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
down	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
me	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
more	O
for	O
the	O
Credit	O
and	O
Service	O
'twould	O
do	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
is	O
an	O
Instrument-maker	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Fair	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
Mother	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
taken	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fair	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Jere	O
.	O
Listen	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Draper	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
so	O
(	O
said	O
she	O
to	O
the	O
Girl	O
)	O
you	O
little	O
B	O
-	O
ch	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
that	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
?	O
and	O
turning	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Peg	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
Girl	O
any	O
harm	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
my	O
own	O
Children	O
may	O
come	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
come	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
,	O
Peg	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goughton	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
some	O
Part	O
of	O
Lister	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Draper	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
then	O
,	O
-	O
We	O
are	O
all	O
Dealers	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
do	O
buy	O
of	O
Children	O
that	O
are	O
sent	O
out	O
with	O
Things	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Children	O
of	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Years	O
old	O
sell	O
Things	O
of	O
considerable	O
Value	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
subject	O
to	O
buy	O
Things	O
in	O
this	O
misfortunate	O
Way	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
troubled	O
myself	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
had	O
not	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
Orders	O
to	O
sue	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
any	O
one	O
attempts	O
to	O
put	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
theirs	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
The	O
Gown	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
is	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
she	O
gave	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
our	O
Dealers	O
wo	O
n't	O
give	O
above	O
half	O
Value	O
for	O
Things	O
'T	O
is	O
worth	O
more	O
Money	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
'praise	O
it	O
to	O
;	O
in	O
our	O
Business	O
I	O
think	O
't	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Axe	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
a	O
spike	O
Gimblet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Handsaw	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
smoothing	O
Plane	O
,	O
value	O
a	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
.	O
And	O
9	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
leaden	O
Pipe	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Welbeloved	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
18.	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Hatchet	O
made	O
of	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
in	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
fore	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Pike	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
strike	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
and	O
Bruise	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
he	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
languishing	O
liv	O
'd	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
charged	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
-	O
Birkenhead	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Wroth	O
,	O
to	O
execute	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
being	O
Headborough	O
,	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
got	O
this	O
Warrant	O
for	O
him	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
with	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
he	O
stands	O
,	O
-	O
let	O
him	O
deny	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
can	O
;	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
kill	O
you	O
,	O
-	O
aye	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
he	O
stands	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
he	O
stands	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
murder	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
comes	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
stood	O
a	O
little	O
o'jar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
's	O
your	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
was	O
just	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Bl	O
-	O
d	O
I	O
will	O
murder	O
you	O
both	O
,	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Motion	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Axe	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pyke	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
my	O
Business	O
.	O
God	O
forbid	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
surprized	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
poor	O
Man	O
bled	O
prodigiously	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
make	O
a	O
Motion	O
,	O
-	O
Truth	O
is	O
Truth	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
near	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Thing	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Birkenhead	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Mob	O
came	O
so	O
fast	O
upon	O
us	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
really	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
After	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
was	O
hurt	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
wash	O
'd	O
with	O
Vinegar	O
and	O
Loaf-Sugar	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
and	O
Justice	O
Worth	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Doctor	O
Godman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Whereabout	O
was	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
?	O
Brickenhead	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
love	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
Wounds	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
clean	O
'd	O
his	O
Wig	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
-	O
as	O
sure	O
as	O
that	O
God	O
made	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Deceased	O
tell	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
?	O
Brickenhead	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
several	O
Times	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Dizziness	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Warrant	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
Birkenhead	O
.	O
Pike	O
was	O
a	O
Headborough	O
in	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
and	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
Parish	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Desborough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
bid	O
him	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
Birkenhead	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
Room	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
entered	O
;	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
toward	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
something	O
large	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
,	O
for	O
't	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
gave	O
but	O
glimmering	O
Light	O
.	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Stroke	O
to	O
fall	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
the	O
Blood	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Neck	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Desborough	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frighted	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
got	O
away	O
I	O
swooned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Birkenhead	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
agree	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
?	O
Birkenhead	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
found	O
himself	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Dizziness	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
nothing	O
detrimented	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
neither	O
off	O
,	O
nor	O
on	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
News	O
was	O
brought	O
Home	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
all	O
over	O
Blood	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
from	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
hurt	O
worse	O
than	O
we	O
imagin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
Cut	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
upon	O
what	O
Part	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Blow	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
Health	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
ail	O
'd	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
ails	O
me	O
now	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
Nights	O
after	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Blow	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
Warrant	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
for	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
my	O
Head	O
is	O
all	O
on	O
Fire	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
with	O
what	O
Instrument	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
?	O
Sims	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
an	O
Axe	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Loveit	I-pers
.	O
The	O
same	O
Night	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
near	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
My	O
Door	O
is	O
No	O
2.	O
and	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stamp	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
Night	O
I	O
am	O
bent	O
to	O
do	O
Murder	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
and	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
serv	O
'd	O
my	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
with	O
a	O
Practitioner	O
in	O
both	O
Ways	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
.	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict-Natural	O
Death	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Caedes	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Sagittal	O
Suture	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Caedes	O
,	O
a	O
simple	O
Fracture	O
,	O
the	O
Skull	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Print	O
of	O
the	O
Weapon	O
just	O
upon	O
the	O
Cranium	O
.	O
I	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
that	O
Blow	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Cranium	O
was	O
not	O
crack	O
'd	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Fissure	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Skull	O
was	O
dented	O
inwards	O
.	O
I	O
improperly	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
that	O
Night	O
a	O
Fissure	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
properly	O
a	O
Caedes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Periostium	O
must	O
be	O
broke	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
will	O
occasion	O
an	O
Inflammation	O
,	O
and	O
St.	O
Anthony	O
's	O
Fire	O
,	O
if	O
proper	O
Care	O
be	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
Blow	O
.	O
The	O
Body	O
was	O
all	O
mortify	O
'd	O
and	O
black	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
3	O
Days	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Longdon	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
Axe	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
about	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
him	O
declare	O
the	O
Blow	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
-	O
Holdwright	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
3	O
Minutes	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
his	O
Death	O
's	O
Wound	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Chidsdell	O
.	O
I	O
nursed	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
complained	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
Night	O
's	O
Work	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
sick	O
,	O
but	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
only	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Head	O
is	O
distracted	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
moved	O
his	O
Pillows	O
20	O
Times	O
in	O
a	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
his	O
Bed	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
was	O
heal	O
'd	O
up	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
Disorder	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Face	O
were	O
swell	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
Degree	O
with	O
the	O
St.	O
Anthony	O
's	O
Fire	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Godman	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
I	O
remov	O
'd	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
superficial	O
Wound	O
,	O
I	O
applied	O
a	O
Tonsil	O
of	O
Lint	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
common	O
Plaister	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
Saturday	O
se'ennight	O
,	O
or	O
fortnight	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Hall	O
to	O
bleed	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
bled	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
St.	O
Anthony's-Fire	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
blooded	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
bleed	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Tumor	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Face	O
began	O
to	O
subside	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
complain	O
of	O
a	O
Difficulty	O
in	O
Breathing	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Leave	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
After	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
Skull	O
bare	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
of	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
no	O
Injury	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
Skull	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Remarks	O
on	O
a	O
Caedes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
means	O
;	O
a	O
Caedes	O
is	O
when	O
a	O
Print	O
of	O
the	O
Weapon	O
is	O
left	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Symptom	O
of	O
a	O
Fracture	O
of	O
the	O
Cranium	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
a	O
Concussion	O
upon	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Cranium	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Brain	O
was	O
injur	O
'd	O
.	O
Can	O
not	O
the	O
Brain	O
receive	O
an	O
Injury	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
outward	O
Appearance	O
of	O
Hurt	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Godman	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
that	O
Injury	O
,	O
Vomiting	O
,	O
Drowsiness	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
Blow	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
You	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
.	O
I	O
inspected	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
when	O
't	O
was	O
laid	O
bare	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Fracture	O
or	O
Depression	O
.	O
The	O
Skull	O
was	O
not	O
laid	O
open	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
is	O
judg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
unnecessary	O
where	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
no	O
Bleeding	O
at	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
or	O
Ears	O
,	O
no	O
Comus	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
a	O
fractur	O
'd	O
Skull	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
alive	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Symptoms	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
bring	O
on	O
sooner	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
St.	O
Anthony	O
's	O
Fire	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Snowd	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Opinion	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
imagined	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
might	O
mistake	O
a	O
Suture	O
in	O
the	O
Cranium	O
for	O
the	O
Caedes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
.	O
And	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
impossible	O
for	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
that	O
Place	O
to	O
cause	O
Death	O
,	O
yet	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Case	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
must	O
have	O
come	O
on	O
sooner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Inflammation	O
was	O
begun	O
on	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
Jaws	O
,	O
and	O
Cheeks	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
a	O
St.	O
Anthony	O
's	O
Fire	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
proper	O
Remedies	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Swelling	O
was	O
increas	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
so	O
violent	O
a	O
Degree	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Face	O
was	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
two	O
Mens	O
.	O
His	O
Fever	O
was	O
decreas	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Humours	O
were	O
flown	O
outward	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
persuaded	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
Room	O
into	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
might	O
throw	O
in	O
again	O
the	O
Humour	O
,	O
which	O
should	O
have	O
perspir	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
So	O
his	O
Fever	O
increasing	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
Doctor	O
Hall	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
Bleeding	O
and	O
Blistering	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
was	O
cur	O
'd	O
before	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
violent	O
pricking	O
Pain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shooting	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Blow	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
Serjeants	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
as	O
quiet	O
a	O
Fellow	O
as	O
any	O
they	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
Regiment	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
19.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chettle	I-pers
,	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Chettle	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
Little	B-place
Tower	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	I-place
some	I-place
call	I-place
it	I-place
Rosemary-Lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Shop	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
fast	O
;	O
the	O
out-side	O
Bar	O
was	O
put	O
up	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
key	O
'd	O
the	O
Pins	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Tugging	O
at	O
the	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Body	O
was	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
listen	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
;	O
for	O
as	O
the	O
Noise	O
did	O
not	O
cease	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
't	O
was	O
some	O
Cats	O
might	O
be	O
lock	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
laid	O
myself	O
down	O
again	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Bounce	O
,	O
open	O
flew	O
the	O
Casement	O
of	O
my	O
Chamber	O
Window	O
.	O
O	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
coming	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
!	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Window	O
again	O
:	O
Then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Silence	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
Noise	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
our	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Bar	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
inner	O
Bolt	O
unfasten	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
check	O
'd	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
white	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table	O
cloth	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Shelves	O
next	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
Woman	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
draw	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
described	O
him	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
green	O
Waistcoat	O
on	O
;	O
a	O
red	O
Jacket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Towsers	O
.	O
My	O
Washerwoman	O
hearing	O
this	O
Description	O
,	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
Cellar	O
where	O
such	O
Out	O
of-the-way	O
Fellows	O
resorted	O
,	O
at	O
all	O
Hours	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
answered	O
the	O
Description	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griggs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
Ripping-chissel	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
by	O
wrenching	O
the	O
Bar	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
check	O
'd	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
white	O
ones	O
and	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
The	O
white	O
ones	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
check	O
'd	O
ones	O
himself	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Wife	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
check	O
'd	O
Shirts	O
and	O
the	O
Table	O
cloth	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
we	O
kept	O
a	O
white	O
Shirt	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
being	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
we	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
Fellow	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Griggs	O
.	O
We	O
liv	O
'd	O
both	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
swore	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Griggs	O
.	O
We	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
two	O
Months	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Trantum	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gribble	O
,	O
took	O
us	O
both	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
Cellar	O
;	O
-	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
us	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Thursday	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
House	O
breakers	O
conceal	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
difficulty	O
got	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
Griggs	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Griggs	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pray	O
'd	O
likewise	O
that	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
for	O
(	O
said	O
he	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
hang	O
five	O
for	O
the	O
Scamp	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
mentioned	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
Stepney	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Griggs	O
had	O
only	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Housebreaking	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Justice	O
had	O
admitted	O
Griggs	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
all	O
their	O
Facts	O
into	O
his	O
Information	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
himself	O
about	O
2	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
Fellow	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
:	O
Harris	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
Fanny	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
upon	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
,	O
by	O
Ashley	O
's	O
Punch	O
House	O
.	O
Martha	O
Cuttiford	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
(	O
the	O
first	O
Witness	O
)	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Trantum	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
were	O
dancing	O
with	O
their	O
Women	O
,	O
'till	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
who	O
saw	O
the	O
Burglary	O
committed	O
,	O
being	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
dear	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
-	O
we	O
are	O
young	O
Men	O
,	O
-	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
to	O
take	O
our	O
Lives	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
white	O
Shirts	O
and	O
the	O
Chissel	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Things	O
through	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Accomplice	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
They	O
beg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
take	O
away	O
their	O
Lives	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
then	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
stands	O
in	O
now	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Bird	O
's	O
ey	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Before	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Bench	O
,	O
in	O
Queen-Street	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gribble	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Trap	O
Door	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Fourteen	O
Stars	O
brought	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Cuttiford	I-pers
declared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
on	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
and	O
Mother	O
's	O
Account	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tuck	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
Harris	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Harris	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
myself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
Money	O
to	O
swear	O
Peoples	O
Lives	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
George	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
may	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
seen	O
Harris	O
several	O
Times	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Greenaway	O
.	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Man	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
and	O
Tom	B-pers
Sylvan	I-pers
,	O
came	O
and	O
talked	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
myself	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
live	O
in	O
Trantum	O
's	O
Cellar	O
?	O
French	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
after	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
29th	O
and	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
abroad	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
Distance	O
is	O
Trantum	O
's	O
Cellar	O
from	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
French	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Poplar	O
,	O
Trantum	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Mother	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cudlick	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Izard	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
20.	O
George	B-pers
Grinway	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
of	O
a	O
Brown	O
Colour	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jude	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
,	O
May	O
25	O
Jude	O
Storer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
my	O
Stable	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
a	O
Saddle	O
and	O
Bridle	O
;	O
some	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
Horse	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
's	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Laylam	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
Belfount	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Half-Moon	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
Robert	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Highway-man	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Half	O
Moon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
his	O
Horse	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
Description	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
3	O
loaded	O
Pistols	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Horse	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Storer	O
came	O
and	O
claimed	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
Guineas	O
at	O
Fulham	O
Bridge	O
.	O
The	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Highway-man	O
upon	O
Hounslow	B-place
Heath	I-place
,	O
between	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
and	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
8	O
s.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
mounted	O
on	O
a	O
Horse	O
about	O
15	O
Hands	O
high	O
,	O
that	O
went	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
Rate	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Broad-side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
hardly	O
give	O
me	O
Leave	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
Hands	O
in	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Haste	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
me	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
Leisure	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Horse	O
's	O
Back-side	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Sir	O
Tho	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
committed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Horse	O
and	O
the	O
Bags	O
being	O
advertised	O
,	O
Storer	O
came	O
and	O
claimed	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Gauntlet	O
of	O
Stockbridge	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
(	O
almost	O
worn	O
out	O
)	O
was	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
every	O
Particular	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Half-Moon	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Substance	O
was	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
alone	O
.	O
So	O
old	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
right	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
alone	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
loaded	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Powder	O
and	O
Balls	O
,	O
or	O
Slugs	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
was	O
doubtful	O
whether	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
have-a	O
Penknife	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
assuring	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Weapons	O
we	O
retir	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
Agony	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
one	O
too	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
in	O
his	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
pity	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
Heir	O
to	O
5	O
or	O
600	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Brother	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
at	O
Stamford	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
was	O
Sawyer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Relations	O
at	O
Reading	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
first	O
Flight	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
remember	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
Broad	O
Side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Pistol	O
into	O
my	O
Chaise	O
,	O
he	O
trembled	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
his	O
Pistol	O
still	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
did	O
this	O
in	O
Terrorem	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
dispatch	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
his	O
left	O
Leg	O
to	O
shake	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
concluded	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
young	O
Beginner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
frighted	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
North	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
lie	O
in	O
wait	O
for	O
a	O
Prize	O
,	O
-	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
smoaking	O
your	O
Pipe	O
in	O
the	O
Chaise	O
;	O
-	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Token	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Mind	O
to	O
have	O
thrown	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
Brown	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
so	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
believe	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
Several	O
.	O
First	O
,	O
my	O
Man	O
swears	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Horse	O
that	O
he	O
rode	O
to	O
the	O
Half-Moon	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Another	O
Reason	O
is	O
,	O
his	O
Manner	O
of	O
dealing	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
swore	O
above	O
an	O
Oath	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
My	O
Man	O
carelesly	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
rifling	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
his	O
Head	O
aside	O
.	O
I	O
reason	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
none	O
of	O
you	O
Gentlemen	O
ever	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
before	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
no	O
one	O
has	O
travell	O
'd	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
nothing	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
Want	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
can	O
draw	O
Bills	O
for	O
more	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
me	O
a	O
Farthing	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
Turnpikes	O
to	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
)	O
except	O
one	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
had	O
dropp	O
'd	O
between	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Chaise	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Habit	O
was	O
I	O
in	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
another	O
Reason	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
too	O
big	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
attack	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
shook	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Coat	O
Sleeve	O
being	O
too	O
long	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Conscience	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
Belfount	O
,	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
Request	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
little	O
Hat	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
over	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
answer	O
doing	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Confidence	O
and	O
Assurance	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
within	O
a	O
Mile	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
return	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Habit	O
into	O
the	O
Town	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roseblade	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Highway-man	O
's	O
Face	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
Notice	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
had	O
a	O
Star	O
in	O
his	O
Forehead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
both	O
his	O
Knees	O
were	O
broke	O
.	O
-	O
Blake	O
,	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Footit	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
three	O
loaded	O
Pistols	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Nutmeg-grater	O
,	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Powder	O
and	O
Slugs	O
.	O
-	O
Footit	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
exactly	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
had	O
given	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Heath	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
exactly	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Heath	O
,	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
driving	O
a	O
Horse	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
upon	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
at	O
Belfount	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
about	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
about	O
Nine	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
claim	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Storer	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
brought	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
at	O
Colebrook	O
till	O
Breakfast-Time	O
,	O
that	O
Morning	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
expected	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Camplin	I-pers
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
bad	O
Action	O
.	O
He	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
Uncle	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
Relations	O
live	O
at	O
Reading	O
,	O
or	O
there	O
about	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
has	O
an	O
Uncle	O
at	O
Reading	O
,	O
one	O
William	O
Greenaway	O
,	O
reputed	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
600	O
per	O
Annum	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
marry	O
'd	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
,	O
a	O
Currier	O
,	O
at	O
Newbury	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
Occupation	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Bargeman	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
of	O
late	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
21.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harbin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Hidesius	B-pers
Trigg	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
John	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Macgee	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25	O
,	O
26.	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Leghorn	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Deng	I-pers
,	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27	O
,	O
28.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
21	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
6	O
double	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
11	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
6	O
Linnen	O
Mobs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
