TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Micajah	O
Perry	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
LORD	O
-	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCXXXIX	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX	O
-	O
PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
Of	O
whom	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
preceding	O
Numbers	O
,	O
or	O
complete	O
Sets	O
on	O
fine	O
large	O
Paper	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
MICAJAH	B-pers
PERRY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENTON	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Giffard	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Newsham	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dixey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lutman	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hampstone	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
.	O
488.	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
the	I-place
less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
300	O
cwt	O
.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Woad	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
,	O
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
489.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sumner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jarrat	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
490	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hanning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
,	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
unlawfully	O
procured	O
John	B-pers
Hough	I-pers
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Subject	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
)	O
to	O
enlist	O
and	O
enter	O
himself	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
without	O
Leave	O
first	O
had	O
and	O
obtained	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Sign	O
Manual	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
in	O
Contempt	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Laws	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
evil	O
Example	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
offending	O
;	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
further	O
charged	O
,	O
-	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Hanning	O
,	O
afterward	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
unlawfully	O
hired	O
and	O
retained	O
John	B-pers
Hough	I-pers
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Subject	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
)	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
cause	O
the	O
said	O
Hough	O
to	O
enlist	O
and	O
enter	O
himself	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
;	O
without	O
Leave	O
first	O
had	O
and	O
obtained	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Councel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Offence	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
Felony	O
without	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
IXth	O
of	O
his	O
Present	O
Majesty	O
)	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
evil	O
,	O
Consequences	O
of	O
this	O
Practice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
John	O
Hough	O
was	O
swornn	O
.	O
Hough	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
English	O
Man	O
,	O
born	O
in	O
Warwickshire	O
;	O
by	O
Trade	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Grenadier	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Troop	O
of	O
Horse-Guards	O
these	O
four	O
Years	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
Application	O
made	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
quit	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
for	O
any	O
other	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
King	O
and	O
Country	O
,	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
great	O
Encouragement	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Connc	O
.	O
From	O
whom	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
last	O
August	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Month	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
last	O
August	O
)	O
one	O
Carrol	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
ill	O
a-bed	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
't	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
would	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
one	O
Anderson	O
,	O
who	O
shook	O
Hands	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
drank	O
my	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Desire	O
to	O
go	O
Abroad	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
it	O
I	O
had	O
dined	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
Carrol	O
for	O
some	O
Beef	O
Stakes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
eating	O
them	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
likely	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Service	O
was	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
's	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
plentifully	O
,	O
he	O
drank	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
a	O
particular	O
Person	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
parted	O
for	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
Anderson	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
several	O
Times	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
promis	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
Work	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Taylor	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Crown	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Crown	O
Alley	O
,	O
Upper	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
some	O
Cloth	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
wants	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
sit	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
meet	O
you	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
Twelve	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
waiting	O
for	O
one	O
Anderson	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
Anderson	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Fowl	O
and	O
Bacon	O
dress	O
'd	O
for	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
several	O
Bottles	O
together	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
plentifully	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Carrol	O
had	O
used	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
in	O
not	O
delivering	O
me	O
the	O
Cloth	O
which	O
Anderson	O
desired	O
I	O
might	O
make	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
assure	O
you	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
whatever	O
Anderson	O
has	O
promis	O
'd	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
pulling	O
a	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
-	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
broad	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
writing	O
:	O
His	O
Master	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
was	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
Power	O
to	O
enlist	O
all	O
Men	O
who	O
were	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
else	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Paper	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
's	O
Arms	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
Contents	O
of	O
the	O
Paper	O
were	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
Scholar	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
English	O
,	O
unless	O
it	O
be	O
wrote	O
very	O
plain	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
produced	O
that	O
Paper	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Day	O
exactly	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
Guild-hall	O
Coffeehouse	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Princes	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
:	O
There	O
we	O
drank	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Oysters	O
for	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
honourable	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
pay	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
paid	O
but	O
one	O
Two-pence	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
Place	O
,	O
when	O
our	O
Reck	O
nig	O
once	O
came	O
to	O
20	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
2	O
d.	O
At	O
this	O
Time	O
he	O
appointed	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
whose	O
Father	O
had	O
a	O
Place	O
under	O
the	O
King	O
)	O
to	O
go	O
Abroad	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
was	O
taller	O
than	O
me	O
by	O
an	O
Inch	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
my	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
might	O
pass	O
for	O
Brothers	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
following	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
Coffeehouse	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
lately	O
been	O
discharged	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
pass	O
for	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Prussia	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
Coffeehouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
Anderson	O
's	O
Promise	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
up	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
me	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
more	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
this	O
Money	O
for	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
this	O
Money	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
stil	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Body	O
Guard	O
:	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Gentlemen	O
is	O
the	O
usual	O
Appellation	O
given	O
to	O
his	O
Body	O
Guards	O
;	O
-	O
we	O
call	O
them	O
here	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
't	O
is	O
so	O
Abroad	O
.	O
Our	O
next	O
Meeting	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
us	O
have	O
brought	O
our	O
Wives	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
have	O
no	O
Wives	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
me	O
this	O
Paper	O
of	O
Directions	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
10	O
l.	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
-	O
what	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
it	O
it	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
Guard	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
Abroad	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Eternal	O
God	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
Cloth	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
against	O
I	O
went	O
Abroad	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
dilatory	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
soon	O
the	O
Captain	O
would	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
According	O
to	O
his	O
Order	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
Clay	O
about	O
Noon	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
Child	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
ded	O
together	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Lamb	O
roasted	O
and	O
a	O
Scrag	O
of	O
Mutton	O
boil	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hough	O
,	O
how	O
soon	O
we	O
may	O
go	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
Cloth	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
'll	O
have	O
Time	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
therefore	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
Thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
to	O
buy	O
you	O
a	O
handsome	O
Coat	O
.	O
Your	O
Cloaths	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
will	O
be	O
but	O
of	O
little	O
Signification	O
to	O
you	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
allows	O
a	O
Summer	O
and	O
a	O
Winter	O
Suit	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
he	O
changed	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Clay	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
;	O
and	O
Clay	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
shook	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
pass	O
for	O
Brothers	O
.	O
Before	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
every	O
Night	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
accordingly	O
went	O
thither	O
the	O
next	O
Evening	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
?	O
Perhaps	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
Money	O
enough	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
left	O
a	O
double	O
Louis	O
d'Or	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
14	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
took	O
Measure	O
of	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
me	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
ruffled	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
put	O
me	O
on	O
board	O
as	O
a	O
Merchant	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
Account	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
these	O
14	O
s.	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
14	O
s.	O
to	O
buy	O
other	O
Things	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
)	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
my	O
going	O
over	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
sometime	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Deveil	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Warrant	O
granted	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
acquaint	O
the	O
Lord	O
Harrington	O
with	O
the	O
Affair	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
I	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Officers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
inform	O
'd	O
my	O
Lord	O
Albemarle	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
enquiring	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
on	O
board	O
to	O
provide	O
for	O
our	O
Passage	O
;	O
Carrol	O
and	O
Anderson	O
were	O
fled	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
several	O
Times	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
Abroad	O
likewise	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
more	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
36	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
14	O
s.	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
mentioned	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
several	O
small	O
Parcels	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
Keeping	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
Excuse	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
not	O
going	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
He	O
press	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Captain	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Intent	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
promis	O
'd	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
my	O
Things	O
ready	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
People	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
fled	O
.	O
Carrol	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
,	O
is	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
Anderson	O
is	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
at	O
Dunkirk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
Inn	O
without	O
Bishopsgate	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
Abroad	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
August	O
run	O
out	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
never	O
three	O
Days	O
asunder	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Money	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Lodging	O
four	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
Days	O
after	O
at	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
Inn	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Look	O
on	O
these	O
Papers	O
.	O
-	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrote	O
them	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
three	O
Directions	O
:	O
These	O
two	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Papers	O
were	O
read.	O
``	O
12	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
,	O
Cripplegate.	O
``	O
At	O
the	O
Bare	O
,	O
(	O
Bear	O
)	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
``	O
Meuse.	O
``	O
12	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
,	O
Cripplegate	O
.	O
''	O
Hough	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Direction	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrote	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
not	O
wrote	O
plain	O
enough	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
what	O
Day	O
in	O
August	O
you	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
21st	O
or	O
22d	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Princes	O
street	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
36	O
s.	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
or	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
for	O
so	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Prussia	O
to	O
serve	O
in	O
that	O
King	O
's	O
Body	O
Guards	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
soon	O
the	O
Ship	O
would	O
sail	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
how	O
soon	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
was	O
the	O
14	O
s.	O
given	O
you	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
'is	O
my	O
Opinion	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Begining	O
and	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Month	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
England	O
but	O
five	O
Days	O
before	O
he	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Man	O
Abroad	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
intimateing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Commission	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
large	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
Abroad	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
our	O
Company	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
I	O
paid	O
you	O
other	O
small	O
Sums	O
at	O
different	O
Times	O
,	O
what	O
were	O
they	O
for	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
such	O
small	O
Sums	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Keeping	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
little	O
Sums	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
10	O
l.	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
10	O
l.	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
second	O
little	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
Coffeehouse	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
speak	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
whatever	O
I	O
wanted	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
mention	O
one	O
Word	O
to	O
you	O
of	O
serving	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
's	O
Army	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
Body	O
Guards	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
my	O
Judge	O
,	O
twenty	O
times	O
over	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
Place	O
was	O
you	O
first	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
serve	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
's	O
Army	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Exchange	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Commission	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
Name	O
enter	O
'd	O
in	O
any	O
List	O
or	O
Roll	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
is	O
what	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Roll	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
is	O
kept	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
Work	O
as	O
a	O
Taylor	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
employ	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
during	O
our	O
Meetings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
his	O
Word	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
angry	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
not	O
employing	O
you	O
?	O
Hough	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
For	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
Work	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
ill	O
and	O
fatigu	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
ca	O
n't	O
express	O
myself	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
base	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
will	O
turn	O
out	O
so	O
.	O
William	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
victualling	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hough	O
about	O
three	O
Years	O
:	O
His	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
Rogue	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Man	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
heard	O
many	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
twenty-three	O
Weeks	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1736	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
paid	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
kiss	O
his	O
Arse	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
his	O
Colonel	O
and	O
the	O
Colonel	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
Hough	O
told	O
him	O
plainly	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
down	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
are	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
known	O
about	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
The	O
Neighbours	O
who	O
use	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Grogan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
,	O
by	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
Hough	O
very	O
well	O
by	O
Sight	O
,	O
for	O
these	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
upwards	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
every	O
one	O
he	O
deals	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
sell	O
Beer	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
values	O
his	O
Oath	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
would	O
[	O
do	O
to	O
]	O
take	O
the	O
Snuff	O
of	O
this	O
Candle	O
and	O
throw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
And	O
how	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
?	O
Grogan	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
during	O
my	O
Continuance	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
Once	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
buying	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
in	O
my	O
Apartment	O
.	O
He	O
bargained	O
for	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
fourteen	O
Shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
the	O
Barley-Mow	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
bring	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
stole	O
;	O
but	O
afterward	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
who	O
did	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Pray	O
where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Grogan	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
,	O
in	O
King's-Head	O
Court	O
,	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
kept	O
this	O
House	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Ireland	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Paris	O
,	O
to	O
edify	O
myself	O
in	O
my	O
Business	O
and	O
from	O
Paris	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
went	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Paris	O
to	O
edify	O
yourself	O
as	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
Alamode	O
de	O
Paris	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
draw	O
Beer	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Exeter-street	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
Hough	O
about	O
sixteen	O
Months	O
.	O
His	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
Rogue	O
.	O
Every	O
one	O
that	O
knows	O
him	O
gives	O
him	O
that	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
nine	O
Months	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sixteen	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
Information	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
before	O
you	O
quitted	O
his	O
House	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
Warning	O
the	O
next	O
Quarter	O
Day	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
paid	O
him	O
his	O
Rent	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
distrained	O
upon	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
Quarter-Day	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
Hough	O
bought	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
good	O
Bargain	O
for	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Stay-Maker	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Alsop	O
,	O
in	O
Blackmoor-street	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hough	O
about	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
His	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
that	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
vile	O
odious	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
for	O
the	O
Lucre	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
whose	O
Life	O
he	O
takes	O
,	O
-	O
nor	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
next	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
little	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
You	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Langford	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
(	O
Hawkins	O
)	O
your	O
Husband	O
?	O
Was	O
not	O
your	O
Evidence	O
set	O
aside	O
on	O
a	O
Trial	O
at	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
Langford	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
his	O
little	O
Apartment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
wash	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
mend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Children	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
Wife	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hough	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
now	O
within	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Doors	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Neighbourhood	O
gives	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
the	O
Lucre	O
of	O
Gain	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
civil	O
Answer	O
in	O
passing	O
and	O
repassing	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
once	O
three	O
Months	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
scruple	O
to	O
swear	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Life	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
nothing	O
,	O
-	O
provided	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gorman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hough	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
Neighbours	O
give	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
unjust	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
believed	O
upon	O
his	O
Oath	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Key	O
,	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
,	O
two	O
Summers	O
,	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
Years	O
:	O
He	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
Way	O
of	O
Business	O
.	O
He	O
buys	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
abroad	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
Dunkirk	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
bought	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Pieces	O
at	O
a	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
four	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
trades	O
sometimes	O
to	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
brings	O
Goods	O
from	O
abroad	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
entered	O
any	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-House	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
contradict	O
his	O
being	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
trades	O
to	O
Dunkirk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
Cambricks	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
reckon	O
him	O
a	O
Merchant	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
his	O
entering	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-House	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hartrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
trades	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
Goods	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
Houses	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
eight	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
paid	O
him	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
inlisting	O
Soldiers	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Oldridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
five	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
Way	O
of	O
Livelyhood	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
enlisting	O
Men	O
for	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
He	O
goes	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
times	O
a	O
Year	O
to	O
Holland	O
and	O
Dunkirk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Captain	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
-	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
him	O
14	O
Great	O
Coats	O
for	O
Exportation	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
Servants	O
pack	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
coarse	O
Cloth	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Remnants	O
of	O
six	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Sums	O
and	O
Bills	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
in	O
my	O
Possession	O
?	O
Oldridge	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
600	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
Bills	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
Colour	O
were	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
you	O
made	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Oldridge	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
dark	O
Drabs	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
lin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
unlin	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
as	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
this	O
Charge	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
Hough	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Timms	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Hough	O
;	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest-Man	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
very	O
near	O
him	O
in	O
White-hart	O
Yard	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
Years	O
.	O
His	O
Character	O
is	O
good	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
forswear	O
himself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Timms	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
from	O
Hough	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
deals	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
pays	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
,	O
of	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
in	O
White-hart	O
Yard	O
;	O
Hough	O
is	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Life	O
away	O
wrongfully	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hopson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hough	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Artichoke	O
in	O
White	O
hart	O
Yard	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
is	O
joining	O
to	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
;	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
forswear	O
himself	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
-	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
from	O
Hough	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bears	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
Scores	O
of	O
Pounds	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
return	O
'd	O
Money	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
myself	O
so	O
proper	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
faithfully	O
accounted	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Hundred	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Pounds	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
entrusted	O
by	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
present	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Man	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
or	O
speak	O
an	O
ill	O
Word	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
perjuring	O
himself	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Fault	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
Crisp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lived	O
about	O
Half	O
a	O
Year	O
where	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Chandler	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
talk	O
about	O
his	O
returning	O
200	O
l.	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
From	O
where	O
did	O
this	O
Sum	O
come	O
?	O
Crisp	O
.	O
From	O
Norfolk	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
Scholar	O
capable	O
of	O
taking	O
Care	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Affairs	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
entrusted	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
Hough	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
a	O
Letter	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
a	O
written	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Shewn	O
Hough	O
.	O
]	O
Hough	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
read	O
this	O
Paper	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
signifies	O
that	O
?	O
I	O
can	O
keep	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
write	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crisp	O
had	O
200	O
l.	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
manag	O
'd	O
the	O
Affair	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
just	O
Account	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
Six-score	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
Fourscore	O
more	O
to	O
receive	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rounsome	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hough	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White-hart	O
Yard	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
lives	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
here	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Neigbourhood	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Captain	O
Hopkins	B-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hough	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
1735-6	O
.	O
I	O
enter	O
'd	O
him	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Troop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
has	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
forswear	O
himself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
never	O
been	O
punish	O
'd	O
?	O
Captain	O
Hopkins	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
never	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
acquainted	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
Major	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Albemarle	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
granted	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
Hough	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
Information	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
till	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Serjeant	O
Lock	O
.	O
Hough	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
our	O
Troop	O
about	O
four	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
his	O
Duty	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
private	O
Affairs	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
in	O
White	O
hart	O
Yard	O
;	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Antelope	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hough	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
?	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
one	O
speak	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
;	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Man	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
491.	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Peck	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
the	O
Goops	O
of	O
William	B-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
492	O
,	O
493.	O
James	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cornforth	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mawle	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cool	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mawle	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Bond-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Things	O
from	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
three	O
Shirts	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
Apartment	O
about	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shirts	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Portmanteau-Trunk	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Shirts	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Notice	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Lock	O
burst	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Shirts	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
Hat	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wore	O
the	O
Hat	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Confinement	O
.	O
-	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Shirt	O
in	O
Pawn	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Cool	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Shirts	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
Cool	O
.	O
What	O
Rent	O
did	O
your	O
Master	O
owe	O
?	O
Cool	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Rent	O
owing	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
ow	O
'd	O
my	O
Master	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Action	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
Bennet	O
)	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
Account	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
my	O
Master	O
20	O
l.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
Cool	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Things	O
away	O
.	O
Cool	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bennet	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
Shirt	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Cornforth	O
.	O
Cool	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Bennet	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shirt	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
(	O
Barbara	O
Withers	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
4	O
s.	O
upon	O
this	O
Shirt	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Cool	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bennet	O
.	O
His	O
Master	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
Money	O
for	O
Rent	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
moving	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
Seizures	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
Manner	O
.	O
People	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
lock	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
his	O
Master	O
a	O
proper	O
Account	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Maule	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tun	O
Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
settle	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
his	O
Things	O
might	O
be	O
delivered	O
to	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
insisted	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
paid	O
before	O
the	O
Delivery	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
my	O
Husband	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
was	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
getting	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
under	O
Arrest	O
,	O
Cool	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Card	O
Table-Drawer	O
.	O
The	O
Shirts	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bennet	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
Bail	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
this	O
Martha	O
Walker	O
went	O
with	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Haste	O
she	O
shut	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Inside	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
'T	O
is	O
true	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Cool	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
upon	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Band-box	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
or	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brumfield	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
with	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
Cool	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Things	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
several	O
Examinations	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Dispute	O
between	O
Landlord	O
and	O
Tenant	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
Cool	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
Cool	O
)	O
never	O
mention	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
having	O
been	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
one	O
Hayman	O
charged	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
with	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
their	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
Cool	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
mention	O
'd	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Goods	O
of	O
theirs	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hayman	I-pers
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
494	O
,	O
495.	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
and	O
stealing	O
80	O
C.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ferdinando	B-pers
John	I-pers
Paris	I-pers
,	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Paris	O
's	O
in	O
Strand-Lane	B-place
,	O
Surrey-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
Sash	O
that	O
looks	O
over	O
a	O
Parlour	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
lower	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Lead	O
)	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
or	O
not	O
:	O
The	O
Leads	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
were	O
very	O
wet	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
putting	O
my	O
Hand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
rain	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Paris	O
.	O
This	O
House	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Parlour	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
mentioned	O
,	O
was	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
near	O
40	O
C.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
that	O
looks	O
over	O
these	O
Leads	O
,	O
toward	O
Somerset	O
Gardens	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Weather	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
usual	O
Custom	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
Lead	O
safe	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
Sept.	O
16.	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
great	O
Strips	O
cut	O
off	O
to	O
the	O
Joinings	O
where	O
the	O
Lead	O
is	O
doubled	O
over	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Strand-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
several	O
People	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
Lead	O
carrying	O
off	O
?	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
William	O
Green	O
of	O
Maypole-Alley	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Job	O
To-night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Stuff	O
had	O
gone	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Hearing	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Maypole-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
Green	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Word	O
of	O
an	O
Answer	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
What	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
To-night	O
?	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
wretched	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
for	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
one	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
planted	O
my	O
own	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
others	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
In	O
short	O
,	O
I	O
beset	O
it	O
all	O
Sunday	O
and	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
myself	O
every	O
Half	O
Hour	O
,	O
or	O
Three-quarters	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
my	O
Watch	O
did	O
Duty	O
.	O
About	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
my	O
Servant	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seiz	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
some	O
Lead	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Hesketh	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Information	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
Leeson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
private	O
Hole	O
under	O
the	O
Stair-Case	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
Quantity	O
press	O
'd	O
as	O
flat	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
still	O
wet	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
flatted	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
laying	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
tallied	O
exactly	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Notches	O
and	O
Indentures	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
all	O
the	O
Lead	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Leeson	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
Place	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
still	O
some	O
wanting	O
:	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
Green	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
small	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
huge	O
large	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
laying	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Places	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
wanting	O
,	O
it	O
tallied	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
exact	O
Manner	O
;	O
in	O
one	O
Place	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
cut	O
round	O
a	O
Nail	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cut	O
in	O
the	O
Lead	O
fitted	O
the	O
Nail	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
took	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
carry	O
'd	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
Lead	O
to	O
Leeson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
exactly	O
opposite	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
in	O
Maypole-Alley	O
)	O
at	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Lead	O
that	O
my	O
Man	O
stopp	O
'd	O
upon	O
Hesketh	O
,	O
that	O
likewise	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Hands	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
cut	O
very	O
irregularly	O
,	O
and	O
tally	O
'd	O
exactly	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
above	O
8	O
C.	O
Wt	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
9	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
Pound	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Oak	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
carry	O
something	O
like	O
Lead	O
under	O
the	O
Flaps	O
of	O
their	O
Coats	O
to	O
Hesketh	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Maypole	O
Alley	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
had	O
a	O
Set-to	O
Coat	O
on	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Cape	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coat	O
like	O
what	O
Green	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
Hesketh	O
's	O
Cellar	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
between	O
Six	O
and	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Hesketh	O
brought	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cellar	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
as	O
two	O
Bunches	O
of	O
Turneps	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Lift-up	O
with	O
the	O
Basket	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
surprized	O
that	O
two	O
Bunches	O
of	O
Turneps	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
heavy	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
Cellar	O
to	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
pitched	O
the	O
Basket	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
those	O
Turneps	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
mill	O
'd	O
Lead	O
under	O
the	O
Turneps	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
Hesketh	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
,	O
who	O
granted	O
us	O
Search-Warrants	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
great	O
Quantities	O
in	O
Leeson	O
's	O
and	O
Green	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
Hesketh	O
,	O
)	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
to	O
the	O
Places	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
When	O
Green	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
that	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
till	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
Liquor	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
Lead	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Cousin	O
took	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
uneasy	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
removed	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
informed	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Asser	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
carried	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Leeson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
himself	O
,	O
nor	O
need	O
he	O
(	O
Leeson	O
)	O
fear	O
coming	O
into	O
any	O
Trouble	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hesketh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lead	O
found	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Basket	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Leeson	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
Green	O
was	O
?	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Lead	O
in	O
his	O
(	O
Leeson	O
's	O
)	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
Leeson	O
wanted	O
to	O
move	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
Green	O
came	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
swore	O
a	O
great	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
Pieces	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
Cellar	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Green	O
presently	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
carry	O
the	O
Lead	O
from	O
my	O
Cellar	O
to	O
Waldron	O
,	O
the	O
Plummer	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Lead	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Turneps	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
't	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
to	O
Waldron	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Peices	O
that	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Name	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Paris	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
.	O
Green	O
being	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
owned	O
that	O
such	O
Lead	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Paris	O
had	O
lost	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
Leeson	O
was	O
not	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Paris	O
.	O
Green	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Asser	I-pers
,	O
(	O
his	O
Cousin	O
)	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
(	O
Green	O
's	O
)	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
this	O
Asser	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
a	O
Horse	O
and	O
Man	O
fifty	O
Miles	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
(	O
he	O
owned	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Nephew	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
remember	O
he	O
mentioned	O
Asser	O
's	O
Name	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Leeson	O
.	O
Green	O
knocked	O
me	O
up	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Lead	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Kinsman	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Trouble	O
before	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
such	O
Accounts	O
)	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
'till	O
the	O
People	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
should	O
come	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
who	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Meddall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Midwife	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russel-Court	O
,	O
by	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Green	O
's	O
Wife	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
her	O
Labour	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
between	O
Four	O
and	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Pretty	O
near	O
Twelve	O
,	O
Green	O
came	O
home	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
safe	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
past	O
One	O
.	O
After	O
his	O
Spouse	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
safe	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Tea	O
.	O
About	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
somebody	O
knocked	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Green	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
Relation	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
down	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Steps	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
curious	O
)	O
listned	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
People	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
where	O
's	O
Green	O
?	O
We	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
Lead	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Green	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
a-bed	O
,	O
fuddled	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
wrong	O
time	O
o'Night	O
to	O
bring	O
Lead	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
(	O
says	O
the	O
Men	O
)	O
we	O
'll	O
leave	O
it	O
till	O
we	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
your	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
heavy	O
Load	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Green	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
buys	O
and	O
sells	O
old	O
and	O
new	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
Lead	O
and	O
Iron	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
this	O
Respect	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Indeed	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Trouble	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Green	O
's	O
Landlord	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Chandler	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Picture	O
Frame-maker	O
,	O
and	O
Keeper	O
of	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Shop	O
)	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Green	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Stanhope	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Maypole-alley	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
had	O
known	O
Green	O
about	O
nine	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Green	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
bad	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
reputed	O
Buyer	O
of	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Henning	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Logan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Rimer	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
Leeson	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
swore	O
he	O
knew	O
Leeson	O
when	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Green	O
Guilty	O
;	O
Leeson	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
496.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hardcastle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
val	O
.	O
4.	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
497.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
498.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
499.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
a	O
Passage	O
from	O
Tower-hill	B-place
into	O
Rosemary-Lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
picked	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
very	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
li't	O
of	O
two	O
Boys	O
,	O
who	O
'ticed	O
me	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Good	O
Lad	O
,	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
-	O
we	O
'll	O
teach	O
you	O
to	O
pick	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
begun	O
with	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
500.	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
and	O
stealing	O
1	O
C.	O
Wt	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
501.	O
Mary	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Calimanco	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding	O
Habit	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
4	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
from	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Raper	O
's	O
Wife	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Steed	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Oak	I-place
in	O
Newport-street	B-place
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Steed	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
's	O
Bed	O
;	O
who	O
missing	O
her	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
an	O
unusual	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
tax	O
'd	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
acknowledging	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
one	O
Paul	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
she	O
had	O
thrown	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
502.	O
William	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gillet	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
503.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tea-Tongs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Octo	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
504.	O
Myers	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Oven-lid	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
505.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Black	B-pers
Sam	I-pers
*	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lillo	I-pers
,	O
Octo	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Kew	O
's	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
for	O
picking	O
Mr.	O
Tanner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
Aldermanbury	O
,	O
of	O
55	O
Guineas	O
,	O
last	O
December	O
Sessions	O
,	O
p.9	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lillo	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
comeing	O
past	O
the	O
Mansion-house	B-place
which	O
is	O
now	O
building	O
for	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayors	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Plank	O
being	O
laid	O
over	O
a	O
very	O
dirty	O
Place	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
kept	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
under	O
my	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Plank	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
cut	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
off	O
the	O
Plank	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
Half-Crowns	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
first	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
somebody	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
?	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
afterward	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
16	O
or	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
17	O
s.	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Lillo	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
same	O
Story	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
now	O
.	O
We	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
?	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
us	O
any	O
direct	O
Answers	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
in	O
what	O
Street	O
?	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Then	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Half-Crowns	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
justly	O
be	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
some	O
People	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
:	O
The	O
Drawer	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
;	O
no	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
send	O
for	O
nobody	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
we	O
advis	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
charge	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
several	O
People	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Lord	O
being	O
at	O
Grocer	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
for	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Black	B-pers
Sam	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
up	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Knife	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
search	O
'd	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Black	O
Sam	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
met	O
nobody	O
between	O
Lombard-street	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Money	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Lillo	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
nor	O
meet	O
any	O
one	O
,	O
(	O
to	O
be	O
near	O
him	O
)	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
506.	O
John	B-pers
Norcut	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dead	O
Goose	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lorman	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
507.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Napkin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
George	O
Gray	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
past	O
Poor	B-place
Jewry-Lane	I-place
,	O
by	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Minutes	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
it	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Head	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
25	O
or	O
26	O
s.	O
in	O
my	O
Right-hand	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
feeling	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
four	O
Half-Crowns	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Half-Crown	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
upon	O
her	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Napkin	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Night	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
asking	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
Discourse	O
happen	O
'd	O
between	O
us	O
I	O
really	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
-	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Half-Crowns	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
stripping	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
the	O
Napkin	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wardley	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
About	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
He	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
11	O
s.	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
still	O
somewhere	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
(	O
knowing	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
)	O
expostulated	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
,	O
-	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
-	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
reprimanded	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
our	O
Watchmen	O
must	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
Gown	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
)	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Bosom	O
of	O
her	O
Shift	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
three	O
Half-Crowns	O
.	O
The	O
Napkin	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
Samuel	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Batman	I-pers
:	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
Fenchurch	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
my	O
Landlady	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
buy	O
some	O
Meat	O
for	O
Sunday	O
's	O
Dinner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
against	O
something	O
like	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Pump	O
by	O
Aldgate	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Man	O
:	O
My	O
dear	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
haste	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Pull	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
intended	O
no	O
Harm	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
Crouched	O
Fryars	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
:	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
perhaps	O
I	O
might	O
want	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
given	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
put	O
three	O
Half-Crowns	O
down	O
my	O
Bosom	O
;	O
and	O
afterward	O
,	O
-	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Half-Crown	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
to	O
my	O
Landlord	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
508.	O
Jane	B-pers
Burgoyne	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Cap	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lora	B-pers
Finney	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Woman	O
's	O
Cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rachael	B-pers
Finney	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
Shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
ditto	O
,	O
(	O
unfinished	O
)	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Flatman	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
509.	O
Jane	B-pers
Thicker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Cobey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
Sept.	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
510.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
511.	O
Francis	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
val	O
9	O
l.	O
and	O
four	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Doctor	O
in	O
Musick	O
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Runcivil	I-pers
.	O
The	O
four	O
Salts	O
and	O
Salt-Spoons	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Turner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
never	O
knew	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
(	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
)	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Goal-keeper	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Beaufet	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Duke-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
eleven	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Street-Door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
four	O
Salts	O
and	O
four	O
Salt-Spoons	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Beaufette	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Walpole	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
my	O
being	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
fled	O
.	O
Runcivil	O
.	O
Robinson	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
this	O
Walpole	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
off	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Ducks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Drake	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
7	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
512	O
,	O
513.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Purvis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver-Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
.	O
Sinclair	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Chandos	B-place
Street	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Back-room	O
,	O
behind	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
A	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
in	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pack-thread	O
which	O
fastened	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Inside	O
was	O
undone	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Purvis	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
Man	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
Purvis	O
stood	O
watching	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
broke	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
in	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
untying	O
the	O
Packthread	O
with	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
.	O
Then	O
Flack	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
Things	O
(	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
)	O
which	O
we	O
sold	O
to	O
Flack	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Shares	O
were	O
6	O
d.	O
a-piece	O
.	O
Flack	O
.	O
When	O
Robinson	O
was	O
before	O
Colonel	O
Deveil	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
four	O
People	O
in	O
this	O
Information	O
.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Tom	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
with	O
us	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
cast	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
6	O
d	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
we	O
.	O
Purvis	O
.	O
Flack	O
is	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
514.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Crosby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Gold	O
Thread	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Marse	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
515.	O
John	B-pers
Sagery	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Foundes	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
516.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Haddon	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
,	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
517.	O
Cossal	B-pers
Jonas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
James	B-pers
Wint	I-pers
having	O
stole	O
a	O
Deal	O
Box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
twenty	O
Doz	O
.	O
of	O
Lambskin	O
Gloves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
l	O
10	O
s.	O
thirteen	O
Doz	O
.	O
of	O
Kid	O
Gloves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
13	O
l.	O
fifteen	O
Doz	O
.	O
of	O
Thread	O
and	O
Cotton	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
ten	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cotten	O
Gloves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
l.	O
one	O
Doz	O
.	O
of	O
Thread	O
Socks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
eighteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Pink	O
Brocade	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
twenty-four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
of	O
blue	O
Damask	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
Yards	O
and	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
Tabby	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Childrens	O
Satten	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Ashburn	I-pers
,	O
April	O
28	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Jonas	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Charles	O
Ashburn	O
.	O
Wint	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
above-mentioned	O
Goods	O
last	O
June	O
Sessions	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Horse	O
Shoe	O
Inn	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Wint	O
,	O
one	O
Akins	O
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Wint	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Bullinbroke	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
has	O
since	O
been	O
transported	O
)	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
Parcel	O
,	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
the	O
whole	O
Cargo	O
.	O
Akins	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
Abroad	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
comes	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chamberlain	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Heusch	O
(	O
lately	O
dead	O
)	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
absconded	O
till	O
Akins	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Charge	O
against	O
him	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
a	O
Fact	O
committed	O
in	O
Bishops-gate-street	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
for	O
June	O
1739.	O
p.	O
98	O
.	O
518.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
five	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Eade	I-pers
,	O
Octo	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
519.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
520.	O
Ann	B-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Hannah	B-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Johanna	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gooday	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
Gooday	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Quartern	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Woman	O
I	O
brought	O
in	O
go	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
would	O
stay	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
me	O
)	O
herself	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Quartern	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
demanded	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
my	O
Fob	O
.	O
Then	O
(	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
impudent	O
Manner	O
indeed	O
)	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
solicited	O
me	O
for	O
more	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
Solicitation	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
:	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
immediately	O
rose	O
from	O
my	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
something	O
into	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
on	O
the	O
Ground-floor	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Mob	O
rose	O
upon	O
me	O
immediately	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
indeed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
duck	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Elephant	O
and	O
Castle	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
kept	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
discharg	O
'd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
521.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
522.	O
William	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Birchman	B-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Birchmore	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Wether	O
Sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Dec.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
523.	O
Francis	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Cask	O
,	O
bound	O
with	O
four	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
524	O
.	O
John	O
Hastings	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Lord	O
Hastings	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bell	O
Metal	O
Mortar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Octo	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
525.	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hillendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
demanding	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Stick	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
the	O
Moneys	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Fisher	O
to	O
steal	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
526	O
,	O
527.	O
Cuthbert	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
(	O
no	O
one	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
Sept.	O
26	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Charles-Square	B-place
,	O
Hoxton	B-place
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
,	O
they	O
neither	O
deny	O
'd	O
nor	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Mill	O
Yard	O
into	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Wharton	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Deacon	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
watch	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
Wharton	O
lifted	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dug	O
up	O
the	O
Threshold	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Hole	O
under	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
which	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
stuck	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
hardly	O
get	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
Wharton	O
found	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
pass	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
he	O
wrench	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
off	O
the	O
Hinges	O
with	O
the	O
Threshold	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
dug	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
seven	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
a	O
Hat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hall	O
;	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Room	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Brandy	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
these	O
Things	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Door	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Wharton	O
's	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
Wharton	O
was	O
taken	O
likewise	O
.	O
Deacon	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Steward	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
Deacon	O
stood	O
behind	O
the	O
Pales	O
to	O
tip	O
Tommy	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
-	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ibbott	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
my	O
Master	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
safe	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Garden-Door	O
was	O
dug	O
under	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Threshold	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Thing	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
which	O
are	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Shadrach	B-pers
Hamman	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Man	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
brought	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
.	O
I	O
seal	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
myself	O
:	O
This	O
Porringer	O
,	O
this	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Shoes	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
Hat	O
and	O
the	O
Shirt	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Cuddy	O
Wharton	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Lads	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
presently	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
Deacon	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
the	O
Goods	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Steward	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
with	O
Cuddy	O
Wharton	O
and	O
Deacon	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
,	O
with	O
what	O
Goods	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Threshold	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
dug	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
Thing	O
in	O
the	O
Condition	O
Steward	O
had	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
Steward	O
)	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
broken	O
Spoons	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
Deacon	O
had	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
Deacon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
Tea-Spoons	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
what	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Deacon	O
:	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
of	O
another	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
what	O
Service	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Wharton	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Thief	O
takers	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
myself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
home	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
;	O
but	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Harris	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
from	O
my	O
Work	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
Steward	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
till	O
then	O
that	O
Wharton	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
my	O
asking	O
Wharton	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
:	O
He	O
did	O
tell	O
me	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
Sullivan	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Deacon	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
pity	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
Wharton	O
)	O
should	O
suffer	O
wrongfully	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
these	O
Men	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Steward	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
toss	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Wharton	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
Deacon	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
528.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tedman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clapham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Octo	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
529.	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Pay	I-pers
,	O
[	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Customs	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	B-place
called	I-place
the	I-place
Voluntier	I-place
,	O
then	O
within	O
the	O
Limits	O
of	O
the	O
Port	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
]	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
did	O
forcibly	O
obstruct	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
likewise	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Pay	I-pers
did	O
beat	O
,	O
wound	O
and	O
evil	O
intreat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
farther	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
on	O
John	O
Pay	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
did	O
evil	O
intreat	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
to	O
him	O
other	O
great	O
Damage	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pay	O
were	O
station	O
'd	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Voluntier	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Ratcliffe	O
Cross	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ship	O
lay	O
facing	O
that	O
Place	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
September	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Turn	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
between	O
Decks	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
Candle	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Boastwain	O
with	O
two	O
twelve-Gallon	O
Casks	O
of	O
Rum	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
arguing	O
with	O
the	O
Boatswain	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
up	O
upon	O
Deck	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
only	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
work	O
the	O
Vessel	O
up	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
with	O
the	O
Liquor	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pay	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
,	O
(	O
an	O
Excise-Officer	O
)	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Casks	O
into	O
the	O
Steerage	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
more	O
Casks	O
in	O
the	O
Bulk-head	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
remove	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
Cable-Teer	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Blake	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Candles	O
and	O
Lanthorns	O
beat	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
:	O
The	O
two	O
first	O
Casks	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Steerage	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
under	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
Pay	O
and	O
Blake	O
:	O
but	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
to	O
search	O
farther	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Officers	O
,	O
beat	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
two	O
Casks	O
over	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Candles	O
beat	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
strike	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
struck	O
me	O
a	O
Blow	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
away	O
my	O
Tinder-box	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
two	O
more	O
Casks	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
damning	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
us	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
our	O
Bloods	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
Liquor	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Direction	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb	O
and	O
Star	O
at	O
Newcranes	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pay	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Custom-house	O
Officer	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Deputation	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
Duty	O
on	O
board	O
this	O
Ship	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pay	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
,	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Cabin	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Partner	O
hearing	O
a	O
Rumbling	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Steerage	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
this	O
Liquor	O
.	O
I	O
roll	O
'd	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Casks	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
carry	O
away	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
two	O
Casks	O
of	O
Rum	O
were	O
under	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
you	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Pay	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
must	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Rum	O
,	O
somebody	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
our	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
immediately	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Cask	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pay	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
(	O
as	O
above	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
forcibly	O
obstructing	O
,	O
beating	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
a	O
Customhouse	O
Officer	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
Sept.	O
7	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
*	O
By	O
6	O
G.c	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
~	O
34	O
.	O
Persons	O
convicted	O
of	O
forcibly	O
hindering	O
,	O
wounding	O
or	O
beating	O
any	O
Officer	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
due	O
Execution	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
such	O
Term	O
as	O
the	O
Court	O
shall	O
think	O
fit	O
,	O
not	O
exceeding	O
seven	O
Years	O
;	O
And	O
this	O
Person	O
was	O
accordingly	O
sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
530.	O
John	B-pers
Cuttle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
71	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Turkey	O
Cotton	O
Yarn	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
val	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Brownsmith	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Goodeve	I-pers
,	O
September	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
531	O
,	O
532.	O
James	B-pers
Fide	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
and	O
abusing	O
Mary	B-pers
Fido	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Infant	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Seven	O
Years	O
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
Mary	O
Fido	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
tender	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
Sworn	O
