TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
12th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Micajah	O
Perry	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
LORD	O
-	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
MICAJAH	B-pers
PERRY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
PAGE	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
FORTESCUE	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Phillibrown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Alnard	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Worral	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Loveledge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Oakman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cholmondley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keate	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
142.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Bunn	O
suspecting	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
sent	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
143	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Udal	I-pers
+	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Tortois-shell	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Dec.	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Udal	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Fluellin	I-pers
,	O
last	O
September	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Street	O
Robbery	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
7.	O
p.	O
122	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
Sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
and	O
convicted	O
;	O
but	O
received	O
corporal	O
Punishment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
at	O
Holloway	B-place
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
't	O
was	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Holloway	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-Broker	O
's	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Watch	O
I	O
then	O
lost	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wornel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
Mann	O
[	O
the	O
Evidence	O
]	O
and	O
Udal	O
.	O
Mann	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
two	O
Men	O
about	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
this	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawned	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
claimed	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Day	O
after	O
Christmas	O
Day	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
at	O
Holloway	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
we	O
called	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Pork	O
Stakes	O
.	O
We	O
returned	O
about	O
Seven	O
or	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
;	O
Udal	O
took	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
He	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
Home	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
's	O
in	O
White-Lyon-Court	O
;	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
out	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
five	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wernel	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
Mann	O
and	O
Udal	O
,	O
Mann	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
one	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Udal	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
Mann	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
granted	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
Directions	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Man	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
.	O
He	O
refused	O
to	O
produce	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Thorn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
described	O
it	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Tortois-shell	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
was	O
broke	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Thorn	O
immediately	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
unless	O
we	O
paid	O
twelve	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
Shillings	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
hang	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
several	O
Times	O
before	O
,	O
his	O
Request	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Mann	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
put	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
more	O
into	O
his	O
Information	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Mann	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Thorn	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
He	O
threatened	O
me	O
;	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
long	O
Causeway	O
.	O
Udal	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
Debtors	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
Prison	O
;	O
we	O
broke	O
out	O
and	O
made	O
our	O
Escape	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
done	O
this	O
for	O
Lucre	O
,	O
-	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
may	O
clear	O
himself	O
of	O
his	O
Debt	O
.	O
Mann	O
.	O
Udal	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Goal	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Key	I-pers
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
urged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crockat	O
.	O
Crockat	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Profession	O
was	O
a	O
most	O
scandalous	O
one	O
;	O
That	O
Pawnbrokers	O
were	O
the	O
Encouragers	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
well	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
warned	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
honester	O
Callings	O
and	O
Employments	O
.	O
Crockat	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
were	O
bound	O
for	O
Key	O
's	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
and	O
Appearance	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Dec.	O
26	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Finchley	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
the	O
Halfway	O
House	O
and	O
Upper	B-place
Holloway	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
jumbled	O
hard	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
fudled	O
.	O
I	O
pushed	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
upon	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
-	O
you	O
're	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
-	O
you	O
're	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
both	O
attacked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Five	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
Mann	O
[	O
the	O
Evidence	O
]	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
my	O
Coat	O
.	O
Mann	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Holloway	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
this	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
attacked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
pull	O
your	O
Coat	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
(	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
him	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
up	O
his	O
Hanger	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
chop	O
the	O
Man	O
down	O
.	O
We	O
pawned	O
the	O
Coat	O
for	O
three	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Bradford	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbroker	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
four	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mann	O
,	O
Then	O
he	O
cheated	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Bradford	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Watch	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
's	O
Direction	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
cautioned	O
in	O
a	O
pathetick	O
Manner	O
,	O
against	O
following	O
those	O
Courses	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
inevitably	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
melancholy	O
End	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
on	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
144	O
,	O
145.	O
John	B-pers
Maud	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
146.	O
John	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fife	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
or	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Muad	O
and	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Leicester-Fields	O
,	O
Piccadily	O
,	O
and	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
near	O
Carnaby	O
Market	O
.	O
In	O
Broad-street	B-place
we	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Starkey	O
's	O
Door	O
open	O
.	O
Maud	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
;	O
turned	O
the	O
Brass	O
Nob	O
of	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Tankard	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
about	O
Dusk	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Maud	O
came	O
running	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Blew	O
Apron	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
all	O
run	O
away	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
down	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Brady	O
;	O
but	O
Brady	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
while	O
We	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Bargain	O
made	O
;	O
Brady	O
bid	O
two	O
Guineas	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
three	O
Pounds	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
to	O
Fletcher	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
eighteen	O
Shillings	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Starkey	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Fife	O
.	O
We	O
stole	O
it	O
about	O
the	O
4th	O
or	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Starkey	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Value	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Pounds	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
this	O
Discovery	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Maud	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Years	O
.	O
His	O
Mother	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
carefully	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
tempted	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
Thing	O
by	O
Fife	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
met	O
in	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
All	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
147	O
,	O
148.	O
James	B-pers
Lawlor	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lawley	B-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Lines	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s	O
.	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
George	O
Lines	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
Denmark	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
upon	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
Lawlor	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
Gun	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
so	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
struck	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
They	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
as	O
dead	O
as	O
a	O
Herring	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
Gun	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
Lawlor	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
Lawlor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
in	O
your	O
Life	O
?	O
Lines	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Lawlor	O
.	O
As	O
God	O
is	O
my	O
Judge	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Lines	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
Lawlor	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
Lot	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Lawlor	O
,	O
and	O
Leonard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
a	O
thieving	O
together	O
,	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Lawler	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
gone	O
a	O
thieving	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Man	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
beside	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
while	O
Leonard	O
watched	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
between	O
us	O
four	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
wanting	O
Money	O
,	O
we	O
said	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Coal	O
Yard	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
this	O
Man	O
with	O
his	O
Gun	O
Lawlor	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
,	O
What	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Stock	O
of	O
the	O
Pistol	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
down	O
I	O
held	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
Blow	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
Gun	O
was	O
seized	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
fourth	O
Man	O
in	O
our	O
Company	O
,	O
was	O
Noland	O
;	O
and	O
Leonard	O
was	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
cry	O
Tommy	O
!	O
Tommy	O
!	O
when	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
by	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
calling	O
out	O
Tommy	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
and	O
Gun	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
Time	O
to	O
rifle	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
Lawlor	O
pawned	O
the	O
Wig	O
for	O
six	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
Hat	O
for	O
three	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
both	O
pawned	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
Leonard	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
if	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
,	O
the	O
Folks	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
Suspicion	O
[	O
Opinio	O
]	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Hat	O
was	O
pawned	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
Time	O
,	O
we	O
pawned	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
Leonard	O
staid	O
at	O
Home	O
in	O
Lawlor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
was	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
divided	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Shillings	O
and	O
three	O
Pence	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
a	O
Judge	O
for	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
-	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Lines	O
's	O
Hat	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
new	O
Loop	O
put	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Wig	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
Sunday	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
without	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
twenty	O
Times	O
to	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
them	O
both	O
on	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
without	O
either	O
.	O
Lines	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
Cavenagh	O
brought	O
the	O
Hat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
three	O
Shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Lawlor	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
six	O
Shillings	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
fetch	O
it	O
again	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
them	O
both	O
very	O
honest	O
Men	O
.	O
Lawlor	O
.	O
Ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
if	O
he	O
knows	O
James	O
Lawlor	O
?	O
The	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
justly	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
[	O
pointing	O
to	O
Lawlor	O
,	O
]	O
is	O
like	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Wig	O
said	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
James	O
Lawlor	O
.	O
Lawlor	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
likely	O
I	O
should	O
pawn	O
a	O
Thing	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Name	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Lines	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
?	O
Lines	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
wanted	O
a	O
Gun	O
for	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
for	O
the	O
Price	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
Lawlor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Call	O
Garret	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
.	O
Garret	O
Cavenagh	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Lawlor	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
honestly	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
no	O
Way	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Bread	O
but	O
by	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Labour	O
of	O
his	O
Hands	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Buckland	O
.	O
He	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
upwards	O
of	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
,	O
by	O
Bridgewater-Square	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lambeth	O
.	O
Leonard	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Christmas-Day	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
tore	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
all	O
Day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lines	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
on	O
St.	O
Stephen	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
Treat	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Leonard	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Day	O
after	O
Christmas	O
Day	O
,	O
Lines	O
came	O
into	O
Lambeth	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
and	O
Gun	O
,	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
close	O
Set-to	O
Coat	O
.	O
Leonard	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Lines	O
would	O
have	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Leonard	O
refus	O
'd	O
:	O
Lines	O
told	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
Leonard	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
labouring	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
149.	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
and	O
stealing	O
148	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Colley	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Hugh	O
Colley	O
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
The	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Colley	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mile-end	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
Cough	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
We	O
imagin	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
somebody	O
going	O
past	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
Cough	O
repeated	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
imagin	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
little	O
fore	O
Garden	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Immediately	O
following	O
the	O
Coughs	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
upon	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Roof	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
shook	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Hall	O
,	O
Immediately	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
(	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
(	O
my	O
Writing-master	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
forwards	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
discover	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
Evan	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
went	O
out	O
backwards	O
;	O
Afterwards	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
like	O
breaking	O
open	O
Doors	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Consternation	O
,	O
and	O
imagin	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Rogues	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
Possession	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
against	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Passage	O
,	O
which	O
led	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
lie	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
!	O
Murder	O
!	O
Davis	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
almost	O
dead	O
with	O
Fear	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Maid	O
in	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
running	O
from	O
one	O
Room	O
to	O
another	O
in	O
their	O
Shirts	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
encouraged	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
and	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
Davis	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Man	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
deceived	O
Davis	O
,	O
by	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
Thieves	O
!	O
without	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
we	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
so	O
Davis	O
at	O
first	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
Lee	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Mistake	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
then	O
Trowsers	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
back	O
Pales	O
,	O
the	O
Tenter-hooks	O
catched	O
in	O
his	O
Trowsers	O
;	O
there	O
Davis	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
engaged	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Owen	O
,	O
and	O
Lee	O
,	O
were	O
examining	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Hammer	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
dispatch	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
through	O
a	O
Window	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
Entrance	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Colley	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Garret	O
Window	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
jump	O
in	O
That	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
hearing	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
into	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
!	O
Evan	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
his	O
Fellow-servant	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
(	O
Davis	O
)	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Garret	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Glass	O
tumble	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Back-yard	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
towards	O
'Squire	O
Heath	O
's	O
Pales	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
Coat	O
upon	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
Witness	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
over	O
them	O
into	O
another	O
Garden	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
hung	O
upon	O
the	O
Tenter-hooks	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
getting	O
over	O
a	O
Brick-wall	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Witness	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Accounts	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
Circumstance	O
therein	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
Davis	O
was	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Witness	O
)	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
Davis	O
in	O
bringing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
crooked	O
Nails	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
murder	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
parting	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
near	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Colley	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
hard	O
at	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
gave	O
a	O
slight	O
Cough	O
,	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Witness	O
)	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
listen	O
'd	O
:	O
That	O
hearing	O
his	O
Foot	O
stop	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
Sudden	O
,	O
he	O
partly	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Colley	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
cough	O
again	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Colley	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
up	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Colley	O
's	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
were	O
Thieves	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
their	O
House	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Colley	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Colley	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Davis	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Witness	O
ran	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Colley	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
what	O
Lead	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
discover	O
'd	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lion	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Nails	O
and	O
a	O
Clasp	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Bean	O
(	O
Watchman	O
)	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
,	O
two	O
Women	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Gin	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
mumbled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
mn	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
left	O
his	O
Hammer	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
Davis	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Colley	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Rails	O
of	O
the	O
Cage	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
accidentally	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
Eaves	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
drop	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Back-door	O
open	O
,	O
ran	O
in	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
Thieves	O
!	O
two	O
Men	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rogues	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
150.	O
Ashby	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
about	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edlin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
John	O
Edlin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
Brian	O
at	O
Loxley	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Harrow	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
sometime	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Four	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
:	O
A	O
Quarry	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
through	O
which	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
unhasped	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Hall	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
of	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Calicoe	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
Things	O
at	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Ganford	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
prove	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
great	O
Coat	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
the	O
Shift	O
belongs	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
Richard	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
great	O
Coat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
binding	O
Hay	O
in	O
the	O
Barn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Boots	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Thompson	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Plush	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Thompson	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
likewise	O
a	O
Plush	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
strip	O
'd	O
Dimity	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Henry	O
Rudd	O
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
A	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
guess	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
the	O
three	O
Men	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
Ealing	O
,	O
two	O
Miles	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Harrow	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Boots	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Plush	O
Coat	O
we	O
ca	O
n't	O
find	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
Boots	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
sell	O
the	O
Man	O
the	O
Boots	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
151	O
,	O
152	O
,	O
153.	O
Edward	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
,	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twenty-four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s	O
.	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
William	O
Mumford	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
fasten	O
'd	O
my	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
rose	O
at	O
Six	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
House	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
twenty-four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
gone	O
:	O
The	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
four	O
Bolts	O
were	O
broke	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
here	O
;	O
this	O
large	O
Pair	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Girls	O
Pumps	O
,	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
2	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
have	O
rubb	O
'd	O
the	O
Marks	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
.	O
Campbel	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
but	O
fourteen	O
Pairs	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
twenty-four	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
number	O
my	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Mumford	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
There	O
are	O
eight	O
Rooms	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Last	O
Valentine	O
's	O
Day	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Nan	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
about	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
The	O
two	O
Women	O
had	O
their	O
Aprons	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
early	O
?	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Birds	O
couple	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
gather	O
Chickweed	O
.	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
put	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Shoes	O
into	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
convey	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
hers	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
Notice	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
would	O
raise	O
some	O
Money	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
share	O
it	O
between	O
themselves	O
I	O
hid	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
Campbel	O
and	O
Booth	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
damn	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
the	O
Shoes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
lick	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
black	O
Eyes	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
Booth	O
and	O
her	O
Sister	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
Pair	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
this	O
Campbel	O
and	O
Booth	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
both	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
a	O
Breeches-maker	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
their	O
Hearing	O
)	O
that	O
Mumford	O
's	O
Shop	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Shoes	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
(	O
Saturday	O
)	O
Booth	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Shoes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
them	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Mumford	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
speaking	O
,	O
-	O
in	O
came	O
Campbel	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
Booth	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Mumford	O
's	O
Shoes	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
Push	O
off	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
away	O
he	O
went	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
(	O
Booth	O
)	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Shoes	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
-	O
yes	O
.	O
Then	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
she	O
)	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
Mumford	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mumford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
Men	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
Aprons	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
open	O
'd	O
their	O
Laps	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
't	O
was	O
fine	O
Chickweed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Campbel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
me	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
-	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Woman	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
more	O
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Mercer	O
;	O
Campbel	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
fourteen	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
cheated	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
were	O
there	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
innocent	O
in	O
the	O
Affair	O
.	O
Campbel	O
.	O
This	O
Martha	O
Clark	O
owes	O
me	O
a	O
Grudge	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
paid	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
and	O
Addey	O
the	O
Thief-Taker	O
have	O
collogu	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Booth	O
.	O
This	O
Lewis	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
see	O
Him	O
,	O
about	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Between	O
Five	O
and	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
we	O
called	O
at	O
this	O
Clark	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
There	O
we	O
found	O
Campbel	O
and	O
Lewis	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Aprons	O
full	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
gave	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
Clark	O
it	O
was	O
Chickweed	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Pints	O
of	O
Gin	O
among	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
they	O
called	O
us	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
Campbel	O
told	O
me	O
-	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
helping	O
him	O
off	O
with	O
those	O
Goods	O
.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
About	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
Words	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
Booth	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
Campbel	O
at	O
Clark	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Mumford	O
.	O
When	O
Booth	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
said	O
Campbel	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Lewis	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
their	O
Aprons	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
Campbel	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
That	O
Lewis	O
's	O
Husband	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
He	O
and	O
Lewis	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
carrying	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
.	O
Campbel	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
it	O
probable	O
that	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
Share	O
of	O
so	O
many	O
Half-pints	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
House	O
!	O
It	O
takes	O
up	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Time	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
.	O
Campbel	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Booth	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Lewis	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Booth	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
154.	O
Peregrine	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Mawley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
value	O
3	O
s	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
William	O
Mawley	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
Rosemary-Lane	B-place
,	O
last	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
was	O
Se'en-night	O
,	O
between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
He	O
walked-up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
me	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
,	O
mumbling	O
something	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
which	O
surprized	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Shilling	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
?	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
brisk	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
loose	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
getting	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
into	O
Justice	O
Riccards	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
all	O
the	O
People	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Colour	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
-	O
a	O
White	O
Loose	O
Coat	O
;	O
a	O
blew	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
speckled	O
Shirt	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Scar	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
minded	O
on	O
which	O
Side	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
we	O
took	O
in	O
Justice	O
Riccards	O
's	O
Garden	O
,	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'en-night	O
,	O
between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Riccards	O
's	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Mawley	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
our	O
Men	O
were	O
standing	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
Mawley	O
)	O
picked	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Coat	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
;	O
a	O
Blew	O
Jacket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
.	O
The	O
Hat	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wig	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
Mawley	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Riccards	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
there	O
were	O
Thieves	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
picked	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
Twenty	O
or	O
Thirty	O
People	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
Last	O
Sunday	O
Se'en-night	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
being	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
too-strong	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Maudley	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
picked	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
People	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Officer	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Custody	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
bare-headed	O
,	O
with	O
only	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Glass	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Maid	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
Thieves	O
in	O
the	O
Glass	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
only	O
playing	O
the	O
Rogue	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Riccards	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
:	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
poked	O
about	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
People	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Justice	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
155.	O
James	B-pers
Grimson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Grimshaw	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buck	O
skin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
five	O
Shirts	O
,	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
four	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
Pounds	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bridley	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
John	O
Ridley	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Stable	O
joins	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
that	O
goes	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
my	O
Chamber	O
.	O
This	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
must	O
be	O
broke	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Chamber-Door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
about	O
my	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
'till	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
lock	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Iron	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	O
Lane	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
seven	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Frock	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buck-skin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
from	O
that	O
Time	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Shirts	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
taking	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
his	O
taking	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
he	O
forced	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
with	O
this	O
Iron	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Were	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
you	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
Ridley	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
-	O
The	O
Shirts	O
were	O
all	O
numbered	O
and	O
marked	O
with	O
I.	O
R.	O
They	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Possession	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
here	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Basiere	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
a	O
Week	O
and	O
two	O
Days	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tye	O
up	O
four	O
Shirts	O
in	O
a	O
Napkin	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
without	O
looking	O
for	O
any	O
Marks	O
,	O
either	O
good	O
or	O
bad	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
upon	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
likewise	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
these	O
Things	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
Linnen	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Ridley	O
owned	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
searched	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
)	O
Back	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Ridley	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
he	O
claimed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
home	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
twice	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
A	O
Coachman	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behaved	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Bury	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
break	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
with	O
that	O
Iron	O
?	O
Ridley	O
.	O
He	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Stable	O
Door	O
was	O
a	O
strong	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bent	O
the	O
Staple	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
forced	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
lock	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
Stock-lock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
:	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
apprehend	O
)	O
he	O
came	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fastened	O
on	O
the	O
Inside	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Pin	O
;	O
for	O
those	O
Doors	O
were	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pin	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Shirts	O
were	O
,	O
-	O
all	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
-	O
every	O
one	O
,	O
-	O
all	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Breeches	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Breeches	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shirts	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
*	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
*	O
Burglary	O
is	O
breaking	O
into	O
an	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Felonious	O
Intent	O
.	O
In	O
Law	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
Night	O
when	O
one	O
Person	O
's	O
Face	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
distinguished	O
from	O
another	O
;	O
Now	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Confession	O
own	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Offence	O
charged	O
as	O
Burglary	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
committed	O
before	O
Night	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
156.	O
Abel	B-pers
Bum	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Burn	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Peartree	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
157.	O
Grace	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
158.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
159.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Postewait	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Starch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barefoot	I-pers
and	O
Company	B-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
Feb.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
160.	O
Barnard	B-pers
Mackennes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Jointing	O
Plane	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Kingscot	I-pers
;	O
and	O
thirty	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Iron	O
Back	O
Hoops	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rosswell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
No	O
one	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
161.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
outside	O
and	O
inside	O
Cases	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Chain	O
made	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Base	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cheveney	I-pers
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
Cheveny	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Club	O
,	O
at	O
The	O
Black	O
Hog	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
King-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Master	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
treat	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
it	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
treat	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
treat	O
next	O
.	O
Upon	O
these	O
Conditions	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Stark	O
,	O
in	O
King	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
spent	O
three	O
Pence	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
me	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
we	O
stood	O
talking	O
together	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Time	O
she	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
in	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Door	O
opened	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
opened	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
them	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
beside	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
of	O
these	O
Women	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
search	O
the	O
House	O
without	O
a	O
Warrant	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
telling	O
us	O
we	O
might	O
search	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
Warrant	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
for	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
.	O
Before	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
felt	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Cheveny	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Watch	O
in	O
Pawn	O
'till	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Shilling	O
or	O
two	O
'till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
mn	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
Pawn	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
five	O
Minutes	O
:	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
-	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
the	O
Bitch	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
but	O
they	O
found	O
no	O
Watch	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
confined	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
-	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
carry	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
the	O
Window-shutter	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
accordingly	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
between	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
Sacking	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
in	O
Cabbage-Lane	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Watch	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
.	O
Stark	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
remember	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
brought	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Watch	O
which	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Stark	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Cheveny	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Stark	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
Watch	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
Two-pence	O
Halfpenny	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
a	O
Stranger	O
any	O
where	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Stark	O
's	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
drank	O
of	O
the	O
Beer	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
sit	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
162.	O
Johannah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Rug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
not	O
appearing	O
when	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
163	O
,	O
164.	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gresham	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cealey	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Court	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
Twopence	O
Halfpenny	O
in	O
Copper	O
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cealey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
Side	O
Hanging-Sword	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
-	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
Nan	O
Price	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Gresham	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
their	O
Fists	O
;	O
-	O
they	O
struck	O
me	O
under	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
'em	O
black	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
-	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
Twopence	O
Halfpenny	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
charged	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
away	O
too	O
.	O
-The	O
Element	O
was	O
thick	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
between	O
Dark	O
and	O
Light	O
;	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
middling	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
marry	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
House-keeper	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
swear	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
That	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
White	O
Lyon	O
Court	O
?	O
Cealey	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
gone	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
below	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Hall	O
.	O
-	O
'T	O
was	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Calendar	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
)	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
old	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
uppermost	O
House	O
in	O
White	O
Lyon	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Watchman	O
have	O
made	O
them	O
open	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
gave	O
Price	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
*	O
*	O
Cealey	O
swore	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
Salter	O
to	O
a	O
Private	O
Stealing	O
;	O
this	O
Indictment	O
was	O
laid	O
for	O
a	O
Street	O
Robbery	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
been	O
convicted	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
intitled	O
to	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
280l	O
.	O
165.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
wicked	O
and	O
evil	O
Disposition	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
by	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
offensive	O
Weapon	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
an	O
Iron	O
Hammer	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lynnel	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
their	O
Money	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
John	O
Dew	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lynnel	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Mother	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
after	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Fleet	O
ditch	O
we	O
took	O
Coach	O
to	O
carry	O
us	O
to	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
Hill	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
South	O
Side	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
)	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
Stop	O
!	O
stop	O
!	O
but	O
the	O
Coachman	O
drove	O
on	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
Coach-door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
-	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Coach	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach-door	O
and	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Lynnel	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
slipp	O
'd	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
Horses	O
Heads	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
door	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
mn	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
!	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
here	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Hammer	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
:	O
But	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
happening	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
assisted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
'till	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Peruke	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Hammer	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
beg	O
'd	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Wig	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
)	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
accordingly	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
his	O
Design	O
was	O
to	O
rob	O
us	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
stopping	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Red	B-place
Lion	I-place
Court	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
South	O
Side	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
-	O
Thieves	O
!	O
-	O
Murder	O
!	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
and	O
pok	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Hammer	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
this	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lynnel	I-pers
gave	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Dew	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
only	O
adding	O
,	O
-	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
Hammer	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Pistol	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
.	O
the	O
Coachman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
by	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
Stop	O
!	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
between	O
Seven	O
and	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
-	O
Murder	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Dew	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
the	O
Posts	O
and	O
the	O
Houses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Where	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
?	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
disengaged	O
himself	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
(	O
What	O
will	O
nobody	O
assist	O
in	O
taking	O
a	O
Street	O
Robber	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Paul	O
's	O
Churchyard	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Knife	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
Coachmen	O
seldom	O
go	O
without	O
Knives	O
about	O
us	O
.	O
Three	O
Witnesses	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
166.	O
David	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
according	O
to	O
due	O
Form	O
of	O
Law	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Allhallows	O
Barkin	O
,	O
13	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Rogers	O
was	O
according	O
to	O
due	O
Form	O
of	O
Law	O
try	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
empannel	O
'd	O
between	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Rogers	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Jury	O
convicted	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
the	O
Record	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
doth	O
more	O
fully	O
appear	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Jurors	O
now	O
farther	O
present	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Adamson	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
13	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Rogers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
some	O
Tobacco	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Rogues	O
,	O
-	O
some	O
from	O
the	O
Tops	O
of	O
the	O
Hogsheads	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hogsheads	O
,	O
-	O
where	O
we	O
can	O
light	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Rogers	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
taking	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
this	O
13	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
we	O
took	O
:	O
we	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
David	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
:	O
He	O
lives	O
two	O
Doors	O
beyond	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
in	O
Petticoat	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Hand	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Adamson	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
then	O
had	O
not	O
Silver	O
enough	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
desiring	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
Notice	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
chang	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
us	O
.	O
Rogers	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
us	O
for	O
13	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
Part	O
of	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
Sort	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
might	O
this	O
be	O
?	O
Keys	O
.	O
Merchants	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
-	O
good	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
enquired	O
into	O
the	O
Worth	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
sometimes	O
we	O
got	O
Threepence	O
,	O
-	O
sometimes	O
a	O
Groat	O
a	O
Pound	O
:	O
What	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Worth	O
of	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
but	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
-	O
for	O
13	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Thursday	O
in	O
Christmas	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
the	O
whole	O
Truth	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
our	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
sometimes	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
,	O
before	O
People	O
were	O
stirring	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
Opportunity	O
.	O
Rogers	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
steal	O
this	O
Tobacco	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
:	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stoln	O
;	O
-	O
and	O
he	O
stole	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
Whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
?	O
Keys	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
several	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
.	O
He	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
Why	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
bad	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
we	O
ca	O
n't	O
make	O
it	O
better	O
than	O
it	O
is	O
-	O
't	O
is	O
such	O
as	O
we	O
can	O
get	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
this	O
very	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
stolen	O
?	O
Keys	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
this	O
very	O
13	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
-	O
and	O
every	O
Bit	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
we	O
sold	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
sold	O
him	O
Tobacco	O
very	O
frequently	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
large	O
Quantities	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crosier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-House	O
Key	O
.	O
My	O
Business	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
lurking	O
Fellows	O
,	O
who	O
steal	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
at	O
Adamson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
the	O
Surveyor	O
;	O
Keys	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Adamson	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
see	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Pilferers	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
go	O
in	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hanbury	O
's	O
Watchman	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
seiz	O
'd	O
in	O
Adamson	O
's	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
of	O
different	O
Sorts	O
,	O
in	O
several	O
Parts	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
some	O
Oroonoko	O
,	O
some	O
Sweet-scented	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
in	O
small	O
Quantities	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
little	O
Snuff-Shop	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
Parcel	O
of	O
different	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
Rogers	O
and	O
Keys	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
Account	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Rogers	O
and	O
Keys	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
tell	O
all	O
they	O
knew	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
People	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
Tobacco	O
of	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
bought	O
this	O
13	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Rogers	O
and	O
Keys	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Parcels	O
of	O
them	O
beside	O
this	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
several	O
People	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
this	O
Tobacco	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
?	O
Crosier	O
.	O
Some	O
Tobacco	O
is	O
better	O
than	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
none	O
can	O
be	O
bought	O
for	O
the	O
Price	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Duty	O
upon	O
it	O
is	O
Five	O
Pence	O
Farthing	O
,	O
or	O
Five	O
Pence	O
Half-penny	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
3000	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
stolen	O
Tobacco	O
from	O
other	O
People	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
forty	O
People	O
now	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
desired	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
wrought	O
about	O
a	O
Twelve-month	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
:	O
And	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
That	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
deal	O
in	O
this	O
Way	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sometimes	O
made	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Snuff	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
And	O
how	O
much	O
Tobacco	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
making	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Snuff	O
?	O
Lindsay	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
that	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
made	O
of	O
Scuts	O
Roll	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
bought	O
Roll	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Campell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Nine	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
come	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
about	O
Three	O
.	O
I	O
served	O
often	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
such	O
Persons	O
come	O
there	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Might	O
he	O
not	O
buy	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
did	O
-	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
He	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Gates	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cootes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
buy	O
sometimes	O
more	O
,	O
sometimes	O
less	O
;	O
-	O
sometimes	O
he	O
'd	O
buy	O
a	O
Roll	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
-	O
sometimes	O
a	O
Cask	O
of	O
Snuff	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
he	O
'd	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Parcel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
Six	O
or	O
Seven	O
Years	O
,	O
full	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
came	O
down	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
bought	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
Roll	O
Tobacco	O
from	O
Scotland	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
sell	O
him	O
any	O
Leaf	O
Tobacco	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Cootes	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foresight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Character	O
is	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
buys	O
his	O
Goods	O
honourably	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Snuff-Maker	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
And	O
do	O
you	O
buy	O
your	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
Small	O
Quantities	O
?	O
Foresight	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
buy	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
now	O
:	O
'T	O
is	O
not	O
usual	O
to	O
buy	O
in	O
small	O
Quantities	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
much	O
Money	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
buy	O
what	O
we	O
can	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
a	O
Shilling	O
's	O
Worth	O
myself	O
,	O
-	O
a	O
Man	O
can	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
his	O
Stock	O
will	O
bear	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Buchanan	O
,	O
a	O
Tobacco-Merchant	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
bought	O
small	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Tobacconist	O
and	O
Snuff-Maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Twelve	O
or	O
Fourteen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
fair	O
Dealer	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
Snuff-Man	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Horner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Catchpole	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
167.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
in	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Case	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Kidd	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
1734	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
168.	O
George	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Kidd	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
169.	O
John	B-pers
Birkenhead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Perukes	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
sundry	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Banjan	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Bason	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
material	O
Witness	O
(	O
George	B-pers
Sherrow	I-pers
)	O
not	O
appearing	O
when	O
called	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Shoe	O
Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Knee-Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
Iron	O
japan	O
'd	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Nutmeg	O
graters	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
Iron	O
Cork-Screws	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
though	O
often	O
called	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Recognizances	O
were	O
estreated	O
,	O
by	O
special	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
170.	O
Mary	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthias	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Recognizances	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
171.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Conyer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Copper	O
Sauce-Pans	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Counterpane	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodging	O
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Aris	I-pers
,	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
their	O
Recognizances	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
172.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Loaf	O
Sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
And	O
173.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
Feb.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
likewise	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
174.	O
Ann	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Clogs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
175	O
.	O
176.	O
Isabell	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
val.6d	O
.	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
val	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Bolster	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
177.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Karrel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Whiffin	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
21	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
178.	O
Richard	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Hats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pomeroy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
Pomeroy	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
three	O
Hats	O
,	O
this	O
Day	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
these	O
People	O
,	O
(	O
Keeble	O
,	O
Crocket	O
,	O
and	O
Huddle	O
)	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
,	O
and	O
Huddle	O
told	O
we	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Hats	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
now	O
keeps	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Huddle	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
mentions	O
,	O
we	O
stole	O
three	O
Hats	O
off	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Shutters	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
reach	O
'd	O
over	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
179.	O
Richard	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Check	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
value	O
at	O
4	O
l.	O
Huddle	O
.	O
Dick	O
Keeble	O
and	O
I	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
:	O
He	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
a	O
spiked	O
Hatch	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
three	O
Rolls	O
of	O
white	O
Cloth	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Roll	O
of	O
Check	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
sold	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
in	O
my	O
Information	O
.	O
That	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
first	O
brought	O
me	O
under	O
these	O
Misfortunes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
did	O
we	O
commit	O
this	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Huddle	O
.	O
Between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
After	O
noon	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
New	O
Prion	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
who	O
cries	O
Earthen	O
Ware	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
?	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
Robbery	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Keeble	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
there	O
too	O
.	O
Huddle	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
-	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
trouble	O
yourself	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
hang	O
an	O
hundred	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
swear	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
,	O
before	O
either	O
he	O
or	O
you	O
shall	O
suffer	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Custody	O
in	O
Newgate	O
herself	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
Maddox	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
180	O
.	O
181.	O
Richard	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Crockat	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
)	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
my	O
Shop	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sashes	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
were	O
shut	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
myself	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Hand	O
take	O
out	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Linen	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Thief	O
was	O
got	O
off	O
with	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
,	O
nor	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
'till	O
Huddle	O
made	O
his	O
Information	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
Huddle	O
said	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
robbing	O
me	O
.	O
Huddle	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
New	B-place
Gravel	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
we	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
this	O
Man	O
's	O
Shop-window	O
.	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
Roll	O
of	O
Check	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
us	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Mrs.	O
Turner	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
Crockat	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
shar	O
'd	O
it	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Keeble	O
.	O
Whereabout	O
did	O
I	O
stand	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
Linnen	O
?	O
Huddle	O
.	O
Keeble	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Steps	O
at	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
,	O
and	O
Crockat	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Post	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Steps	O
.	O
Keeble	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
parted	O
?	O
Huddle	O
.	O
At	O
Mrs.	O
Turner	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
we	O
turn	O
'd	O
our	O
Backs	O
upon	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
check	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
Crockat	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
generally	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
all	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
Gloves	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
brought	O
this	O
Linnen	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Higgens	I-pers
had	O
known	O
Crockat	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Riles	I-pers
had	O
known	O
Crockat	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
trusted	O
wich	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Hundred	O
thousand	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
182	O
.	O
183	O
.	O
184.	O
George	B-pers
Haggis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
GOD	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
on	O
Sarah	B-pers
Main	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
did	O
carnally	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
abuse	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
And	O
Richard	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
was	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
feloniously	O
were	O
present	O
helping	O
,	O
comforting	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Haggis	O
,	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Rape	O
to	O
commit	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Main	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
New	B-place
'Change	I-place
,	O
in	O
Rag-fair	B-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
single	O
Woman	O
,	O
-	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
;	O
she	O
blacks	O
Shoes	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
others	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
a-piece	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Pipe	O
,	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
beg	O
a	O
little	O
Bit	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
George	O
Haggis	O
[	O
the	O
Butcher	O
,	O
]	O
Keeble	O
and	O
Gibbons	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Seven	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
Haggis	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
B	O
-	O
ch	O
,	O
(	O
said	O
he	O
)	O
you	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
[	O
in	O
order	O
]	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
New	O
'Change	O
.	O
The	O
New	O
'Change	O
is	O
a	O
Place	O
like	O
a	O
Square	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
People	O
bring	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
them	O
down	O
for	O
Sale	O
.	O
He	O
overtook	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Pump	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
'Change	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
my	O
Gown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gathers	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
impudent	O
with	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Witness	O
here	O
gave	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
beastly	O
Behaviour	O
of	O
Haggis	O
in	O
this	O
Place	O
.	O
]	O
But	O
somebody	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
desisted	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
my	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
Landlady	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
Landlady	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
big	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
Ground	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Night	O
.	O
When	O
Haggis	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
six	O
other	O
Fellows	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
among	O
whom	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Keeble	O
,	O
Gibbons	O
(	O
the	O
Barber	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fidler	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
no	O
sooner	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Closet	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
Keeble	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
who	O
abused	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
)	O
Then	O
they	O
blew	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
blow	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
this	O
they	O
did	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
:	O
[	O
The	O
Witness	O
express	O
'd	O
herself	O
here	O
in	O
Terms	O
necessary	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
such	O
an	O
unparallel	O
'd	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Abuse	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Gibbons	O
's	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
as	O
would	O
be	O
shocking	O
to	O
every	O
chaste	O
Ear	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
but	O
Haggis	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
his	O
Knife	O
into	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
did	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
abused	O
me	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Men	O
laughed	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
beat	O
the	O
B	O
-	O
ch	O
,	O
beat	O
the	O
B	O
-	O
ch	O
,	O
make	O
her	O
be	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
Gibbons	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
Haggis	O
was	O
abusing	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Gibbons	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
Keeble	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Condition	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
burnt	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Fidler	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
present	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
play	O
'd	O
several	O
Tunes	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
Landlady	O
came	O
in	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
Complaint	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
Fear	O
of	O
having	O
her	O
Brains	O
dash	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
complain	O
'd	O
likewise	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
:	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Men	O
left	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
for	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Maxim	O
,	O
[	O
Geneva	O
,	O
]	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
alone	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Friends	O
these	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
give	O
this	O
Woman	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
lie	O
there	O
:	O
Her	O
Name	O
is	O
Pegey	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
sometime	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
People	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
served	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
