TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
Country	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
M.DCC.XL	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
SALTER	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
COMYN	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FORTESCUE	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pardoe	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Say	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bold	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Lemmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mackay	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Mold	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littlewood	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	O
Symson	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coker	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Knightsbridge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
434	O
.	O
+	O
Susannah	B-pers
Kellow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
5	O
brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
Coffee-Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	O
Brooks	O
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
Charles	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Green-Arbour-Court	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Little	B-place
Old-Bailey	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
Things	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
offered	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Directions	O
,	O
from	O
another	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
double	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
Home	O
at	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Key	O
turn	O
'd	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
flew	O
open	O
.	O
Upon	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sarney	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecuter	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Thief	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
given	O
into	O
my	O
Custody	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
435	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quart	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
;	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
Jonathan	O
Gladman	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Anchor-Alehouse	B-place
in	I-place
White-Friars	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
need	O
not	O
thank	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
Custom	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Rain	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
dress	O
her	O
a	O
Pigeon	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
three	O
Minutes	O
but	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Quart	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
Bedstead	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
laid	O
her	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Stick	O
down	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
enquired	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
directed	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
up	O
Glass-house-Alley	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Night	O
following	O
,	O
Mr	O
Gosling	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Fore-Room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
through	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
stopped	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
that	O
sells	O
Stockings	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I.	O
Gladman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Tankard	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
answered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Description	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Trigg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
in	O
the	O
Fore-Room	O
,	O
when	O
Mrs	O
Gladman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
positive	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
when	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
Mr	O
Gladman	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
promised	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mrs	O
Gladman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
;	O
the	O
Stocking-Man	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
2	O
Tankards	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
stood	O
talking	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
People	O
there	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
Man	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
436.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
October	O
9th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
437.	O
Edward	B-pers
Trevor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Freehold	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Father	O
in	O
God	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Rochester	I-pers
,	O
Dean	O
of	O
St	O
Peter	O
's	O
Westminster	O
;	O
and	O
Edmund	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
London	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Dean	O
of	O
the	O
Chapel-Royal	O
.	O
August	O
31	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Falconer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
Stone	O
or	O
2	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
Lead	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
How	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
Friend	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Brown	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Alms-houses	O
near	O
the	O
Blue-Coat	O
School	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
(	O
Falconer	O
)	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Lead	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
one	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Ford	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Lead	O
from	O
the	O
Alms-houses	O
,	O
rolled	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
behind	O
the	O
School	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
him	O
this	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
forward	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
Men	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
never	O
could	O
take	O
them	O
:	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
Lead	O
stole	O
from	O
the	O
Alms-houses	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
this	O
Lead	O
match	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
from	O
.	O
Mr	O
Ilsley	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Alms-houses	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Dean	O
of	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dean	O
of	O
the	O
Chapel-Royal	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
Deans	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
Estate	O
of	O
52	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
Fee-Farm	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
Will	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1682	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Alms-houses	O
were	O
left	O
under	O
their	O
Direction	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Will	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
438	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Castor	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
1	O
Callimancoe	O
Waistcoat	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
September	O
29th	O
.	O
Charles	O
Steward	O
.	O
On	O
Michaelmas	O
Day	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Hatch	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turning	O
up	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
Coming	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
under	O
a	O
Gateway	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
went	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
scower	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
all	O
on	O
that	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Castor	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Albermarle-Street	O
,	O
almost	O
out	O
of	O
Breath	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Castor	O
we	O
found	O
concealed	O
between	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
his	O
Skin	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Lad	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
439.	O
William	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Turnover	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
September	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
440	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
William	O
Phillips	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Craven-Buildings	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
take	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
linnen	O
Cloth	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
which	O
Way	O
he	O
ran	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
coat	O
on	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
dropped	O
within	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
my	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
this	O
Man	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
by	O
his	O
coat	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
441	O
.	O
+	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
inside	O
Work	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
Theophilus	O
Swift	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
St	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-Yard	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
insulted	O
,	O
or	O
assaulted	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
jostled	O
me	O
almost	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
recover	O
myself	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
Villain	O
has	O
stole	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
Cannon-Alley	O
,	O
into	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head-Alley	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
lying	O
within	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
'till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
that	O
declares	O
itself	O
,	O
otherwise	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
missed	O
the	O
Watch	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Hand	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
Circumstances	O
is	O
he	O
sure	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
I	O
pursued	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
come	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
Way	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
against	O
Swift	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Villain	O
is	O
gone	O
with	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
through	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
Way	O
up	O
another	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
over	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Steps	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
Fall	O
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
not	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
I	O
took	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
probable	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
throw	O
the	O
Watch	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
so	O
close	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Force	O
of	O
the	O
Fall	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
might	O
fly	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen's-Head-Alley	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
fall	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
lying	O
within	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Way	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
together	O
;	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
jostled	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
up	O
this	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Reverent	O
Mr	O
James	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
24	O
,	O
or	O
25	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
Action	O
done	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
no	O
Trade	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
bred	O
a	O
Scholar	O
,	O
in	O
Writing	O
and	O
Book-keeping	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
His	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
by	O
Writing	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bracken	I-pers
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
had	O
known	O
him	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
to	O
write	O
for	O
the	O
Keeper	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
honest	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
442	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Ed	B-place
.	I-place
monton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Finch	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
9	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Warming-Pan	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Scales	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot-lid	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
October	O
7	O
.	O
William	O
Finch	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Southgate	B-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
at	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
every	O
Thing	O
was	O
then	O
safe	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
at	O
5	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
broke	O
under	O
the	O
Dresser	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Seabrooke	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Coates	O
,	O
went	O
from	O
London	O
on	O
Monday	O
7-night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
disappointed	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Finch	O
's	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Wall	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Boards	O
nail	O
'd	O
over	O
it	O
:	O
We	O
broke	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
packed	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Coates	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Jonathan	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Lane	O
,	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
Mr	O
Finch	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
at	O
10	O
o'clock	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
in	O
Maiden	O
head-Court	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-Street	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Scabrooke	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
an	O
open	O
Confession	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
confess	O
this	O
very	O
Robbery	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Manner	O
as	O
Sea-brooke	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
that	O
Lad	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
one	O
.	O
My	O
Aunt	O
promised	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
now	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
this	O
Fellow	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
443.	O
Rose	B-pers
Mahone	I-pers
*	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bignell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Brian	B-pers
Hollrina	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
This	O
Woman	O
kept	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
in	O
Oxendon-Street	O
,	O
when	O
George	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
(	O
Coachman	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Pawlett	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
)	O
was	O
murdered	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
Her	O
Husband	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
Richard	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
were	O
transported	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
See	O
their	O
Trials	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
159	O
,	O
160	O
.	O
Hollrina	O
.	O
On	O
Michaelmas	O
Day	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
clapp	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
?	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Stand	O
off	O
;	O
She	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
Hands	O
over	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
immediately	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
were	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
2	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
within	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
her	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
String	I-pers
fellow	O
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
White-Horse-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
Clare-Court	O
,	O
toward	O
Wych-Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
She	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Woman	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pursue	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
Pair	O
of	O
Heels	O
she	O
has	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
shift	O
to	O
run	O
20	O
Miles	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
run	O
15	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
searched	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
readily	O
?	O
String	O
fellow	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
innocent	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Duran	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Woman	O
running	O
;	O
my	O
Brother	O
Watchman	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
an	O
hundred	O
Irish	O
Dogs	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
mind	O
that	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Englishman	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
no	O
Hat	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
stopped	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
clandestine	O
Manner	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Hat	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
strip	O
from	O
Top	O
to	O
Toe	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
444.	O
Catherine	B-pers
(	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
)	I-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Adderson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Adderson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
rented	O
a	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
Lodging	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
would	O
bring	O
(	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
some	O
People	O
into	O
Trouble	O
.	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
2	O
Sheets	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Hall	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
at	O
Mr	O
Eyre	O
's	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Directions	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
Want	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
designed	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
find	O
out	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
again	O
.	O
Adderson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
enquired	O
no	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
445.	O
John	B-pers
Mounslow	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Smith	O
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Trunk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
Summer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
a-bed	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
Trunk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
sign	O
any	O
Confession	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
this	O
Boy	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Upon	O
Smith	O
's	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
Walham	O
Green	O
:	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
work	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
or	O
any	O
Thing	O
like	O
this	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
446.	O
Ann	B-pers
Connelly	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
O	I-pers
Hara	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
outside	O
and	O
the	O
inside	O
Case	O
made	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Bezer	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
,	O
October	O
3	O
Bezer	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Russel	O
street	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
treat	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
Halfpenny	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
one	O
Gerrard	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Windsor-Court	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-Lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
main	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
in	O
pulling	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
some	O
Resistance	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
swore	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
break	O
it	O
to	O
Pieces	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
offered	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Friends	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
sign	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
they	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
white	O
Paper	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
afterwards	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
in	O
a	O
Recognizance	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
5	O
l.	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Indecency	O
passed	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
Conversation	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
above	O
five	O
Minutes	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
5l	O
.	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
Friends	O
here	O
these	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Days	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
gone	O
now	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
447.	O
Philip	B-pers
Lipscombe	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
Cock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
October	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
Evidence	O
against	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
February	O
Sessions	O
on	O
Two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
;	O
the	O
one	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
and	O
robbing	O
Mr	O
Lane	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Hackney	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
and	O
robbing	O
Mr	O
Crane	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Bow	O
.	O
See	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
161	O
.	O
448.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Haunch	O
of	O
Venison	O
,	O
1	O
piece	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
a	O
Spring	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
6	O
brass	O
Cocks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
8	O
.	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick-house	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
my	O
Cellar	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
among	O
the	O
Trees	O
at	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
these	O
Things	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Business	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
Peril	O
I	O
might	O
touch	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
449	O
.	O
+	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Mumpman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	O
Rode	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spo	O
ons	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
5	O
Knives	O
,	O
5	O
Forks	O
,	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Rode	I-pers
,	O
September	O
16	O
.	O
Peter	O
Rode	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
cross-barr	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
at	O
3	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Bundles	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Bundles	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
them	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
directly	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Shumaker	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
nobody	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
little	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
little	O
Seat	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
;	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
Boards	O
with	O
a	O
Pick-Axe	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
with	O
much	O
ado	O
we	O
got	O
her	O
out	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
2	O
Men	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Directions	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
our	O
Men	O
getting	O
up	O
at	O
3	O
o'clock	O
,	O
disturbed	O
them	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Shumaker	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
Rode	O
came	O
that	O
Morning	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
near	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Beef	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Vault	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
little	O
Seat	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Head	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
see	O
nothing	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
smelt	O
very	O
strong	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
the	O
Bundle	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
Pick-Axe	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stir	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
one	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
some	O
Water	O
.	O
To	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
we	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Brandy	O
,	O
cut	O
off	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Sack	O
to	O
clean	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
Men	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Directions	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Mr	O
Mason	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Shumaker	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
these	O
Things	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Beef	O
in	O
one	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
Bread	O
,	O
Butter	O
,	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Manner	O
of	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
Candles	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
little	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Pick-Axe	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
Body	O
;	O
we	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
gravel	O
Walk	O
;	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
without	O
Life	O
or	O
Motion	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
some	O
pails	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
moved	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
then	O
perceived	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Woman	O
:	O
we	O
got	O
some	O
Brandy	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
force	O
her	O
Mouth	O
open	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
herself	O
.	O
Some	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
cleaned	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Speech	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
never	O
spoken	O
to	O
her	O
from	O
that	O
Time	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
before	O
Justice	O
Dennet	O
,	O
that	O
2	O
Men	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
were	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Servants	O
coming	O
down	O
at	O
3	O
o'clock	O
surprized	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Men	O
made	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
backwards	O
;	O
whence	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
she	O
chose	O
rather	O
to	O
perish	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
than	O
be	O
taken	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Rode	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
People	O
in	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
Seat	O
in	O
the	O
little	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Board	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
we	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
2	O
Men	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Directions	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
Evidence	O
,	O
with	O
Respect	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
450.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Sides	O
of	O
Pig	O
Pork	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thennit	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
451.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
1737	O
,	O
took	O
to	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
he	O
feloniously	O
married	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Mary	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
full	O
Life	O
.	O
Mary	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
1737	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Things	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Certificate	O
of	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Parson	O
who	O
wrote	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Certificate	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Parson	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
his	O
Register	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
this	O
Certificate	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
true	O
Copy	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
;	O
``	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
certify	O
whom	O
it	O
may	O
concern	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
Timothy	O
Field	O
,	O
of	O
St	O
James	O
's	O
Westminster	O
,	O
``	O
Vintner	O
,	O
Batchelor	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Walker	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
``	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
were	O
married	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
``	O
of	O
St	O
Bride	O
's	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Form	O
prescribed	O
``	O
in	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
Common-Prayer	O
,	O
as	O
appears	O
by	O
``	O
the	O
Register.	O
``	O
Michael	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Minister	O
.	O
''	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Guardian	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Effects	O
in	O
my	O
Hands	O
;	O
her	O
Husband	O
coming	O
to	O
demand	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
with	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
married	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Marriage	O
not	O
being	O
legally	O
proved	O
,	O
[	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
being	O
the	O
lawful	O
Wife	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
neither	O
the	O
Clergyman	O
who	O
married	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Person	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Register	O
,	O
nor	O
indeed	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Register	O
produced	O
]	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
452	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
outside	O
and	O
inside	O
Case	O
made	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
Half-a-Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Collin	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
August	O
17	O
.	O
Frazier	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Bed-fellow	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
out	O
till	O
almost	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
walk	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
six	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
stood	O
arguing	O
the	O
Case	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
:	O
she	O
threw	O
herself	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
asleep	O
presently	O
:	O
I	O
awaked	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Landlady	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
:	O
I	O
allowed	O
her	O
eight	O
Days	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
me	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
Frazier	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certainly	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
fancy	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
Oath	O
:	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
Frazier	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
together	O
about	O
5	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russel-Street	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Lodger	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
suffer	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
owed	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
accuses	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
as	O
common	O
to	O
every	O
Body	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
several	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
refuse	O
any	O
Body	O
's	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
453	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
May	I-pers
*	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Moidores	O
,	O
5	O
Thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
44	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Silver	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
.	O
1736	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Last	O
January	O
Sessions-Book	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
125	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
that	O
Set	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
go	O
under	O
the	O
Denomination	O
of	O
Gamblers	O
;	O
the	O
most	O
dangerous	O
Community	O
to	O
the	O
Publick	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Schemes	O
they	O
lay	O
to	O
trap	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
Providence	O
takes	O
care	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
ensnar	O
'd	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
fall	O
into	O
that	O
Pit	O
which	O
they	O
dig	O
for	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
now	O
brought	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
William	O
Silver	O
was	O
called	O
and	O
sworn	O
.	O
Couns	O
.	O
Go	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Man	O
.	O
Silver	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
:	O
He	O
met	O
me	O
by	O
Milford-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Bobb	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
O	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
Pardon	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
somebody	O
else	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
believe	O
my	O
Eyes	O
:	O
Pray	O
,	O
What	O
Countryman	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
Berkshire	O
;	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
High-Wicomb	O
myself	O
:	O
Pray	O
,	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
?	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Bracken	B-pers
,	I-pers
O	I-pers
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
Person	O
I	O
drank	O
with	O
,	O
may	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Person	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
:	O
What	O
Part	O
of	O
Berkshire	O
?	O
I	O
came	O
(	O
said	O
I	O
)	O
from	O
Walgrove	O
;	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
?	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
your	O
Parish	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Debt	O
owing	O
him	O
from	O
one	O
in	O
Town	O
who	O
paid	O
him	O
but	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
him	O
the	O
remainder	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Feathers-Tavern	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
smoak	O
half	O
a	O
Pipe	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
lighting	O
our	O
Pipes	O
,	O
he	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Paper	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
somebody	O
had	O
had	O
very	O
bad	O
Luck	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
the	O
Owner	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
Do	O
n't	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
leave	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
peeped	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
Pardon	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
drop	O
a	O
Paper	O
here	O
just	O
now	O
;	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
mortgage	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
immediately	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Wine	O
;	O
on	O
his	O
Persuasion	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Cock	O
Match	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Landlord	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
told	O
him	O
one	O
particular	O
Cock	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
Wager	O
on	O
it	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Landlord	O
was	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Before	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
Wine	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Stranger	O
turned	O
himself	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sell	O
to	O
shewing	O
Tricks	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
pulled	O
a	O
Card	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
that	O
Card	O
is	O
before	O
I	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
lay	O
you	O
a	O
100	O
l.	O
that	O
I	O
tell	O
any	O
Card	O
in	O
the	O
Pack	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thereupon	O
fetched	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
told	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
up	O
;	O
There	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
Damage	O
,	O
(	O
said	O
he	O
)	O
only	O
tender	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
Hand	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
win	O
the	O
Fool	O
's	O
Money	O
as	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
borrow	O
some	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
over-persuaded	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Davis	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
got	O
25	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
to	O
Mr	O
Ford	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
30	O
l.	O
Coming	O
back	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
Bishop	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Fleece	O
below	O
St	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
tell	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
how	O
much	O
was	O
wanting	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
80	O
l.	O
There	O
were	O
10	O
l.	O
wanting	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
borrow	O
of	O
a	O
Friend	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Money	O
into	O
my	O
Bag	O
with	O
that	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
borrowed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
turn	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Time	O
he	O
changed	O
my	O
Bag	O
for	O
another	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Remainder	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
only	O
Half-a-crown's-worth	O
of	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
Lead	O
.	O
Couns	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Wager	O
was	O
laid	O
?	O
Silver	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
his	O
Money	O
into	O
my	O
Bag	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
Couns	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Stranger	O
?	O
Silver	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Feathers	O
,	O
while	O
we	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Couns	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
Wager	O
?	O
Silver	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
The	O
Wager	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Stranger	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Couns	O
.	O
On	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
Was	O
your	O
Money	O
ever	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
?	O
Silver	O
.	O
Not	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
borrow	O
Money	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
you	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
?	O
Suppose	O
the	O
Stranger	O
had	O
won	O
,	O
Who	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
he	O
should	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
happened	O
otherwise	O
,	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
good	O
.	O
Couns	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
Gold	O
or	O
Silver	O
?	O
Silver	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
Pieces	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
His	O
Money	O
and	O
mine	O
were	O
mixed	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
here	O
made	O
an	O
Objection	O
in	O
Point	O
of	O
Law	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
borrowed	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depended	O
upon	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Re-payment	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
Fact	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
deem	O
'd	O
Felony	O
.	O
In	O
Answer	O
to	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
urged	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
That	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
worst	O
Sort	O
of	O
Felonies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Case	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Publick	O
are	O
greatly	O
concern	O
'd	O
:	O
That	O
this	O
Money	O
never	O
having	O
been	O
lent	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
entrusted	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
deem	O
'd	O
a	O
felonious	O
taking	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Person	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
Ring	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
adjudged	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
this	O
Indictment	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
laid	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
sufficient	O
Sureties	O
to	O
appear	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Trial	O
for	O
the	O
Fraud	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
454	O
.	O
+	O
Cane	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Quant	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Quant	O
,	O
October	O
4	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Quant	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Compton	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Wood's-Close	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
are	O
Button-makers	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
poor	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
leave	O
to	O
work	O
and	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
my	O
Trunk	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
took	O
it	O
all	O
on	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
Cold-Bath-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
lost	O
in	O
tossing	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Keys	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Trunk	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Boy	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
6	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
tossed	O
up	O
and	O
lost	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
a-sleep	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Cold	O
Bath-Fields	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stanbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
Father	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
all	O
himself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
a	O
Farthing	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
hurt	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
own	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
hurt	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
kept	O
most	O
within	O
Doors	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Years	O
;	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
and	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
live	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Quant	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
somebody	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Chamber	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
455.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Laney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
September	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
456.	O
Cadman	B-pers
Gritton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
in-indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
September	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
457	O
.	O
+	O
Roger	B-pers
Walgrove	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Drake	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pottage	O
Pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
13	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
Day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Russel	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
at	O
Spithead	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
Padlocks	O
on	O
my	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
fast	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
had	O
Word	O
sent	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
looks	O
into	O
a	O
Back-Yard	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Shippery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
had	O
been	O
open	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Frame	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
put	O
up	O
only	O
to	O
give	O
Light	O
to	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lives	O
,	O
is	O
next	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
at	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
flung	O
a	O
String	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
haul	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
standing	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tying	O
a	O
Pot	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
stepp	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
the	O
Pot	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
lay	O
Things	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
:	O
I	O
broke	O
no	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
very	O
Pot	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
458.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lochlin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Copper	O
Scuttles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
October	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
459.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
9	O
.	O
Edward	O
Walker	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
6	O
,	O
a	O
Fellow	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Thread	O
;	O
while	O
y	O
Girl	O
was	O
turned	O
about	O
to	O
serve	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
these	O
Things	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
run	O
by	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
White	O
cap'd-coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Black	O
Wig	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
about	O
2	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
hustled	O
out	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Dray	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
which	O
hinder	O
'd	O
him	O
from	O
running	O
much	O
further	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
taken	O
,	O
therefore	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
ran	O
past	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
St	O
Ann	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
me	O
,	O
nothing	O
vexes	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
taken	O
by	O
such	O
a	O
little	O
Animal	O
as	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
a	O
White-cap	O
'd	O
Coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Dray	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Robottom	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
blue	O
Thread	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
colour	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
turned	O
about	O
to	O
serve	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
snatched	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Hat	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
if	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Hat	O
?	O
Robottom	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Grey	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
Leather	O
Apron	O
on	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
Evening	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Grey	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leather	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
just	O
,	O
upright	O
Man	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	O
Harper	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Forth	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
460.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea-Chest	O
with	O
Brass	O
Mouldings	O
,	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
Key	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Tin	O
Cannisters	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
August	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
461.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Season	I-pers
,	O
September	O
29	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Season	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Cherry-Garden	I-place
Stairs	I-place
,	I-place
Rotherhith	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
some	O
Spoons	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Tea-Spoons	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
stopped	O
with	O
some	O
,	O
on	O
St	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
Mantle-piece	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
thrown	O
away	O
with	O
Dish-Water	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
St	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoons	O
hung	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
Rags	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
Spoons	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
462	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
John	O
Johnson	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
one	O
Saturday-Night	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
Home	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
Way	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
Home	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
Madam	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
clothes	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
long	O
camlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
three	O
Razors	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
Josh	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rinstead	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
about	O
6	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
swearing	O
in	O
St	O
Ann's-Lane	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
good	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
good	O
cloaths	O
,	O
since	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
King-street	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
Woman	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Fulner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
the	O
6	O
d.	O
she	O
borrowed	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
change	O
,	O
so	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
opened	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Brother	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
more	O
Money	O
besides	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
King-street	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
overtook	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
House	O
full	O
of	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Wife	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
clean	O
his	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
work	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
before	O
,	O
how	O
then	O
could	O
I	O
find	O
the	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
nothing	O
but	O
some	O
Small-Beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pipe	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
she	O
knows	O
I	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Pin	O
.	O
Fulner	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
always	O
honest	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
463.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Twickenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
3	O
Moidores	O
,	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
Half-Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
September	O
18	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
Months	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Bureau	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
looking	O
over	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
15	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
only	O
to	O
sweep	O
and	O
dust	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Bureau	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
persisted	O
in	O
a	O
Denial	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
filled	O
the	O
Bag	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Servants	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Little-house	O
had	O
been	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Bag	O
found	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
different	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
but	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Place	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
shew	O
us	O
whereabouts	O
it	O
was	O
hid	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
threaten	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Conjurer	O
about	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Mrs	O
Hewitt	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
her	O
Mother	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
they	O
call	O
a	O
Cunning-Man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
in	O
my	O
Senses	O
when	O
I	O
made	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
Mrs	O
Hewitt	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
here	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
Actions	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
disordered	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	O
Hewitt	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
her	O
Money	O
was	O
right	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
both	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Little-house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
were	O
Women	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
hold	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
thought	O
something	O
had	O
been	O
thrown	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
Bag	O
full	O
of	O
Stones	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
following	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
first	O
threw	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
dug	O
a	O
Hole	O
and	O
hid	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
?	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
not	O
some	O
odd	O
Methods	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Thief	O
?	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
cover	O
a	O
Table	O
with	O
Soot	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
Maids	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
their	O
Hands	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
guilty	O
Person	O
would	O
be	O
black	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
their	O
Hands	O
were	O
footed	O
.	O
I	O
imagined	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
guilty	O
should	O
pass	O
by	O
without	O
touching	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
blacked	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
done	O
without	O
Mrs	O
Hewitt	O
's	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
own	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
she	O
knew	O
my	O
Step	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
hardly	O
get	O
the	O
Bureau	O
shut	O
down	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
lower	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
little	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
after	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
no	O
Threats	O
that	O
were	O
made	O
Use	O
of	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
confess	O
.	O
-	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Sorts	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
mentioned	O
any	O
such	O
Word	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Temple	O
Eating-House	O
in	O
Sheer-Lane	O
:	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
entrusted	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Abundance	O
of	O
Gentlemens	O
Chambers	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
desire	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
better	O
,	O
nor	O
an	O
honester	O
Servant	O
while	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
Mr	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
Mr	O
Miller	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Apartment	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
3	O
Years	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
thought	O
her	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
Servant	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Woodward	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
stained	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
wrong	O
any	O
Body	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
464	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hand	O
kerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
Lewis	O
Hayes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
and	O
felt	O
somebody	O
at	O
my	O
Pocket	O
very	O
close	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
:	O
He	O
threw	O
it	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Minutes	O
,	O
but	O
up	O
on	O
his	O
swearing	O
terribly	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
John	O
!	O
John	O
!	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Crouch	O
hearing	O
him	O
calling	O
John	O
,	O
likewise	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
falling	O
,	O
Mr	O
Pantrey	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Mr	O
Hayes	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
East-End	O
of	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Fellow	O
come	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
calling	O
John	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
;	O
the	O
Way	O
is	O
there	O
so	O
narrow	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
either	O
stand	O
up	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
push	O
me	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
Looks	O
of	O
the	O
Fellow	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
my	O
cane	O
against	O
the	O
Boards	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Pantrey	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
Mr	O
Hayes	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pantrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
thrown	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
strange	O
Thing	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
that	O
the	O
Lamp	O
should	O
not	O
shew	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
465	O
,	O
466.	O
John	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
John	O
Chase	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
coat	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Golden-square	I-place
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
fastening	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
push	O
'd	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
no	O
Hats	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
no	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
my	O
coat	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Hands	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
one	O
Night	O
about	O
five	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
King	O
street	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
coat	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
we	O
attempted	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
prevented	O
us	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
did	O
get	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
Beale	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
Bristow	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Hats	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Beale	O
,	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
that	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
Beale	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
new	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
House	O
is	O
the	O
corner	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
the	O
coat	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
Bristow	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Chandler	O
for	O
Half-a-crown	O
.	O
Beale	O
is	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
a	O
Carman	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
on	O
these	O
Occasions	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
coat	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Chandler	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Cucumber	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Beale	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
this	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
above	O
3	O
Times	O
.	O
Bristow	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Crossby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Beale	O
ever	O
since	O
Christmas	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
Tenant	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
honestly	O
and	O
justly	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Bristow	O
,	O
nor	O
Andrews	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
told	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
that	O
Beale	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Robbery	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
back	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
since	O
Christmas	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
civilly	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
House	O
over	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
(	O
for	O
Bristow	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
2	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Carman	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
pains-taking	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
early	O
and	O
late	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Indictments	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
467.	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	O
Lawrence	B-place
Pountney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Leaden	O
Pumps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Pump	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Seller	I-pers
,	O
October	O
13	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Machen	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
brought	O
3	O
Pumps	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
2	O
Porters	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
Baskets	O
on	O
their	O
Backs	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
the	O
Porters	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
fetch	O
somebody	O
to	O
their	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Ware-house	O
by	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
others	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
heard	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
escap	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
we	O
lock	O
'd	O
in	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
2	O
Hours	O
allowed	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
Dates	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
on	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
1729	O
,	O
R.F	O
.	O
another	O
1738	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
1689	O
,	O
W.S.I	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
another	O
Brother	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
brought	O
in	O
Baskets	O
;	O
besides	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Pump	O
which	O
was	O
put	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
38	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Ask	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
order	O
his	O
Sister	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
of	O
my	O
Brother	O
?	O
Machen	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
allow	O
my	O
Sister	O
to	O
buy	O
Lead	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Richard	O
Seller	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
Pumps	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Yard	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
or	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
mark	O
'd	O
1689	O
,	O
W.S.I	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
10	O
o'clock	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
this	O
other	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Porters	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
being	O
stole	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Glibbery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
ill	O
Thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Waterman	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
17	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Culverwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ratcliffe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
thought	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
Living	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Upham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
an	O
ill	O
Action	O
done	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
19	O
Years	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
25	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
-	O
Ratson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
16	O
or	O
18	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
468.	O
Mary	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Rasey	I-pers
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
Constance	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
7-night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Spoon	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Rosey	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
tell	O
the	O
Woman	O
where	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Coal-Yard	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Hands	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
469.	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	I-pers
(	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
Price	I-pers
)	I-pers
)	O
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
4	O
Damask	O
Clouts	O
,	O
3	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cloggs	O
,	O
I	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sconce	O
,	O
3	O
Mobs	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
laced	O
Pinners	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
September	O
13	O
.	O
Catherine	O
Hughes	O
.	O
I	O
hir	O
'd	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Charterhouse	B-place
lane	I-place
,	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
cloaths	O
in	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
3	O
Locks	O
,	O
left	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Boxes	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
were	O
not	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Boards	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Wainscott	O
between	O
her	O
Room	O
and	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
so	O
many	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
my	O
Gown	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
Cloggs	O
,	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
Things	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
;	O
the	O
Wainscot	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
crack	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
Half	O
a	O
Gui	O
nea	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
promise	O
me	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
lays	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Sleeves	O
that	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
lost	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
has	O
drest	O
my	O
child	O
in	O
them	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
drest	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Lucy	B-pers
Towel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
3	O
Years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
entrusted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
alway	O
acted	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
470.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Gown	O
rob	O
'd	O
with	O
Sattin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stanborough	I-pers
,	O
September	O
16	O
.	O
John	O
Stanborough	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
came	O
to	O
bring	O
my	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
all	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
home	O
at	O
7	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
:	O
my	O
Wife	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
John	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Gown	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
all	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
Halfpenny	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
enquire	O
,	O
if	O
her	O
child	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr	O
Glover	O
,	O
in	O
Sharp	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Stanborough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
my	O
Husband	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Neck	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
to	O
beg	O
a	O
Mess	O
of	O
Broth	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
get	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
no	O
Conversation	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
this	O
child	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Full-pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
before	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
