TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
TUESDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
15th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1742	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Godschall	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
South-Sea-House	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC.XLII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GODSCHALL	I-pers
.	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
CHAPPLE	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
ABEY	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
REYNOLDS	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Alnut	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Phillibrown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Winder	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	O
>	O
Davis	O
``	O
/	O
>	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
>	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
``	I-pers
/	I-pers
>	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cogan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Soleby	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Heritage	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rosamond	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Foister	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Rogerson	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Toft	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Half-hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Holmes	B-pers
,	O
November	O
10	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2	O
,	O
3.	O
Richard	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Flexmore	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1741	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
November	O
6	O
,	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
Value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Flexmore	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
wilfully	O
they	O
did	O
kill	O
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Servant	O
into	O
my	O
Grounds	O
to	O
fetch	O
up	O
eighteen	O
Sheep	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
two	O
Calves	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
some	O
Sheep	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
brought	O
but	O
seventeen	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
perhaps	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
obtained	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Clitherow	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Dean	O
,	O
and	O
Flexmore	O
's	O
Father	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Dean	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
House	O
pretty	O
rightly	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Flexmore	I-pers
,	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
the	O
Sheep	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carried	O
it	O
Home	O
to	O
Flexmore	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Robert	O
Flexmore	O
's	O
enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
Constable	O
found	O
something	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Mutton	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
Dean	O
behind	O
me	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Master	O
we	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Cart-rut	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
Skin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Rut	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Fork	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
by-lane	O
where	O
Carts	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
sometimes	O
for	O
two	O
Months	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
the	O
Skin	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
into	O
ten	O
Pieces	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
-	O
Westmore	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
brought	O
the	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
Dean	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Flexmore	O
's	O
went	O
into	O
Hawkins	O
's	O
Ground	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
killed	O
the	O
Sheep	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Robert	B-pers
Flexmore	I-pers
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Westmore	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Flexmore	O
said	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Dean	O
when	O
the	O
Sheep	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Flexmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Brother	O
to	O
Flexmore	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
no	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dyson	I-pers
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
Years	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
did	O
what	O
I	O
commanded	O
him	O
without	O
making	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
through	O
his	O
Father	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
that	O
Act	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Flexmore	I-pers
.	O
Flexmore	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
Dean	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
other	O
than	O
Honesty	O
by	O
Flexmore	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Dean	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Flexmore	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4.	O
George	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Benfield	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
October	O
20	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
.	O
About	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
about	O
some	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
drank	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
enticed	O
me	O
from	O
Place	O
to	O
Place	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
while	O
I	O
lay	O
backwards	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
seize	O
her	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
My	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
three	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
to	O
pay	O
three	O
Persons	O
that	O
I	O
dealt	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
Vessel	O
,	O
and	O
trade	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Ipswich	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Money	O
I	O
brought	O
from	O
Ipswich	O
to	O
pay	O
away	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
for	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Mutton	O
Stakes	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pulling	O
some	O
Women	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
watched	O
me	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
got	O
up	O
Stairs	O
but	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Change	O
.	O
Herne	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Drink	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Thing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
6.	O
Wm	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
alias	O
Goody	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
2	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Quart	O
Glass	O
Bottle	O
filled	O
with	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pocket	O
Piece	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Nov	O
1	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Desire	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Wm	O
Blackburn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
towards	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
near	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Wells	O
back	O
Gate	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
grey	O
Coat	O
and	O
red	O
Waistcoat	O
(	O
Warner	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Hanger	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Warner	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Pistol	O
.	O
Blackburn	O
.	O
Another	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Horse	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
dropped	O
my	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Brandy	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
Warner	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
5	O
s	O
and	O
two	O
Box	O
Keys	O
.	O
Warner	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Watch	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
me	O
Jack	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
his	O
Watch	O
!	O
come	O
along	O
Jack	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
along	O
the	O
Field	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
lying	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
O	O
Dear	O
!	O
Upon	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Mind	O
to	O
turn	O
again	O
and	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
deserved	O
his	O
Brains	O
blown	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
passed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
'Squire	O
Edward	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Woolpack	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Men	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
Man	O
himself	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Blackburn	I-pers
)	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Blackburn	O
.	O
A	O
Star	O
light	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
the	O
Persons	O
?	O
Blackburn	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Warner	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
us	O
up	O
?	O
Blackburn	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
their	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
House-breaking	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
Warner	O
only	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Employment	O
?	O
Blackburn	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Forcer	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Night	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
to	O
a	O
Benefit	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
dressed	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
:	O
Blackburn	O
.	O
Warner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Dress	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
Newman	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Newman	O
.	O
The	O
Almanack	O
will	O
convince	O
these	O
People	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
Night	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Frock	O
on	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
Frock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
that	O
which	O
you	O
had	O
on	O
then	O
?	O
Newman	O
.	O
Yes	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
Goal	O
in	O
this	O
Frock	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
dark	O
Night	O
?	O
Blackburn	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
Star-light	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shippey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
recovered	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Blackburn	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
my	O
Skull	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
my	O
Meat	O
and	O
Potatoes	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
Warner	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
comes	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
Head	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
he	O
spoke	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Blackburn	O
in	O
his	O
white	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
penny	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket-piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Brandy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Shippey	O
.	O
Not	O
two	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
?	O
Shippey	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
distant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
Blackburn	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Shippey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Warner	O
ran	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
a	O
Drive	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hurt	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
two	O
Places	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Horse-Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
that	O
Blow	O
,	O
Newman	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
with	O
what	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
lay	O
senseless	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
they	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Shippey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Warner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
his	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
about	O
me	O
worth	O
your	O
taking	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
one	O
Pocket	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
my	O
other	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
my	O
Meat	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
before	O
Blackburn	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
?	O
Shippey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
three	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
comes	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Apron	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
a	O
Knock	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
another	O
when	O
Blackburn	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
imagining	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
my	O
Part	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
Words	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
were	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
his	O
B	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
Mind	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Brains	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
deserves	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Star-light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
were	O
going	O
Twelve	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
through	O
Wood	O
's	O
Close	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Shippey	O
.	O
Warner	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
Newman	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
Newman	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Starlight	O
Night	O
.	O
Shippey	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Star-light	O
Night	O
.	O
Warner	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
Rain	O
?	O
Shippey	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Warner	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
look	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
did	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shippey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
together	O
Day	O
and	O
Night	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Court	O
Officer	O
.	O
Warner	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Thief-taker	O
.	O
Revington	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blackburn	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Word	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
grey	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
Frock	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
hearing	O
that	O
these	O
Men	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Shippey	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
frequently	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
passing	O
and	O
repassing	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
had	O
you	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
?	O
Revington	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
attacked	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Kind	O
before	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
mix	O
'd	O
Company	O
when	O
Blackburn	O
picked	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
?	O
Revington	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
directly	O
in	O
,	O
because	O
Warner	O
threw	O
a	O
Pipe	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Prisoners	O
about	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
shew	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
Blackburn	O
?	O
Revington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
challenged	O
him	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Blackburn	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
Body	O
point	O
out	O
Warner	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Blackburn	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
you	O
Rogue	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
for	O
?	O
I	O
saw	O
Newman	O
in	O
Tothillfields	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
Revington	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
myself	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Revington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Hog-Lane	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
at	O
Christmas	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Newman	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
something	O
better	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
Newport	O
Market	O
:	O
that	O
was	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
much	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
since	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
Shoes	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Warner	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blackburn	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
together	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
this	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
then	O
.	O
C.	O
That	O
happens	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Warner	O
.	O
My	O
Witnesses	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
here	O
till	O
To-morrow	O
.	O
Newman	O
.	O
Examine	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Star-light	O
Morning	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
ca	O
n't	O
get	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
7.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blackburn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
Pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
8.	O
John	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Nodder	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
Night	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
the	O
Back	B-place
Side	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
into	O
this	O
Burnham	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
sell	O
Drams	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
kept	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
I	O
dismissed	O
the	O
Woman	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
up	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
my	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
three	O
Minutes	O
before	O
she	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shove	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
push	O
away	O
till	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
.	O
Finding	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
lose	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
any	O
Body	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Questions	O
asked	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
rectly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
Purse	O
to	O
have	O
Change	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
:	O
She	O
seeing	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
called	O
me	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thinking	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
of	O
my	O
Purse	O
and	O
Gold	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
that	O
very	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
caught	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
this	O
Money	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
fuddled	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
Nodder	O
came	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
Nodder	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Roach	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sumner	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
some	O
Difficulty	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
Nodder	O
's	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
Nodder	O
)	O
was	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
set	O
a	O
Watch	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Nodder	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
Side	O
.	O
He	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Eyes	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Nodder	I-pers
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
two	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
yours	O
?	O
Bowers	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
hard	O
Matter	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
Pieces	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
.	O
These	O
Things	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
Nodder	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
Place	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
searching	O
him	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Purse	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Burnham	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
two	O
Women	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
Side	O
.	O
Bowers	O
.	O
One	O
Woman	O
I	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
I	O
dismissed	O
.	O
Burnham	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
Woman	O
might	O
take	O
your	O
Things	O
?	O
Bowers	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
chang	O
'd	O
my	O
Money	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
some	O
Time	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Nodder	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
mislefted	O
(	O
molested	O
)	O
him	O
in	O
any	O
Shape	O
,	O
or	O
meddled	O
with	O
him	O
good	O
,	O
bad	O
,	O
or	O
indifferent	O
?	O
Bowers	O
.	O
Once	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
and	O
he	O
hinder	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Nodder	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Woman	O
there	O
?	O
Bowers	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
and	O
see	O
.	O
Robin	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Robe	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
call	O
in	O
at	O
this	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
my	O
Bed-fellow	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
loose	O
Woman	O
that	O
used	O
that	O
House	O
.	O
At	O
Nodder	O
's	O
Desire	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
Side	O
about	O
two	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
(	O
Bowers	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
about	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Burnham	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
both	O
missing	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
two	O
Minutes	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Body	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
very	O
fast	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Screen	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
any	O
Body	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
Nodder	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
come	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
Bowers	O
insisted	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
Nodder	O
wanted	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Passage	O
Door	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
there	O
.	O
Bowers	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Nodder	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
Room	O
,	O
because	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
gone	O
up	O
higher	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
Nodder	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
up	O
higher	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
Immediately	O
Burnham	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Shrub	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Change	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
:	O
she	O
seeing	O
his	O
Money	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
hither	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
!	O
Upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
very	O
near	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
run	O
out	O
crying	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
if	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
served	O
so	O
.	O
He	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Nodder	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
bring	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
Nodder	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Struggle	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Coachman	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
Nodder	O
fasten	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
bid	O
Nodder	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Roach	O
together	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
that	O
my	O
Shop	O
mate	O
keeps	O
Company	O
with	O
.	O
Nodder	O
had	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Burnham	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
.	O
Burnham	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
known	O
me	O
?	O
Sumner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
that	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
.	O
Burnham	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
see	O
me	O
go	O
into	O
any	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Coachman	O
?	O
Sumner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Nodder	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
silent	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
should	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Present	O
.	O
Nodder	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
I	O
used	O
the	O
Coachman	O
ill	O
?	O
Sumner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Woman	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Sumner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb-Inn	O
,	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
,	O
within	O
five	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Servant	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
beset	O
with	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
was	O
bolted	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
got	O
it	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
Nodder	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
below	O
Stairs	O
:	O
He	O
rubbed	O
his	O
Eyes	O
and	O
yawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Watch	O
on	O
the	O
Edge	O
of	O
a	O
Brick	O
between	O
the	O
Closet	O
and	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
Corner	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Bowers	O
.	O
This	O
Watch	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
one	O
Davis	O
.	O
Roach	O
.	O
Nodder	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Poker	O
and	O
stirred	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
more	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Nodder	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
private	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
would	O
disperse	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
should	O
be	O
forth	O
coming	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Females	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Devil	O
to	O
deal	O
with	O
.	O
Burnham	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
stripp	O
'd	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
?	O
Roach	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
small	O
Time	O
before	O
,	O
John	O
Bower	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
:	O
The	O
Robe-maker	O
(	O
Sumner	O
)	O
came	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
stand	O
and	O
secure	O
the	O
Fore-door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
used	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
Means	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Burnham	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
going	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
Nodder	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
ignorant	O
of	O
our	O
Business	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
my	O
Brother	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
some	O
Dirt	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
and	O
some	O
Guineas	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
Williams	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
he	O
might	O
Pocket	O
some	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
above	O
Deposition	O
,	O
with	O
Regard	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
Burnham	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
House	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Shrub	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
something	O
very	O
particular	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Man	O
should	O
lose	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
be	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
I	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
fuster	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
Freedom	O
there	O
was	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Bowers	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Freedom	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
.	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Peter	O
street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Burnham	O
last	O
Summer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Family	O
before	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
something	O
after	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Nodder	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
.	O
She	O
keeps	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
Liquor	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
,	O
-	O
common	O
Liquor	O
,	O
-	O
Gin	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
this	O
Coachman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
laced	O
Hat	O
on	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Shaw	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
followed	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
sat	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
a	O
Crum	O
of	O
a	O
Minute	O
.	O
He	O
accused	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Burnham	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
accused	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Hair	O
was	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
another	O
of	O
you	O
if	O
that	O
be	O
all	O
(	O
to	O
Roach	O
)	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
appear	O
you	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
imagine	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
robb	O
'd	O
Bowers	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
left	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
for	O
some	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
lived	O
with	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
mine	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
wrong	O
'd	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bett	I-pers
Burnham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
Burnham	O
,	O
but	O
Nodder	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Body	O
accuse	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
this	O
Kind	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
a	O
Public-House	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
till	O
within	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
Roach	O
.	O
Lane	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
insolent	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
desired	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
commit	O
her	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
commit	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Burnham	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
keep	O
my	O
Christmas	O
in	O
another	O
World	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
determined	O
to	O
hang	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
.	O
These	O
Gentlemen	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
as	O
she	O
charges	O
them	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
Lane	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
impudent	O
Creature	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
commit	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Burnham	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Nodder	O
acquitted	O
.	O
9	O
Robert	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
green	O
Baize	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holdsworth	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
October	O
19	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
13	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lilliston	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
October	O
23	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12	O
,	O
13.	O
John	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
half	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
Value	O
14	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
November	O
16	O
Both	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15	O
,	O
16	O
,	O
17.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lee	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Martha	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
.	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Tapster	I-pers
.	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
next	O
Monday	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
my	O
Lady	O
King	O
's	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-Square	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
three	O
Women	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Little-Turnstile	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	B-place
Six	I-place
Canns	I-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
swore	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
her	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
knock	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
fore	O
my	O
Cloak	O
off	O
my	O
Shoulders	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Martha	B-pers
Tapster	I-pers
standing	O
at	O
an	O
Oyster	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
People	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
next	O
Morning	O
where	O
they	O
lived	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Six	O
Canns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Beer	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
without	O
drinking	O
it	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
nine	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Waters	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Six	O
Canns	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
My	O
Maid	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
quick	O
in	O
drawing	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
stay	O
for	O
the	O
Beer	O
,	O
but	O
come	O
along	O
.	O
He	O
immediately	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
towards	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
Shop	O
by	O
Little	O
Turnstile	O
without	O
drinking	O
the	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Waters	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Waters	O
keeps	O
a	O
Lodging	O
House	O
in	O
Goldsmith's-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
having	O
lent	O
a	O
Gown	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
next	O
Monday	O
;	O
I	O
really	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
at	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Black	O
Boy-Alley	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
Waters	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
his	O
Wife	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
getting	O
him	O
along	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutrix	O
happen	O
'd	O
then	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Face	O
:	O
then	O
Ann	O
Lee	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
another	O
Knock	O
and	O
tore	O
her	O
Cloak	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
ran	O
away	O
after	O
Waters	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
gone	O
a	O
good	O
Way	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Water	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
What	O
Gown	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
A	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
Linnen	O
one	O
:	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Oyster	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Six	O
Canns	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
Moll	O
Waters	O
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lee	O
run	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Bess	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
after	O
this	O
Affair	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Headborough	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Waters	O
's	O
House	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Waters	O
's	O
Wife	O
drinking	O
Tea	O
together	O
.	O
Lee	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
only	O
took	O
Waters	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
the	O
Examination	O
that	O
Lee	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Fellow	O
in	O
an	O
Apron	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
swear	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
seemed	O
to	O
make	O
Words	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
Hunt	O
left	O
behind	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
too	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Hunt	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
had	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Coal-yard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
search	O
Warrant	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
according	O
to	O
their	O
Directions	O
.	O
Nan	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Waters	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
them	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
for	O
further	O
Examination	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
my	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
'till	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
We	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
Waters	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Hunt	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
one	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
told	O
where	O
the	O
Cloak	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
afterwards	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
deeply	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Wom	O
an	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Standwell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
Women	O
Prisoners	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
Cloak	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
three	O
Shillings	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Lee	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Headborough	O
came	O
with	O
Hunt	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Cloak	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Woman	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
directly	O
.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
You	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
Cloak	O
!	O
Hamlin	O
.	O
Lee	O
owned	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Turnstile	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
to	O
my	O
Mothers	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
at	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
Mr	O
.	O
Waters	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
away	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
this	O
Cloak	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
over-persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Hunt	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Hunt	O
This	O
young	O
Woman	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
very	O
innocently	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Lee	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Holland	O
and	O
Waters	O
acquitted	O
.	O
18	O
Frances	B-pers
Hamlin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Clasp	O
Knives	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
October	O
23	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
William	B-pers
Bunch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
leaden	O
Pipe	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
Messuage	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Redhead	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
November	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Fraser	B-pers
Honeywood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
two	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leaden	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
November	O
,	O
30th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21	O
,	O
22.	O
James	B-pers
Arters	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Arkins	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
leaden	O
Sash	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
24.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Shuffle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lacock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
.	O
November	O
,	O
15th	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
behind	O
the	O
Two	O
Loggerheads	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
by	O
three	O
Persons	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
Cut	O
upon	O
the	O
Left-side	O
of	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
see	O
my	O
Skull	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
Master	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
Morning	O
for	O
Memorandums	O
for	O
planting	O
Flowers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
they	O
first	O
attack	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Gray	O
.	O
They	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
before	O
they	O
spoke	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
him	O
,	O
keep	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Lacock	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
again	O
?	O
Gray	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Lacock	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Book	O
with	O
no	O
Writing	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
we	O
pretended	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
Home	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
Brick	O
Lane	O
into	O
Swan-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Arm	O
when	O
Lacock	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Mopstick	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
tumbled	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
together	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Pocket-Book	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Shuffle	O
about	O
12	O
Months	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Velvet-weaver	O
by	O
Trade	O
.	O
Lacock	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
ever	O
since	O
Mackarel	O
Season	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
Things	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
before	O
Gray	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Standley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lacock	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
some	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
desirons	O
to	O
leave	O
off	O
this	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
come	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Standley	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Lacock	O
in	O
one	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
Standley	O
and	O
Shuffle	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
Lacock	O
)	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Mopstick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Buckles	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
and	O
the	O
Shoes	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
We	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
who	O
perceiving	O
that	O
Lacock	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Person	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
Gray	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
admitted	O
Standley	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
This	O
Pocket-Book	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
from	O
Standley	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Direction	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
scrupulous	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Memorandum	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
relates	O
to	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Standley	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
these	O
Words	O
in	O
it	O
myself	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wornel	O
.	O
Did	O
Shuffle	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Wornel	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
the	O
greatest	O
Discovery	O
.	O
All	O
of	O
them	O
owned	O
it	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
These	O
three	O
Men	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
before	O
we	O
knew	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Blake	O
,	O
a	O
Gardiner	O
at	O
Walthamstow	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
appear	O
'd	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
25.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wornell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Huntley	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Steel	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Movement	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bessier	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
25	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
Sevennight	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Bear	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
pretty	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Pocket	O
picked	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Black-Bear	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
o'Clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
losing	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fish	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
Account	O
than	O
myself	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
.	O
They	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Door-way	O
near	O
Brownlow	O
street	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Dutton	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
'cross	O
the	O
Way	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
run	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
by	O
that	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
Dutton	O
ran	O
up	O
Warwick	O
Court	O
by	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
seized	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
and	O
thrust	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Fish	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Watch	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Rose	O
felt	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Name	O
on	O
the	O
Dial-Plate	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
where	O
Bessier	O
charg	O
'd	O
Dutton	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Guts	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn-Fields	O
.	O
Dutton	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
fetch	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
Sister	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Order	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fish	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Guts	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
besides	O
.	O
Rose	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
fell	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
muddy	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Eyes	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Paulson	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
Dutton	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
Bessier	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
other	O
Things	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
principal	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
refused	O
to	O
admit	O
her	O
Information	O
.	O
Dutton	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
through	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn-Fields	O
,	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
called	O
after	O
us	O
.	O
His	O
Hat	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
again	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
that	O
knew	O
me	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
stop	O
me	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
over	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
the	O
Watch	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fish	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
?	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Guts	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
left	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
Consequence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
keep	O
them	O
.	O
Bessier	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn-Fields	O
we	O
met	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Thing	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
was	O
the	O
Guts	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Brownlow-street	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grasing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
that	O
my	O
Daughter	O
(	O
Bessier	O
)	O
never	O
behav	O
'd	O
unhandsome	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Horn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
good	O
Things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
she	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Dutton	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Bessier	O
acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
Mary	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckskin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ramskin	O
ditto	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jeffreys	I-pers
,	O
November	O
,	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
John	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Mechlin	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
12	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Breach	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sweet	I-pers
,	O
Nov	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30	O
,	O
31.	O
John	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dominick	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Welch	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1736	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
September	O
16th	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
Bennet	O
Paul	O
's	O
Wharf	O
,	O
feloniously	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
and	O
forged	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
Paper	O
Instrument	O
,	O
partly	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
partly	O
written	O
,	O
seal	O
'd	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
Will	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Derneane	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Mark	O
thereto	O
subscrib	O
'd	O
,	O
pretended	O
by	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
proper	O
Hand-writing	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Perry	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Mistake	O
,	O
which	O
said	O
Paper	O
Instrument	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Words	O
following	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
Amen	O
,	O
I	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Mariner	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
disposing	O
Mind	O
and	O
Memory	O
,	O
do	O
hereby	O
make	O
my	O
last	O
Will	O
and	O
Testament	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
First	O
,	O
and	O
principally	O
,	O
I	O
commend	O
my	O
Soul	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Almighty	O
God	O
,	O
hoping	O
for	O
Remission	O
of	O
my	O
Sins	O
through	O
the	O
Merits	O
of	O
Jesus	O
Christ	O
,	O
my	O
blessed	O
Saviour	O
and	O
Redeemer	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Body	O
to	O
the	O
Earth	O
or	O
Sea	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
shall	O
please	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
such	O
worldly	O
Estate	O
and	O
Effects	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
my	O
Decease	O
be	O
possess	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
or	O
entitled	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
give	O
and	O
devise	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
I	O
give	O
to	O
my	O
dearly	O
beloved	O
Sister	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
all	O
such	O
Sum	O
or	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
as	O
now	O
is	O
,	O
or	O
hereafter	O
shall	O
grow	O
,	O
and	O
become	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
Service	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Lancaster	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Ship	O
or	O
Ships	O
whatsoever	O
;	O
And	O
I	O
hereby	O
nominate	O
,	O
constitute	O
and	O
appoint	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Heirs	O
and	O
Assigns	O
,	O
sole	O
Executrix	O
of	O
this	O
my	O
last	O
Will	O
and	O
Testament	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
and	O
residue	O
of	O
my	O
Estate	O
whatsoever	O
,	O
both	O
real	O
and	O
personal	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
declare	O
,	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
last	O
Will	O
and	O
Testament	O
,	O
hereby	O
revoking	O
all	O
former	O
Will	O
or	O
Wills	O
by	O
me	O
made	O
.	O
Sign	O
'd	O
,	O
Seal	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
Us	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
as	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
his	O
last	O
Will	O
and	O
Testament	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
With	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
farther	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
publishing	O
the	O
said	O
Will	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forg	O
'd	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Crimes	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stood	O
indicted	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Nature	O
,	O
as	O
destructive	O
of	O
Society	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Heinons	O
as	O
any	O
Crimes	O
could	O
possibly	O
be	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
this	O
Reason	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Crimes	O
of	O
Forgery	O
and	O
Perjury	O
being	O
so	O
frequent	O
,	O
the	O
Error	O
that	O
flieth	O
by	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
secret	O
Transactions	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
Lives	O
and	O
Properties	O
of	O
every	O
Man	O
were	O
in	O
Danger	O
)	O
the	O
Punishment	O
which	O
was	O
extremely	O
mild	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
thought	O
adequate	O
to	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Wisdom	O
of	O
the	O
Legislature	O
,	O
thought	O
fit	O
by	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
Offence	O
Felony	O
,	O
without	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
.	O
That	O
this	O
Law	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Force	O
for	O
five	O
Years	O
only	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
its	O
Expiration	O
,	O
the	O
good	O
Effects	O
of	O
it	O
were	O
perceived	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
therefore	O
revived	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
perpetual	O
,	O
by	O
another	O
Act	O
of	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Act	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
which	O
made	O
this	O
Offence	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Act	O
for	O
the	O
reviving	O
and	O
making	O
the	O
same	O
perpetual	O
,	O
were	O
read	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Deputy-Register	O
of	O
the	O
Prerogative	O
Court	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
the	O
Proctor	O
,	O
brought	O
this	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
original	O
Will	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
This	O
Paper	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
Perry	O
's	O
Will	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Dominick	O
Fitzgerald	O
,	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
it	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
Fitzgerald	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Executrix	O
too	O
.	O
Lee	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Will	O
was	O
first	O
brought	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
account	O
for	O
the	O
Error	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Executrix	O
sworn	O
before	O
Doctor	O
Chapman	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
Mistake	O
of	O
John	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Peter	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
Register	O
's	O
Clerk	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Error	O
must	O
be	O
accounted	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
the	O
Executrix	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Dominick	O
's	O
hearing	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
either	O
produce	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
wrote	O
the	O
Will	O
,	O
or	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
account	O
for	O
the	O
Mistake	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
Dominick	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Lee	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
Kelly	O
was	O
present	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
Lee	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
that	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
subscribing	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
any	O
Affidavit	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Thing	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
serious	O
Nature	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
draw	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Condition	O
.	O
I	O
appointed	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
some	O
other	O
Time	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
Instructions	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
sworn	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
attested	O
it	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
Body	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
swear	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
Fitzgerald	O
)	O
his	O
Person	O
is	O
so	O
particular	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
easily	O
forget	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asserted	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
Council	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
left	O
you	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
the	O
Will	O
and	O
Affidavit	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Probate	O
filled	O
up	O
.	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Condition	O
now	O
,	O
except	O
this	O
Tear	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Will	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Read	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
read.	O
``	O
This	O
Day	O
appeared	O
personally	O
,	O
James	O
``	O
Welch	O
,	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
Linnen	O
draper	O
,	O
``	O
aged	O
about	O
50	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
alledges	O
,	O
that	O
``	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
``	O
late	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Lancaster	O
,	O
``	O
Widower	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
25	O
Years	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
``	O
he	O
enter	O
'd	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
``	O
farther	O
deposes	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
Deponent	O
)	O
did	O
``	O
write	O
and	O
fill	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
Blanks	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
one	O
``	O
of	O
the	O
subscribing	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Will	O
``	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
beginning	O
thus	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Name	O
``	O
of	O
God	O
Amen	O
,	O
and	O
ending	O
thus	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
his	O
``	O
Mark	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Perry	O
did	O
make	O
his	O
``	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
``	O
said	O
Deponent	O
,	O
did	O
by	O
Mistake	O
write	O
the	O
Name	O
``	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Deceased	O
's	O
``	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lee	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
swore	O
this	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Welch	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
fat	O
Person	O
(	O
Lee	O
)	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Doctor	O
Chapman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
proper	O
Person	O
to	O
grant	O
Probates	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
granting	O
one	O
to	O
this	O
Will	O
;	O
-	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
Hand	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
swore	O
that	O
Affidavit	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
transacted	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Chambers	O
at	O
Doctors-Commons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Benedict	O
.	O
The	O
Probate	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Lee	O
.	O
Ask	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
what	O
Condition	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
made	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
;	O
his	O
Eyes	O
looked	O
heavy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
as	O
People	O
usually	O
do	O
under	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
perfectly	O
Sober	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
crazy	O
and	O
as	O
lunatic	O
as	O
any	O
Thing	O
could	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
thin	O
the	O
Child	O
that	O
is	O
unborn	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
thin	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
Fitzgerald	O
,	O
the	O
fat	O
one	O
is	O
Lee	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Fitzgerald	O
's	O
reputed	O
Wife	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ecklin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dernean	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Discourse	O
about	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Navy-Office	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
with	O
my	O
Coal-Man	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
walk	O
so	O
far	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
At	O
their	O
Desire	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
attempted	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
Company	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tyger	O
:	O
that	O
House	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
we	O
adjourned	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Crowns	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
We	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Lee	O
said	O
to	O
Fitzgerald	O
,	O
Dominick	O
!	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
we	O
come	O
about	O
!	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
do	O
that	O
Thing	O
?	O
So	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
said	O
Fitzgerald	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Paper	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
blank	O
Sailor	O
's	O
Will	O
.	O
He	O
filled	O
up	O
the	O
Spaces	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
James	O
Lee	O
signed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Parrel	I-pers
did	O
the	O
like	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dernean	I-pers
.	O
Counc	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Will	O
as	O
you	O
saw	O
Fitzgerald	O
fill	O
up	O
?	O
Ecklin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
rubbing	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
look	O
old	O
and	O
dirty	O
,	O
they	O
tore	O
it	O
here	O
before	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
's	O
;	O
besides	O
Fitzgerald	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Come	O
Mr.	O
Ecklin	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
this	O
Will	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
(	O
said	O
Lee	O
)	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
received	O
Money	O
but	O
last	O
Week	O
on	O
such	O
an	O
Account	O
as	O
this	O
;	O
no	O
Body	O
can	O
be	O
a	O
Sufferer	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
Money	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Chatham	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
never	O
pays	O
twice	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
excused	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Fitzgerald	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
any	O
Body	O
would	O
discover	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
run	O
a	O
Knife	O
into	O
him	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
Fitzgerald	O
's	O
Wife	O
there	O
?	O
Ecklin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
personated	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
known	O
me	O
?	O
Ecklin	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
intimate	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
known	O
me	O
?	O
Ecklin	O
.	O
About	O
6	O
or	O
8	O
Months	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
signed	O
the	O
Will	O
?	O
Ecklin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
Manner	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
he	O
keeps	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Clerk	O
i	O
n	O
the	O
Ticket-Office	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Navy	O
:	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Money	O
due	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Bentham	I-pers
?	O
Bentham	O
.	O
He	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
Lancaster	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
Decease	O
there	O
were	O
42	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Ticket	O
made	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
transmitted	O
by	O
the	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
to	O
the	O
Navy-Office	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Ticket	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
delivered	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
?	O
Bentham	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
myself	O
to	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
She	O
brought	O
the	O
Probate	O
of	O
a	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
He	O
owns	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
me	O
is	O
but	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
consider	O
that	O
it	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
forging	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
to	O
write	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
This	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
knew	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
formerly	O
made	O
a	O
Will	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
John	O
Perry	O
by	O
Mistake	O
.	O
That	O
Will	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
trump	O
'd	O
up	O
this	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
real	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
this	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
tear	O
me	O
to	O
Pieces	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Welch	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
sometimes	O
obliged	O
to	O
conceal	O
my	O
true	O
Name	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
32	O
,	O
33.	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
I	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Watson	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dogget	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lyons	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Dogget	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Oct.	O
33.	O
William	B-pers
Head	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mrs.	O
Watson	O
near	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
leaning	O
her	O
Head	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
.	O
She	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
her	O
Child	O
had	O
net	O
eat	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
Bread	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
a	O
Penny	O
.	O
She	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
hardly	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
Apartment	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
At	O
her	O
Request	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Holford	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
Dogget	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Present	O
.	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
knocked	O
with	O
her	O
Heel	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
below	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Above	O
!	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
above	O
.	O
Immediately	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
stole	O
down	O
Stairs	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Thief	O
myself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
Watson	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rice	O
's	O
in	O
Vinegar-Yard	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
5	O
s.	O
Poundage	O
for	O
pawning	O
it	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Candle	O
away	O
?	O
Head	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Head	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Head	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
in	O
Vinegar-Yard	O
.	O
One	O
Friday	O
Night	O
after	O
10	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Head	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
very	O
melancholy	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
They	O
say	O
one	O
Lyons	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Prudence	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
who	O
uses	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Watson	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Head	O
immediately	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Cordelia	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
Dogget	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Watson	O
wrung	O
her	O
Hands	O
and	O
cried	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Head	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
notwithstanding	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
refused	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
Dogget	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
send	O
to	O
the	O
Parliament	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
would	O
go	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
afterwards	O
brought	O
up	O
for	O
further	O
Examination	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dogget	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Crown	O
Poundage	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
to	O
Head	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
miss	O
your	O
Watch	O
?	O
Head	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
before	O
10	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Dogget	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
see	O
her	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
I	O
bring	O
in	O
any	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Head	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Dogget	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
,	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
serv	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
Drop	O
of	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Head	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
you	O
but	O
Watson	O
?	O
Head	O
.	O
One	O
Bess	B-pers
Dogget	I-pers
brought	O
up	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Watson	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
Dogget	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Dogget	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Ann	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
Oct.	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
gilt	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
Damask	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
And	O
36.	O
James	B-pers
Nelthorp	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Darling	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Hymer	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Hymer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
Robert	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Common-Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Book	O
called	O
the	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Gill	O
Blass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
St.	I-pers
John	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
39.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dimity	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Cazavan	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40.	O
Adam	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
of	O
-	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Sept.	O
on	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
Ribs	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Herne	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
beat	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
23d	O
of	O
Sept.	O
to	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
said	O
Shotton	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
to	O
commit	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
charg	O
'd	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Shotton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Cricket-Match	O
at	O
Staines	B-place
Moor	I-place
,	O
between	O
the	O
Men	O
of	O
Staines	O
and	O
Brentford	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulling	O
Herne	O
among	O
the	O
Croud	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Shotton	O
strike	O
him	O
twice	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
presently	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Deceased	O
engage	O
in	O
the	O
Play	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Pelton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
play	O
'd	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
bowl	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
ran	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
Reason	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
Pelton	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
in	O
to	O
play	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
more	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pelton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
him	O
to	O
force	O
him	O
to	O
o	O
la	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
forcing	O
he	O
chuck	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Shotton	O
strike	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Blows	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Opinion	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
but	O
Weeks	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Throat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
Thing	O
said	O
to	O
your	O
Brother	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
asked	O
to	O
play	O
before	O
by	O
any	O
Body	O
:	O
the	O
laying	O
hold	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
complain	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
playing	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
any	O
way	O
affected	O
by	O
those	O
Blows	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
it	O
to	O
help	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
to	O
pull	O
him	O
in	O
to	O
play	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
this	O
Man	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wicket	O
to	O
play	O
.	O
Shotton	O
hit	O
him	O
2	O
Blows	O
,	O
one	O
over	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
complain	O
of	O
any	O
Injury	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Witness	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
those	O
Rogues	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
the	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Collar	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
play	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
play	O
long	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Witness	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
one	O
Notch	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Rule	O
of	O
the	O
Play	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
the	O
next	O
Day	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
to	O
lead	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Wicket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Shotton	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Blows	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
He	O
complained	O
that	O
his	O
Breast	O
and	O
his	O
Throat	O
were	O
very	O
sore	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
pulling	O
him	O
along	O
chuck	O
'd	O
his	O
Throat	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
to	O
swallow	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
complained	O
of	O
the	O
Blow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Cricket-Match	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
's	O
Boat	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
low	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
so	O
barbarously	O
at	O
the	O
Cricket-Match	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Servant	O
drew	O
him	O
some	O
Beer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
drink	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
mention	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lie	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
all	O
Night	O
?	O
Banks	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
common	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
their	O
Boats	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
our	O
Beds	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Boat	O
?	O
Banks	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Three	O
Pidgeons	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Nurse	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Illness	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
Fever	O
and	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
Complaint	O
was	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
Side	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
lie	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
his	O
Complaint	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
those	O
Rognes	O
that	O
beat	O
one	O
have	O
killed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
them	O
,	O
hang	O
them	O
:	O
These	O
were	O
his	O
Words	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
all	O
black	O
on	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Ribs	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
Account	O
of	O
that	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stood	O
Umpter	O
(	O
Umpire	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Wicket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Demur	O
about	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bring	O
him	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Shotton	O
strike	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
.	O
He	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
unwilling	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
to	O
play	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
in	O
next	O
.	O
C.	O
What	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Shotton	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
this	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
except	O
they	O
laid	O
any	O
Betts	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
did	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
ran	O
one	O
Notch	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
End	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
make	O
any	O
particular	O
Complaint	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
civil	O
done	O
or	O
said	O
by	O
me	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
him	O
ill	O
any	O
otherwise	O
than	O
bringing	O
him	O
along	O
to	O
play	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dudhill	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
an	O
external	O
Contusion	O
on	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
Inches	O
Diameter	O
,	O
which	O
extended	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
Hypocondriack	O
.	O
Upon	O
opening	O
the	O
Body	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Cartilage	O
of	O
the	O
eighth	O
Rib	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
broken	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Thorax	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
between	O
15	O
or	O
20	O
Ounces	O
of	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
on	O
that	O
same	O
Side	O
were	O
vastly	O
inflam	O
'd	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
right	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Thorax	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Colon	O
and	O
the	O
interior	O
Parts	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
were	O
gangreen	O
'd	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
apprehend	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Dudhill	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Blows	O
I	O
should	O
imagine	O
,	O
and	O
certainly	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
for	O
otherwise	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
C.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Dudhill	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
opened	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
.	O
C.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
any	O
Fever	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
this	O
Disorder	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Dudhill	O
.	O
That	O
has	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
:	O
my	O
Opinion	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
proceeded	O
from	O
these	O
Bruises	O
and	O
Blows	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
common	O
in	O
a	O
malignant	O
Fever	O
to	O
have	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
inflamed	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Dudhill	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
that	O
Rib	O
be	O
broke	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Dudhill	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
might	O
.	O
C.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Appearance	O
of	O
Blackness	O
upon	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Rib	O
was	O
broke	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Dudhill	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
Inches	O
Diameter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
any	O
Person	O
receives	O
a	O
Blow	O
,	O
will	O
the	O
Cartilage	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Rib	O
break	O
first	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Dudhill	O
.	O
The	O
Cartilage	O
would	O
break	O
sooner	O
than	O
the	O
Rib	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Cricket-Match	O
between	O
the	O
Towns	O
of	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
Staines	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Friend	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
thought	O
we	O
might	O
after	O
Dinner	O
divert	O
ourselves	O
in	O
seeing	O
this	O
Cricket-Match	O
.	O
They	O
played	O
very	O
easy	O
and	O
quiet	O
till	O
the	O
latter	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Game	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
Brentford	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
neither	O
of	O
those	O
Men	O
would	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
so	O
a	O
great	O
Uproar	O
began	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Coat	O
was	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
very	O
inoffensively	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
d	O
-	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
play	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
worse	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
stand	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
them	O
righted	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
20	O
l.	O
He	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
smoaking	O
a	O
Pipe	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
Sue	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
20	O
l.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempt	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
Shotton	O
meddle	O
with	O
him	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
the	O
Man	O
play	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Humour	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
one	O
Neighbour	O
does	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
Horseback	O
on	O
a	O
pretty	O
bighish	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
talk	O
'd	O
off	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
seemed	O
unwilling	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
play	O
a	O
fair	O
Game	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
assist	O
the	O
Staines	O
Men	O
in	O
getting	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
play	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
'till	O
he	O
was	O
bowl	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
done	O
to	O
hurt	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
was	O
never	O
higher	O
than	O
his	O
Breast	O
.	O
He	O
afterwards	O
leap	O
'd	O
and	O
skip	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
most	O
active	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
and	O
twenty	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
above	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
played	O
many	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Cricket	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
just	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
in	O
the	O
Time	O
before	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
would	O
go	O
in	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
his	O
Turn	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
loosed	O
him	O
,	O
Shotton	O
struck	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
junior	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
lose	O
the	O
Money	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
20	O
l.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
shuffled	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Kitt	O
Shotton	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
push	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
You	O
call	O
it	O
a	O
push	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
Shotton	O
give	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Blows	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
?	O
Haysler	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
Push	O
could	O
break	O
his	O
Ribs	O
?	O
Haysler	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
hurt	O
him	O
neither	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Haysler	I-pers
,	O
senior	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
horse	O
Chaise	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
the	O
Man	O
along	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
got	O
loose	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
Seat	O
,	O
and	O
Blows	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
Game	O
plaid	O
out	O
?	O
Haysler	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
about	O
thirteen	O
Minutes	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
play	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
looked	O
as	O
sprightly	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
Blows	O
or	O
Fighting	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Merrick	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
very	O
strong	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
a	O
malignant	O
Fever	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
sufficient	O
to	O
kill	O
any	O
Man	O
without	O
Bruises	O
.	O
I	O
viewed	O
his	O
Body	O
in	O
his	O
Life-time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
Blackness	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dudhill	O
apprehended	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Mischief	O
about	O
his	O
Ribs	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
one	O
Cartilage	O
to	O
stand	O
hither	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
press	O
hard	O
enough	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
broken	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
any	O
Complaints	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Merrick	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
rather	O
too	O
low	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
;	O
what	O
Questions	O
I	O
asked	O
about	O
his	O
Disorder	O
,	O
were	O
rather	O
answered	O
by	O
the	O
People	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Haysler	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
different	O
Numbers	O
of	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
Man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
41	O
,	O
42	O
,	O
43.	O
Robert	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
hundred	O
one	O
quarter	O
,	O
5	O
pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Scotch	O
Snuff	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hominy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
Nov.	O
14	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
Abram	B-pers
Sweeting	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
28	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
And	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
five	O
Pounds	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
knowing	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Hominy	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Brandel	O
and	O
Barnes	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
John	B-pers
