TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1741	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XLI	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
DANIEL	B-pers
LAMBERT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PROBYN	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
FORTESCUE	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Salventine	B-pers
Savery	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Seagrave	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bohun	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Grainger	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gatton	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kinnister	I-pers
,	O
1	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Brooks	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Linen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
Linen	O
Stocks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Stock-Buckle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linen	O
Stock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
May	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Bazil	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
,	I-pers
Basil	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
being	O
certain	O
Pieces	O
made	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Israel	I-pers
,	O
June	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3	O
,	O
4.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Angel-Inn	O
,	O
Islington	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
13th	O
or	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
Sheep	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Word	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Mutton	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-House	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
they	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sheep	O
.	O
They	O
very	O
particularly	O
described	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
some	O
Steps	O
and	O
over	O
a	O
Stile	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
rising	O
Hill	O
or	O
Bank	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Sheep	O
up	O
the	O
Field	O
and	O
dressed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
Hay-Cock	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
no	O
other	O
Sheep	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
but	O
this	O
?	O
Day	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
Robinson	O
mark	O
his	O
Sheep	O
with	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Skin	O
?	O
Day	O
.	O
A	O
Fleur	O
de	O
Lis	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
other	O
Marks	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ilsley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Alder	O
in	O
King's-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
posture	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
that	O
made	O
him	O
go	O
almost	O
double	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
falling	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
could	O
overtake	O
him	O
again	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Tothill-Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
who	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
their	O
Doors	O
,	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
hind	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pretty	O
large	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Neck	O
and	O
Breast	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
Thompson	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Debt	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
kill	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
that	O
Butchers	O
kill	O
their	O
Meat	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
.	O
He	O
still	O
kept	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
us	O
the	O
Man	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
sold	O
any	O
Mutton	O
to	O
Alder	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Hind	B-pers
Quarter	I-pers
of	O
Mutton	O
hanging	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Sheep	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
Alder	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Fat	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Shirt	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
it	O
signified	O
nothing	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
did	O
steal	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
dinner	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Falconer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
Soldier	O
,	O
(	O
Alder	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Load	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
in	O
King's-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
flesh	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
that	O
owed	O
him	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
of	O
his	O
Debt	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-House	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Alder	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Colonel	O
De	O
Viel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
likewise	O
present	O
when	O
Thompson	O
and	O
Alder	O
were	O
together	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
it	O
signified	O
nothing	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
Primrose	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
equally	O
concerned	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Mutton	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Sheep	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Alder	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Field	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
Sheep	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
Primrose-Hill	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Thompson	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
weary	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
under	O
a	O
Hay-Cock	O
to	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Mutton	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
and	O
heard	O
Alder	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
this	O
Mutton	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Field	O
going	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
Primrose-Hill	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
;	O
we	O
enlisted	O
him	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
lay	O
in	O
Hounslow	O
Camp	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
Tent	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Barclay	I-pers
.	O
Alder	O
used	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Running	O
Footman	O
,	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
honestly	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Running	O
Footman	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Standix	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Thompson	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Year	O
1739	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
dishonest	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5	O
,	O
6.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gloide	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
Arabella	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
Cap	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Straw	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Arabella	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
;	O
March	O
10th	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
desire	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Arabella	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Coach	O
No	O
248	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Steers	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
Coach	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
highest	O
end	O
of	O
Bridges-Street	O
,	O
by	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Catharine	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
stop	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
regard	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
continued	O
going	O
on	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Somerset	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
thither	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Rascal	O
,	O
what	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
my	O
Coach	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Steers	O
then	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach-Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
hand	O
he	O
employed	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
indecent	O
manner	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
paid	O
no	O
regard	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
other	O
Man	O
appear	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
kept	O
beating	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Butt	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Whip	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
you	O
alone	O
,	O
what	O
followed	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
Steers	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Backside	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
While	O
Steers	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
another	O
Man	O
(	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
)	O
poked	O
in	O
his	O
Whip	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Handle	O
of	O
it	O
struck	O
out	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
sore	O
Teeth	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
Steers	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
Watch	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Steers	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Cloak	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
2	O
Women	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
B	O
-	O
ch	O
,	O
what	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
our	O
Husbands	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
several	O
Blows	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Steers	O
cut	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
small	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Whip	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
over	O
against	O
Somerset	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
there	O
hearing	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Men	O
took	O
to	O
their	O
Coach	O
and	O
drove	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Cellar	O
by	O
the	O
New-Church	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Condition	O
did	O
they	O
leave	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
Without	O
my	O
Cap	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Apron	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
over	O
Blood	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Things	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Steers	O
,	O
and	O
Gloide	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
stopped	O
with	O
their	O
Coach	O
at	O
this	O
Cellar-Door	O
,	O
what	O
follow	O
'd	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
3	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Men	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Scar	O
on	O
his	O
Eye	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
neither	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
although	O
they	O
had	O
changed	O
Coats	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
Steers	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
that	O
was	O
sufficient	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hackney-Coach	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
there	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
for	O
about	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
and	O
Steers	O
were	O
both	O
summoned	O
to	O
appear	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
Clark	O
appeared	O
,	O
but	O
Steers	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
desired	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
indict	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
Steers	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
another	O
Crown	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
not	O
taken	O
till	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Distance	O
between	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
remember	O
either	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
Lights	O
against	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
Steers	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
could	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
Thing	O
as	O
to	O
Gloide	O
?	O
Strickland	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
recollect	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
whom	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
with	O
Steers	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
did	O
they	O
own	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Steers	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
horse-whipped	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
robbing	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
horse-whipped	O
me	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Gloide	O
confess	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
Gloide	O
only	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
commit	O
Indecencies	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
that	O
they	O
confessed	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
No	O
nothing	O
else	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
horse-whipped	O
me	O
because	O
they	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Whore	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
she	O
own	O
to	O
several	O
People	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
fuddled	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Murphey	O
or	O
Mrs.	O
Rockham	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
Women	O
tore	O
your	O
Pocket	O
off	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
only	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Business	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
their	O
Husbands	O
.	O
Steers	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
that	O
you	O
staid	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
from	O
March	O
to	O
June	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
us	O
up	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
besides	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
hear	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
our	O
Stand	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
Time	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
only	O
out	O
at	O
Nights	O
;	O
besides	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
about	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
Strickland	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Stand	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Catharine	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
murdered	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Lashes	O
of	O
a	O
Whip	O
for	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Parish	O
I	O
durst	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
except	O
she	O
could	O
call	O
the	O
other	O
Watchmen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
3	O
other	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Woodward	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
standing	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Men	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
first	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
Steers	O
shuffling	O
about	O
from	O
one	O
Table	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
hide	O
his	O
Whip	O
.	O
I	O
accused	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Woman	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Steers	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
she	O
might	O
never	O
rise	O
more	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Man	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Haydon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
Gloide	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
discovered	O
Steers	O
would	O
she	O
have	O
charged	O
you	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Haydon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
sufficient	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
our	O
Brains	O
beat	O
out	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Steers	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
pushed	O
the	O
Woman	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
looked	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
whipped	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
said	O
;	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
B	O
-	O
ch	O
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Farthing	O
I	O
would	O
horse	O
whip	O
you	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
to	O
the	O
Coach-Office	O
about	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
summoned	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
her	O
another	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
Steers	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Haydon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Steers	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
whipped	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
double	O
thong	O
'd	O
Whip	O
:	O
The	O
Justice	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Gloide	O
,	O
smiled	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
your	O
Stand	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
Haydon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
her	O
Landlady	O
's	O
Cloak	O
,	O
her	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Persons	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
she	O
charge	O
some	O
Women	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Hay	O
don	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Women	O
came	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
At	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
drove	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
248	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
a	O
Summons	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Complaint	O
against	O
that	O
Number	O
to	O
appear	O
at	O
the	O
Office	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
Summons	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Complaint	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
appear	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
a	O
bed	O
the	O
best	O
Part	O
of	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
instead	O
of	O
appearing	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Promise	O
,	O
he	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
and	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
complain	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
went	O
into	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Steers	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
,	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
Apron	O
and	O
Cap	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Power	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
afterward	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
5	O
d.	O
or	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
get	O
blooded	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
De	O
Viel	O
,	O
and	O
Steers	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
Glide	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Steers	O
being	O
asked	O
why	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
Coach	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Glide	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
2	O
o'clock	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Glide	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
with	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
Woodward	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
Word	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Westminster	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Linkman	O
on	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
Woman	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Strokes	O
with	O
his	O
Whip	O
.	O
Gloide	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
this	O
Woman	O
live	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
then	O
at	O
one	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
in	O
King	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
Russel	O
Street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
Steers	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
Warrant	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
7	O
Days	O
.	O
-	O
Black	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Parish	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
Steers	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Men	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
in	O
Bow	O
Street	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
Gloide	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
speak	O
in	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
Steers	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
what	O
would	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
them	O
both	O
together	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Gloide	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
Steers	O
said	O
he	O
horse-whipped	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
double	O
Thong	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Steers	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Gloide	O
with	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
he	O
staid	O
long	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Woodward	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
stopped	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
Somerset	O
House	O
Water	O
Gate	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
that	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Fellow	O
on	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
Gloide	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Catharine	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Woodward	O
's	O
Cellar	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
watered	O
my	O
Horses	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
Gloide	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
in	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
this	O
Woman	O
came	O
with	O
this	O
Watchman	O
to	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
2	O
Women	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
I	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
my	O
Coat	O
.	O
Gloide	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Southampton	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Cast	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
waiting	O
at	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
Withers	O
's	O
Work	O
,	O
Gloide	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Westminster	O
with	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Job	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
Westminster	O
,	O
that	O
Woman	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Southampton	O
Street	O
.	O
Gloide	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
Ride	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
trust	O
herself	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drove	O
on	O
slowly	O
to	O
Somerset	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Coachman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Legs	O
with	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
for	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
.	O
Gloide	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Steers	O
took	O
the	O
Woman	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
his	O
Whip	O
a	O
little	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
cried	O
out	O
Watch	O
!	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
seeing	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
near	O
her	O
Clothes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Coach	O
stood	O
about	O
2	O
Yards	O
beyond	O
Somerset	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
above	O
10	O
Yards	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
House	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
what	O
passed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
locked	O
out	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
my	O
Brother	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
Scott	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Night	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
in	O
Lewkener	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
(	O
Strickland	O
)	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
took	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Cap	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Men	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Buckham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
Smallcoal-Dust	O
in	O
Lewkener	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
say	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
2	O
Women	O
robbed	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
Landlady	O
'd	O
velvet	O
Hood	O
and	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Gloide	O
did	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
Steers	O
horse-whipped	O
her	O
.	O
Gloide	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Strickland	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
?	O
Buckham	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Murphey	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
Steers	O
horse-whipped	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Women	O
punched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lost	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
Gloide	O
did	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
a	O
Question	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
Gloide	O
's	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Fool	O
,	O
and	O
foolish	O
Tom	B-pers
Gloide	I-pers
is	O
a	O
common	O
Word	O
in	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Leneve	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
in	O
Dark-house	O
Lane	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
wished	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
damned	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
till	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Night-Cellar	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
a	O
Scar	O
under	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
very	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
he	O
robbed	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
Steers	O
for	O
he	O
horse-whipped	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Leneve	O
's	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Refreshment	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Woman	O
(	O
Strickland	O
)	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Leneve	O
in	O
Discourse	O
together	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Leneve	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
robbed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Coachman	O
or	O
Tradesman	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Night-Cellar	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Gravesend	O
Waterman	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
this	O
Woman	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
in	O
Darkhouse	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
plyed	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
going	O
by	O
Water	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
some	O
Men	O
had	O
prompted	O
her	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
save	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
asked	O
who	O
the	O
Persons	O
were	O
that	O
robbed	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Tradesman	O
or	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
till	O
a	O
Man	O
shewed	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Night-Cellar	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Father	O
keeps	O
an	O
Ale-Cellar	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
His	O
Name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Steers	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
Cellar	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Day	O
:	O
He	O
staid	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
less	O
,	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
,	O
Gloide	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
before	O
Strickland	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
somebody	O
shewed	O
her	O
Steers	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
whipped	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
without	O
mentioning	O
a	O
Word	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Charles-Street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
Street-Walker	O
.	O
Steers	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
rob	O
any	O
Body	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Strickland	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
;	O
she	O
lives	O
at	O
one	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
in	O
King	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
Russel	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
Street	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Steers	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Steers	O
about	O
18	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
accused	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
as	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
robbed	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Steers	O
a	O
dozen	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
bears	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gloide	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
or	O
Child	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gloide	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
sucked	O
at	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
robbed	O
or	O
assionted	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Gloide	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
Steers	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
7.	O
William	B-pers
Cornew	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
2	O
Quart	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Colwell	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Ann	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Abraham	I-pers
)	I-pers
Bradey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
lb	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
;	O
June	O
19th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9.	O
James	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Three	O
Pounds	O
Twelve	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
6	O
Thirty	O
Six	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tortoiseshell	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Westover	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
April	O
12th	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Westover	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
this	O
Money	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
safe	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
my	O
Chamber	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
unlock	O
my	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
:	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Inside	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
imagining	O
he	O
might	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
other	O
Apprentice	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
down	O
Stairs	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Drawer	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
Painter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
use	O
his	O
Master	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
People	O
were	O
waiting	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
spent	O
at	O
the	O
White-Conduit-House	O
,	O
in	O
White-Conduit	O
Fields	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Drawer	O
with	O
this	O
Knife	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Directions	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
his	O
Master	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Long	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
;	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Knife	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Drawers	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
his	O
Master	O
come	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
recommended	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
Object	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Mercy	O
.	O
10.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Quart	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Pint	O
Pots	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
;	O
July	O
1st	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11.	O
Ann	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
June	O
4th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
pretty	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
thinking	O
to	O
stay	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Brick-maker	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
Night	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Brick-maker	O
got	O
him	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alone	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
bed	O
long	O
before	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
Gin	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
weary	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
she	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Bond	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
Father	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
only	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
Farthing	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9th	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Whitechapel	O
with	O
2	O
other	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
Pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
Petticoat	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
pursue	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	B-pers
Alderman	I-pers
Westley	I-pers
at	O
Guild	O
Hall	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Pendon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Westley	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
,	O
14	O
,	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Carnaby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
outside	O
and	O
inside	O
Cases	O
made	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe	O
Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Knee-Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
36	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spectacles	O
with	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Case	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
spotted	O
linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Stopper	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Thirty	O
Six	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Silver	O
Coin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
May	O
28th	O
.	O
J.	O
R	O
..	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
New-Wells	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Bull	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Eccles	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
should	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Norman	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Cable	I-place
Stree	I-place
t.	O
She	O
shewed	O
me	O
up	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Eades	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
other	O
Women	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
a	O
Blanket	O
or	O
Rug	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
sat	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Eccles	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
all	O
those	O
Things	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
fell	O
asleep	O
?	O
J.	O
R	O
..	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
did	O
you	O
awake	O
?	O
J.	O
R	O
..	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
before	O
the	O
Wells	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Tap-House	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
late	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
not	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
or	O
were	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
J.R	O
..	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
very	O
sober	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Senses	O
enough	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Things	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
People	O
milking	O
their	O
Cattle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Milk	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
'wak	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
off	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
Boys	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
covered	O
over	O
and	O
hid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manley	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
which	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
Knee-Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
Stopper	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Bag	O
which	O
contained	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
here	O
is	O
not	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Eccles	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knows	O
this	O
Shilling	O
?	O
J.	O
R	O
..	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
very	O
Shilling	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
:	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
leaden	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Fob-Pocket	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
This	O
Silver	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
was	O
likewise	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Pikington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Tothill-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Buckles	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
other	O
Girl	O
came	O
up	O
equipp	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Eades	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
bought	O
Buckles	O
.	O
The	O
Neighbours	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
observe	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
believed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suspecting	O
them	O
myself	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manley	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
Purse	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Eades	O
in	O
the	O
Gate	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
J.	O
R	O
's	O
.	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
not	O
thinking	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
let	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
go	O
together	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
2	O
least	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
,	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Boys	O
informing	O
us	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
deposited	O
by	O
the	O
Girls	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
them	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
the	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Tobacco-Stopper	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
J.	O
R	O
's	O
.	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Eades	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
13	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
Oath	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Devil	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
take	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Buckles	O
from	O
his	O
Shoes	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
Eades	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
13	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
Oath	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Devil	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Eades	O
take	O
Mr.	O
J.	O
R	O
's	O
.	O
Watch	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Buckles	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Bag	O
with	O
some	O
Gold	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Shoes	O
on	O
?	O
J.	O
R.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Boots	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
The	O
Buckles	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Knees	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Paine	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
only	O
the	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
taken	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Eades	O
.	O
That	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
he	O
waked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
these	O
Girls	O
Money	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
is	O
entirely	O
false	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Paine	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Oath	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Mr.	O
J.	O
R.	O
give	O
the	O
Girls	O
any	O
Money	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
and	O
Eades	O
alone	O
?	O
Paine	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
J.	O
R.	O
was	O
asleep	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
our	O
Room	O
at	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
this	O
Money	O
to	O
quit	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
We	O
wanted	O
some	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
bought	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
met	O
us	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Mr.	O
J.	O
R.	O
;	O
he	O
clapp	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
he	O
should	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
dogg	O
'd	O
me	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
this	O
leaden	O
Shilling	O
to	O
quit	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
him	O
and	O
Eades	O
alone	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
with	O
Eades	O
and	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
J.	O
R.	O
brought	O
this	O
Girl	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
take	O
us	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
J.	O
R.	O
Every	O
Word	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
have	O
said	O
is	O
absolutely	O
false	O
.	O
Pilkington	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
pretended	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
this	O
Defence	O
.	O
Eades	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Stratford	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
Colour	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wash	I-pers
;	O
May	O
31st	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
from	O
Colengale	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Essex	I-place
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Bow	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
faddled	O
and	O
bridled	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Bow	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
lie	O
at	O
another	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Stable	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
seeing	O
her	O
Shoes	O
were	O
bad	O
,	O
immediately	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
at	O
Halstead	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
was	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
to	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
not	O
satisfied	O
with	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
any	O
Name	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
then	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
cried	O
at	O
Rumford	O
and	O
Epping	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
the	O
Collar-Maker	O
,	O
sent	O
a	O
Letter	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wash	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
Wash	O
.	O
The	O
Mare	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Edwards	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
Bow	O
is	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
Mare	O
?	O
Wash	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
40	O
Miles	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
at	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
Wash	O
's	O
and	O
designed	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
but	O
Business	O
prevented	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sat	O
out	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Spread-Eagle	O
in	O
Grace-Church	O
Street	O
to	O
inform	O
Wash	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
went	O
together	O
to	O
Bow	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Mare	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
same	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Wash	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
Spot	O
on	O
her	O
Flank	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wash	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Mare	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Bow	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Wash	O
lost	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Haggard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
tell	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
to	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
again	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
as	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Work	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Things	O
,	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
Home	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
Home	O
my	O
Friends	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
my	O
Things	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
follows	O
the	O
farming	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Horse	O
whenever	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Horses	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
made	O
bold	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Horses	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
Mr.	O
Wash	O
may	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
concerning	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
Wash	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Son	O
.	O
His	O
Friends	O
bear	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
his	O
Father	O
live	O
so	O
near	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
your	O
Horses	O
run	O
together	O
?	O
Wash.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
go	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Lay	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
his	O
Friends	O
bear	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
Servant	O
with	O
this	O
Man	O
.	O
Lay	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Servant	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
18	O
,	O
19.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rouse	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Minton	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
about	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
5	O
Years	O
;	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Callimanco	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Stay	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Minton	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Minton	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Minton	I-pers
is	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
for	O
stripping	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
a	O
Gown	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
Vine	O
's	O
in	O
Albemarle-Street	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
this	O
Child	O
under	O
my	O
Care	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
I	O
drest	O
her	O
in	O
this	O
Coat	O
and	O
Stay	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
play	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
Home	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
8	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
Dung-hill	O
without	O
her	O
Coat	O
and	O
Stay	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
her	O
Frock	O
was	O
cut	O
from	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
pinn	O
'd	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
by	O
two	O
Girls	O
,	O
who	O
promised	O
her	O
a	O
plum	O
cake	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
things	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Tottenham-Court	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
sent	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Daughter	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
her	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Fields	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
twenty	O
yards	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
Child	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
Lay-stall	O
or	O
Dung-hill	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
's	O
Daughter	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
``	O
Ruth	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
if	O
those	O
2	O
creatures	O
``	O
have	O
not	O
stripped	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
``	O
old	O
one	O
have	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
''	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
those	O
Women	O
were	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
Coat	O
and	O
Stay	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
bid	O
the	O
Child	O
sit	O
still	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
within	O
two	O
Fields	O
of	O
Pancras	O
.	O
The	O
great	O
one	O
,	O
Rouse	O
,	O
made	O
several	O
attempts	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
a	O
Bank	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
slung	O
this	O
Coat	O
and	O
Stay	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
stripp	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
ourselves	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
grow	O
robustical	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
we	O
called	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
our	O
assistance	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
secur	O
'd	O
them	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
help	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
great	O
one	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
``	O
Mall	O
,	O
``	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
to	O
buy	O
you	O
a	O
new	O
Gown	O
,	O
I	O
``	O
had	O
not	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
''	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
to	O
serve	O
herself	O
and	O
not	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Field	O
off	O
when	O
Rouse	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Rouse	O
when	O
she	O
decoy	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Lay-stall	O
?	O
Bagley	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
Rouse	O
decoy	O
the	O
Child	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
her	O
a	O
Plum-cake	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
Servant	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
:	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Child	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
Lay-stall	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
those	O
creatures	O
had	O
stripped	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
old	O
one	O
,	O
Rouse	O
,	O
have	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Lay-stall	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
?	O
Giles	O
.	O
Very	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
leading	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
something	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
replied	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
there	O
presently	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
her	O
Stay	O
on	O
?	O
Giles	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
her	O
Frock	O
on	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Lay-stall	O
,	O
we	O
asked	O
the	O
Child	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
coat	O
and	O
stay	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
we	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
great	O
one	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
supposed	O
we	O
had	O
stripp	O
'd	O
the	O
child	O
ourselves	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Jennison	I-pers
coming	O
to	O
our	O
assistance	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
secured	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
great	O
one	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
out	O
of	O
Albemarle-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
.	O
The	O
great	O
one	O
,	O
Rouse	O
,	O
likewise	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
to	O
have	O
bought	O
Smith	O
a	O
new	O
gown	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
this	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Jennison	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
were	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
to	O
Pancras	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
2	O
girls	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Road	O
crying	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
ditch	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
:	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
ditch	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
sister	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
child	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Rouse	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Giles	O
's	O
at	O
Tottenham-Court	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
great	O
one	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
robbed	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
a	O
new	O
gown	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
till	O
a	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Trent	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
busy	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
,	O
where	O
Rouse	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
from	O
Albemarle-Street	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Tottenham-Court	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
hear	O
them	O
say	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Giles	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
Dung-hill	O
or	O
Lay-stall	O
near	O
the	O
highway	O
?	O
Giles	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
highway	O
.	O
Bagley	O
.	O
It	O
lies	O
open	O
to	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
neither	O
hedge	O
nor	O
ditch	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Rouse	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Edward	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dressing	O
glass	O
,	O
a	O
mahogony	O
tea-board	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
mahogony	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5th	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Tompkins	O
in	O
Moor	O
Fields	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
mov	O
'd	O
my	O
goods	O
away	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Tompkins	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Perk	I-pers
.	O
The	O
unhappy	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
my	O
son	O
:	O
his	O
character	O
from	O
his	O
cradle	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
honest	O
and	O
just	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
can	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
dishonest	O
action	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Purcas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
fellow	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
James	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
glass	O
globe	O
lamps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Butrich	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pike	O
,	O
18	O
Eels	O
,	O
and	O
96	O
Craw-Fish	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
October	O
25th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
24.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Castaigne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Nisswith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
mouth-piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Case	I-pers
;	O
June	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Case	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
George	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
Hayes	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
&	O
c.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
on	O
Eli	B-pers
Dupree	I-pers
feloniously	O
,	O
willfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
along	O
the	O
common	O
highway	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
2	O
surlongs	O
and	O
upwards	O
the	O
said	O
Dupree	O
did	O
drag	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
feet	O
on	O
the	O
legs	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Dupree	O
divers	O
times	O
did	O
kick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
,	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
to	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
ground	O
the	O
said	O
Dupree	O
divers	O
times	O
did	O
throw	O
and	O
cast	O
down	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
dragging	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
divers	O
mortal	O
bruises	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
back	O
and	O
legs	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
11	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
God	O
will	O
not	O
bless	O
me	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
George	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
seeing	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
at	O
Hayes	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
Day	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
done	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
Man	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
hard	O
by	O
the	O
Angel	O
at	O
Hayes	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
He	O
damn	O
'd	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
Sir	O
do	O
n't	O
damn	O
my	O
Blood	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
pilsering	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
throw	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Gate	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
he	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
fell	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Gate	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
Gate	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Gate	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Man	O
make	O
any	O
Complaints	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
He	O
cried	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Thing	O
done	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
thrown	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Cart-Rut	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
again	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
Sir	O
,	O
not	O
'till	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
Light	O
there	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Angel	O
does	O
your	O
Father	O
live	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
at	O
Coombes	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
13	O
Miles	O
from	O
the	O
Angel	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
Night	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
and	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
my	O
Aunt	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
Stones	O
throw	O
from	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
Home	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
any	O
Body	O
what	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Aunt	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
almost	O
as	O
old	O
as	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
called	O
next	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
of	O
so	O
tender	O
an	O
Age	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
proper	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
sworn	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Hayes	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
there	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
bringing	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
drunken	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
drunk	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
idle	O
Fellow	O
and	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
some	O
Body	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Conveniency	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
from	O
Woodrosse	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
long	O
enough	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drunk	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
sober	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
distant	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
keeps	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
bringing	O
him	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Intention	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
but	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
duck	O
him	O
well	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
Man	O
hearing	O
him	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
said	O
in	O
a	O
low	O
Tone	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
will	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
hear	O
the	O
Rogue	O
,	O
now	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
will	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
Then	O
a	O
young	O
Fellow	O
took	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
gently	O
under	O
the	O
Gateway	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
poor	O
Soul	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
somebody	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
throw	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Gate	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
hit	O
upon	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
Man	O
then	O
cried	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lie	O
there	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
Sister	O
Walker	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
Mrs	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
me	O
put	O
this	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Rogue	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
to-morrow	O
he	O
will	O
swear	O
I	O
have	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
14	O
d	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
ducked	O
him	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
a	O
Man	O
went	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
turned	O
a	O
Man	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
drunk	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
then	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
stand	O
.	O
Presently	O
afterwards	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
dying	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
moved	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
.	O
We	O
called	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
about	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
little	O
Rum	O
,	O
Water	O
and	O
Sugar	O
in	O
a	O
Sp	O
oon	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
swallowed	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
his	O
Head	O
or	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
scratch	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
strip	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Clothes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Raisins	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Bread	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
all	O
wet	O
.	O
His	O
Shirt	O
was	O
dry	O
just	O
on	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Part	O
was	O
wet	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
'till	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
Body	O
brought	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
him	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Coroner	O
or	O
Surgeon	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
apprehend	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
against	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
judge	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Saturday	O
in	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
travel	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
much	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulling	O
another	O
rudely	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
you	O
use	O
the	O
Man	O
so	O
roughly	O
;	O
you	O
will	O
break	O
his	O
Legs	O
;	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
see	O
his	O
Legs	O
bend	O
under	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
imagined	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
jogging	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
Man	O
behind	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
London	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
an	O
offer	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
,	O
sorry	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
the	O
carts	O
and	O
waggons	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
duck	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
would	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
then	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
weary	O
and	O
weak	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
apprehend	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sick	O
or	O
a	O
dying	O
Man	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
weary	O
and	O
weak	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
any	O
Mischief	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
before	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
happened	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
George	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
at	O
Hayes	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
bustle	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
pilsering	O
Rogue	O
that	O
has	O
lurked	O
about	O
the	O
Road	O
ever	O
since	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
rob	O
somebody	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
nor	O
whither	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Pond	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Knees	O
bending	O
under	O
him	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
along	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
pilsering	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
rob	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	B-pers
Door	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
myself	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
Murder	O
!	O
What	O
happened	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
along	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
misuse	O
him	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Ashman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drawing	O
the	O
Man	O
along	O
at	O
Hayes	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
him	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
drawing	O
him	O
very	O
easily	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
you	O
think	O
could	O
be	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Ashman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answered	O
,	O
they	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
Man	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lie	O
prostrate	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pulling	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
insisting	O
on	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Coachman	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
Man	O
alone	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
himself	O
he	O
will	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
comes	O
of	O
listning	O
to	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
foolish	O
Women	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
Man	O
then	O
complained	O
of	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
still	O
insisted	O
on	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Pond	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
Murder	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
imagine	O
he	O
did	O
by	O
the	O
Answer	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
old	O
Rogue	O
,	O
he	O
cries	O
Murder	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
any	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
marks	O
except	O
a	O
few	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
spots	O
on	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
any	O
violence	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
in	O
pulling	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
Bruise	O
which	O
you	O
saw	O
on	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
indeed	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Bruise	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
swelled	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
the	O
Skin	O
broke	O
.	O
These	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Garters	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
wore	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Bruise	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
spots	O
on	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
those	O
were	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
;	O
-	O
They	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
for	O
any	O
Thing	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dupree	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
these	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Garters	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
my	O
Brother	O
Eli	O
Dupree	O
wore	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
Gloucester	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
murdered	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
about	O
some	O
Worsted-Yarn	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
75	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
quiet	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
ever	O
lived	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
for	O
these	O
32	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
drank	O
any	O
Liquor	O
but	O
what	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
Spoon	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Sidey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Deceased	O
30	O
Years	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Cow	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Change	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
Rent	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
rose	O
at	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
boiled	O
him	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
Milk	O
for	O
his	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
eat	O
up	O
very	O
heartily	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
directly	O
for	O
Gloucester	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Home	O
by	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
perfect	O
Health	O
and	O
had	O
these	O
very	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Garters	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
drank	O
any	O
Thing	O
but	O
Milk	O
these	O
30	O
Years	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
spite	O
or	O
malice	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
Inn	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
12	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
either	O
a	O
quarrelsom	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
addicted	O
to	O
drunkenness	O
.	O
Mintey	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Peace	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
in	O
all	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
give	O
any	O
abusesul	O
(	O
abusive	O
)	O
language	O
;	O
neither	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
abused	O
or	O
desranded	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
Job	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Years	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
rather	O
put	O
up	O
with	O
an	O
Injury	O
than	O
resent	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
Years	O
:	O
He	O
always	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
quiet	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
bad	O
Action	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
28.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hagan	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Egan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crossley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Alice	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
2	O
lb	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Pocket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Loadstone	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
silver	O
Button	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
1	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Alice	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
November	O
7	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
November	O
was	O
twelvemonths	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
some	O
Men	O
between	B-place
the	I-place
two	I-place
little	I-place
Bridges	I-place
in	I-place
Holloway	I-place
Road	I-place
.	O
They	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
complexioned	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
carrotty	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Crossley	O
to	O
be	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Crossley	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
without	O
taking	O
any	O
Thing	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
Things	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
returned	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
Face	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Pocket	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Loadstone	O
,	O
3	O
Keys	O
,	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Ring	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
lb	O
of	O
Butter	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Basket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
this	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Perry	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
afterwards	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
sight	O
before	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
any	O
Body	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Perry	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
a	O
mischief	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
him	O
up	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
summoned	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
no	O
discovery	O
that	O
Crossley	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
summoned	O
in	O
?	O
Perry	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Row	O
at	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
rode	O
the	O
Horses	O
at	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
present	O
except	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Crossley	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hagan	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rowlins	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
last	O
November	O
was	O
twelvemonths	O
.	O
Crossley	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Long	O
Canseway	O
in	O
Holloway	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
Hagan	O
and	O
Rawlins	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
to	O
watch	O
while	O
we	O
robbed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
lodging	O
;	O
and	O
Crossley	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
Hay-Loft	O
where	O
we	O
usually	O
lay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
again	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
parted	O
the	O
Booty	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
divide	O
it	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
We	O
divided	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
before	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Crossley	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lewis	O
's	O
Hay	O
Lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Banister	O
's	O
where	O
they	O
lodged	O
.	O
We	O
broke	O
the	O
Loadstone	O
which	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Silver	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
shared	O
it	O
among	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
Penny	O
divided	O
among	O
you	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
all	O
share	O
and	O
share	O
alike	O
.	O
We	O
likewise	O
took	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
Keys	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
flung	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
.	O
Perry	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Half	O
pence	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
White	O
.	O
What	O
could	O
you	O
divide	O
a	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
money	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Crossley	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
the	O
silver	O
which	O
you	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Loadstone	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
d	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
's	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
Crossley	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
we	O
drink	O
the	O
liquor	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
Banister	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
.	O
Crossley	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
liquor	O
had	O
we	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
full	O
pots	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Perry	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
man	O
(	O
White	O
)	O
like	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
attacked	O
you	O
?	O
Perry	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
blackish	O
complexioned	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
hollowness	O
in	O
his	O
cheeks	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
White	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Crossley	O
20	O
years	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
was	O
faithful	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
stables	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
drank	O
together	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
perhaps	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
.	O
Crossley	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Lewis	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
brick	O
fields	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Graves	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Crossley	O
drinking	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
and	O
White	O
?	O
Banister	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hagan	O
these	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
desranded	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whitefield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Rawlins	O
about	O
8	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
except	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
not	O
paying	O
his	O
debts	O
.	O
All	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	O
Hall	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
Aug.	O
3	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goulding	I-pers
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
2	O
muslin	O
stocks	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
;	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
4th	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hazelhurst	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
5th	O
Time	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
garters	O
,	O
a	O
horn	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
guineas	O
;	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
being	O
offered	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
above	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
6th	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Islington	O
on	O
Thomas	O
Wall	O
feloniously	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
certain	O
large	O
sticks	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
most	O
inhumanly	O
and	O
barbarously	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Wall	O
did	O
beat	O
and	O
strike	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
which	O
beating	O
they	O
the	O
said	O
Crossley	O
,	O
Rawlins	O
and	O
Hagan	O
,	O
did	O
give	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Wall	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
over	O
his	O
left	O
eye	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
and	O
confused	O
wound	O
whereby	O
his	O
skull	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fractured	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
14th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
to	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
he	O
languished	O
and	O
languishing	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Bartholomew	O
the	O
Less	O
died	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Beadle	O
of	O
Islington	O
parish	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
deceased	O
Tho	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
in	O
a	O
cart	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
He	O
complained	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
view	O
his	O
wounds	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
