TOKEN	NE
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
TUESDAY	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
15th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1741	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XLI	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
DANIEL	B-pers
LAMBERT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Austen	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Goulding	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Waylet	I-pers
,	O
Josias	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fowel	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Oakman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Skeates	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Teague	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Palton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Windley	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
peruke	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Timms	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
peruke	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Barnard	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
August	O
12th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
2.	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
gent	O
.	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
traiterously	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
malice	O
afore-thought	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Hall	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
traiterously	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
malice	O
afore-thought	O
did	O
strike	O
,	O
giving	O
to	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
blow	O
which	O
broke	O
his	O
skull	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
mortal	O
blow	O
he	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
case	O
for	O
instruments	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
shagreen	O
,	O
a	O
lancet	O
with	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
handle	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
scissars	O
,	O
a	O
blade	O
of	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
blade	O
of	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
ear	O
picker	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tweesers	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
spurs	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pencil	O
,	O
2	O
razors	O
,	O
7	O
sticks	O
of	O
sealing	O
wax	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
12	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
gent	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
June	O
18th	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
case	O
for	O
instruments	O
,	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
shagreen	O
,	O
a	O
lancet	O
with	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
handle	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
scissars	O
,	O
a	O
blade	O
of	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
blade	O
of	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
ear	O
picker	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
tweesers	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pencil	O
,	O
2	O
razors	O
,	O
7	O
sticks	O
of	O
sealing	O
wax	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
12	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
June	O
18th	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
each	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
accordingly	O
.	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
*	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stoke-Newington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Zachary	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
gelding	O
of	O
a	O
sorrel	O
colour	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
saddle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
bridle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
whip	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Zachary	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17th	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Sessions	O
book	O
,	O
1740	O
.	O
No	O
8	O
.	O
Part	O
2	O
d.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
arraign	O
'd	O
stood	O
mute	O
;	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
demanded	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
considerable	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
who	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
unless	O
that	O
was	O
restor	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
determin	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
plead	O
.	O
The	O
court	O
then	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
clause	O
in	O
an	O
act	O
of	O
parliament	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
wherein	O
it	O
is	O
ordain	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
monies	O
or	O
other	O
effects	O
found	O
upon	O
persons	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
highway	O
robberies	O
,	O
shall	O
on	O
the	O
parties	O
conviction	O
,	O
be	O
divided	O
among	O
the	O
persons	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
apprehending	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
an	O
acquittal	O
,	O
those	O
effects	O
shall	O
be	O
again	O
restor	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
parties	O
.	O
Notwithstanding	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
still	O
continued	O
obstinate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
court	O
then	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
persisting	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
resolution	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
appearing	O
unconcern	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
following	O
sentence	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
be	O
sent	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prison	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
,	O
mean	O
room	O
stopp	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
light	O
,	O
his	O
back	O
on	O
the	O
bare	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
save	O
something	O
to	O
cover	O
his	O
nakedness	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
arm	O
shall	O
be	O
stretch	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
cord	O
soften	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
leg	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
other	O
arm	O
and	O
leg	O
shall	O
be	O
serv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
.	O
Then	O
shall	O
be	O
laid	O
on	O
his	O
body	O
iron	O
and	O
stone	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
bear	O
and	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
shall	O
have	O
3	O
morsels	O
of	O
barley	O
bread	O
without	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
shall	O
drink	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
next	O
the	O
prison	O
door	O
,	O
except	O
it	O
be	O
running	O
water	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
drink	O
at	O
three	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
shall	O
be	O
his	O
diet	O
till	O
he	O
die	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
necessary	O
orders	O
were	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
executioner	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
perform	O
the	O
usual	O
office	O
of	O
tying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
thumbs	O
before	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
the	O
sentence	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
that	O
was	O
proceeded	O
upon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
evidence	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
.	O
On	O
friday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
on	O
horseback	O
from	O
Edmonton	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
dust	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
the	O
lanes	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
the	O
great	O
road	O
.	O
At	O
Palmer	O
's	O
Green	O
I	O
first	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behind	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
horse	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
meanly	O
drest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
very	O
little	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
following	O
me	O
for	O
near	O
three	O
miles	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
new	O
sluice	O
at	O
Newington	B-place
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
whether	O
that	O
road	O
went	O
to	O
Islington	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
that	O
Newington	O
church	O
was	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Islington	O
was	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
farther	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
immediately	O
his	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
oaths	O
and	O
imprecations	O
he	O
threaten	O
'd	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
producing	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
directly	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
still	O
threaten	O
'd	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
horse	O
's	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
pistol	O
in	O
so	O
dangerous	O
a	O
position	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
hand	O
trembled	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
unless	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
avoid	O
drawing	O
the	O
trigger	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
deliver	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
drop	O
his	O
pistol	O
and	O
behave	O
well	O
:	O
He	O
then	O
did	O
drop	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
behave	O
as	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
any	O
thing	O
farther	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
alight	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
till	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
promise	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
alight	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
had	O
our	O
horses	O
bridles	O
in	O
our	O
hands	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
search	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
silver	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
.	O
After	O
all	O
this	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
horse	O
and	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
his	O
own	O
horse	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
switch	O
whip	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
horse	O
worth	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
15	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
whip	O
I	O
paid	O
17	O
s.	O
for	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
then	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
horse	O
which	O
was	O
saddled	O
and	O
bridled	O
,	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
mounted	O
and	O
rode	O
off	O
towards	O
Palmer	O
's	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
my	O
horse	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
by	O
his	O
directions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Justice	O
Chandler	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
two	O
days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
horse	O
was	O
at	O
Mimms	O
Wash.	O
Pursuant	O
to	O
this	O
direction	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
saddle	O
,	O
bridle	O
and	O
whip	O
in	O
a	O
stable	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Justice	O
Chandler	O
's	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
watch	O
was	O
then	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
ever	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
where	O
your	O
horse	O
was	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
persons	O
that	O
came	O
directly	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
You	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
those	O
persons	O
here	O
then	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
On	O
tuesday	O
morning	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Bow-Church	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
at	O
Norton-Falgate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
murder	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Cruiashanks	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
at	O
Norton-Falgate	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Chandler	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
5	O
watches	O
,	O
9	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
46	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
those	O
watches	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
5	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
in	O
a	O
snuff	O
colour	O
'd	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
tuesday	O
morning	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
that	O
woman	O
's	O
(	O
Underwood	O
's	O
)	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
and	O
4	O
other	O
watches	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
number	O
,	O
M.	O
Storr	O
3321	O
.	O
Haines	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
him	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
these	O
gloves	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
.	O
These	O
gloves	O
fit	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
these	O
.	O
Haines	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
.	O
This	O
silver	O
is	O
the	O
button	O
to	O
my	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
exactly	O
answers	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
advertised	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beadle	O
of	O
Shoreditch	O
parish	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
hand-cuffs	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Chandler	O
's	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
search	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Cooke	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Bromley	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
Stratford	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Justice	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Stratford	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
up	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
inhabitants	O
to	O
prove	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
shake	O
hands	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Haines	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
indulg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Chandler	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Haines	O
produce	O
the	O
watches	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
body	O
here	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
must	O
rely	O
on	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
advertis	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
5	O
feet	O
3	O
inches	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
pock	O
holes	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
5	O
feet	O
7	O
inches	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
watches	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
time	O
I	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
persons	O
whom	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Birmingham	O
in	O
Warwickshire	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
watches	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
time	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
better	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
5.	O
Jane	B-pers
Stevely	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
bedcase	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
our	O
sovereign	O
lord	O
the	O
King	B-pers
;	O
October	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
And	O
Mary	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
July	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
Stevely	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Burn	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
John	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gloucestershire	O
cheese	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
;	O
July	O
13th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
7.	O
James	B-pers
Heater	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
geese	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
fowls	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keeling	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keeling	I-pers
.	O
All	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
8	O
live	O
geese	O
and	O
9	O
fowls	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
from	O
Avery	B-place
farm	I-place
,	O
near	O
Chelsea-water-works	B-place
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Broadway	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
8	O
geese	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
shoulders	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
pursuing	O
him	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
fowls	O
thrown	O
over	O
into	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
which	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
geese	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Beadle	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Keeling	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
geese	O
at	O
the	O
Beadle	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
by	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
in	O
the	O
webs	O
of	O
their	O
feet	O
.	O
-	O
Bates	O
.	O
Between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
geese	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
robbery	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
taking	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Beadle	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
hot	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
harvest	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
this	O
bag	O
of	O
geese	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
fowls	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gelding	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
colour	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
;	O
April	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
with	O
a	O
stripe	O
down	O
his	O
face	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
stable	O
near	O
the	O
Fox	B-place
and	I-place
Goose	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
Dog-house	B-place
bar	I-place
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
but	O
what	O
my	O
servants	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
George	I-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
One	O
day	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
stable	O
in	O
Oldstreet	B-place
,	O
and	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Gregory	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
stag	O
for	O
fear	O
any	O
body	O
should	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
Gregory	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
collar	O
maker	O
to	O
be	O
knock	O
'd	O
o'the	O
head	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
horse	O
.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
was	O
blind	O
indeed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
they	O
sold	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
collar	O
maker	O
.	O
Gregory	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
sell	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
collar	O
maker	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
odd	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Emley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
at	O
7	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
11	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
hay	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gilton	I-pers
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
the	O
collar	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
lame	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
us	O
a	O
horse	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
father	O
bid	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
we	O
never	O
give	O
more	O
for	O
any	O
horse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
sell	O
his	O
price	O
to	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
took	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Cumberland	O
's	O
killing	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
beat	O
with	O
broomsticks	O
from	O
shoulder	O
to	O
flank	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
worth	O
10	O
s.	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
(	O
ever	O
)	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Death	O
.	O
9	O
,	O
10.	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
68	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
bolt	O
staves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
.	O
July	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
White	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
at	O
Limehouse	B-place
bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
neighbours	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
thieves	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Rose	O
!	O
Keeper	O
!	O
and	O
t'other	O
dog	O
's	O
name	O
-	O
a	O
young	O
puppy	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
a	O
roaring	O
like	O
mad	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
there	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
thieves	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
White	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
struck	O
a	O
light	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
(	O
White	O
)	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
:	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
walk	O
without	O
shoes	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
hot	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
or	O
somebody	O
else	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
'nointed	O
him	O
heartily	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
set	O
him	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
pipe	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
foreman	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
1200	O
of	O
bolt	O
staves	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
weigh	O
'd	O
over	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
White	O
desired	O
my	O
foreman	O
to	O
save	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
hundred	O
weight	O
more	O
than	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
foreman	O
informing	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
cane	O
was	O
a	O
sword	O
I	O
would	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Gray	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Gray	O
's	O
house	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
against	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
96	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
my	O
iron	O
standing	O
upright	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
my	O
iron	O
,	O
Gray	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
bond	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
expect	O
nothing	O
from	O
me	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
law	O
directed	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smalwood	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
above	O
deposition	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
is	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Gray	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
again	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
court	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
Gray	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
affected	O
by	O
this	O
indictment	O
,	O
therefore	O
directed	O
the	O
jury	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
recommended	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
prefer	O
a	O
bill	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
accessary	O
after	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Gray	O
acquitted	O
,	O
White	O
guilty	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
a	O
sessions	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
according	O
to	O
due	O
course	O
of	O
law	O
tried	O
on	O
an	O
indictment	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ashley	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
68	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
called	O
bolt	O
staves	O
did	O
steal	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
certain	O
jury	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
White	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Gray	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
did	O
receive	O
and	O
have	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
record	O
of	O
White	O
's	O
conviction	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
evidence	O
being	O
produced	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
above	O
trial	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Freake	I-pers
,	O
another	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Dudley	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brookshank	I-pers
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Freake	I-pers
;	O
July	O
9th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Chaise	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ryan	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
five	O
guinea	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
July	O
11th	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Maynard	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
supper	O
with	O
some	O
friends	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
dumb	O
fortune	O
teller	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
who	O
must	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Having	O
a	O
mind	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
diversion	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
appear	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
signs	O
with	O
her	O
fingers	O
that	O
an	O
old	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
an	O
accusation	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
against	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
presence	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
closet	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
11	O
five	O
guinea	O
pieces	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
she	O
toss	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
lady	O
's	O
lap	O
,	O
then	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
began	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
my	O
servant	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
that	O
moment	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
servant	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
false	O
key	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
patient	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
9	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
made	O
the	O
false	O
key	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
all	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
impatience	O
I	O
waited	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
trouble	O
at	O
being	O
accus	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
coming	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
promise	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
looking	O
over	O
my	O
money	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
3	O
five	O
guinea	O
pieces	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
with	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
guinea	O
reward	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
that	O
should	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
justice	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
monday	O
following	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
5	O
guinea	O
piece	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
intelligence	O
that	O
my	O
servants	O
got	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
5	O
guinea	O
piece	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
changed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
supper	O
,	O
wine	O
,	O
punch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
search	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
his	O
house	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Maynard	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
then	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
before	O
his	O
daughter	O
's	O
and	O
his	O
house	O
keeper	O
's	O
face	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lincham	I-pers
.	O
On	O
sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
at	O
Kensington	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
unless	O
I	O
could	O
change	O
her	O
a	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
.	O
This	O
piece	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lock	O
's	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
changed	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
this	O
piece	O
from	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lock	O
's	O
the	O
distiller	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
monday	O
morning	O
.	O
Lincham	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
saved	O
it	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
farmer	O
's	O
at	O
Ealing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
summer	O
's	O
work	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
Lincham	O
brought	O
a	O
5	O
guinea	O
piece	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Rigley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Grey-Hound	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
and	O
made	O
signs	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
sunday	O
.	O
We	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
lodging	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
afterward	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
spoke	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
:	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
my	O
hat	O
to	O
cover	O
her	O
face	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
seen	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lincham	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
change	O
this	O
5	O
guinea	O
piece	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
change	O
a	O
guinea	O
the	O
thursday	O
before	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
I	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
more	O
?	O
Rigley	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
change	O
a	O
guinea	O
at	O
my	O
landlady	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
5	O
more	O
in	O
her	O
petticoats	O
beside	O
that	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
changed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
this	O
piece	O
from	O
Ireland	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
6	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
come	O
and	O
spent	O
3	O
d.	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
her	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
6	O
months	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
drank	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
14.	O
William	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
wt	O
.	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
,	O
August	O
14th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
pottage-pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richford	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
12th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
serjeant	O
at	O
law	O
,	O
Aug.	O
5th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17	O
,	O
18.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
callimanco	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
camlet	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
camlet	O
cloak	O
,	O
4	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
3	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
5	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
Ashley	O
guilty	O
,	O
Ward	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Vernhart	B-pers
Shalhayes	I-pers
,	O
August	O
5th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Haly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
outside	O
and	O
inside	O
cases	O
made	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Haly	O
,	O
July	O
2d	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Haly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
for	O
2	O
years	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
in	O
harvest-time	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
him	O
loose	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
thursday	O
following	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Hampstead	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
fork	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
work	O
with	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
saturday	O
morning	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
rode	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
country	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
at	O
sunset	O
,	O
I	O
spy	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
gunshot	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
spurs	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
43	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
my	O
brewhouse	O
window	O
with	O
this	O
knife	O
,	O
then	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
which	O
is	O
adjoining	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
small	O
bureau	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
a	O
field	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
of	O
44	O
s.	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
mourning	O
buckles	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
corner	O
cupboard	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
to	O
look	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
grounds	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
field	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
broke	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
papers	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
flying	O
about	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Haly	I-pers
,	O
junior	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
heard	O
our	O
clock	O
strike	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
was	O
the	O
small	O
bureau	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
a	O
field	O
or	O
two	O
and	O
then	O
rifled	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
closet	O
and	O
the	O
corner	O
cupboard	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
mention	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Haly	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
brewing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
fetching	O
some	O
grains	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
quite	O
safe	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
cut	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
silver	O
watch	O
and	O
spurs	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
must	O
refer	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
21.	O
James	B-pers
Moulds	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Rotherhith	I-place
,	O
mariner	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
contriving	O
and	O
intending	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
liquid	O
laudanum	O
,	O
being	O
deadly	O
poison	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
certain	O
liquor	O
called	O
flip	O
,	O
did	O
put	O
and	O
mix	O
,	O
he	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
poison	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Moulds	O
the	O
poison	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
so	O
mixed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Stone	O
did	O
give	O
and	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
and	O
swallow	O
down	O
:	O
And	O
afterwards	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Stone	O
the	O
said	O
poison	O
by	O
the	O
procurement	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Moulds	O
did	O
drink	O
and	O
swallow	O
down	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Stone	O
by	O
the	O
poison	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
taken	O
was	O
render	O
'd	O
sick	O
and	O
distemper	O
'd	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
sickness	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
3d	O
to	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
counsel	O
for	O
the	O
king	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Stimpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
boatswain	O
of	O
the	O
ship	B-place
Samuel	I-place
and	I-place
Rebecca	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
chief	O
mate	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ship	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Norway	O
to	O
this	O
port	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
laden	O
with	O
deals	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
Edward	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
custom-house	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
us	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
ship	O
to	O
Hanover	B-place
Hole	I-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
cast	O
anchor	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
ship	O
been	O
here	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sick	O
with	O
drinking	O
some	O
flip	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
making	O
this	O
slip	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
my	O
self	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
directions	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
remember	O
what	O
you	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
beer	O
,	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
brandy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
limons	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
into	O
it	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
phial	O
of	O
stuff	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
might	O
there	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
phial	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
small	O
dram-glass	O
full	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
reddish	O
colour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
as	O
limons	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
taste	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
taste	O
the	O
flip	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
drank	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
made	O
me	O
vomit	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
bitter	O
taste	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
taste	O
sour	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
drink	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
drink	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
gill	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
I	O
drank	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
about	O
3	O
pints	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Who	O
drank	O
of	O
it	O
besides	O
you	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Davy	O
,	O
another	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
more	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
drank	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
Davy	O
vomiting	O
in	O
the	O
hold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
drink	O
of	O
it	O
quite	O
well	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
maid	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
drink	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
complain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
liquor	O
in	O
the	O
phial	O
been	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
drank	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
stirr	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
stuff	O
in	O
this	O
phial	O
was	O
laudanum	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
of	O
detriment	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Yarmouth	O
goal	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
Alexander	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
foremast	O
men	O
,	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
give	O
my	O
information	O
so	O
strong	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sleeping	O
dose	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
if	O
this	O
flip	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
usual	O
manner	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
this	O
effect	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
Yarmouth	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Stone	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
the	O
surveyor	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
and	O
examined	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
cabbin	O
about	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cabbin	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
should	O
come	O
into	O
trouble	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
shore	O
I	O
saw	O
Stone	O
on	O
the	O
half	O
deck	O
by	O
the	O
main	O
shrouds	O
vomiting	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
drank	O
of	O
the	O
flip	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
the	O
people	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
this	O
liquor	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
Stone	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
hours	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
awake	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
walking	O
sore	O
and	O
ast	O
on	O
the	O
deck	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
discourse	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
Stone	O
died	O
?	O
Stimpson	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
an	O
officer	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
reported	O
that	O
capt	O
.	O
Cox	O
's	O
people	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
by	O
his	O
persuasion	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Yarmouth	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
were	O
officers	O
of	O
the	O
customs	O
on	O
board	O
this	O
ship	O
.	O
On	O
saturday	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
Banks	O
alias	O
Vanderbank	O
,	O
a	O
one-eyed	O
man	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
cann	O
of	O
flip	O
down	O
and	O
recommended	O
it	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
one	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
watermen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drank	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Did	O
Banks	O
drink	O
of	O
it	O
himself	O
?	O
Davy	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
cann	O
to	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
my	O
service	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
lips	O
wet	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
complaint	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
taste	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
?	O
Davy	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
an	O
ill	O
taste	O
and	O
an	O
ill	O
smell	O
too	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
taste	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
Davy	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
spicey	O
taste	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
about	O
a	O
coffee	O
cup	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
work	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
as	O
if	O
my	O
dinner	O
did	O
not	O
fit	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
small	O
beer	O
;	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
vomit	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
continued	O
drinking	O
and	O
vomiting	O
'till	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
If	O
this	O
liquor	O
had	O
been	O
honestly	O
made	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
troubled	O
you	O
?	O
Davy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
st	O
ay	O
on	O
board	O
?	O
Davy	O
.	O
'	O
Till	B-pers
Mr	I-pers
.	O
Foster	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
brandy	O
which	O
was	O
conceal	O
'd	O
in	O
half	O
anchors	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
Stone	O
drank	O
any	O
?	O
Davy	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
hold	O
had	O
drank	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
deck	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drank	O
of	O
this	O
flip	O
before	O
the	O
brandy	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
me	O
no	O
hurt	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
Stone	O
?	O
Chandler	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drink	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
quantity	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Chandler	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
The	O
officers	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
ships	O
crew	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
hold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
drank	O
besides	O
Stone	O
?	O
Chandler	O
.	O
Stimpson	O
and	O
Banks	O
.	O
One	O
Gardiner	O
who	O
was	O
cook	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sick	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
he	O
drank	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
stirr	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
knife	O
.	O
No	O
other	O
evidence	O
being	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Leger	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Handley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradburn	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Horrobin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
;	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
25.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
alias	O
Murphey	B-pers
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
martyr	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hester	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
topknots	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hester	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
;	O
July	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
desire	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
apart	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
satisfactory	O
answers	O
,	O
was	O
sworn	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
following	O
evidence	O
.	O
One	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Harris	O
in	O
Lamb	B-place
's	I-place
Conduit-fields	I-place
.	O
She	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
my	O
mamma	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
my	O
mamma	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
penknife	O
if	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
cry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
you	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
the	O
knife	O
pretty	O
near	O
my	O
stomach	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
if	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
she	O
put	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
ditch	O
side	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
plumb	O
bunn	O
or	O
a	O
plain	O
bunn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
plain	O
bunn	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
lifted	O
me	O
off	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
little	O
girls	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
and	O
a	O
knot	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
frock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
pins	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
set	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
bank	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
man	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
first	O
took	O
you	O
up	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
frock	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
woman	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
rip	O
you	O
up	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
after	O
my	O
frock	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Does	O
she	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
first	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
8	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
persons	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
dress	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
so	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
disfigur	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
small-pox	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
on	O
old	O
black	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
worsted	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
very	O
gown	O
she	O
wore	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
she	O
described	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
lying	O
behind	O
the	O
ditch	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
among	O
the	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
tuesday	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
twopenny	O
lodgings	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
child	O
if	O
she	O
cou	O
'd	O
recollect	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
streets	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
her	O
through	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
Bond	O
's	O
stables	O
,	O
crying	O
for	O
the	O
missing	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
knew	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
Pancras	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
very	O
gladly	O
embrac	O
'd	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
child	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
tell	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
she	O
recollected	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
Lane	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
up	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
the	O
green	O
trees	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
carried	O
her	O
through	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
Lane	O
,	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
being	O
led	O
through	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
Lane	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
turning	O
goes	O
to	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Wells	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
that	O
way	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Daddy	O
!	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
glass	O
and	O
bunn	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
see	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
She	O
soon	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
bottle	O
,	O
glass	O
and	O
bunn	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gateway	O
somewhere	O
thereabout	O
through	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
gate	O
and	O
a	O
dunghill	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
clothes	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
unsuccessful	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
afterwards	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
Castle	O
to	O
execute	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
sate	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Harris	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
scream	O
'd	O
out	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
her	O
pull	O
off	O
her	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
cap	O
and	O
topknot	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
cap	O
and	O
topknot	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
stammer	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
of	O
whom	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
further	O
examination	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
thursday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Murphey	O
on	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
shopboard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
expected	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
cloaths	O
he	O
usually	O
wore	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
coat	O
from	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
cloaths	O
that	O
were	O
pil	O
'd	O
up	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
strenuously	O
denied	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
he	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
not	O
take	O
us	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
reward	O
'till	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
child	O
of	O
this	O
size	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
enquir	O
'd	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
some	O
place	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
place	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
where	O
her	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Harris	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
questions	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
conduct	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
led	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Murphey	O
was	O
lying	O
asleep	O
on	O
a	O
bank	O
at	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
tied	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
went	O
away	O
he	O
slept	O
on	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
gingerbread	O
by	O
Powis	O
's	O
wells	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
to	O
desire	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
Mrs	O
Hart	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Harris	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Murphey	O
presently	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
himself	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bank	O
with	O
a	O
dirty	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
slept	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
down	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
together	O
in	O
Southampton	O
Row	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
meet	O
me	O
in	O
Holborn	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
meet	O
him	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Justices	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
afterwards	O
contradicted	O
himself	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
cap	O
off	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
head	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
which	O
the	O
child	O
tore	O
by	O
turning	O
her	O
head	O
aside	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
wash	O
'd	O
topknot	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
common	O
for	O
people	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
ends	O
of	O
ribbon	O
to	O
prevent	O
fraying	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
do	O
cut	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Birt	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
's	O
warrant	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
took	O
this	O
cap	O
and	O
knot	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
that	O
sells	O
gingerbread	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
asking	O
for	O
her	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
I	O
led	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Red	O
Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
a	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
child	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Murphey	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
their	O
taking	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
every	O
day	O
at	O
my	O
work	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Murphey	O
has	O
us	O
'd	O
my	O
house	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
wrong	O
'd	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Eston	O
Pattison	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
mother	O
kept	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
trusted	O
in	O
it	O
drunk	O
and	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
base	O
action	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Draytonbury	I-pers
.	O
He	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
fuddled	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Prison	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lanson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
18	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
live	O
3	O
days	O
on	O
a	O
chew	O
of	O
tobacco	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
rob	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
mad	O
Murphey	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
so	O
mad	O
as	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Stilgo	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Murphey	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Harris	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
26.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Foreshew	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
callico	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
August	O
19th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28.	O
Frances	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
;	O
August	O
8th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Robert	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
deal	O
boards	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Poogey	I-pers
;	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
August	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31	O
,	O
32.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
July	O
31	O
.	O
Coleman	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Mason	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Nancy	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
velvet	O
hood	O
lac	O
'd	O
with	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
34.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
of	O
Paddington	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wainwright	I-pers
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Clark	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
4	O
pewter	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
2	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
pins	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
broken	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
money	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
1/4	O
in	O
copper	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wainwright	O
,	O
July	O
12th	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wainwright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Paddington	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
off	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
something	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
condition	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
quarri	O
of	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
room	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
4	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
farthings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
pin	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
6	O
d.	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
2	O
cap	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
linen	O
or	O
holland	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
believe	O
so	O
?	O
Wainwright	O
.	O
She	O
must	O
have	O
some	O
liberty	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
could	O
it	O
be	O
?	O
This	O
man	O
took	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
to	O
him	O
Isabella	O
Wainwright	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fasten	O
'd	O
and	O
barr	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
hasp	O
'd	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
open	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
glass	O
broke	O
about	O
the	O
place	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
my	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
place	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
goods	O
away	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
gone	O
further	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
interrupted	O
by	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
.	O
On	O
sunday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Clark	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
garret	O
window	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Saunders	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
landlord	O
and	O
landlady	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
somebody	O
was	O
robbing	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
fore	O
window	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
which	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
shutter	O
which	O
encloses	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
drawer	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
legs	O
half	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
getting	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
immediately	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
pocket	O
being	O
over	O
fill	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
purple	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
cap	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
36.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dimity	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
diaper	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
velvet	O
hood	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
Thomas	O
guilty	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Young	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
and	O
two	O
brass	O
seals	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hepwell	I-pers
;	O
August	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
38.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fenshaw	I-pers
;	O
July	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
39	O
*	O
Alexander	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Earnest	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
Crull	I-pers
,	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
40	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
20	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Crull	O
:	O
February	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Sessions	O
book	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
V	B-pers
.	I-pers
1741.	O
pag	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crull	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
habit	O
maker	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
stocking	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
parish	O
.	O
On	O
sunday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
fasten	O
'd	O
my	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
my	O
doors	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
goods	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
party	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Lupton	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
executed	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
one	O
sunday	O
night	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
We	O
unlatch	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
this	O
stocking	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
side	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
130	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
Flack	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
lighted	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
Flack	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
into	O
Flack	O
's	O
apron	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
we	O
took	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jenny	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Rag	O
fair	O
;	O
we	O
kept	O
a	O
pair	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
our	O
own	O
wear	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
we	O
sold	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
Lupton	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
remainder	O
was	O
divided	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
please	O
to	O
grant	O
me	O
one	O
favour	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
hang	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Gumley	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
debtor	O
in	O
Newgate	O
be	O
brought	O
hither	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
shew	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Gumley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
for	O
debt	O
and	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Lowther	O
say	O
-	O
C.	O
Look	O
about	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
see	O
Lowther	O
here	O
?	O
Gumley	O
.	O
I	O
fancy	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
:	O
-	O
that	O
man	O
is	O
like	O
him	O
.	O
C.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
that	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
Gumley	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
I	O
do	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
may	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
alter	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
Lowther	O
say	O
?	O
Gumley	O
.	O
Lowther	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
visit	O
Peg	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
but	O
for	O
one	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
swearing	O
against	O
Flack	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
name	O
any	O
particular	O
robbery	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
yesterday	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
last	O
thursday	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Lowther	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
Flack	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
any	O
way	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Lowther	O
's	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
forty	O
odd	O
robberies	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
*	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
:	O
My	O
mistress	O
has	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
her	O
drawers	O
and	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Sessions	O
book	O
1739	O
.	O
No	O
8.	O
page	O
161.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Pennyl	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
barber	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
indulgent	O
man	O
to	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver-handled	O
cup	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Zachary	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
February	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
two-handled	O
cup	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
March	O
29	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Denmark-Court	B-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
On	O
Easter-sunday	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
shutters	O
of	O
my	O
parlour	O
windows	O
were	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blind	O
which	O
was	O
fasten	O
'd	O
with	O
two	O
brass	O
bolts	O
,	O
taken	O
down	O
and	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
beauset	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Lupton	O
,	O
Flack	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
.	O
Flack	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wheeler	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Denmark-Court	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
brave	O
chance	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
but	O
nail	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
winder-shutters	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
keep	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
push	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
down	O
the	O
blinds	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
Flack	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Devil	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
unbolted	O
the	O
blind	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
2	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
quart	O
cup	O
,	O
a	O
pepper	O
box	O
and	O
a	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
lap	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
a-cross	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Lupton	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
tip	O
him	O
Peter	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
us	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
we	O
let	O
a	O
spoon	O
drop	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
never	O
staid	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
coach	O
and	O
drove	O
to	O
Jenny	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
Flack	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
but	O
he	O
sunk	O
the	O
odd	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
us	O
.	O
Lupton	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
divided	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
Fighting	O
Cocks	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
at	O
Chelsea-college	O
gate	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
ten	O
guineas	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
excus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
rogue	O
that	O
would	O
swear	O
his	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
skettle	O
ground	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bowling	O
for	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
any	O
where	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
search	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
We	O
neither	O
of	O
us	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
himself	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Butler	O
Davenport	B-pers
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
skettle-ground	O
standing	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
people	O
bowl	O
.	O
He	O
desir	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
college	O
gate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Davenport	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
by	O
divers	O
people	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
robber	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
Johnson	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
besides	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
for	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Poulson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
several	O
information	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
felonies	O
and	O
burglaries	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Lowther	O
was	O
the	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
see	O
him	O
face	O
to	O
face	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
Lowther	O
in	O
several	O
felonies	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
transported	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
hang	O
him	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Justice	O
read	O
Lowther	O
's	O
information	O
,	O
all	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
say	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
leave	O
off	O
that	O
discourse	O
and	O
begin	O
another	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Walhank	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Lowther	O
accuse	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
neither	O
confess	O
'd	O
nor	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dearmore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
callico	O
bed-curtain	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Dearmore	O
;	O
a	O
lutestring	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
riding	O
hood	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Ukely	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Hazelrig	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
.	O
Aug.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
chocolate	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42	O
,	O
43	O
,	O
44.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gommery	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Glasscock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingoldsby	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
pair	O
of	O
Worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
August	O
13	O
.	O
Gommery	O
and	O
Ingoldsby	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Glasscock	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
towing	O
line	O
for	O
a	O
barge	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
150	O
yards	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Usher	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
46.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
5	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
made	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
worsted	O
,	O
2	O
napkins	O
,	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
3	O
guineas	O
,	O
2	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
August	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
47.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harbut	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
2	O
cambrick	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Tancred	I-pers
;	O
2	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
made	O
of	O
cambrick	O
and	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
clasps	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Attack	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Car	I-pers
;	O
July	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
Jane	B-pers
Harbut	I-pers
alias	O
Potter	B-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
mackarel	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
unless	O
she	O
chang	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
guinea	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
brought	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
49.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
canvas	O
hoop	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
:	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kilburn	B-place
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
no	O
soul	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
wall	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
goods	O
ransackled	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
a	O
nursing	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
thursday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
at	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
cloaths	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
undrest	O
herself	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
Witner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
wall	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
long	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
house-breaker	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
then	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
saw	O
her	O
cloaths	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
tied	O
nothing	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
who	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
aunt	O
's	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
frighted	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
rooms	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
these	O
cloaths	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
drest	O
myself	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
'trusted	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
found	O
money	O
of	O
mine	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
honestly	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
her	O
dishonest	O
.	O
Once	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
I	O
dropp	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50	O
,	O
51.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
.	O
This	O
day	O
sevennight	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
some	O
musick	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
as	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
.	O
They	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
nothing	O
but	O
China	O
ale	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
quarterns	O
of	O
liquor	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
women	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
Davis	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
our	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Martin	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
made	O
a	O
bargain	O
with	O
another	O
creature	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
paid	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
our	O
beds	O
.	O
I	O
fasten	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
bed	O
6	O
minutes	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ross	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
like	O
a	O
Chimney-sweeper	O
or	O
coal-heaver	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
beat	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
very	O
hard	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
suffer	O
'd	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
bed	O
stead	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
sword	O
by	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
drew	O
it	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
kill	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
considering	O
with	O
myself	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
best	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
sword	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
broke	O
in	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Davis	O
took	O
my	O
breeches	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
bolster	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
down	O
stairs	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
was	O
in	O
care	O
for	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Davis	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
creature	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
breeches	O
and	O
rifled	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
search	O
about	O
the	O
bed-clothes	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
tumble	O
the	O
clothes	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
my	O
pockets	O
I	O
found	O
only	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ross	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Alcock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
as	O
thick	O
as	O
my	O
wrist	O
while	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
breeches	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
bring	O
in	O
Frances	B-pers
Provert	I-pers
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
4	O
years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
?	O
Alcock	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Ross	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
offer	O
to	O
strike	O
you	O
in	O
any	O
shape	O
?	O
Alcock	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
up	O
swearing	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Provert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
a-bed	O
,	O
Ross	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
took	O
the	O
breeches	O
from	O
the	O
bolster	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Davis	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Ross	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
took	O
the	O
breeches	O
away	O
?	O
Provert	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
standing	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
his	O
breeches	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
laid	O
at	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Martin	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
at	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
His	O
breeches	O
were	O
brought	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
disbursted	O
,	O
for	O
Ross	O
had	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Ross	O
had	O
it	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
crown	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
breeches	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
and	O
Heath	O
were	O
with	O
Alcock	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
Davis	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
52.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wildix	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wicker	O
flat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Eagle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
63	O
pounds	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sam	B-pers
Garnham	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
weight	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
July	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
54.	O
John	B-pers
Carrigan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
roasted	O
fowl	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lamb	O
's	O
heart	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
August	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
55	O
,	O
56.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
was	O
indicated	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
23	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
money	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
down	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Haines	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
quarterns	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
Mr.	O
Downer	O
's	O
the	O
Greyhound	B-place
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
day	O
received	O
28	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
safe	O
,	O
for	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
over-charg	O
'd	O
with	O
liquor	O
fell	O
asleep	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
'wak	O
'd	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
she	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
enquiry	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Haines	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Gibbs	O
gave	O
me	O
ten	O
guineas	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
,	O
upon	O
condition	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
prosecute	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Haines	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Gibbs	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
ten	O
guineas	O
?	O
Tailor	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
gin	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
monday	O
the	O
ten	O
guineas	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
