TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
TUESDAY	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Humphry	O
Parsons	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1741	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
MDCCXLI	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHRY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PROBYN	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
FORTESCUE	O
,	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Albone	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daxon	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomlinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cutterns	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Robotham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taaffe	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hiron	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Tuting	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Norgate	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Bohea	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scrivener	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Akerman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
,	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shooter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishop's-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Worsted	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
28	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Dec.	O
15	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Weaver	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Peter-Street	B-place
,	O
Bishop's-gate	B-place
Parish	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Chest	O
open	O
in	O
my	O
Chamber	O
,	O
(	O
into	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
my	O
Money	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Keys	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
Lock	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
which	O
likewise	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Chest	O
were	O
left	O
behind	O
.	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
that	O
somebody	O
who	O
knew	O
the	O
House	O
must	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Quill-Boy	O
,	O
being	O
observed	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Magpye-Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
;	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
my	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Keys	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Table-Drawer	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Purse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
four	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
wise	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
Pieces	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
Promises	O
of	O
Pardon	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
made	O
Use	O
of	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
Confession	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
Truth	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
acquainted	O
with	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Quill-Boy	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
between	O
13	O
and	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
13	O
yet	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Brother	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
hid	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Nettle	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
Wilson	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
who	O
had	O
absconded	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
relate	O
something	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
declare	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
Mercy	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
expected	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
by	O
such	O
Methods	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
an	O
Evasion	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
declare	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
then	O
fairly	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
Barnard	O
's	O
Wall	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Bed-Chamber	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Table-Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Keys	O
in	O
a	O
String	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Closet	O
where	O
the	O
Chest	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
try	O
'd	O
several	O
Keys	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
the	O
right	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Purse	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
little	O
Pill-Box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whether	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
examining	O
him	O
again	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
burst	O
in	O
Tears	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
hang	O
his	O
Mother	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
inhuman	O
as	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Rope	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
:	O
He	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
Home	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Sister	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
his	O
Mother	O
the	O
Remainder	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
it	O
chang	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Butter	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
appropriated	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
and	O
the	O
Daughter	O
,	O
both	O
abscond	O
for	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Magpye	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Nettle	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
;	O
-	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
Small	O
Beer	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
one	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
John	O
Malton	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Cash	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Place	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
suspected	O
any	O
Body	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
suspect	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
the	O
Mother	O
and	O
Daughter	O
absconded	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Uncle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
several	O
People	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nettle	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
did	O
(	O
said	O
he	O
)	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
``	O
Master	O
's	O
Chamber	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
where	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
``	O
Keys	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
threw	O
away	O
.	O
''	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
Money	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
brave	O
large	O
yellow	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Pieces	O
as	O
big	O
again	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
alike	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Moidore	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
bigger	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
four	O
Pieces	O
to	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
Silver	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Brother	O
he	O
hid	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
under	O
a	O
Shed	O
in	O
the	O
Tenter-Ground	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
dropp	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
Crevice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
:	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
dug	O
out	O
these	O
four	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Shooter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
13	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
Oath	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
Hell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Brother	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
No	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Tenter	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
roll	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
with	O
Barnard	O
and	O
Malton	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
;	O
I	O
try	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Pick-Axe	O
,	O
and	O
dug	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Shooter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Uncle	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Chatham	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
another	O
Brother	O
who	O
is	O
bound	O
to	O
a	O
Hoy-Man	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
Shore	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
Friends	O
into	O
so	O
much	O
Trouble	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
Mother	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Stroud	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Tenter-Ground	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
commence	O
(	O
commit	O
)	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Mother	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
Mother	O
assisted	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
about	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Tenter-Ground	O
,	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Rag	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
myself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Mercy	O
.	O
3.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ducket	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
dry	O
'd	O
Citron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Pound	O
of	O
Biscuits	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
December	O
30	O
,	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Ann	B-pers
Greenhall	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gallough	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
striped	O
Lutestring	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Paduasoy	O
Gown	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Tabby	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Bed-Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Dimity	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Sattin	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
9	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
five	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
six	O
Damask	O
Clouts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Lutestring	O
Apron	O
,	O
with	O
Bugles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
17	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
who	O
loged	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Rigg	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Time	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
all	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
safe	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
or	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Box	O
)	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
taking	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
one	O
Wilson	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Hart-Street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hankinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rigg	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
left	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Goods	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
sometime	O
afterwards	O
she	O
sent	O
the	O
Key	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
send	O
her	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
unlock	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Hart-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
Goods	O
to	O
me	O
fourteen	O
different	O
Times	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
All	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
Law	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
36	O
s.	O
is	O
the	O
largest	O
Sum	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
lent	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
her	O
every	O
Time	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
Things	O
of	O
more	O
Consequence	O
than	O
these	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
thought	O
her	O
honest	O
.	O
Hankinson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
but	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
5.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilmore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
December	O
29	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Burdet	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
Muslin	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
eight	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
28	O
l.	O
16	O
s	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
11	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Dec.	O
6	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Request	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
a-part	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
cleaning	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
out	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
returning	O
in	O
the	O
Time	O
I	O
expected	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
afterwards	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
my	O
Buckles	O
in	O
her	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
on	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
Wife	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Griffith	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
the	O
Hospital	O
when	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
those	O
Things	O
?	O
Griffith	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
die	O
this	O
Moment	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
shew	O
me	O
your	O
Wife	O
's	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
your	O
Wife	O
died	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
your	O
Second	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
would	O
be	O
mine	O
?	O
Griffith	O
.	O
No	O
!	O
on	O
my	O
Oath	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Gown	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
at	O
Harwich	O
,	O
whither	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Holland	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
surprized	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
little	O
Silver	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
Trunk	O
to	O
my	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
enquiring	O
after	O
her	O
Mistresses-Ring	O
,	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
'till	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
these	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
in	O
her	O
Shoes	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stage-Coach	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
accordingly	O
found	O
an	O
old	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
four	O
new	O
ones	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
;	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
83	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
a	O
two	O
Guinea	O
Piece	O
,	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
Piece	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
three	O
Crowns	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
weigh	O
'd	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
this	O
Gown	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Gown	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
of	O
robbing	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
'till	O
that	O
very	O
Morning	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Bed-chamber	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
Drawers	O
open	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Thursday	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Kell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Crime	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Aunt	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
Years	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Girl	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Sherrard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
15	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sherrard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
8	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
her	O
Character	O
was	O
universally	O
good	O
,	O
set	O
aside	O
this	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
hear	O
now	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Misdemeanor	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
7.	O
George	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
John	B-pers
Sheriff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
of	O
a	O
Bay	O
Colour	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
15	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
is	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Right	O
and	O
Property	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Grass	O
at	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
last	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
Edw	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
where	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
he	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
mention	O
the	O
Place	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fearon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
Weston	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Stable	O
whilst	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
with	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
threw	O
himself	O
into	O
my	O
Company	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Beer	O
,	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
my	O
Friends	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Weston	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Stable	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
my	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Fearon	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
,	O
on	O
Bushy-Heath	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Mare	O
into	O
my	O
Hands	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
to	O
slipt	O
her	O
Bridle	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
shut	O
her	O
in	O
secure	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Deserter	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Colonel	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
20	O
s.	O
Reward	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
Fearon	O
his	O
Mare	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
both	O
Man	O
and	O
Mare	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Excuse	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
ride	O
to	O
his	O
Colonel	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
her	O
Home	O
again	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Kemston	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
at	O
Kensington-Gravel-Pits	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
Corn	O
and	O
Hay	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
Stable	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Shed	O
with	O
a	O
Table	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
draw	O
the	O
Table	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mare	O
might	O
eat	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
Garter	O
to	O
te	O
to	O
her	O
Bridle	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
apt	O
to	O
slip	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
loose	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
agreed	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
rode	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Kemston	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Enfield-Common	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
ride	O
behind	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
;	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
lent	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Farmer	O
Fearon	B-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
(	O
Fearon	O
)	O
did	O
say	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
ride	O
to	O
my	O
Colonels	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
my	O
Discharge	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
9.	O
Robert	B-pers
Farnham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Augustus	B-pers
,	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Berkley	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
26	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
William	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
22	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
John	B-pers
Catt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
at	O
a	O
Delivery	O
of	O
the	O
Goal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Sussex	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
East-Grinstead	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Commyns	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
appointed	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
said	O
Goal	O
;	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Catt	O
,	O
was	O
according	O
to	O
due	O
Course	O
of	O
Law	O
,	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
dissolute	O
and	O
disorderly	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
20	O
Persons	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1736	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Great	O
Groine	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Sea	O
Coast	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
County	O
of	O
Sussex	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
arm	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
Fire-Arms	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
assemble	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
clandestine	O
running	O
certain	O
uncustom	O
'd	O
Goods	O
,	O
imported	O
into	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Merchandize	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
2000	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Duties	O
were	O
then	O
due	O
and	O
payable	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Terror	O
of	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
thereon	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Catt	O
,	O
was	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
adjudged	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Plantations	O
in	O
America	O
,	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
id	O
Catt	O
was	O
Transported	O
to	O
the	O
Colony	O
of	O
Virginia	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Indictment	O
farther	O
charged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Catt	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
in	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishop's-gate	I-place
,	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Term	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
large	O
;	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
:	O
-	O
Jones	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Record	O
of	O
Catt	O
's	O
Conviction	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
examined	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
true	O
Copy	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
Sussex	O
to	O
wit.	O
``	O
Be	O
it	O
remember	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
a	O
``	O
Sessions	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
East-Grinstead	O
,	O
``	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
``	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
before	O
``	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
directed	O
to	O
enquire	O
``	O
the	O
Truth	O
by	O
good	O
and	O
lawful	O
Men	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
``	O
of	O
all	O
Treasons	O
,	O
Mis-prisons	O
of	O
Treason	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
``	O
John	B-pers
Catt	I-pers
being	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
in	O
his	O
proper	O
``	O
Person	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
``	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
tried	O
,	O
put	O
himself	O
on	O
his	O
Country	O
,	O
``	O
therefore	O
let	O
a	O
Jury	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
come	O
before	O
our	O
``	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
enquire	O
whether	O
he	O
``	O
be	O
guilty	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
``	O
say	O
on	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Catt	I-pers
is	O
guilty	O
``	O
in	O
Manner	O
and	O
Form	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Catt	O
``	O
being	O
asked	O
why	O
the	O
Court	O
should	O
not	O
proceed	O
``	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
faith	O
nothing	O
``	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
therefore	O
it	O
is	O
consider	O
'd	O
,	O
``	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
Transported	O
to	O
``	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Plantations	O
in	O
America	O
,	O
``	O
there	O
to	O
remain	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Abram	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Brother	O
to	O
the	O
Goal-Keeper	O
,	O
in	O
Sussex	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
us	O
whether	O
you	O
remember	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
Goal	O
in	O
Sussex	O
.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
an	O
Assistant	O
to	O
the	O
Goal-Keeper	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
assist	O
at	O
the	O
Assizes	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Magier	I-pers
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Magier	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Crew	O
that	O
I	O
carried	O
to	O
Virginia	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1737	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Forward	O
Galley	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
Land	O
him	O
?	O
Magier	O
.	O
At	O
South	O
Potomock	O
in	O
Virginia	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Goal	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
Mr	O
.	O
Forward	O
's	O
Attorney	O
's	O
Hands	O
at	O
Virginia	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Goalers	O
Assistant	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
I	O
carried	O
that	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
from	O
Horsham	O
in	O
Sussex	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Magier	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
in	O
May	O
,	O
1737.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Quaif	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
first	O
?	O
Quaif	O
.	O
In	O
Surry	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
from	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
Hill	O
into	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
's	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
George	O
and	O
Catherine	O
Wheel	O
Yard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Transportation	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
others	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
that	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
12.	O
Joseyh	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Axtel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
6	O
Shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15	O
,	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jenny	B-pers
Diver	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Catherine	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Judith	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Judith	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Woolchurch	I-place
,	O
Jan.	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
Jenny	O
Diver	O
,	O
was	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
in	O
April	O
Sessions	O
,	O
1758	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
74.	O
Judith	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Sherbourne-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Half-penny	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
House	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
was	O
the	O
Black-Bull	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
Boards	O
laid	O
over	O
a	O
wet	O
Place	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Mansion	B-place
House	I-place
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Boards	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
Assistance	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
the	O
Man	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
my	O
Arm	O
up	O
a	O
great	O
Height	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
numm	O
'd	O
my	O
Fingers	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Young	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
seized	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Wrist	O
;	O
-	O
her	O
Hand	O
was	O
clench	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
doing	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
with	O
her	O
other	O
Hand	O
struck	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
quit	O
her	O
Hand	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
else	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
left	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Cloak	O
and	O
never	O
left	O
her	O
'till	O
I	O
got	O
Assistance	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
immediately	O
quitted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
stop	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
held	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Woman	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
:	O
A	O
Coal-Heaver	O
happening	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
other	O
Woman	O
Davis	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
House-keeper	O
and	O
lived	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
-	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
molest	O
me	O
but	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Man	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
escaping	O
she	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Young	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
whose	O
Hand	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
first	O
Lamp	O
by	O
the	O
Mansion	O
House	O
as	O
you	O
go	O
from	O
hence	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
Hand	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
it	O
was	O
clenched	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
near	O
Davis	O
was	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
pull	O
the	O
Man	O
from	O
the	O
Coal-Heaver	O
,	O
and	O
Young	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
'till	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Money	O
in	O
either	O
of	O
our	O
Hands	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
Young	O
had	O
her	O
Hand	O
clenched	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Hussey	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
struck	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
Blow	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
quit	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
kept	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Young	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Bearbinder-Lane	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
put	O
up	O
with	O
this	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Jefferies	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
near	O
an	O
Hour	O
in	O
Custody	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
an	O
Officer	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
other	O
Woman	O
Davis	O
on	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
escaping	O
was	O
secured	O
by	O
the	O
Coal	O
Heaver	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Young	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Blow	O
before	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
Fear	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
kept	O
me	O
close	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Boards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
immediately	O
.	O
Young	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
between	O
your	O
losing	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
left	O
her	O
'till	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
the	O
Green-Grocer	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Young	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
Just	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Walbrook	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
set	O
my	O
Foot	O
on	O
the	O
Planks	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
.	O
Davis	B-pers
How	I-pers
far	O
from	O
Stocks-Market	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
pull	O
the	O
Man	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
red	O
Cloak	O
(	O
Young	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
other	O
into	O
Bearbinder-Lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
any	O
Fear	O
when	O
your	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
a	O
Mischief	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
the	O
Man	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
right	O
Arm	O
which	O
the	O
Man	O
held	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Pocket	O
I	O
commonly	O
wear	O
under	O
my	O
Gown	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
my	O
left	O
Hand	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
Liberty	O
,	O
under	O
my	O
Apron	O
,	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
[	O
Here	O
the	O
Witness	O
shewed	O
the	O
Manner	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
seiz	O
'd	O
Young	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
]	O
and	O
seized	O
her	O
Hand	O
clench	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
help	O
you	O
over	O
Child	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
slip	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
worse	O
off	O
:	O
immediately	O
Young	O
's	O
Hand	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
has	O
got	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
I	O
quitted	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
to	O
get	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prevent	O
her	O
doing	O
me	O
further	O
mischief	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Sister	O
and	O
her	O
Child	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
poor	O
Woman	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ruin	O
'd	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
ruin	O
'd	O
!	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
Man	O
has	O
ruin	O
'd	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Minute	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
Women	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
-	O
Those	O
are	O
the	O
Women	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
my	O
Affidavit	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
upon	O
me	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
held	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
How	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
struggling	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
away	O
run	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
that	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
white	O
Cloak	O
(	O
Davis	O
)	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
red	O
Cloak	O
on	O
then	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
a	O
Lie	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
People	O
were	O
running	O
by	O
to	O
Bearbinder-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
against	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
this	O
Man	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
with	O
the	O
white	O
Cloak	O
(	O
Davis	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prosecutrix	O
said	O
that	O
Woman	O
(	O
Young	O
)	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
of	O
12	O
Shillings	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Hat	O
on	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
under	O
her	O
Cloak	O
I	O
was	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Upshot	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Jefferies	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
one	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
Young	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Shop	O
by	O
?	O
Day	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
you	O
go	O
'till	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
Rights	O
;	O
-	O
You	O
took	O
a	O
Black	O
Hat	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Pales	O
at	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
held	O
her	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Woman	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
my	O
Brother	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
slew	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
both	O
their	O
Hands	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
House-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Davis	O
's	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
use	O
her	O
ill	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
that	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
really	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
Young	O
's	O
Cloak	O
.	O
C.	O
Was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
complain	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
following	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
How	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
directly	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Boards	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Child	O
into	O
the	O
China-Shop	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
.	O
Young	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Hatter's-Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Lothbury	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Church	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Wine-Vault	O
in	O
Bearbinder-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Hat	O
to	O
dress	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
him	O
!	O
Stop	O
him	O
!	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
.	O
Coming	O
nearer	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
one	O
nearer	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
farther	O
off	O
,	O
one	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
these	O
Women	O
to	O
my	O
thinking	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
soberly	O
along	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Woman	O
(	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
)	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
Cloak	O
under	O
her	O
Scarlet	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Woman	O
that	O
stands	O
there	O
(	O
Davis	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
going	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Bishop's-gate-street	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Square	O
there	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
strange	O
Thing	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
should	O
cry	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
T	O
hrogmorton-street	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Cough	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
even	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
founded	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
'till	O
they	O
came	O
hither	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
stood	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
say	O
who	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Words	O
Stop	O
him	O
!	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Bearbinder-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Salter's-Hall	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
these	O
Wine-Vaults	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Wine-Vault	O
just	O
through	O
Salter's-Hall	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Name	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
left	O
Word	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
Name	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
-	O
if	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Wine	O
Vault	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
Servant	O
that	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Hat	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
Cellar	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Hundred	O
Pipes	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
C.	O
Is	O
it	O
customary	O
to	O
dress	O
Hats	O
for	O
People	O
whose	O
Names	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
carry	O
them	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
am	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
not	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
carry	O
a	O
Hat	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
enquire	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
the	O
Owner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
Women	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Croud	O
altogether	O
,	O
that	O
Davis	O
was	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
20	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Croud	O
.	O
C.	O
Were	O
they	O
not	O
held	O
by	O
any	O
Body	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Gentlewoman	O
(	O
Young	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
Body	O
held	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Davis	O
before	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
her	O
passing	O
by	O
my	O
Shop	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
Man	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Michena	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Siddal	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Rogue	O
has	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
said	O
about	O
Women	O
;	O
-	O
no	O
one	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
neither	O
Man	O
nor	O
Woman	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
2	O
Women	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
directly	O
Home	O
.	O
Davis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Mantua-maker	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
Bethlem-Wall	O
,	O
through	O
Great-Moregate	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
between	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
,	O
in	O
Deadman's-Place	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
by	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
fighting	O
and	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frighten	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
;	O
-	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
Clear	O
starching	O
and	O
Plain-Work	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Broadwater	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
(	O
Davis	O
)	O
has	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Months	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Mantua-Maker	O
;	O
she	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
every	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Cook's-shop	O
,	O
almost	O
the	O
very	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Baker	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
London-Wall	O
,	O
by	O
Great-Moregate	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
are	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
very	O
often	O
.	O
Broadwater	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Father	O
lives	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Walk	O
which	O
leads	O
from	O
Holy-Well	O
Mount	O
,	O
to	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
in	O
Quilting	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
she	O
rents	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
in	O
Plain-work	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
receive	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
modest	O
and	O
well	O
behaved	O
.	O
Amelia	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
about	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
Mrs	O
Walker	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
some	O
Plain-work	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Workwoman	O
she	O
is	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
good	O
House-keepers	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
liked	O
her	O
extraordinary	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
,	O
at	O
Holborn-Bridge	O
,	O
so	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
China-Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Croud	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
said	O
,	O
somebody	O
is	O
beating	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
a	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
that	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
:	O
presently	O
another	O
Woman	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
C.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Young	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
so	O
much	O
Surprize	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
Notice	O
.	O
C.	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Was	O
any	O
Body	O
in	O
your	O
Company	O
except	O
Davis	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
that	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
red	O
Cloak	O
(	O
Young	O
)	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
17.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
(	O
Deborah	B-pers
Damaris	I-pers
being	O
then	O
therein	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Laced	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
laced	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Callamanco	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
January	O
3	O
,	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
only	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18	O
,	O
19	O
,	O
20	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Mahon	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Trilcourt	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Elvar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
put	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
l	O
and	O
1	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Fox	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
Mistress	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
cold	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
Dram	O
wou	O
'd	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
we	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
Rum	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
belived	O
it	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
neither	O
of	O
our	O
Shares	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Mabon	O
followed	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
3	O
Quarterns	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
,	O
but	O
Fox	O
and	O
Mabon	O
siezed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
a	O
little	O
Stick	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
;	O
they	O
struck	O
and	O
punched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
Cheeks	O
bleed	O
;	O
-	O
the	O
Blood	O
is	O
now	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
on	O
my	O
Coat	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
Landlord	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Meaning	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
almost	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
Landlord	O
curs	O
'd	O
them	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
set	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
staid	O
some	O
Time	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
went	O
for	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Elvar	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
Richardson	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
Liquor	O
;	O
the	O
Landlord	O
set	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
poured	O
out	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
red	O
Stuff	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
somebody	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
swore	O
I	O
should	O
drink	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
O	O
!	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
Bitters	O
and	O
very	O
wholsome	O
.	O
We	O
sat	O
talking	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
seemingly	O
very	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
Time	O
that	O
the	O
Watchman	O
should	O
come	O
about	O
?	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
late	O
as	O
you	O
think	O
.	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
after	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
vastly	O
desirous	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
drink	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
have	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
plain	O
Gin	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
insisted	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
drink	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
swore	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Richardson	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
,	O
all	O
rushed	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
Richardson	O
held	O
my	O
two	O
Arms	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Knee	O
on	O
my	O
Back	O
;	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
Moment	O
;	O
Elvar	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
on	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Left	O
to	O
my	O
Mouth	O
-	O
his	O
Hand	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
my	O
Left	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
aside	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
Hand	O
Pocket	O
,	O
my	O
Bag	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
5	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
18	O
s.	O
Piece	O
.	O
Some	O
how	O
or	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
Struggle	O
I	O
threw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
against	O
a	O
Settle	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Racket	O
;	O
so	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
rifled	O
me	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
;	O
I	O
rolled	O
myself	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
and	O
Murder	O
!	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
in	O
View	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
Ground	O
of	O
them	O
every	O
Minute	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
Mabon	O
separated	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Watchman	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
Fox	O
but	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
go	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
Mabon	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
found	O
Elvar	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
to	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
Mabon	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
the	O
Men	O
or	O
the	O
Women	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Layton	O
.	O
Elvar	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Women	O
rifled	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
Elvar	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
passed	O
for	O
Landlord	O
that	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
your	O
Throat	O
,	O
or	O
me	O
?	O
Layton	O
.	O
Elvar	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
me	O
and	O
very	O
cold	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Elvar	O
.	O
Who	O
put	O
his	O
Knee	O
on	O
your	O
Back	O
?	O
Layton	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Richardson	O
.	O
Mabon	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
who	O
broke	O
his	O
Stick	O
?	O
Layton	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
Women	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Elvar	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Coventry-Court	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
Tea	O
Cup	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
Betty	O
,	O
(	O
whom	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
my	O
Wife	O
)	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Mahon	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Mabon	I-pers
were	O
within	O
Doors	O
.	O
Mabon	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
says	O
held	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Richardson	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
Elvar	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
(	O
Layton	O
)	O
was	O
busie	O
with	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
them	O
directly	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Potion	O
of	O
Liquid	O
Laudanum	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
quiet	O
;	O
the	O
Women	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Room	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fore-Room	O
,	O
Elvar	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Draught	O
had	O
no	O
Effect	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Cup	O
which	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
with	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Potion	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
John	O
Mabon	O
and	O
Elvar	O
told	O
the	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Room	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
(	O
the	O
Women	O
)	O
must	O
pick	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
out	O
to	O
assist	O
them	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Back-Room	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
followed	O
and	O
siezed	O
the	O
Countryman	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Elvar	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
his	O
Mouth	O
with	O
his	O
Coat	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Mabon	I-pers
bent	O
him	O
backwards	O
;	O
then	O
Priscilla	O
Mabon	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Buckskin	O
Breeches	O
and	O
took	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Canvass	O
Bag	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
Pocket	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
their	O
Way	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Layton	O
's	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
.	O
Mabon	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Oath	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
put	O
his	O
Knee	O
against	O
Layton	O
's	O
Back	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Threshold	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mabon	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Eleven	O
when	O
the	O
Thing	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
-	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
sung	O
the	O
Countryman	O
some	O
Songs	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Watch	O
pass	O
by	O
.	O
Elvar	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
ever	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
Elvar	O
fill	O
'd	O
the	O
second	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Liquor	O
brown	O
.	O
Elvar	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
Layton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
once	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
twice	O
.	O
Elvar	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
we	O
drink	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Liquor	O
as	O
you	O
?	O
Layton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
of	O
the	O
red	O
Liquor	O
;	O
the	O
Landlord	O
touch	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Lips	O
,	O
and	O
fill	O
'd	O
the	O
Glass	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
It	O
swell	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
pleased	O
God	O
I	O
cast	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Watchman	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
called	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Eleven	O
,	O
this	O
Layton	O
cryed	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
;	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
Fox	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
Layton	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
Fox	O
to	O
my	O
Partner	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
after	O
Mabon	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
Men	O
concerned	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
described	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
short	O
well	O
set	O
Man	O
,	O
another	O
a	O
little	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
Wig	O
and	O
a	O
light	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
Coat	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
Description	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
Elvar	O
;	O
we	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
-	O
the	O
House	O
has	O
no	O
Landlord	O
in	O
it	O
long	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
People	O
are	O
here	O
to	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
To-Morrow	O
.	O
Salathiel	O
Gardiner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Countryman	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Oxendon-Street	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
Woman	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
Mabon	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Mabon	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
Share	O
of	O
three	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
left	O
our	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fore	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Landlord	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
Girls	O
,	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
will	O
take	O
you	O
.	O
No	O
Watchman	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Layton	O
himself	O
.	O
Fox	O
.	O
The	O
Men	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
bid	O
us	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
would	O
charge	O
us	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
in	O
that	O
Manner	O
?	O
Layton	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
Richardson	O
pinion	O
'd	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
Woman	O
,	O
(	O
Fox	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Right	O
Hand	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Mahon	O
.	O
Two	O
People	O
could	O
not	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
Layton	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Little	O
One	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
my	O
Pocket	O
together	O
.	O
Elvar	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
quarrelling	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
lay	O
Hands	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
began	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
one	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
Layton	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mahon	O
from	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
maintain	O
'd	O
clear	O
Character	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mahon	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
No	O
Ill	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
always	O
did	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
handsome	O
.	O
-	O
Burnet	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
Three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Elvar	O
six	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
or	O
Child	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Elvar	O
was	O
Innocent	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
clear	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
Shop	O
and	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
bear	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
over-against	O
his	O
Mother	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
Children	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
Manner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Fit	O
of	O
Illness	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Poor	O
,	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
with	O
this	O
Place	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
another	O
.	O
Elvar	O
.	O
Richardson	O
has	O
another	O
Wife	O
living	O
now	O
.	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
(	O
Fox	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Fleet	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
Parson	O
2	O
s.	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
another	O
Wife	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
is	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
21.	O
Gasper	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Quartern	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Pumps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
;	O
December	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24	O
,	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
and	O
Matth.ias	O
Dennison	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Arthur	O
O	O
Hara	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cullin	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Parish	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
,	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Stacey	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Lacey	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
1.	O
p.	O
18	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Desire	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
a-part	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Parish	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Gingerbread-Baker	O
and	O
Confectioner	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Grocery	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Brother-in-Law	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
for	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fulman	I-pers
's	O
,	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
in	O
Windsor-Court	B-place
,	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
.	O
I	O
accordingly	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Country-Woman	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
-	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
private	O
House	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Fulman	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
least	O
any	O
ill	O
Consequence	O
might	O
attend	O
my	O
going	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
Eleven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
designing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Inn	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
close	O
by	O
Keogh	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
immediately	O
two	O
Men	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
laid	O
violent	O
Hands	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
*	O
Ruggaty	O
Madge	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lineham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Dennison	O
and	O
Stacey	O
;	O
they	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
executed	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
Stacey	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
tore	O
open	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Gold	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
23	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
Guineas	O
and	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
Cherry-Brandy	O
in	O
Pint	O
Mugs	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
stab	O
me	O
or	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
drink	O
till	O
they	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Room	O
into	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
found	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
slumber	O
,	O
they	O
jostled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
drink	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
which	O
appeared	O
like	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
Stacey	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Stacey	O
,	O
some	O
how	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
slipped	O
my	O
Watch	O
into	O
my	O
Great	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
search	O
myself	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hop	O
'd	O
was	O
my	O
Gold	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
dar	O
'd	O
not	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
get	O
that	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Sessions-Book	O
,	O
1740	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
8.	O
p.	O
271	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Pocket	O
was	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
great	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
They	O
forced	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
me	O
into	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
where	O
Stacey	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
Dennison	O
held	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
rifled	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
several	O
People	O
by	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Knee-buckles	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hat	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
charge	O
them	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
roll	O
'd	O
into	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
very	O
plain	O
when	O
they	O
forced	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
led	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
quitted	O
me	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Dennison	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
you	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
Brandy	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
facing	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
convey	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Cart	O
and	O
Horse	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
Stacey	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
Dennison	O
talked	O
Irish	O
with	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
I	O
sat	O
there	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
it	O
should	O
cost	O
me	O
nothing	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
there	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
Day-light	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ostler	O
of	O
my	O
Inn	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
a	O
Violin	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
merry	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Thoughts	O
of	O
my	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Sometime	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
not	O
knowing	O
how	O
to	O
proceed	O
,	O
a	O
Fellow	O
,	O
one	O
Baker	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
his	O
Assistance	O
as	O
an	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
drawn	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Way	O
of	O
Thinking	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
dropp	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
here	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
just	O
such	O
another	O
Affair	O
,	O
one	O
Lloyd	O
offer	O
'd	O
himself	O
as	O
an	O
Attorney	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
Dennison	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
the	O
Justice	O
upon	O
any	O
Account	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
the	O
first	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Parties	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Street	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
Information	O
from	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
Business	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Macdonnel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
great	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Stacey	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
Dennison	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Keogh	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Holford's-Alley	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Windsor	O
Court	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
one	O
Parish	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
Keogh	O
's	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Catherine	O
lineham	O
,	O
Stanton	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
,	O
Kate	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Stacey	O
,	O
all	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Broad	O
of	O
his	O
Back	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
O	I-pers
'	I-pers
Hara	I-pers
held	O
him	O
while	O
Stanton	O
that	O
was	O
hanged	O
,	O
tore	O
open	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Gold	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
Keogh	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Back	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Signs	O
to	O
Stacey	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
came	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
Watch	O
into	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
Cherry	O
Brandy	O
in	O
Pints	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
drink	O
it	O
by	O
Glasses	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
till	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
Stacey	O
,	O
Dennison	B-pers
,	O
O	B-pers
'Hara	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cullin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
Stacey	O
and	O
Dennison	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
went	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Inn	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
manner	O
we	O
led	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
belo	O
Dirty-Lane	O
into	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
silent	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Stacey	O
put	O
his	O
Foot	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Broad	O
of	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
about	O
18	O
or	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
empty	O
Cannister	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
his	O
Hat	O
;	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Keogh	O
asked	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
?	O
Stacey	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
what	O
was	O
doing	O
to	O
him	O
than	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Moon	O
.	O
Stacey	O
shewed	O
Keogh	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cast	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
amounted	O
to	O
20	O
l.	O
all	O
in	O
Gold	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
Money	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
equally	O
divided	O
among	O
all	O
the	O
People	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
divided	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Keogh	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Sessions	O
that	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
Affair	O
.	O
Stacey	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Custody	O
before	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
found	O
against	O
Stanton	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
very	O
Day	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
Stacey	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Defence	O
to	O
make	O
but	O
to	O
plead	O
my	O
own	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
call	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Sawyer	O
-	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
Lodging-House	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Lyon	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
rescuing	O
Margaret	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
charged	O
for	O
rescuing	O
Margaret	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
from	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
at	O
Keogh	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fulman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Windsor-Court	O
,	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Parish	O
came	O
'	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
that	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
her	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Country-Man	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
staid	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
by	O
Two	O
Women	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
executed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
afterwards	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Court	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
put	O
him	O
off	O
from	O
Time	O
to	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Stacey	O
;	O
and	O
Parish	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
Five	O
Guineas	O
a-piece	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Attorney	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Parish	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
honest	O
Attorney	O
that	O
assisted	O
me	O
.	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
Clerkship	O
with	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hartshorne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Northampton	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Parish	O
in	O
October	O
Sessions	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prosecute	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
Public	O
House	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Stacey	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
us	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
no	O
Pretension	O
to	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
said	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
more	O
Reason	O
to	O
believe	O
so	O
,	O
because	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
passed	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
,	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
that	O
Woman	O
to	O
be	O
Catherine	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
Mind	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
this	O
Minute	O
;	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
(	O
said	O
I	O
)	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
she	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
treat	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
you	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
your	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
severely	O
reprimanded	O
Baker	O
for	O
his	O
Conduct	O
in	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Stacey	O
is	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
Business	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Marshal's-Court	O
Officer	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
Year	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
He	O
has	O
employed	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
Cloaths	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
honestly	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Eoklin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Stacey	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
'till	O
his	O
Consinement	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
did	O
my	O
Business	O
faithfully	O
.	O
Dennison	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Bull	O
in	O
Vine-Street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Dennison	O
almost	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
Rowland	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
,	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
;	O
they	O
began	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
off	O
playing	O
just	O
at	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
be	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
till	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
exact	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Hour	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
Because	O
my	O
Master	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
bid	O
the	O
People	O
leave	O
off	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Old-Cloaths-Man	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
small	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Dennison	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
Years	O
;	O
his	O
Business	O
is	O
selling	O
Cloth	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Cribbidge	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Bull	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
,	O
from	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
6	O
,	O
to	O
almost	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
Wife	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
stay	O
out	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Landlord	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Cards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
Dennison	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
undress	O
himself	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Bull	O
,	O
at	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
playing	O
at	O
Cards	O
with	O
Dennison	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
at	O
Twelve	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Landlord	O
took	O
the	O
Cards	O
away	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
see	O
Dennison	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
Home	O
ogether	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
remembered	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
happened	O
on	O
my	O
Child	O
's	O
Birthday	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whittaker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Dennison	O
Ten	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
listed	O
in	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Albermarle	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
his	O
Duty	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
Five	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
with	O
me	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Hickenbottom	I-pers
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Street	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
ten	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Public	O
House	O
in	O
Windmill-Street	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
Ten	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Guards	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
Cloth	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
.	O
Ann	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Dennison	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
within	O
three	O
Doors	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
Vine-Street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Customer	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Harm	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
Cloth	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Litchfield-Street	O
,	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Dennison	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
his	O
coming	O
in	O
visit	O
a	O
Grenadier	O
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
26.	O
George	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
and	O
Matthias	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
,	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lineham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Arthur	B-pers
O	I-pers
Hara	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Cullin	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
Redman	O
Keogh	O
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mossey	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Benjamin	O
Parish	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Redman	O
Keogh	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
fourteen	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
.	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Parish	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Fulman	O
's	O
in	O
Windsor-Court	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
forced	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Redman	O
Keogh	O
,	O
by	O
George	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Keogh	O
,	O
Kate	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ruggaty	O
Madge	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lineham	I-pers
there	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
held	O
me	O
while	O
Stanton	O
tore	O
down	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
three	O
and	O
twenty	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
Robbery	O
!	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
Cherry-Brandy	O
in	O
Pint	O
Mugs	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
it	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
concerned	O
in	O
robbing	O
you	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
Kate	O
Butler	O
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lineham	I-pers
,	O
helped	O
to	O
hold	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
Stanton	O
rifled	O
me	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
Lineham	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
assisted	O
in	O
robbing	O
you	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
you	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
Brandy	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Lineham	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
they	O
forced	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
Lineham	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
in	O
Goal	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
Parish	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
Reason	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
60	O
Miles	O
from	O
London	O
Stephen	B-pers
Macdonnel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lineham	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Twelve	O
month	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
this	O
House	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
there	O
almost	O
every	O
Night	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Parish	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Stacey	O
,	O
Dennison	O
,	O
Lineham	O
,	O
and	O
Massey	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
I	O
keep	O
Company	O
,	O
all	O
on	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
once	O
;	O
Stacey	O
kept	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
crying	O
out	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Money	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
20	O
l.	O
all	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
Keogh	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
Time	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
divided	O
among	O
us	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
On	O
your	O
Oath	O
was	O
Lineham	O
there	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
helped	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Lineham	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
I	O
kept	O
Company	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
get	O
People	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
me	O
off	O
.	O
Lineham	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
did	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
twice	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Lineham	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
Case	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
detain	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Prison	O
.	O
Dennison	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Stacey	O
and	O
Lineham	O
,	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
27.	O
Morgan	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
East-India	B-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Game	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Board	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
a	O
Card	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
