TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
OF	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
16th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Heathcote	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
1742	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
Of	O
whom	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
The	O
Trial	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1742	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralties	O
of	O
Mr	O
Alderman	O
Perry	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HEATHCOTE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
REYNOLDS	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Currier	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Green	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dymock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prettyman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ottey	I-pers
,	O
Edgate	O
Sandwell	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hennell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Keyworth	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Wildair	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Ernest	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lutman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hamston	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Humblebee	I-pers
.	O
N.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
importunate	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
excused	O
,	O
upon	O
Account	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
Manner	O
disagreeable	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
not	O
excuse	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
coming	O
on	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
were	O
excused	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Richard	O
Green	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
's	O
Officers	O
went	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
in	O
Time	O
,	O
so	O
Elisha	O
Cawish	O
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
Green	O
was	O
fined	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
paid	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
112.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
11	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
Gown	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
dry	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
twelve	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
this	O
Gown	O
off	O
the	O
Line	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
School	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Gown	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Gown	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Paine	O
to	O
wash.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
113.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Francis	B-pers
Dodsworth	I-pers
Carver	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
October	O
10	O
.	O
Carver	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
Black-Boy-Alley	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Chick-Lane	I-place
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
.	O
She	O
whipt	O
my	O
Bundle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
a	O
Woman	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
under	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Mr	O
Dickerson	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
seeing	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Cross-Daggers	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
Things	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
brought	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
why	O
should	O
he	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
?	O
There	O
was	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
due	O
for	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
them	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
detained	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
.	O
114.	O
George	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hamstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hurd	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
18	O
William	B-pers
Hurd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
Coat	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
got	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
bring	O
this	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
's	O
Stable	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
115	O
,	O
116.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Luke	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Gallons	O
of	O
strong	O
Beer	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howson	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
Beer	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
known	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
some	O
People	O
in	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
the	O
Beer	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
missed	O
seven	O
Barrels	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
Green	O
's	O
Sister	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Floor	O
over	O
the	O
Store-Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Beer	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
help	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Beer	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
has	O
been	O
going	O
on	O
about	O
six	O
Months	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
last	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
Custody	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
now	O
:	O
They	O
got	O
in	O
by	O
taking	O
up	O
two	O
Boards	O
in	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hundred	O
Gallons	O
taken	O
out	O
:	O
Jane	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
took	O
out	O
about	O
fifteen	O
Gallons	O
:	O
Green	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
and	O
handed	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Difference	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Revenge	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
but	O
three	O
Months	O
in	O
Town	O
:	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
117.	O
Richard	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Bernard	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
September	O
28	O
.	O
Bernard	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
Hendon	B-place
Common	I-place
and	O
Ealing	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
Mr	O
Lawrence	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
partly	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
Mr	O
Lawrence	O
was	O
towards	O
the	O
Right-hand	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
the	O
Man	O
said	O
;	O
he	O
turns	O
about	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
Crown	O
Pieces	O
and	O
some	O
Shillings	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
lay	O
my	O
Hand	O
upon	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Shillings	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
keep	O
these	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
had	O
rode	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
the	O
Man	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
ill	O
Usage	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Heart	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
pleased	O
Mr	O
Lawrence	O
said	O
,	O
Mr	O
Gates	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
forward	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Way	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
:	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
my	O
Retinue	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
provided	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Fellows	O
are	O
all	O
couragious	O
,	O
they	O
shall	O
pursue	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
as	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Cape	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
about	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
sickly	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Fellow	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
then	O
as	O
the	O
poor	O
unhappy	O
Man	O
has	O
now	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
committed	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
Crown	O
Pieces	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
King	O
William	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Journeys	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Disguise	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Cape	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
buttoned	O
round	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Servants	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
directly	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mr	O
Gates	O
September	O
28	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
Track	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Gates	O
in	O
another	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
robbing	O
me	O
turned	O
about	O
to	O
Mr	O
Gates	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
turn	O
from	O
you	O
to	O
Mr	O
Gates	O
?	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
other	O
Reason	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
Mr	O
Gates	O
was	O
better	O
dressed	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Money	O
might	O
be	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
clapped	O
Spurs	O
to	O
my	O
Horse	O
and	O
rode	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
with	O
Mr	O
Gates	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Servants	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Servant	O
-	O
Stockwell	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
Mr	O
Gates	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
By	O
whom	O
says	O
my	O
Lord	O
?	O
Mr	O
Gates	O
described	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
riding	O
by	O
our	O
Coach	O
with	O
a	O
Cape	O
round	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
flapped	O
:	O
These	O
two	O
Men	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
Miles	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
Publick-House	O
by	O
Hanwell	O
Bridge	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
:	O
We	O
all	O
three	O
whipt	O
in	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
two	O
Bullets	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Flints	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
Crown-Pieces	O
,	O
several	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
surprising	O
thing	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
your	O
Condition	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Way	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
entirely	O
Necessity	O
that	O
has	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
London	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hired	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Pistol	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
really	O
in	O
Want	O
.	O
-	O
Clark	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
sent	O
us	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
the	O
People	O
told	O
us	O
was	O
called	O
Chevy-Chace	O
,	O
by	O
Hanwell-Bridge	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
robbed	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
.	O
Bryan	O
confirmed	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Evidence	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
he	O
made	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
;	O
he	O
therein	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
he	O
hired	O
a	O
Bay-Horse	O
in	O
Finsbury	O
,	O
by	O
Chiswell-Street	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
rob	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
stopped	O
Mr	O
Gates	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
by	O
three	O
Men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
118.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brighton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Turnagain-lane	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
between	O
Holborn	B-place
Bridge	I-place
and	O
Shoe-Lane	B-place
,	O
says	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
That	O
Fellow	O
has	O
picked	O
your	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
Fellow	O
's	O
Feet	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Grocer	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Fellows	O
came	O
to	O
rescue	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
Blows	O
from	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Mr	O
Lewin	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
Bellamy	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
These	O
four	O
Handkerchiefs	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Tenant	O
to	O
Esquire	O
Herbert	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbour-hood	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
Rent-gatherer	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
goes	O
a	O
-	O
Grubbing	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
gathering	O
old	O
Iron	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
-	O
His	O
Business	O
is	O
Grubbing	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
for	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Channel	O
Raking	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
119.	O
William	B-pers
Budge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
printed	O
Book	O
commonly	O
called	O
the	O
First	O
Volume	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
this	O
Book	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Book	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
Adams	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Shilling	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
120	O
,	O
121.	O
Mary	B-pers
Vearpoint	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Vearpoint	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
and	O
Bristow	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Things	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Brompton	B-place
;	O
Vearpoint	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
Michaelmas	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
two	O
Spoons	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
Linnen	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
several	O
Things	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Linnen	O
.	O
I	O
discharged	O
her	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
that	O
Woman	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
gone	O
the	O
Way	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Goodwin	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
this	O
Woman	O
had	O
pawned	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Linnen	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
fetched	O
out	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
These	O
are	O
all	O
Mine	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
Spoons	O
about	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Linnen	O
was	O
brought	O
about	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
This	O
Linnen	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
she	O
brought	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Vearpoint	O
's	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
About	O
last	O
Monday	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
about	O
Mrs	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Spoons	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
lent	O
Bristow	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
Vearpoint	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
Bristow	O
had	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
but	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
has	O
kept	O
the	O
rest	O
herself	O
.	O
Vearpoint	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
these	O
Things	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
designed	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
[	O
Bristow	O
's	O
]	O
Husband	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Spoons	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
Vearpoint	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
Woman	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Vearpoint	O
guilty	O
,	O
Bristow	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
122.	O
Robert	B-pers
Logan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
Spittle-Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Owden	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Owden	I-pers
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Shirt	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Noon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
123.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Corral	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
Gold	O
Locket	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Brinkwell	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Necklace	O
from	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Necklace	O
from	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
kiss	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Necklace	O
fell	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Necklace	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Locket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
Value	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
down	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Back	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Locket	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
School	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Necklace	O
upon	O
her	O
Neck	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
After	O
she	O
denied	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
they	O
be	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lines	I-pers
.	O
The	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
break	O
this	O
off	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Neck	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
124.	O
John	B-pers
Heaney	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ceeney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
-	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
Chain	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lemmon	I-pers
.	O
Henry	O
Lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
like	O
Man	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
accepted	O
of	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
into	O
Pope's-Court	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Bell-Yard	I-place
;	O
and	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
we	O
met	O
John	B-pers
Heaney	I-pers
;	O
says	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
Shilling	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
treat	O
this	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
They	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
inner	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
some	O
Wine	O
,	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
talk	O
of	O
cutting	O
of	O
Cards	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
out	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
Cards	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
returned	O
so	O
quick	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
played	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
prevailed	O
on	O
to	O
bet	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
won	O
two	O
Shillings	O
;	O
so	O
this	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
Shilling	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
good	O
Cards	O
,	O
Court	O
Cards	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
cut	O
;	O
I	O
apprehend	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Packs	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
cut	O
,	O
I	O
cut	O
nothing	O
but	O
Aces	O
and	O
Duces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
two	O
Shillings	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
venture	O
another	O
Shilling	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
a	O
Shilling	O
:	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
no	O
Watch	O
nor	O
nothing	O
to	O
put	O
down	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Watch	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
;	O
still	O
the	O
Cards	O
were	O
low	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
every	O
Time	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Shillings	O
that	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
afterwards	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Newgate-street	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
brisk	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
release	O
me	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
Watch	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
begged	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
your	O
Watch	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
So	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
he	O
might	O
trouble	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
walk	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Guild-Hall	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
fumbling	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Hopes	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
two	O
Packs	O
of	O
Cards	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Another	O
Man	O
put	O
down	O
a	O
Ring	O
to	O
answer	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
plaid	O
till	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
Six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
won	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
Body	O
put	O
down	O
a	O
Ring	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
did	O
to	O
bet	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
while	O
Mr	O
Lane	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
has	O
sworn	O
a	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
won	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
unlikely	O
a	O
Man	O
should	O
be	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
at	O
Noon-Day	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
.	O
Lane	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
some	O
Murders	O
and	O
Robberies	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Blakesley	I-pers
says	O
she	O
has	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
kept	O
good	O
Hours	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Watch-Maker	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
got	O
his	O
Living	O
honestly	O
and	O
truly	O
,	O
without	O
following	O
this	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
gave	O
him	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
125	O
,	O
126.	O
Jane	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
and	O
Isabella	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Plad-Banjan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth-Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Brown	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
Russel	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
my	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Banjan	O
were	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
presently	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
charged	O
Russel	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Person	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Brown	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
Pence	O
.	O
Brown	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
,	O
Russel	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Brown	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
but	O
three	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Closet	O
;	O
the	O
Girl	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
nailed	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
Word	O
used	O
among	O
Thieves	O
.	O
Russel	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Brown	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
127	O
,	O
128	O
,	O
129.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Maccomb	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hambly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cady	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Working-Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Alloby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
several	O
Persons	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
lost	O
the	O
Tools	O
therein	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
Joseph	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Verginia-Street	B-place
,	O
October	O
3.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Tools	O
produc	O
'd	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Tools	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
broke	O
open	O
Mr	O
West	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Virginia-Street	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
agreed	O
before	O
Hand	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
broke	O
the	O
Street-door	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Tools	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
-	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
which	O
prevented	O
us	O
breaking	O
that	O
Way	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eady	I-pers
had	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Working-Tools	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
new	O
Building	O
,	O
some	O
we	O
carried	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
where	O
the	O
Tools	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
Tools	O
that	O
we	O
four	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
commit	O
one	O
Robbery	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
that	O
Night	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
any	O
House	O
.	O
Thomson	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Tools	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Chamber	O
with	O
Mc	O
Comb	O
on	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Being	O
from	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
six	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Sampson	O
,	O
Matthews	O
,	O
and	O
Tyrrel	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
that	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
.	O
Hambly	O
has	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
these	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
on	O
Sunday	O
at	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
till	O
after	O
six	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
He	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
general	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Hasbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
on	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
rose	O
till	O
after	O
six	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
lie	O
underneath	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
never	O
stir	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
hear	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Eady	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
till	O
near	O
six	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
130.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Homan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
by	O
striking	O
her	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
one	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Eye	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
August	O
2	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stayner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Raven	O
's	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dicks	O
's	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	B-place
,	O
August	O
2.	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
dreadful	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
I	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
and	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Blood	O
come	O
against	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
woollen	O
Cap	O
peep	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
Mrs	O
Dicks	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
deplorable	O
Manner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
gore	O
Blood	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
lived	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Widow	O
Gentlewoman	O
of	O
74	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
her	O
Senses	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
;	O
we	O
laid	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
run	O
through	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
Marks	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Left-side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dreadful	O
Cut	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Cut	O
by	O
a	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
by	O
a	O
Knife	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
other	O
Wounds	O
on	O
her	O
Neck	O
and	O
Breast	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
this	O
Condition	O
from	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
eleven	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
being	O
undressed	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
speak	O
you	O
should	O
tell	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
!	O
Lord	O
!	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
me	O
?	O
Stayner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
you	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nannay	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
an	O
half	O
after	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Wounds	O
in	O
her	O
Head	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
attended	O
with	O
a	O
Fracture	O
in	O
her	O
Skull	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Brain	O
was	O
wounded	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
dressing	O
the	O
Woman	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
villainous	O
Thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
assaulted	O
him	O
first	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
Lord	O
!	O
Lord	O
!	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Hamper	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
use	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
in	O
so	O
barbarous	O
a	O
Manner	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
.	O
I	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
afterwards	O
the	O
committing	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
?	O
Palmer	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
Near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
I	O
found	O
an	O
Iron	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
,	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
some	O
Dirt	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
bloody	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Dirt	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
his	O
Linnen	O
was	O
bloody	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Mr	O
Cooch	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Master	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
directly	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
murdered	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
the	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
:	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
running	O
through	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Cieling	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
live	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Cap	O
put	O
the	O
Curtain	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
set	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
People	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
My	O
Lad	O
took	O
a	O
Stick	O
and	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
a	O
Hamper	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
jumps	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Dicks	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
would	O
live	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
your	O
Hand	O
bloody	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
my	O
Nose	O
has	O
bled	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
lying	O
Rogue	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
not	O
bled	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Head	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
His	O
Hand	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
bloody	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Fingers	O
Ends	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
an	O
Alderman	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Heart	O
always	O
misgave	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
the	O
Alderman	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Bar	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
lay	O
somewhere	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
he	O
resolved	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
concealed	O
till	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
:	O
He	O
wrenched	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs-foot	O
Door	O
off	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
down	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
but	O
she	O
run	O
back	O
,	O
frightened	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bar	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
:	O
She	O
clapped	O
a	O
Chair	O
and	O
Table	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Poker	O
or	O
Tongs	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
repeated	O
the	O
Blows	O
till	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
confessed	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
without	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
running	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
under	O
a	O
Hamper	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
murdered	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
said	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
little	O
deaf	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
:	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
Lock	O
off	O
the	O
Door	O
?	O
Coach	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
aid	O
and	O
assist	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
lying	O
in	O
her	O
Blood	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
his	O
Blows	O
till	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
that	O
Condition	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
signed	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sleepy	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
slept	O
his	O
Time	O
away	O
.	O
Mr	O
Jefferies	O
likewise	O
confirmed	O
great	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
131.	O
William	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Aldin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
August	O
24	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Aldin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
stole	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
I	O
drew	O
it	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
about	O
some	O
Business	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
Drinking-room	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Charity	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
on	O
Monday	O
-	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
Beer	O
there	O
the	O
best	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
drawed	O
him	O
a	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
drew	O
him	O
a	O
Pint	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
moved	O
himself	O
nearer	O
towards	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
drank	O
all	O
your	O
Beer	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
drink	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
leave	O
Tankards	O
in	O
this	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
just	O
turned	O
my	O
Back	O
.	O
-	O
No	O
Body	O
else	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Windows	O
were	O
open	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
Tankard	O
away	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
there	O
but	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Oath	O
is	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
your	O
's	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
two	O
Tankards	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Tankards	O
to	O
Wooburn	O
in	O
Bedfordshire	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wrote	O
a	O
Letter	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
directing	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Tankards	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Aldin	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Tankard	O
-	O
this	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Sherbert	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
Tankard	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Friend	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Marks	O
and	O
Weight	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
Account	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
five	O
Shillings	O
and	O
three	O
Pence	O
per	O
Ounce	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
six	O
Pounds	O
fourteen	O
Shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Am	O
I	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
you	O
that	O
Tankard	O
?	O
Sherbert	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
very	O
Person	O
who	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bramston	O
produced	O
his	O
Examination	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Bedford	O
,	O
taken	O
September	O
13	O
,	O
1742.	O
and	O
signed	O
William	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
;	O
wherein	O
he	O
confesses	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Aldin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	O
George	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	O
Mary	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
Mr	O
Ellis	O
's	O
for	O
five	O
Pounds	O
two	O
Shillings	O
over	O
or	O
under	O
;	O
and	O
Mr	O
Aldin	O
's	O
for	O
six	O
Pounds	O
two	O
Shillings	O
over	O
or	O
under	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
drunk	O
with	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
thing	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
prosessed	O
great	O
Friendship	O
to	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
discover	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
:	O
They	O
promised	O
punctually	O
they	O
would	O
no	O
ways	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
be	O
made	O
Retaliation	O
for	O
the	O
Loss	O
-	O
they	O
frightened	O
me	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Friends	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bramston	O
.	O
This	O
Examination	O
was	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
neither	O
Threats	O
,	O
or	O
Promises	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
voluntarily	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
132.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
116	O
Ells	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
called	O
Gulix	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
l.	O
623	O
Lawn	B-pers
Handkerchiefs	I-pers
,	O
value	O
44	O
l.	O
and	O
90	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
August	O
21	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
The	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
my	O
Cellar-Window	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
rose	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
was	O
broke	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
killed	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Rogues	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Watchman	O
stands	O
at	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar-Door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
fastens	O
with	O
two	O
Bolts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dog	O
into	O
a	O
Kirb	O
;	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Warehouse	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
things	O
into	O
that	O
my	O
Shop	O
will	O
not	O
hold	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
August	O
20.	O
William	B-pers
Pritchet	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
your	O
Company	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
Cock's-head-Court	O
,	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
Kent	O
lives	O
;	O
says	O
Kent	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
a	O
Penny	O
?	O
So	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
:	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
Kent	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
somebody	O
is	O
coming	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Kent	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Load	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
Bird	O
with	O
two	O
long	O
Pieces	O
rolled	O
up	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
Kent	O
put	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
:	O
Seeing	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
robbing	O
:	O
They	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
:	O
They	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
Kent	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
Says	O
Kent	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
,	O
take	O
this	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Stones-throw	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Ken	O
t	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Load	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Grub-street	O
,	O
says	O
Kent	O
,	O
Pritchet	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
now	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
go	O
now	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
Says	O
Kent	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
has	O
got	O
an	O
old	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
that	O
for	O
your	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Kent	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
About	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Bird	O
and	O
Kent	O
bring	O
several	O
Bundles	O
into	O
Kent	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
afterwards	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rugby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
Aug.	O
21	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Sanders	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
intended	O
Sale	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
sold	O
to	O
some	O
Jews	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
conscientious	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Holland	O
,	O
that	O
cost	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
an	O
Ell	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
at	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sanders	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
that	O
Pritchet	O
may	O
be	O
detained	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
(	O
Kent	O
)	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
incorrigible	O
Villain	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
catch	O
him	O
very	O
quickly	O
.	O
Pritchet	O
gave	O
his	O
own	O
Consent	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
rather	O
be	O
there	O
than	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
killed	O
.	O
133.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Feather-Bed	O
and	O
Bolster	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Chimney-Glass	O
,	O
two	O
Sconces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Houshold	O
Furniture	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
24	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lodging	O
which	O
I	O
let	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
ready	O
furnished	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
above	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
Things	O
missing	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Chimney-Glass	O
and	O
Sconces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Feather-Bed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cadwallader	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pawned	O
several	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Fountaine	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
Sheets	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
134.	O
William	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
*	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
9	O
.	O
No	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Mat	O
.	O
Mooney	O
,	O
condemned	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
detained	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
in	O
Surrey	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
135.	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
one	O
Phillis	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Phillis	O
,	O
then	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
close	O
Room	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
then	O
being	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Building	O
called	O
St	O
Martin	O
's	O
Round-House	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
confine	O
and	O
continue	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Phillis	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
Space	O
of	O
Time	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
eight	O
Hours	O
,	O
during	O
great	O
Part	O
of	O
which	O
Time	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
four	O
Hours	O
thereof	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
other	O
Persons	O
confined	O
as	O
Prisoners	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
close	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Largeness	O
to	O
confine	O
twenty	O
Persons	O
therein	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
three	O
Hours	O
,	O
without	O
manifest	O
Danger	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
said	O
confining	O
and	O
continuing	O
of	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Phillis	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Manner	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Phillis	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
within	O
the	O
said	O
close	O
Room	O
,	O
was	O
suffocated	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Suffocation	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
Day	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Year	O
,	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
,	O
[	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
above	O
]	O
the	O
said	O
Phillis	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
did	O
feloniously	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Case	O
having	O
been	O
fully	O
opened	O
by	O
the	O
Council	O
,	O
and	O
printed	O
at	O
length	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
now	O
begin	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
charged	O
by	O
the	O
High-Constable	O
with	O
Phillis	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
High-Constable	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
conduct	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
Charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
High-Constable	O
sent	O
one	O
Clark	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
Bone-House	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
Brother-in-Law	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
Frazer	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
House	O
keeper	O
in	O
my	O
Beat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
High-Constable	O
called	O
out	O
Watch	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
her	O
lawful	O
Affairs	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Bird	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
my	O
general	O
Behaviour	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
is	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
Complaints	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
if	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
rude	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
sent	O
them	O
down	O
into	O
that	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
Usage	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
disorderly	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
speak	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Some	O
speak	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
speak	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
?	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
kind	O
Goaler	O
,	O
or	O
is	O
he	O
otherwise	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
Answer	O
to	O
that	O
:	O
-	O
The	O
Girl	O
was	O
in	O
good	O
Health	O
,	O
only	O
frightened	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
which	O
she	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
before	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Saint	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Phillis	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
about	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
the	O
Place	O
was	O
full	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
,	O
-	O
my	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
there	O
-	O
Mrs	O
Frazer	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
seeming	O
good	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
freely	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Phil	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
here	O
?	O
She	O
cried	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Saint	I-pers
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
Water	O
?	O
I	O
stepped	O
up	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Bird	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Saint	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
dead	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
came	O
from	O
Deptford	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
lightish	O
Callimanco	O
Gown	O
on	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
about	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
Number	O
of	O
Persons	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
cried	O
out	O
they	O
should	O
all	O
be	O
smothered	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Frazer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
called	O
me	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
sell	O
Physical	O
Herbs	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
High-Constable	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
St	O
Martin	O
's	O
Round-House	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Danger	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
my	O
Maid	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
there	O
about	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
dead	O
,	O
one	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Right-Hand	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
on	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
lightish	O
Brown	B-pers
Colour	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Frazer	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Frazer	I-pers
is	O
my	O
Brother	O
:	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
Phillis	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
whitish	O
brown	O
Gown	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
modest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Churchman	I-pers
then	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
customary	O
for	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
that	O
lets	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
open	O
?	O
Churchman	O
.	O
It	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
customary	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
thing	O
that	O
hardly	O
ever	O
did	O
happen	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cosier	I-pers
.	O
-	O
We	O
cried	O
out	O
Fire	O
and	O
Murder	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
People	O
in	O
Labour	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
had	O
better	O
be	O
hanged	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
One	O
Woman	O
pulled	O
her	O
Shoe	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
hear	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
could	O
but	O
just	O
stand	O
upright	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
half-pence	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
offered	O
that	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Air	O
.	O
-	O
Bird	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
fastened	O
the	O
Door	O
enough	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
Poker	O
to	O
fasten	O
it	O
with	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
because	O
we	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
Noise	O
for	O
Water	O
,	O
Air	O
,	O
and	O
Light	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
the	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
except	O
three	O
besides	O
the	O
dead	O
Women	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
in	O
Fits	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
Heat	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
we	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
There	O
were	O
Women	O
in	O
Fits	O
,	O
Women	O
in	O
Labour	O
,	O
and	O
Women	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
Have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
the	O
Infants	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
none	O
upon	O
us	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
Bird	O
heard	O
us	O
.	O
If	O
that	O
Door	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
saved	O
all	O
their	O
Lives	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
wanted	O
Air	O
most	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
continual	O
Cry	O
from	O
that	O
Time	O
till	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Skin	O
of	O
my	O
Face	O
rose	O
in	O
Blisters	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
came	O
off	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
she	O
agreed	O
with	O
her	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Amey	I-pers
(	O
having	O
given	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
)	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
some	O
came	O
out	O
stark	O
naked	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Bed-Gown	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
wet	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
rung	O
the	O
Sweat	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Mrs	O
Bird	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
stinking	O
Water	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
drank	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
drank	O
about	O
three	O
Quarts	O
of	O
clean	O
Water	O
.	O
Bird	O
said	O
once	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Window	O
should	O
be	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
shut	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
Account	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
bringing	O
some	O
spiritual	O
Liquor	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
Room	O
enough	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
without	O
Money	O
.	O
-	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
was	O
in	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
as	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
herself	O
for	O
two	O
Days	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
upon	O
some	O
Account	O
or	O
other	O
?	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
Oxendon	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Coachman	O
was	O
murdered	O
?	O
*	O
Amey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
Waiter	O
at	O
Mr	O
Eastmead	O
's	O
Bagnio	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lay	O
a	O
Night	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
Trials	O
in	O
Mr	O
Alderman	O
Perry	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
390.	O
page	O
110	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
's	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
159.	O
page	O
89.	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
274.	O
page	O
163.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Starks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Eleven	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
by	O
Mr	O
Bird	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
six	O
down	O
there	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
see	O
how	O
many	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
twenty-six	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Window	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
might	O
be	O
open	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
That	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
again	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
Four	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
again	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
Five	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
were	O
crying	O
out	O
for	O
Water	O
and	O
Air	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Bird	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Mr	O
Bird	O
came	O
down	O
several	O
Times	O
-	O
And	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
Water	O
and	O
Air	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
we	O
should	O
neither	O
have	O
Air	O
nor	O
Water	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
positively	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
made	O
Answer	O
so	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Shilling	O
offered	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Water	O
;	O
we	O
raised	O
among	O
ourselves	O
four	O
Shillings	O
for	O
a	O
Gallon	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Woman	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
struck	O
her	O
because	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
Wine	O
or	O
something	O
to	O
comfort	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
all	O
suffer	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
die	O
and	O
be	O
damned	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
Fire	O
and	O
Murder	O
.	O
-	O
Bird	O
shut	O
the	O
Window	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
twice	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
die	O
and	O
be	O
damned	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
should	O
stay	O
till	O
let	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
High-Constable	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
he	O
struck	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Kick	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
her	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
die	O
and	O
be	O
damned	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
my	O
Intention	O
in	O
shutting	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
to	O
stifle	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
sober	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
Starks	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
his	O
Intention	O
was	O
to	O
stifle	O
us	O
all	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bed	O
from	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watchhouse	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
kept	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
Money	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
Six-pence	O
for	O
sitting	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
out	O
for	O
Air	O
and	O
Water	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
cried	O
out	O
Fire	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Labour	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
for	O
a	O
Gallon	O
:	O
Bird	O
sat	O
writing	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
the	O
Bitches	O
they	O
want	O
Gin	O
.	O
On	O
their	O
crying	O
out	O
they	O
should	O
die	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
die	O
and	O
be	O
damned	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
indeed	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
supplying	O
them	O
with	O
Water	O
through	O
a	O
Tobacco-Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
Bird	O
said	O
he	O
caught	O
them	O
drinking	O
of	O
Gin	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Henry	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
William	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Coach-maker	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
-	O
Bird	O
ordered	O
Bushel	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
put	O
some	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Bushel	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
put	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
Bird	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pushed	O
them	O
down	O
Stairs	O
one	O
over	O
another	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Room	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
above	O
Stairs	O
.	O
-	O
Bird	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
were	O
kept	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
pay	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Norton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
Six-pence	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Usquebaugh	O
,	O
and	O
Six	O
pence	O
to	O
your	O
Wife	O
for	O
sitting	O
up	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
before	O
;	O
have	O
not	O
you	O
expressed	O
yourself	O
much	O
in	O
my	O
Favour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
you	O
examined	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
Norton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Mr	O
Bird	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
wrong	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
examined	O
of	O
your	O
Side	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
wrong	O
my	O
Conscience	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
was	O
consistent	O
with	O
her	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
this	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
with	O
some	O
Coltsfoot	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
(	O
My	O
Cousin	O
Maurice	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
my	O
Knee	O
.	O
)	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
;	O
if	O
my	O
Brother	O
knew	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
grow	O
crazy	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
faint	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Drop	O
of	O
Water	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
better	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Support	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
after	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
nobody	O
came	O
near	O
us	O
:	O
She	O
died	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
or	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
She	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
Health	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
took	O
on	O
upon	O
Account	O
of	O
being	O
carried	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
Bird	O
himself	O
brought	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
wanted	O
Water	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Water	O
,	O
you	O
Bitches	O
,	O
be	O
damned	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
die	O
,	O
then	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Surridge	I-pers
was	O
very	O
exact	O
with	O
her	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
Mr	O
Leathes	O
Serjeant	O
Burns	O
gave	O
the	O
like	O
Account	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Cries	O
and	O
Condition	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
.	O
Mr	O
Bushel	O
the	O
Beadle	O
called	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
submit	O
it	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
proper	O
Witness	O
;	O
because	O
he	O
attended	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
being	O
sent	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
Women	O
,	O
as	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
the	O
upper	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
have	O
been	O
secure	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Women	O
had	O
been	O
let	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
?	O
Bushel	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
:	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Lock	O
and	O
two	O
Bolts	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
strong	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
They	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Round-House	O
.	O
-	O
Three	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
one	O
got	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
there	O
:	O
About	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
after	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
Bird	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
die	O
,	O
one	O
Betty	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
You	O
Bitch	O
of	O
Hell	O
,	O
no	O
Carrion	O
will	O
kill	O
a	O
Crow	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
made	O
no	O
Reply	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
speak	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
without	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
almost	O
stifled	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
being	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
ill	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
send	O
you	O
for	O
Spirits	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
People	O
to	O
bleed	O
them	O
.	O
Bushel	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
sent	O
Broadbent	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
would	O
send	O
the	O
Chair	O
from	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Chair	O
was	O
brought	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Recollect	O
yourself	O
.	O
Bushel	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
bleed	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
-	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Tilton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
on	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
now	O
examined	O
on	O
the	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Bird	O
's	O
putting	O
down	O
some	O
Prisoners	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
after	O
Bushel	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
put	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
stifled	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
what	O
passed	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
leaving	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
]	O
Bird	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Order	O
given	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Shutter	O
open	O
?	O
Who	O
gave	O
the	O
Order	O
?	O
Tilton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
Order	O
given	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
Air	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
open	O
at	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
kept	O
open	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
?	O
Tilton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
Out-cry	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
Bird	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
Mr	O
Bushel	O
?	O
Bushel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Desborough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
confined	O
in	O
St	O
Martin	O
's	O
Round-house	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
Bushel	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
some	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
Time	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
nor	O
how	O
many	O
he	O
brought	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
fastened	O
;	O
he	O
spoke	O
this	O
to	O
Bird	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
Answer	O
Bird	O
made	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
directly	O
,	O
struck	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Amey	I-pers
,	O
pulled	O
her	O
Cap	O
off	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
pushed	O
us	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
Room	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
several	O
Expressions	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
when	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
?	O
Desborough	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
some	O
might	O
stand	O
just	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
Bushel	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
close	O
with	O
it	O
shut	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
Refreshment	O
came	O
into	O
us	O
from	O
the	O
Air	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Perkins	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Colclough	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
bleed	O
these	O
People	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
now	O
,	O
of	O
their	O
Condition	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
Place	O
would	O
contain	O
twenty	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
three	O
Hours	O
,	O
without	O
manifest	O
Danger	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
?	O
Perkins	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
would	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
were	O
shut	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
apprehend	O
they	O
were	O
suffocated	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
a	O
due	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Air	O
,	O
for	O
Inspiration	O
and	O
Respiration	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Bodies	O
opened	O
?	O
Perkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Dropsy	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
the	O
Suffocation	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
a	O
Person	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
distinguished	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
Suffocation	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
Liquor	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Air	O
?	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Sir	O
Hans	B-pers
Sloane	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Case	O
that	O
happened	O
at	O
Hertford	O
some	O
Years	O
ago	O
*	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
Spoonfuls	O
of	O
Liquor	O
will	O
suffocate	O
a	O
Person	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
late	O
Edition	O
of	O
State-Trials	O
,	O
Vol	O
.	O
V.	O
pag	O
.	O
217	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Colclough	O
.	O
Would	O
that	O
Place	O
contain	O
twenty	O
Persons	O
three	O
Hours	O
,	O
without	O
manifest	O
Danger	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
?	O
Colclough	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
dead	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Heat	O
as	O
that	O
for	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
live	O
under	O
those	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
hot	O
Weather	O
;	O
indeed	O
Winter	O
Time	O
makes	O
a	O
Difference	O
.	O
-	O
Their	O
Death	O
was	O
occasioned	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Opinion	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
confined	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
Air	O
and	O
Water	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
in	O
your	O
Opinion	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
their	O
Death	O
?	O
Colclough	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Person	O
who	O
stands	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Crime	O
of	O
Murder	O
;	O
a	O
Crime	O
of	O
the	O
highest	O
Nature	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
,	O
with	O
your	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Assistance	O
,	O
in	O
Points	O
of	O
Law	O
,	O
bring	O
myself	O
off	O
this	O
Charge	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
clamoured	O
abroad	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
Effect	O
upon	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
endeavour	O
to	O
bring	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Credit	O
to	O
be	O
believed	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
from	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
such	O
Persons	O
as	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Warrant	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
returned	O
at	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
proper	O
Officer	O
had	O
came	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
lay	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
at	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
I	O
lay	O
till	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
Application	O
for	O
Assistance	O
to	O
relieve	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
Number	O
it	O
could	O
hold	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Occasion	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
get	O
,	O
no	O
Liquor	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
doing	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Property	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
declare	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Affair	O
was	O
without	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
or	O
Inclination	O
.	O
[	O
William	B-pers
Malpas	I-pers
called	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
]	O
Bird	O
.	O
Will	O
your	O
Lordship	O
please	O
to	O
order	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
speak	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Malpas	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Persons	O
that	O
died	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
whole	O
Night	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
use	O
any	O
Cruelty	O
towards	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
from	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
Ten	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
particular	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
all	O
my	O
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Hole	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
knocked	O
out	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
confined	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
was	O
bustling	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
Mr	O
Bird	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
believe	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Mr	O
Malpas	O
,	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
what	O
Part	O
I	O
acted	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
acted	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Malpas	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
writing	O
most	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Mr	O
Akins	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
ordered	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
cleared	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
do	O
this	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Head	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
without	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Order	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
make	O
any	O
Objection	O
to	O
the	O
Discharge	O
of	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
for	O
breaking	O
of	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
discharged	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Wells	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
put	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
till	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
down	O
?	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
down	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Who	O
knocked	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Amey	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
behave	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
She	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
abrupt	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
bred	O
Differences	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
ordered	O
down	O
at	O
first	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
that	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Six	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
did	O
you	O
call	O
me	O
again	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
About	O
Nine	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
laid	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
on	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
Time	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
or	O
Water	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
Malpas	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
from	O
first	O
to	O
last	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
The	O
Place	O
is	O
so	O
accustomed	O
to	O
Noises	O
that	O
one	O
does	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
there	O
is	O
Danger	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
Cries	O
of	O
Murder	O
while	O
you	O
were	O
up	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
do	O
them	O
an	O
Injury	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
was	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
Bird	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
who	O
brought	O
Liquor	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
their	O
Friends	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
they	O
defend	O
themselves	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
Liquor	O
?	O
And	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
how	O
bad	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
bleed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
Care	O
he	O
could	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
being	O
up	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
once	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
Bird	O
all	O
the	O
Service	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
civil	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Now	O
she	O
tells	O
another	O
Tale	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
divers	O
Times	O
with	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
I	O
could	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
were	O
near	O
forty	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
that	O
could	O
neither	O
read	O
nor	O
write	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
sit	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
.	O
Malpas	O
.	O
Several	O
were	O
put	O
down	O
by	O
Watchmen	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Pray	O
did	O
I	O
drink	O
with	O
Serjeant	O
Burns	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Bird	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
Liquor	O
come	O
from	O
.	O
Malpas	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
Pray	O
did	O
I	O
take	O
any	O
Money	O
of	O
Mrs	O
Norton	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
stay	O
up	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
forced	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Distress	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
relieved	O
them	O
?	O
Malpas	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
heard	O
any	O
Noise	O
or	O
Outcry	O
upon	O
any	O
Occasion	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
wanting	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Expression	O
't	O
is	O
said	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
of	O
Die	O
and	O
be	O
damned	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
such	O
Words	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
inadvertent	O
Expression	O
of	O
my	O
Tongue	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
from	O
my	O
Heart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Bird	O
when	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
struggling	O
with	O
Amey	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
immediately	O
shut	O
up	O
by	O
Mr	O
Bird	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
when	O
you	O
carried	O
the	O
Candle	O
down	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
full	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
disagreeable	O
Smell	O
or	O
Stench	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Bushel	O
's	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
put	O
any	O
more	O
down	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
said	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Bushel	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
Reason	O
assigned	O
why	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
stifled	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
like	O
that	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
Answer	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
hear	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
fear	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
should	O
be	O
stifled	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
hear	O
it	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
spoke	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
desire	O
the	O
Shutter	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
to	O
be	O
lest	O
open	O
?	O
Malpas	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
shut	O
again	O
between	O
Five	O
and	O
Six	O
by	O
Bird	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
Gin	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mr	O
Bird	O
shut	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Room	O
above	O
extends	O
over	O
the	O
two	O
Holes	O
and	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
that	O
Room	O
Mr	O
Bird	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
lie	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Drinking-Room	O
till	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
above	O
Stairs	O
till	O
nine	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Misbehaviour	O
in	O
Bird	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
ill	O
Word	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
most	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
writing	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
At	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
the	O
Beadle	O
insisted	O
on	O
the	O
Room	O
being	O
cleared	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
Body	O
cry	O
out	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Distress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
singing	O
?	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
singing	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
singing	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Sure	O
you	O
are	O
mistaken	O
!	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
Indeed	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
Singing	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
?	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Women	O
's	O
Voices	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Men	O
down	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Women	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
above	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
pay	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
more	O
already	O
than	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
more	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
nothing	O
amiss	O
in	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
yourself	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
civil	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
so	O
civilly	O
?	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
;	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
on	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
Condition	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
desired	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
to	O
all	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
-	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
Complaints	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
you	O
:	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
the	O
Beadle	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
sit	O
on	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
single	O
Woman	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
Mr	O
Bird	O
;	O
the	O
Rooms	O
are	O
parted	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Speech	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Speech	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
?	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
when	O
Bird	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
tall	O
Man	O
(	O
Bushel	O
)	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Bushel	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Bushel	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
Tilton	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Beadle	O
who	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Curiosity	O
.	O
Akins	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
Man	O
[	O
pointing	O
to	O
Akins	O
]	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
?	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
?	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
Mr	O
Bushel	O
that	O
made	O
that	O
Speech	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Akins	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
any	O
Woman	O
into	O
the	O
Hole	O
?	O
Akins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
Bird	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
?	O
Akins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
Bird	O
knows	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
that	O
Woman	O
says	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
?	O
Akins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
?	O
Akins	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
such	O
Expression	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
none	O
down	O
all	O
the	O
Year	O
.	O
Bushel	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
Bird	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
from	O
Good	O
will	O
.	O
Tilton	O
.	O
Bird	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Akins	O
never	O
did	O
stir	O
down	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Akins	O
,	O
you	O
swore	O
you	O
were	O
down	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Steps	O
:	O
I	O
shall	O
catch	O
you	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
.	O
-	O
What	O
Time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
away	O
?	O
Akins	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Four	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Cries	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
hear	O
Singing	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
Mens	O
Hole	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Womens	O
Hole	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
no	O
Orders	O
whether	O
the	O
Window	O
should	O
be	O
shut	O
or	O
open	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hooper	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
and	O
Apothecary	O
;	O
being	O
informed	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
at	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Colclough	O
bleeding	O
the	O
Women	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
best	O
,	O
for	O
Expedition	O
,	O
to	O
cut	O
them	O
down	O
the	O
temporal	O
Artery	O
.	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
bleed	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
that	O
expired	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
Duty	O
incumbent	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
Mr	O
Colclough	O
to	O
bleed	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
well	O
.	O
Bird	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
both	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Humanity	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Drops	O
and	O
Water	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
what	O
we	O
wanted	O
,	O
as	O
often	O
as	O
we	O
called	O
.	O
Bird	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
of	O
any	O
Complaints	O
of	O
my	O
using	O
People	O
ill	O
?	O
Hooper	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
one	O
Way	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
their	O
Death	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
Air	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Liquor	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
.	O
-	O
Want	O
of	O
Air	O
only	O
might	O
occasion	O
it	O
:	O
This	O
want	O
of	O
Air	O
was	O
the	O
more	O
prejudicial	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
too	O
much	O
Liquor	O
before	O
.	O
They	O
would	O
have	O
