TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
15th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1742	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Godschall	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
South-Sea-House	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC.XLII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GODSCHALL	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
AENEY	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BURNET	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pargiter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ruffin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kirke	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Richard	O
Cowling	O
was	O
sworn	O
on	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Goodman	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Knightsbridge	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sommers	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
,	O
Increase	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Vaines	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
of	O
the	O
five	O
following	O
Persons	O
having	O
been	O
omitted	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions-Book	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
inserted	O
to	O
obviate	O
any	O
Surmise	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
out	O
with	O
any	O
Design	O
or	O
sinister	O
View	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
+	O
58.	O
George	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hearsay	B-pers
Broomhead	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
October	O
7th	O
.	O
This	O
Mark	O
+	O
is	O
prefixed	O
to	O
such	O
Indictments	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
would	O
receive	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
should	O
the	O
Jury	O
find	O
them	O
guilty	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
in	O
this	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Cases	O
account	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
's	O
either	O
finding	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
less	O
than	O
is	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
or	O
abating	O
the	O
Charge	O
.	O
By	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
any	O
Person	O
convicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
any	O
Sheep	O
or	O
other	O
Cattle	O
,	O
or	O
feloniously	O
killing	O
any	O
Sheep	O
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
must	O
suffer	O
Death	O
,	O
as	O
Persons	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
without	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
.	O
The	O
following	O
are	O
likewise	O
capital	O
Offences	O
.	O
Privately	O
stealing	O
above	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
1	O
Shilling	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Stealing	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
5	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
Coach-house	O
or	O
Stable	O
.	O
Stealing	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
dwelling	O
House	O
.	O
Hearsay	O
Broomhead	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
last	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
staid	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Q	O
:	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
?	O
Broomhead	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
for	O
four	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
at	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Snelling	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Tankard	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
another	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
miss	O
your	O
Tankard	O
?	O
Broomhead	O
.	O
Within	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
People	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Broomhead	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Tankard	O
you	O
missed	O
was	O
the	O
Tankard	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
?	O
Broomhead	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
old	O
sterling	O
,	O
and	O
cost	O
me	O
8	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
spent	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
ever	O
wrong	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
?	O
Broomhead	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
lodge	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
late	O
about	O
Business	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
'till	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Snelling	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
4	O
Guineas	O
on	O
a	O
Tankard	O
.	O
I	O
accordingly	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
asked	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
's	O
Wife	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
I	O
scrupled	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
usual	O
to	O
deliver	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
returned	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
still	O
insisted	O
on	O
seeing	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
George	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whose	O
Hand	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
Account	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
fetched	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
,	O
Swanson	O
's	O
laying	O
down	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
Tankard	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
for	O
4	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Snelling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
the	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
three	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
pledged	O
a	O
Tankard	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
redeemed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
an	O
Officer	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
no	O
Lies	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
much	O
?	O
Snelling	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
directly	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
no	O
lies	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pledg	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
White	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
Swanson	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
at	O
2	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
good	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
therefore	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
prevail	O
on	O
my	O
Landlord	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
redeem	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
for	O
4	O
Pounds	O
or	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
My	O
Landlord	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
Swanson	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Swanson	I-pers
.	O
Martin	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
4	O
Guineas	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
being	O
desirous	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
better	O
Hands	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Martin	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
directly	O
pledged	O
it	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
me	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
in	O
Aldersgate-Street	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
October	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
from	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Allen	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Tankard	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
fetched	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
lent	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Woodfield	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
set	O
up	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
bought	O
Shoes	O
of	O
him	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
wronging	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
or	O
Child	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
no	O
(	O
any	O
)	O
Crime	O
against	O
him	O
till	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Apprentice-ship	O
.	O
His	O
Master	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Another	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Years	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
made	O
Shoes	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
Word	O
of	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
no	O
Account	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
:	O
He	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Follit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Crime	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
the	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
simple	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
in	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
15	O
January	O
1742	O
.	O
]	O
59	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Albut	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Knives	O
,	O
with	O
Silver	O
Handles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Dec.	O
9	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
in	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
15	O
January	O
1742	O
.	O
]	O
60	O
.	O
+	O
Daniel	B-pers
Redtup	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
40	O
lbs	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wagg	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
Dec.	O
23	O
,	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
in	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
15	O
January	O
1742	O
.	O
]	O
61	O
Samuel	B-pers
Oldbury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Silver	O
Links	O
for	O
Buttons	O
,	O
5	O
Silver	O
Studs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
in	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
15	O
January	O
1742	O
.	O
]	O
62	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wherley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Asary	O
Stanford	O
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Stock-buckle	O
,	O
a	O
Stock	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Jan	O
11	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
1	O
,	O
2.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Afflack	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lowdon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Shoe	O
Buckles	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
,	O
60	O
pair	O
of	O
Pinchbeck	O
metal	O
Buckles	O
,	O
4	O
Gold	O
rings	O
set	O
with	O
doublets	O
,	O
5	O
silver	O
Stay	O
hooks	O
set	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
,	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Garnets	O
,	O
50	O
Pinchbeck	O
Metal	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Chrystal	O
Buttons	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
36	O
silver	O
Thimbles	O
,	O
20	O
Pinchbeck	O
Metal	O
Thimbles	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
one	O
Ivory	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
a	O
Tortoiseshell	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
an	O
Egyptian	O
Pebble	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Coral	O
with	O
8	O
Bells	O
,	O
1	O
silver	O
Stock	O
Buckle	O
set	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Glass	O
Smelling	O
Bottles	O
with	O
Pinchbeck	O
Metal	O
Collars	O
and	O
Stoppers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Andrew	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
just	O
by	O
my	O
Parlour-Door	O
with	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
three	O
Persons	O
pass	O
by	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
look	O
in	O
very	O
often	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
3	O
Shew	O
Glasses	O
standing	O
within	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
I	O
saw	O
Afflack	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
the	O
Window	O
Frame	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
lift	O
up	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
the	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
away	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
.	O
It	O
stood	O
within	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
was	O
bolted	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Afflack	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
let	O
Jack	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
the	O
Thief	O
catcher	O
be	O
called	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
.	O
Lowdon	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
before	O
Mr	O
Deveil	O
that	O
Afflack	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Person	O
that	O
carried	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
was	O
one	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Lowdon	O
)	O
had	O
sold	O
my	O
Goods	O
to	O
2	O
Jews	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
for	O
15	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
the	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
little	O
Door	O
that	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
sworn	O
to	O
Afflack	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
so	O
earnestly	O
at	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
discern	O
so	O
particularly	O
as	O
to	O
distinguish	O
Afflack	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
my	O
Face	O
towards	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
Woman	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
-	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Name	O
is	O
Andrew	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Westbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
and	O
Skirt	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Afflack	O
standing	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Post	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
Coat	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
complain	O
of	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
?	O
Westbury	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Mistress	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Pris	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
enquire	O
of	O
you	O
whether	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
Body	O
about	O
her	O
Shop	O
?	O
Westbury	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
described	O
Afflack	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
Men	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
one	O
Burt	O
had	O
some	O
Talk	O
with	O
you	O
about	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Westbury	O
.	O
Burt	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
(	O
Westbury	O
)	O
is	O
verbatim	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
then	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
Afflack	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
Lowdon	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
's	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Lowdon	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Afflack	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
were	O
likewise	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
carrying	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
Lowdon	O
mentioned	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
which	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
took	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
was	O
declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
with	O
Roses	O
and	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
Smith	O
then	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Werwood	O
Barret	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Colonel	O
Deveil	B-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
heard	O
Lowdon	O
say	O
,	O
what	O
Afflack	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
In	O
Regard	O
to	O
the	O
shutting	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
Lowdon	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
Proviso	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
accordingly	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
two	O
Jews	O
,	O
Aaron	B-pers
Polock	I-pers
and	O
Moses	B-pers
Brew	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Shoemaker	O
Row	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Lowdon	O
)	O
had	O
15	O
Guineas	O
for	O
his	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
proper	O
Assistance	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Lowdon	O
confess	O
the	O
selling	O
your	O
Goods	O
to	O
those	O
Jews	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Stock	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
15	O
Guineas	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
sunk	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jews	O
had	O
got	O
every	O
Skin	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
Expression	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
(	O
Smith	O
)	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
Buckles	O
with	O
Roses	O
and	O
Diamonds	O
in	O
his	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
this	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Stock	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
-	O
not	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
's	O
hearing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stock	O
declar	O
'd	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
nothing	O
that	O
Lowdon	O
had	O
said	O
should	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
except	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stock	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
such	O
Proposition	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
mentioned	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
Proviso	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Stock	O
can	O
get	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
contradict	O
Colonel	O
Deveil	B-pers
when	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Stock	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Hopes	O
of	O
having	O
my	O
Goods	O
restor	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
3	O
Men	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
Burlington-Gardens	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
an	O
empty	O
Shew-glass	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
their	O
Persons	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
pretty	O
short	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
blue	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Coat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
Afflack	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
to	O
Lowdon	O
,	O
John	O
!	O
make	O
yourself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
save	O
your	O
own	O
Life	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
mind	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
Afflack	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
sworn	O
wrongfully	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burt	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
They	O
fetch	O
'd	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
long	O
Cutteau	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
till	O
he	O
hang	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
unless	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
myself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
Watchman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burt	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
with	O
these	O
Prisoners	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr	O
Afflack	O
say	O
to	O
Lowdon	O
,	O
make	O
yourself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Information	O
to	O
save	O
your	O
own	O
Life	O
!	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
came	O
about	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Justice	O
Trent	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
undressing	O
her	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Sash	O
throw	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
threw	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Story	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
to	O
Justice	O
Trent	O
,	O
who	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
talk	O
very	O
loud	O
to	O
your	O
Husband	O
?	O
Bradbury	O
.	O
She	O
talked	O
so	O
loud	O
that	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
People	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
heard	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
them	O
all	O
here	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
after	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
.	O
C.	O
That	O
she	O
says	O
now	O
.	O
Bradbury	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
neither	O
before	O
nor	O
after	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Trent	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stapleton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Trent	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
I	O
that	O
got	O
the	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Trent	O
myself	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Weaker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Shew-glass	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bradbury	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lovet	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
perhaps	O
she	O
might	O
see	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
short	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Bradbury	O
's	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Stock	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
Justice	O
Trent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Shew-glass	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
dressing	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
(	O
said	O
Bradbury	O
)	O
how	O
can	O
I	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
describe	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
Ship	O
About	O
six	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
drinking	O
at	O
Bradbury	O
's	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Shew-glass	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
over-against	O
Major	O
Foubert	B-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
at	O
Bradbury	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Shew	O
glass	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
(	O
as	O
how	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
dressing	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
Justice	O
Trent	O
named	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
gave	O
no	O
Ear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
Rent	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
no	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Lowdon	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
Innocent	O
,	O
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
the	O
Thief-catcher	O
has	O
trump	O
'd	O
up	O
this	O
Story	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
come	O
for	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Flack	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Bradbury	O
's	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
Shew-glass	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
undressing	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
-	O
Bradbury	O
.	O
This	O
Gentlewoman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Shew-glass	O
worth	O
40	O
l	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Body	O
in	O
any	O
shape	O
whatever	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Trent	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Afflack	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Lowdon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
3.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Skeen	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phithian	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coatsworth	I-pers
;	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Alice	B-pers
Rackett	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Upmore	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Lowdon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
about	O
some	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
them	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Earl's-Court	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
:	O
my	O
Hat	O
was	O
likewise	O
taken	O
away	O
and	O
carried	O
about	O
20	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
thrown	O
into	O
an	O
Area	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
some	O
Friends	O
took	O
me	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
mention	O
they	O
,	O
were	O
there	O
several	O
Persons	O
there	O
?	O
Payne	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
say	O
they	O
took	O
your	O
Watch	O
?	O
Payne	O
.	O
Only	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Gilson	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
informs	O
me	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
ever	O
knew	O
,	O
or	O
saw	O
me	O
before	O
?	O
Payne	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
Fellow-Servant	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Spring-Gardens	O
,	O
Vaux-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
from	O
thence	O
about	O
three	O
Summers	O
ago	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Gaming	O
Table	O
in	O
Vinegar	O
Yard	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
playing	O
at	O
a	O
Game	O
card	O
Reds	O
and	O
Whites	O
;	O
-	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
House	O
kept	O
by	O
one	O
Mitford	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Gaming	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Night-house	O
,	O
the	O
Brown-Bear	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
brought	O
myself	O
very	O
low	O
,	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
Lowdon	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Earl's-Court	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
,	O
lay	O
quite	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
two	O
Yards	O
past	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
groaned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Jack	O
!	O
I	O
'm	O
afraid	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
Man	O
dead	O
!	O
I	O
set	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Buckles	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
push	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
come	O
along	O
?	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
directly	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
Mr.	O
Paines	O
's	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
again	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
lugg	O
'd	O
me	O
away	O
for	O
fear	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
supposed	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
more	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Gentlemen	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Phoenix-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Lamp	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
large	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fetch	O
about	O
a	O
Ridge	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
mean	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Ridge	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
the	O
Watch	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
Home	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
and	O
Flack	O
's	O
Girl	O
went	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
Fox's-Court	O
,	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
them	O
then	O
?	O
Gilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
but	O
it	O
seems	O
he	O
had	O
thirty-five	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
half	O
?	O
Gilson	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
as	O
my	O
Share	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
clean	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
two	O
Women	O
coming	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
Man	O
lay	O
drunk	O
?	O
Gilson	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
perceived	O
.	O
Pris	O
Did	O
he	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Drawer	O
?	O
Gilson	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Chain	O
gingle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
4	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Drift	O
or	O
assist	O
him	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
Man	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
?	O
Gilson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
set	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pushed	O
him	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Parsons	O
,	O
in	O
Fox-Court	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
35	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
State	O
of	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
entrusted	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
Business	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Watch	O
is	O
worth	O
50	O
s.	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
wants	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Profits	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Property	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
four	O
Hours	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
besides	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
The	O
Interest	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Ten-pence	O
Half-penny	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Midwife	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
Register	O
:	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Thornton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
about	O
twice	O
;	O
-	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
Clock-maker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
something	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
French	O
woman	O
's	O
in	O
Shorts-Gardens	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Servant	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
safe	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
by	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Body	O
say	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
lies	O
dead	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
young	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
snatch	O
up	O
something	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
which	O
shone	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
lay	O
for	O
dead	O
?	O
Thornton	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
lie	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Gilson	O
there	O
:	O
What	O
I	O
took	O
most	O
Notice	O
of	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Colour	O
of	O
the	O
Buttons	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coat	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
desire	O
she	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
how	O
she	O
knew	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Thornton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Half-Moon-street	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Son	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Man	O
set	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
?	O
Thornton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
stay	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
up	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
Watch	O
or	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
see	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
Face	O
:	O
As	O
my	O
Mistress	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
pick	O
up	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Hickson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
him	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
by	O
seeing	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
light	O
being	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
no	O
Man	O
but	O
him	O
that	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
Watch	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
stand	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Hickson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
my	O
Mistres	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Hickson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
Twelve	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Clock	O
struck	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
died	O
about	O
eight	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Thornton	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
some	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
7	O
,	O
8.	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
1731	O
,	O
)	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Sink	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
24	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
8	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
belonging	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Duffin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
fixed	O
to	O
several	O
Houses	O
in	O
Cable-street	B-place
,	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
stuff	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Duffin	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
C.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
belonging	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Duffin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
fix	O
'd	O
in	O
several	O
Houses	O
in	O
New	B-place
Gravel-Lane	I-place
May	O
2	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
)	I-pers
Buriace	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pound	O
5	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Beaver	O
Fur	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Barnabas	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
11.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Effer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Long	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brunnil	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
dead	O
Turkeys	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
9	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
13	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
15.	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Loxton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Money	O
Bags	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
50	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
100	O
Moidores	O
,	O
400	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Jan	O
9	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wethersden	I-pers
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
in	O
our	O
back	O
Shop	O
,	O
when	O
two	O
Men	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Franklin	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
?	O
The	O
second	O
Man	O
made	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Bustle	O
with	O
his	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
Man	O
then	O
put	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Fright	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
third	O
Fellow	O
making	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Reason	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
who	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
then	O
st	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
third	O
Fellow	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Confusion	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pistols	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
perceived	O
that	O
3	O
Bags	O
had	O
been	O
removed	O
to	O
a	O
different	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
t	O
hey	O
first	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
1000	O
l.	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Persons	O
?	O
Wethersden	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
Ralph	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Downings	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Clifford	B-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
in	O
Fleet	B-place
street	I-place
.	O
My	O
Time	O
being	O
expired	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
was	O
paving	O
me	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
Report	O
of	O
a	O
Pistol	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
2	O
Fellows	O
in	O
the	O
Banker	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Grey	O
Cloaths	O
(	O
something	O
taller	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
behind	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
athwart	O
our	O
Shop	O
towards	O
Chancery-Lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
Footman	O
presently	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
seemingly	O
in	O
some	O
Confusion	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
I	O
joined	O
in	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Bell-Yard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
Arrested	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooksbank	I-pers
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brome	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
facing	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Report	O
of	O
a	O
Pistol	O
.	O
Immediately	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
them	O
a	O
third	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
pursued	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
Footman	O
with	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
They	O
ran	O
up	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
Tavern	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
at	O
Crown-Court	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
People	O
say	O
,	O
Let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
an	O
Arrest	O
!	O
Notwithstanding	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Court	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
Bailiffs	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
that	O
were	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Crown-Court	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
as	O
swift	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
discern	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
Gutter	O
which	O
the	O
Water	O
runs	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
shot	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
under	O
the	O
Gutter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Pistol	O
:	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cock	O
was	O
broken	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Fall	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Hoare	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
up	O
the	O
Gutter	O
again	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Cock	O
of	O
the	O
Pistol	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
notorious	O
Thing	O
?	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
my	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
He	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
no	O
Promises	O
of	O
Favour	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
Hackney	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
fetched	O
him	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
better	O
Bread	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
walked	O
about	O
this	O
Place	O
for	O
three	O
Days	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
commit	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Pistol	O
that	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Discharge	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
his	O
accidentally	O
hirting	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Lucas	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
his	O
Brother	O
Lloyd	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
stand	O
Centry	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
the	O
Stairs	O
Foot	O
to	O
prevent	O
any	O
Person	O
's	O
coming	O
up	O
or	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
fetched	O
me	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Place	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
disappointed	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
I	O
got	O
another	O
Place	O
at	O
Black-Fryars	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Day	O
we	O
committed	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
suddled	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
fictitious	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
Lucas	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Face	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
Mercy	O
and	O
consider	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
18.	O
John	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
February	O
10th	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19.	O
James	B-pers
Bustrat	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Adzs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cricklow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
feloniously	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
forged	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
counterfeit	O
Order	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
,	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Wm	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
Gray's-Inn-Gate	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
if	O
he	O
pleas	O
'd	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
an	O
half	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Elephant	O
and	O
Castle	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
this	O
(	O
here	O
)	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Brasier	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
against	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
Paper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coking	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
Coking	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
suspect	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
Paper	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
Elephant	O
and	O
Castle	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
scrupled	O
giving	O
me	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
waited	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
upwards	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
sent	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Servants	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Elephant	O
and	O
Castle	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
left	O
Word	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
this	O
Paper	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Hand-writing	O
,	O
and	O
wondered	O
why	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Coffin	O
to	O
finish	O
in	O
haste	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-Square	O
.	O
The	O
Paper	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
St.	O
Alban's-Church	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
.	O
Send	O
by	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
one	O
set	O
of	O
Brass	O
Work	O
for	O
Drawers	O
,	O
fifteen	O
Handles	O
,	O
nine	O
Locks	O
,	O
six	O
Scutcheons	O
,	O
two	O
Keys	O
,	O
one	O
Tenant	O
Saw	O
,	O
two	O
sets	O
of	O
three	O
Shilling	O
Leather	O
Castors	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sett	O
of	O
Ditto	O
Brass	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Upholder	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
heretofore	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
near	O
2	O
Years	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
Paper	O
your	O
Hand-writing	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
compared	O
it	O
with	O
several	O
Receipts	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Writing	O
agrees	O
exactly	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
that	O
this	O
Paper	O
was	O
his	O
Hand-writing	O
.	O
Hutton	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
Goods	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
first	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Elephant	O
and	O
Castle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
Gough	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
begged	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Hand-writing	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Coking	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
received	O
this	O
Paper	O
of	O
the	O
Porter	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Elephant	O
and	O
Castle	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
shewn	O
the	O
Note	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Elephant	O
and	O
Castle	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
afterwards	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
,	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
?	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
Right	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
glad	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Paper	O
was	O
his	O
Writing	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Gough	O
's	O
Servant	O
he	O
had	O
wrote	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
Order	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
has	O
been	O
somebody	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
wrote	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Martin	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Morgan	I-pers
Newland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement-Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
procuring	O
Tho	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Subject	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
foreign	O
Prince	O
)	O
without	O
the	O
Consent	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Sign	O
Manual	O
first	O
had	O
and	O
obtained	O
,	O
in	O
Contempt	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
his	O
Laws	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Councel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
grounded	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
salutary	O
Law	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Strength	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
from	O
being	O
carried	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
into	O
foreign	O
Countries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Welshman	O
,	O
and	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
Employment	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
upon	O
Duty	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
Keys	O
between	O
Billingsgate	O
and	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
first	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
His	O
Countryman	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
carried	O
Men	O
abroad	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
sometime	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
5	O
Pence	O
Half-penny	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Loaves	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
every	O
one	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
a	O
three-penny	O
Loaf	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
all	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
barely	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Meredith	O
My	O
Brother	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
Then	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
never	O
mind	O
that	O
(	O
said	O
he	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
Money	O
enough	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Borough-Market	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Beer	O
,	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
go	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
we	O
should	O
get	O
to	O
Dover	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
fair	O
Wind	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
over	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Hours	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
four	O
and	O
forty	O
Miles	O
to	O
travel	O
by	O
Land	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
To	O
what	O
Purpose	O
where	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
those	O
four	O
and	O
forty	O
Miles	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
meet	O
his	O
Regiment	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Conversation	O
passed	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
then	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Quarters	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Quarters	O
in	O
Kent	O
street	O
,	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
Red-Cow	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
3	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tea	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
which	O
cost	O
him	O
but	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
France	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
his	O
Regimentals	O
on	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
Only	O
my	O
Regimental	O
Waistcoat	O
:	O
my	O
Brother	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Regimentals	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
us	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Landlady	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
live	O
like	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
his	O
Landlady	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Breast	O
of	O
Mutton	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
Bed	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Barracks	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Public	O
House	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
Brother	O
wanted	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
what	O
we	O
must	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Coal	O
Hole	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
House	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
that	O
House	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
4	O
Welshmen	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
Tom	O
Richards	O
,	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
this	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
what	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
three	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
Reckoning	O
Upon	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
your	O
going	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
must	O
make	O
every	O
Thing	O
good	O
when	O
you	O
get	O
to	O
France	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
present	O
then	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Guineas	O
Advance	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
you	O
told	O
him	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
gave	O
you	O
6	O
d.	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
considered	O
it	O
as	O
Money	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
'list	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
promised	O
me	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Guineas	O
Advance	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
promise	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
five	O
Peace	O
Halfpenny	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Loaves	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
every	O
one	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
a	O
three	O
penny	O
Loaf	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Welshman	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
would	O
all	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
shewed	O
us	O
his	O
Furloe	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
pretended	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
snatch	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
out	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
See	O
if	O
that	O
Paper	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
my	O
Name	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q.	O
Recollect	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
Words	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
let	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
Meredith	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
after	O
you	O
go	O
over	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
make	O
every	O
Thing	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
there	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Guineas	O
Advance	O
Money	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
over	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Regiment	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
Regiment	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
France	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Regiment	O
as	O
he	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Brother	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
watching	O
for	O
Work	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-House	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
talking	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
Brother	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
Regimentals	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
could	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
those	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
should	O
certainly	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
coloured	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
must	O
sell	O
them	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
Barracks	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
your	O
Brother	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
enlist	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
's	O
Service	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Borough	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
Barracks	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
well	O
then	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
Brass	O
as	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
London-Bridge	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
He	O
there	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
living	O
there	O
than	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
5	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Leaves	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
my	O
Oath	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
to	O
this	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
my	O
Oath	O
again	O
when	O
I	O
go	O
over	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
only	O
kiss	O
the	O
Book	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Quarters	O
in	O
Kent	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
we	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
and	O
sell	O
our	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Monmouth-street	O
was	O
a	O
better	O
Place	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
ask	O
some	O
Advice	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Serjeant	O
Taylor	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Coal-Hole	O
,	O
Griffith	O
and	O
Richards	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
might	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
some	O
Talk	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
listing	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
passed	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
Paper	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
tore	O
a	O
Piece	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
pulling	O
it	O
away	O
:	O
-	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
wrote	O
my	O
Name	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
producing	O
that	O
Paper	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
Griffith	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
How	O
can	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Furloe	O
;	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
Griffith	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
directly	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
Countryman	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
Meredith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Irishman	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
The	O
first	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Coal-	O
Hole	O
by	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
three	O
Men	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
enlisting	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
?	O
for	O
he	O
might	O
want	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
O	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Furloe	O
from	O
my	O
Captain	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
produce	O
the	O
Furloe	O
?	O
Griffith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
my	O
Name	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
that	O
Bit	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Griffith	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
the	O
Furloe	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
read	O
French	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Richards	O
talked	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
wanted	O
to	O
snatch	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Piece	O
out	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
about	O
any	O
Oath	O
?	O
Griffith	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Oath	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
bound	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Griffith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Meredith	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
6	O
d	O
by	O
Way	O
of	O
Earnest	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
France	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
Furloe	O
?	O
Griffith	O
.	O
Before	O
we	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
before	O
you	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Griffith	B-pers
About	I-pers
half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
Side	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Welchman	O
.	O
My	O
Comerade	O
John	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Barracks	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
enlist	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
French	O
Service	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Gate	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Coal	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
John	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
Meredith	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
enlist	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
French	O
Service	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
Griffith	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
France	O
?	O
He	O
then	O
produc	O
'd	O
this	O
Furloe	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
tore	O
a	O
Bit	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
himself	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
my	O
Quarters	O
(	O
the	O
Coal	O
Hole	O
)	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
these	O
Soldiers	O
.	O
They	O
whisper	O
'd	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
enlisting	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
he	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
desir	O
'd	O
Richards	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
read	O
the	O
Furloe	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Landlord	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
read	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
These	O
People	O
were	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
this	O
Furloe	O
.	O
They	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
enlisting	O
Men	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Service	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
obstinate	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
this	O
sort	O
of	O
Business	O
by	O
one	O
Mackinnar	O
,	O
who	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Officers	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Furloe	O
that	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
People	O
that	O
were	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Business	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
others	O
either	O
landed	O
,	O
or	O
just	O
landing	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
pressed	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Paper	O
was	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
English	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
]	O
''	O
Foot	O
,	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Dillon.	O
``	O
We	O
who	O
have	O
undersign	O
'd	O
this	O
,	O
do	O
certifie	O
``	O
all	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
given	O
Leave	O
for	O
``	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
named	O
Martin	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
a	O
``	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Morris	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
``	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Dillon	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Jurisdiction	O
of	O
``	O
(	O
Blank	O
)	O
aged	O
35	O
Years	O
,	O
Height	O
5	O
Feet	O
one	O
``	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
Chesnut	O
colour	O
'd	O
Hair	O
,	O
blue	O
``	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
pretty	O
much	O
sunk	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
very	O
meagre	O
Countenance	O
:	O
Given	O
at	O
Bethune	O
,	O
``	O
Dec.	O
25	O
1741	O
.	O
Sign	O
'd	O
Morris.	O
``	O
Counter	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
us	O
Lieutenant	O
Colonel	O
``	O
commanding	O
the	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Dillon	O
,	O
Gavon	O
;	O
``	O
Certified	O
by	O
us	O
Captain	O
Adjutant	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Dillon	B-pers
,	I-pers
O	I-pers
'Hara	O
.	O
''	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
have	O
invented	O
themselves	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
give	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Margaret	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
James	I-pers
)	I-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brocker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Rockleaur	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
with	O
Brass	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
Jan	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
24.	O
George	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Lock	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Wadman	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Judith	B-pers
Cartey	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cartney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
checqued	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Macfarson	I-pers
;	O
a	O
checqu	O
'd	O
Apron	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Macfarson	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Coupee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Edward	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Kates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Alice	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
)	I-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Hugh	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
Bart.Feb	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Copper	O
Scales	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
27th	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barrsley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
,	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Brass	O
Patterns	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s	O
and	O
4	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
16th	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
George	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15th	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
33	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Outwich	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
other	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Fawdrey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fawdrey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Mourning	O
Bush	O
,	O
at	O
Aldersgate	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
very	O
carefully	O
down	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Lame	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
near	O
that	O
Part	O
that	O
is	O
opposite	O
to	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Outwich	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
fastened	O
round	O
my	O
Arm	O
;	O
-	O
my	O
Dear	O
!	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
You	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
good-natur	O
'd	O
Fellow	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
!	O
I	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Imprecation	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
be	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
directly	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
-	O
the	O
whole	O
Transaction	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
speaking	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
tripp	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
my	O
Right	O
Fore-finger	O
in	O
a	O
terrible	O
Manner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
will	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
produce	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
were	O
found	O
talking	O
together	O
at	O
Creed-Lane	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Victim	O
of	O
their	O
Intentions	O
.	O
Q	O
After	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
tripped	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
mentioned	O
,	O
what	O
happened	O
then	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
Watch	O
!	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Hind	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
fortunately	O
I	O
believe	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
call	O
Watch	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
left	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
Woman	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
down	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
what	O
Hour	O
the	O
Woman	O
met	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
forcibly	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
near	O
a	O
Lamp	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
Lamp	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Moment	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
your	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
very	O
Instant	O
that	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
my	O
Heels	O
flew	O
up	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
apprehend	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
Man	O
before	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
her	O
neither	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
Transaction	O
was	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
Minute	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
guess	O
how	O
near	O
to	O
12	O
or	O
1	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
could	O
say	O
it	O
wanted	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
one	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Hind	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
or	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Darby	O
's	O
in	O
Stationer's-Court	O
.	O
It	O
struck	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Landlord	O
according	O
to	O
Custom	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
every	O
Body	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
crossed	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Creed-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Cloak	O
and	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
tallish	O
Man	O
,	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
half	O
a-cross	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Hog	O
!	O
Hog	O
!	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
down	O
Creed	O
lane	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
one	O
Dick	B-pers
Too	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
pretty	O
leisurely	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
beyond	O
the	O
Change	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Cloak	O
then	O
passed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
which	O
Way	O
they	O
turned	O
,	O
but	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
by	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
there	O
stood	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
just	O
cross	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
there	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Coachman	O
drive	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Doors	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Watch	O
!	O
Hearing	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
mended	O
my	O
Pace	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
Pair	O
of	O
wooden	O
Gates	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
white	O
Cloak	O
were	O
then	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
What	O
(	O
said	O
I	O
)	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
murder	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
said	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
directly	O
:	O
-	O
he	O
ran	O
one	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
helped	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
about	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Pump	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
.	O
What	O
Dress	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Linnen	O
or	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
Colour	O
'd	O
short	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
to	O
Hind	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Hind	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
?	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
such	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
?	O
Hind	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
Handkerchief	O
with	O
white	O
Spots	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Coat	O
on	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
or	O
light	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
?	O
Hind	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Lamp	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Creed-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
over-against	O
it	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
o'Clock	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
Hind	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
12	O
,	O
because	O
when	O
the	O
Watch	O
go	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Darby	O
always	O
turns	O
the	O
Customers	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
only	O
staid	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
Reckoning	O
and	O
finish	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Watchman	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Palmer	O
Hind	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
it	O
related	O
to	O
the	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
knocking	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
rescuing	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Fawdrey	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
related	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
:	O
He	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
perceived	O
the	O
Watch	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
recovered	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
Watch	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
Fellow	O
then	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
Palmer	O
Hind	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Questions	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
cry	O
'd	O
Watch	O
!	O
he	O
ran	O
-	O
for	O
Fear	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
insisted	O
on	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
two	O
Friends	O
towards	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
'till	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
with	O
them	O
only	O
towards	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
of	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
struggling	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
complained	O
of	O
the	O
Injury	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cumber	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
White	O
chapple	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Catherine	O
street	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
our	O
Departure	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
our	O
Way	O
Home	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
in	O
Catherine-street	O
?	O
Cumber	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
:	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
was	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
directly	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
our	O
Leaves	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
White	O
chapple	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
Company	O
but	O
we	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
Gibbs	O
lives	O
in	O
White	O
chapple	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
Meat	O
of	O
him	O
lately	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
keep	O
any	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
carries	O
it	O
about	O
in	O
a	O
Tray	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
no	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
seems	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
industrious	O
Care	O
for	O
his	O
Bread	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Well-Court	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
's	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
Creed-Lane	O
as	O
you	O
were	O
going	O
Home	O
?	O
Cumber	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
Creed-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
no	O
Lane	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Cumber	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
Shop	O
like	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Catherine-street	O
:	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
near	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
12	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alone	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Woman	O
in	O
our	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
no	O
Street	O
at	O
all	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
directly	O
towards	O
Whitechappel	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
near	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
quite	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Body	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
about	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Yorkshire	O
Grey	O
in	O
Gravel-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
cross	O
to	O
Thread-needle-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Person	O
say	O
,	O
Stop	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
!	O
Presently	O
a	O
Woman	O
ran	O
by	O
,	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
Wings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
Person	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
hold	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Mob	O
then	O
began	O
to	O
gather	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hookham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
Sight	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
His	O
Character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
common	O
Sharper	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
general	O
't	O
is	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
34.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Twist	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Heifer	O
's	O
Hide	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Remington	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
John	B-pers
Ashridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
was	O
printed	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
,	O
for	O
March	O
1737	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Manby	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Books	O
called	O
the	O
curious	O
Traveller	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Book	O
called	O
a	O
Mechanical	O
Account	O
of	O
Poisons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roland	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fitch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Eagle	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
37.	O
John	B-pers
Shute	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
38.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Quire	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Charley	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Handley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
long	O
before	O
,	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Macdurmot	I-pers
was	O
an	O
Inhabitant	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
near	O
a	O
certain	O
Place	O
called	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Adlam	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Macdurmot	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
is	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	O
Durmot	O
as	O
James	B-pers
Macdurmot	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Handley	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
Premises	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
regarding	O
the	O
Laws	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
did	O
cause	O
and	O
procure	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
personally	O
to	O
appear	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
,	O
then	O
and	O
now	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
and	O
Description	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Durmot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Adlam	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
himself	O
indebted	O
to	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
186	O
l.	O
on	O
Condition	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
said	O
Handley	O
should	O
appear	O
to	O
satisfy	O
all	O
that	O
should	O
be	O
required	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
an	O
Information	O
exhibited	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
Sir	O
Dudley	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
or	O
in	O
Default	O
thereof	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
said	O
Handley	O
should	O
surrender	O
himself	O
,	O
then	O
this	O
Obligation	O
to	O
be	O
void	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
remain	O
in	O
full	O
Force	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Macdurmot	I-pers
not	O
being	O
privy	O
thereto	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Damage	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
+	O
This	O
Offence	O
was	O
made	O
Felony	O
by	O
a	O
Statute	O
in	O
the	O
21st	O
Year	O
of	O
James	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Councel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Offence	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Attornies	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
Office	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
is	O
an	O
Information	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Attorney	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Remembrance	O
Office	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Substance	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Dated	O
Easter-Term	O
,	O
14th	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
;	O
Be	O
it	O
remember	O
'd	O
that	O
Sir	O
Dudley	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
proper	O
Person	O
presents	O
,	O
that	O
certain	O
Merchants	O
unknown	O
,	O
did	O
between	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
1738	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
exhibiting	O
this	O
Information	O
,	O
import	O
to	O
Ratcliff	O
within	O
the	O
Port	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Ship	O
by	O
Way	O
of	O
Merchandise	O
,	O
346	O
lbs	O
.	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
4	O
lbs	O
.	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
51	O
Yards	O
of	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
amounting	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
186	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
being	O
liable	O
to	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
Custom	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Merchants	O
did	O
unship	O
and	O
land	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
before	O
the	O
Customs	O
and	O
other	O
Duties	O
were	O
paid	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
afterwards	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Handley	I-pers
,	O
he	O
well	O
knowing	O
every	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
imported	O
,	O
the	O
Customs	O
not	O
being	O
paid	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
other	O
Parchment	O
in	O
your	O
Hand	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Ayres	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Bail	O
Piece	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
,	O
who	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
twice	O
in	O
my	O
Presence	O
;	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
Justification	O
.	O
One	O
James	B-pers
Durmot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Dowling	O
,	O
both	O
swore	O
in	O
my	O
Presence	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
worth-186	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Housekeepers	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
]	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Notice	O
given	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
this	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
enter	O
'd	O
