TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
16th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Heathcote	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
1742	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
whom	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
The	O
Trial	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1742	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HEATHCOTE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Barthelomew	O
Paine	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
Goldsbury	O
Frost	O
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Polliday	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tumar	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Flipper	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sclater	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lasting	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Jarman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Whincop	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
55.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Jack	B-pers
the	I-pers
Sailor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
*	O
with	O
one	O
William	O
Briers	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Oil-Skin	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
seventeen	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
February	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Messuurs	O
Huntley	O
,	O
Linnen	O
Drapers	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall-Street	B-place
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Penny-worth	O
of	O
Sugar-Candy	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
afterwards	O
another	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
Back	O
,	O
another	O
young	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
Call	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
believe	O
two	O
Persons	O
took	O
this	O
Bag	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
seventeen	O
Pound	O
Custom-House	O
Weight	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
above	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Pound	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
other	O
Customer	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
their	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
my	O
missing	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Briers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Britrs	I-pers
went	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Sugar-Candy	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
Briers	O
,	O
to	O
skreen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Oil-Skin	O
Bag	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Tea	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
waited	O
to	O
see	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
Briers	O
said	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
call	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bartfoot	I-pers
for	O
five	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Pound	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
-	O
Briers	O
is	O
transported	O
+	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
no	O
Business	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
an	O
Attorney	O
.	O
+	O
He	O
was	O
convicted	O
in	O
April	O
Sessions	O
of	O
stealing	O
two	O
Perukes	O
from	O
Mr	O
Bonnell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
Hands	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
for	O
Mercy	O
.	O
56.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
36	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
called	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Church	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Drawer	O
open	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
this	O
Lad	O
came	O
Home	O
a	O
little	O
fuddled	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
.	O
-	O
Mr	O
James	O
(	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
)	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
begged	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
so	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
begged	O
Pardon	O
for	O
being	O
Drunk	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
charged	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
any	O
Money	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
:	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Drawer	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Bag	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
less	O
than	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
presently	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
him	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr	O
James	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
Mr	O
James	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
at	O
Welsh-Fair	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
at	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
pushed	O
back	O
the	O
Lock	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Devil	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Devil	O
bid	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
took	O
.	O
Mr	O
James	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Boy	O
drinking	O
with	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Carpenters	O
in	O
Welsh-Fair	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
throwing	O
his	O
Money	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
Country-Boy	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Wales	O
;	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
Ale	O
;	O
perhaps	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
this	O
Ale	O
,	O
though	O
my	O
Hat	O
on	O
my	O
Head	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
can	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
one	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
his	O
Master	O
should	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
Home	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
should	O
not	O
beat	O
him	O
:	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
would	O
be	O
angry	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
think	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
Money	O
till	O
Mr	O
Clarke	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Said	O
Mr	O
Clarke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
two	O
Guineas	O
of	O
my	O
Boy	O
's	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
one	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
Drawer	O
was	O
locked	O
?	O
Clarke	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
petitioned	O
the	O
Court	O
on	O
his	O
Behalf	O
.	O
57.	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
*	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Stock-Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Shoe-Buckle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
One	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
val	O
1	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
*	O
He	O
swore	O
himself	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
robbing	O
Alice	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
in	O
Holloway-Road	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
,	O
1739	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
wise	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Wall	O
,	O
September	O
14	O
,	O
1710.	O
by	O
the	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
near	O
Canbury-House	O
,	O
Islington	O
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
July	O
1741	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kingsbury	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
any	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
a	O
back	O
Apartment	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
the	O
Wall	O
was	O
broke	O
into	O
my	O
Cellar	O
;	O
seeing	O
that	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
lone	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
how	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
this	O
?	O
How	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
described	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Farmer	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
described	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Twyford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
this	O
Mrs	O
How	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
turned	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
works	O
for	O
me	O
one	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Hendon	O
Church	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Hutchins	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
by	O
the	O
Plough	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
fuddled	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pound	O
twelve	O
Shillings	O
.	O
in	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
Handkerchiefs	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
four	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
given	O
one	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
trouble	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
crope	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
crope	O
out	O
there	O
again	O
afterwards	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
they	O
can	O
go	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Hart	O
Skin	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
Mrs	O
How	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
all	O
mine	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
Purse	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
more	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
thinking	O
these	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
58	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Booney	O
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
one	O
Abraham	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
in	O
Fear	O
and	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
Bow	O
and	O
the	O
Alms-Houses	O
at	O
Mile	B-place
Edd	I-place
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
Moon-shiney	O
Night	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Fellows	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Causeway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Right-Hand	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
:	O
They	O
demanded	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
deliver	O
all	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
use	O
me	O
well	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
delivered	O
was	O
a	O
Seal	O
with	O
a	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
String	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Case	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Guts	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
18	O
d.	O
(	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
towards	O
Bow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
meeting	O
with	O
some	O
Body	O
else	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Word	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
may	O
save	O
myself	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
;	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
spoke	O
with	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Carman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Carman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answers	O
to	O
the	O
Heighth	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
Scar	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Cheek	O
.	O
Cavenagh	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
Brown	B-pers
Coat	I-pers
,	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
Cavenagh	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Mooney	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
Scar	O
better	O
then	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
now	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Beard	O
was	O
long	O
and	O
black	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
pray	O
observe	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
Beard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
black	O
Beard	O
.	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
His	O
Beard	O
was	O
rather	O
blacker	O
than	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
[	O
William	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
Consider	O
now	O
you	O
are	O
admitted	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
Care	O
to	O
speak	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
strictly	O
true	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
went	O
towards	O
Bow	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
Why	O
not	O
beat	O
Dragon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
Martin	O
said	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
Way	O
;	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
:	O
He	O
delivered	O
first	O
the	O
Out-side	O
case	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
into	O
Mooney	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Mooney	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
compleat	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Guts	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
forgot	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
say	O
if	O
he	O
met	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
the	O
Carman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Cavenagh	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
April	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
bought	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
kept	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
first	O
Information	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
mention	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
first	O
Information	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
it	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Information	O
was	O
read	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
)	O
.	O
-	O
*	O
Lot	O
Cavenagh	O
is	O
no	O
Relation	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Person	O
on	O
whose	O
Information	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Trials	O
in	O
Mr	O
Alderman	O
Perry	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
147	O
,	O
148	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Father	O
would	O
spend	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
great	O
Reward	O
that	O
is	O
depending	O
upon	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
he	O
passed	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
bleed	O
me	O
.	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
William	O
Cavenagh	O
's	O
Father	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Joiner	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrought	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
Dublin	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
is	O
a	O
Day	O
of	O
Diversion	O
among	O
the	O
Tradesmen	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
piping	O
and	O
dancing	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
his	O
working	O
for	O
me	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
2d	O
,	O
and	O
3d	O
of	O
M	O
ay	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
Son	O
?	O
Moone	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
Son	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
his	O
Mother	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
never	O
passed	O
for	O
my	O
Son	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
customary	O
to	O
work	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
now	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
proves	O
by	O
the	O
Almanack	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Moone	O
.	O
Yes	O
sometimes	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
Coffins	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
making	O
Coffins	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
Day	O
the	O
Coffin	O
was	O
made	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
the	O
Coffin	O
was	O
for	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Oak	O
Coffin	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Undertaker	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
Undertaker	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
supply	O
the	O
whole	O
Funeral	O
?	O
-	O
Moone	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Funeral	O
than	O
making	O
of	O
a	O
Coffin	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Goal	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Countrymen	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
William	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
Lot	O
Cavenagh	O
had	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Moone	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
St	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
Gerrard	O
Cavenagh	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
since	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Dublin	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
Debt	O
.	O
-	O
a	O
Debt	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
l.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Irishman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
young	O
Man	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
such	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
asked	O
what	O
Mr	O
Goodwin	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Reward	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
.	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Mr	O
Penny	O
,	O
an	O
Attorney	O
in	O
New	O
Broad	O
street	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
is	O
a	O
Woolstapler	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
59.	O
John	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
sundry	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
;	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
Houses	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
Golden	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
French-Alley	B-place
,	O
which	O
last	O
was	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
it	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
out	O
side	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wall	O
likewise	O
broke	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
has	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
shut	O
it	O
up	O
about	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
locked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
away	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
other	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Windows	O
fast	O
shut	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shutters	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
all	O
missing	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
frequently	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
Things	O
from	O
our	O
Bakehouse	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
The	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
to	O
be	O
shaved	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
shaved	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
to	O
comb	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
casting	O
my	O
Eye	O
into	O
the	O
Work	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Wig	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
;	O
we	O
searched	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Shirt	O
which	O
Mary	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
proved	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
by	O
its	O
being	O
made	O
of	O
two	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Cloth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Wig	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Wig	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
worn	O
it	O
.	O
Foster	O
.	O
You	O
might	O
have	O
worn	O
it	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Holgate	I-pers
,	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
60.	O
Elias	B-pers
Veesing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Ward	O
of	O
Queenhith	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
.	O
Having	O
lost	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
Shirt	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
marked	O
J.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
3.	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Shirt	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Hamborough	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
plead	O
himself	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
.	O
He	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
understands	O
English	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
answer	O
any	O
common	O
Question	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Sugar-Baker	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr	O
Cope	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Box	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
the	O
Shirt	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Hamborough	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
bring	O
the	O
Washerwoman	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
Frederick	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
as	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cope	O
being	O
examined	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
the	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
unlocked	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
61.	O
Mary	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
out-side	O
Case	O
and	O
an	O
in-side	O
Case	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pantell	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Pantell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
selling	O
my	O
Milk	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
Hat	O
off	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
unless	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Quartern	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Hat	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
snatched	O
my	O
Watch	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Jest	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
to	O
serve	O
another	O
Customer	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
demanded	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
selling	O
Milk	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
lived	O
in	O
Love's-Court	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
pouring	O
his	O
Milk	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
Kettle	O
into	O
another	O
,	O
she	O
snatched	O
his	O
Hat	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
into	O
Love's-Court	O
,	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Boy	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
were	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Mr	O
Banks	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Boy	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Inside	O
of	O
her	O
Shift	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
felt	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Inside	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Stays	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Watch	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Pantell	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Pearce	O
,	O
under	O
St	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Watch	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
Man	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
young	O
Man	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
alone	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Banks	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
loose	O
Woman	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
third	O
Person	O
there	O
?	O
Pantell	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
't	O
was	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	O
-	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
Liquor	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
62.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Alban	I-place
,	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
August	O
10	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Woodroffe	O
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
the	O
Dish	O
in	O
Mr	O
Scot	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
with	O
some	O
Tarts	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Oven	O
,	O
the	O
Dish	O
stood	O
empty	O
.	O
This	O
good	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Dish	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Dish	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Winterbottom	I-pers
proved	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr	O
Scot	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
63.	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
August	O
31	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Hat	O
off	O
Wiggin	B-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
,	O
it	O
lay	O
between	O
two	O
Sticks	O
upon	O
the	O
Key	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr	O
Mascal	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
where	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
sold	O
or	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Hat	O
again	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Mascal	I-pers
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
produce	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
64.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Judith	B-pers
Haswell	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
large	O
Piece	O
of	O
Brick	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Judith	B-pers
Haswell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
did	O
hit	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Judith	B-pers
Haswell	I-pers
did	O
die	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Haswell	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
throw	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Brick	O
at	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
carry	O
Malt	O
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Brick	O
,	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
easy	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
the	O
Brick	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
another	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
unconcerned	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
Length	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
got	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
*	O
-	O
She	O
never	O
went	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
Name	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
Griffiths	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Brick	O
was	O
almost	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
my	O
Fist	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
stood	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Yards	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
get	O
away	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
,	O
it	O
hit	O
her	O
pretty	O
hard	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
flew	O
behind	O
her	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Breaks	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
and	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
are	O
to	O
shew	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
follows	O
is	O
in	O
Answer	O
to	O
Questions	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
which	O
Questions	O
are	O
omitted	O
for	O
Brevity	O
sake	O
,	O
the	O
Answers	O
denoting	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
designedly	O
.	O
Walton	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
,	O
throw	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
say	O
I	O
will	O
throw	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
my	O
Word	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rollison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
and	O
Judith	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
(	O
as	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
otherwise	O
before	O
)	O
go	O
up	O
Three	O
Leg	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Brick	O
thrown	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
Words	O
pass	O
between	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
knock	O
your	O
Brains	O
out	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
speak	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
must	O
all	O
appear	O
before	O
one	O
Tribunal	O
Judge	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
afterwards	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
your	O
Eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
kill	O
'd	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
kill	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
it	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
value	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
else	O
worth	O
mentioning	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Passion	O
?	O
Rollison	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
him	O
very	O
provoking	O
Words	O
I	O
do	O
assure	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Rogue	O
in	O
an	O
illiterate	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Way	O
,	O
for	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
Impudence	O
meet	O
together	O
,	O
it	O
mixes	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
God	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
righteous	O
Judge	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
as	O
true	O
a	O
Thing	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
spoke	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
.	O
Rollison	O
.	O
My	O
Soul	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
apparent	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
always	O
speak	O
the	O
Truth	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
ask	O
God	O
's	O
Pardon	O
,	O
not	O
your	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
Blemish	O
of	O
my	O
Escutcheon	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
said	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
declare	O
upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
holl	O
a	O
Brick	O
at	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
come	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
Violence	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
flew	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
Occasion	O
was	O
given	O
for	O
throwing	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
Yards	O
from	O
her	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Brickbat	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
second	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
throw	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
being	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
Bitch	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
lived	O
about	O
9	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Brislet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
throw	O
a	O
Brickbat	O
at	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
thrown	O
at	O
her	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
Name	O
than	O
Judith	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
;	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
Brickbat	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
White	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
struck	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
Burr	O
of	O
the	O
Ear	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
killed	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Spot	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
the	O
Bitch	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
being	O
hanged	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
kill	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
she	O
had	O
was	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Skull	O
was	O
bare	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Surgery	O
in	O
Basing-hall	O
Street	O
,	O
these	O
Wounds	O
are	O
frequently	O
healed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
caught	O
Cold	O
in	O
coming	O
in	O
the	O
Rain	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Membrane	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
was	O
inflam	O
'd	O
and	O
that	O
caused	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
complained	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
warden	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
die	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
better	O
Place	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
a	O
warm	O
Room	O
and	O
Necessaries	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
more	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Death	O
than	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
Deceased	O
for	O
two	O
Days	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
confused	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
:	O
The	O
Woman	O
had	O
no	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
a	O
fractured	O
Skull	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Injury	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
when	O
I	O
attended	O
her	O
;	O
her	O
Head	O
and	O
Neck	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
tumisied	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
I	O
did	O
prov	O
'd	O
unsuccessful	O
,	O
the	O
Humour	O
was	O
suddenly	O
repelled	O
and	O
struck	O
into	O
her	O
Brain	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
got	O
Cold	O
,	O
as	O
Mr	O
Wheeler	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
but	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
caught	O
Cold	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
cured	O
:	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
Skull	O
bare	O
,	O
and	O
carefully	O
examined	O
it	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
Injury	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
Skull	O
:	O
Sometimes	O
the	O
Skull	O
shall	O
remain	O
whole	O
and	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
Concussion	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
Brain	O
very	O
carefully	O
and	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
as	O
in	O
dead	O
Bodies	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
he	O
be	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haswell	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
Rollison	O
and	O
Walton	O
were	O
called	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
Name	O
than	O
Griffiths	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Petts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Judith	B-pers
Haswell	I-pers
before	O
she	O
departed	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Judith	B-pers
Haswell	I-pers
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Blow	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
designedly	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
any	O
Damage	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
provoked	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
any	O
Damage	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
rest	O
in	O
her	O
Grave	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
said	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Words	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Malt	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Peacock	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
pump	O
some	O
Water	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
rioted	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
patiently	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
bear	O
it	O
no	O
longer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
that	O
Piece	O
of	O
Brickbat	O
and	O
hit	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
any	O
Damage	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
small	O
Relation	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Aunt	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
Nurse	O
in	O
the	O
Work-house	O
where	O
this	O
Woman	O
died	O
:	O
Her	O
Name	O
was	O
Judith	B-pers
Haswell	I-pers
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
provoked	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Provocation	O
occasioned	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
him	O
die	O
for	O
it	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Rollison	O
.	O
That	O
Woman	O
that	O
swore	O
last	O
is	O
his	O
own	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
swore	O
you	O
was	O
his	O
Aunt	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Crime	O
in	O
swearing	O
you	O
was	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Crime	O
in	O
swearing	O
you	O
are	O
his	O
Aunt	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
his	O
Mother	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Mother	O
indeed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
distracted	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
say	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
poor	O
,	O
harmless	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
Fellow	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
half-witted	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
sad	O
provoking	O
Woman	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
both	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
arlow	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Peaceable	O
,	O
harmless	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
laborious	O
Man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
65.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
August	O
24	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Hemp	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
confessed	O
before	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
particular	O
Parcel	O
,	O
one	O
being	O
like	O
another	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
He	I-pers
said	O
before	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Hemp	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
terrified	O
and	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
Madman	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
66.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Axe	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Axe	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-Inn	B-place
Passage	I-place
,	I-place
without	I-place
Temple-Bar	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
last	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Lodging	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Smith	O
The	O
second	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
my	O
Daughter	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
Alderman	O
Hankey	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
lodge	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
Mary	O
Axe	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
that	O
Man	O
's	O
lodging	O
at	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
Am	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
only	O
wanted	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Axe	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
67	O
John	B-pers
Bloxom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hayes	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	B-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Greenleaf	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
five	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
nine	O
Plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
an	O
Apron	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Greenleaf	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
August	O
26	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Greenleaf	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Norwood-Green	B-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
this	O
Day	O
fortnight	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Fore-Door	O
,	O
the	O
Lock	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
was	O
fastened	O
both	O
with	O
Pin	O
and	O
Bolt	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
my	O
Way	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
Distance	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Body	O
throw	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Back	O
Window	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Glass	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
just	O
Room	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
off	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Goods	O
that	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Shoes	O
were	O
dropped	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
All	O
these	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
were	O
together	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
one	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Coat	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
lying	O
under	O
a	O
Bush	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
about	O
2	O
Yards	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
I	O
wanted	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
lie	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Deserter	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
run	O
away	O
to	O
hide	O
himself	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Filby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Mr	O
Henry	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Norwood-Green	O
,	O
this	O
Bag	O
was	O
wrapped	O
up	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
some	O
Small-beer	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
good	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
some	O
Small-beer	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Pear-tree	O
,	O
or	O
an	O
Apple-tree	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
some	O
Apples	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
cried	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
Thieves	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
catched	O
up	O
my	O
Coat	O
and	O
away	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
hid	O
myself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
68	O
,	O
69.	O
John	B-pers
Pesoley	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
70.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Emmes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norgate	I-pers
,	O
and	O
13	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camblet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Norgate	I-pers
,	O
July	O
12	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Norgate	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Byrom	O
,	O
in	O
Catherine-wheel-Alley	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Byrom	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
Mrs	O
Byrom	O
's	O
Husband	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spital	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Girl	O
before	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
71.	O
John	B-pers
Toe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
August	O
17	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
goes	O
of	O
Errands	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
his	O
Sister	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
it	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Miller	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
broke	O
it	O
in	O
several	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Boy	O
but	O
one	O
Penny	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
the	O
Boy	O
is	O
between	O
14	O
and	O
15	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Relations	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
my	O
Sister	O
is	O
.	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
is	O
an	O
innocent	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
is	O
a	O
notorious	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Boy	O
happened	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Incitement	O
of	O
Miller	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Penny	O
for	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
72.	O
Mary	B-pers
Crosby	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew's-Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
July	O
31	O
.	O
Mrs	O
White	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr	O
Redhead	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
Sheet	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
Sheet	O
is	O
this	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
proper	O
to	O
mention	O
whose	O
Sheet	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
offending	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
owns	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
having	O
his	O
Name	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
:	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
Linnen	O
to	O
wash.	O
Mary	B-pers
Exal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs	O
White	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Sheet	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
.	O
She	O
owned	O
before	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
where	O
the	O
Sheet	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
Court	O
.	O
This	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
White	O
.	O
Mrs	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
*	O
Property	O
while	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
In	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
the	O
Butler	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
(	O
September	O
Sessions	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
391	O
.	O
)	O
concerning	O
some	O
Plate	O
that	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Butler	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
to	O
keep	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
Case	O
;	O
though	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
is	O
answerable	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
is	O
entrusted	O
with	O
.	O
73.	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Swawbrook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
John	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
called	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
I	O
suspected	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
)	O
but	O
she	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
small	O
matter	O
of	O
Money	O
to	O
lay	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Thing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Disappointment	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Windows	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
House	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
outside	O
Shutters	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
them	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
or	O
Frame	O
was	O
upheld	O
by	O
a	O
long	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Spike-Nail	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
conjectur	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
St	O
Martin	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
nothing	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
deaf	O
as	O
this	O
Board	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
39	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
Ground-Room	O
:	O
The	O
Window	O
was	O
fastened	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
generally	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
Time	O
it	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Father	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
your	O
own	O
Daughter	O
?	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
must	O
pull	O
out	O
my	O
Barnacles	O
*	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
my	O
Daughter	O
;	O
(	O
and	O
wept	O
.	O
)	O
*	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
quite	O
deaf	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
a	O
written	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Oath	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pronounced	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Questions	O
were	O
all	O
put	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Writing	O
.	O
[	O
His	O
other	O
Daughter	O
was	O
called	O
for	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
Daughter	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
eleven	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
Four	O
Score	O
and	O
Eight	O
.	O
[	O
She	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
young	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
admit	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
.	O
]	O
Radford	O
.	O
The	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
by	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Palace	O
Yard	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
,	O
which	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
open	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Door	O
between	O
Justice	O
Blackerby	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
the	O
Bridge-Office	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Bench	O
the	O
Watermen	O
have	O
to	O
sit	O
upon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
sitting	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
else	O
with	O
her	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
under	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
King	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Parliament	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Bench	O
moves	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Report	O
that	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Daughters	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
Father	O
(	O
from	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
Mother	O
)	O
till	O
the	O
Time	O
this	O
thing	O
happen	O
'd	O
:	O
Thinks	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
this	O
Thing	O
;	O
this	O
young	O
Witness	O
was	O
gone	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
Daughter	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
King's-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Horse-Grenadier	O
:	O
The	O
old	O
Man	O
finding	O
his	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
cried	O
,	O
What	O
will	O
no	O
Body	O
help	O
me	O
!	O
So	O
I	O
being	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manley	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Evening	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Examination	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
sign	O
'd	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Horse-Grenadier	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
Forces	O
to	O
Flanders	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
Women	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
Troop	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
74.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Harrateen	O
Bed-Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cheney	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
Set	O
of	O
Curtains	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
if	O
I	O
approved	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grubb	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
Woman	O
by	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
your	O
Duty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
every	O
one	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
take	O
care	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
must	O
be	O
delivered	O
without	O
being	O
paid	O
for	O
:	O
You	O
have	O
bought	O
a	O
thing	O
the	O
Seller	O
had	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
75.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
four	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Portugal	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
36	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
called	O
Guineas	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pauncefort	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pauncefort	I-pers
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pauncefort	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Bureau	O
set	O
on	O
Fire	O
about	O
eleven	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
best	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
Linnen	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
laid	O
but	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
this	O
Fire	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
Shop-Maid	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Till	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Bureau	O
burnt	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Well	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
then	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
had	O
her	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Bureau	O
on	O
Fire	O
?	O
Pauncefort	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Drawers	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
mout	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
bottom	O
Drawer	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
Linnen	O
was	O
,	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
Fire	O
began	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
apprehend	O
,	O
was	O
lost	O
by	O
the	O
Bureau	O
being	O
opened	O
with	O
a	O
Key	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
me	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
of	O
Gloucester	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pauncefort	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
both	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Worral	I-pers
.	O
I	O
caught	O
her	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Till	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
unseemly	O
Manner	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Key	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
my	O
Key	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Bureau	O
's	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Worral	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
after	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
out	O
-	O
The	O
Drawers	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
People	O
called	O
out	O
Fire	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
carry	O
any	O
Water	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
very	O
near	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Pauncefort	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
on	O
Fire	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
at	O
the	O
Kitchen-Door	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Bureau	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
higher	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
under	O
Drawer	O
of	O
the	O
Bureau	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
Flame	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
threw	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
upon	O
it	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Light	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
brought	O
none	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
other	O
People	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
more	O
Water	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
till	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
quite	O
extinguished	O
,	O
I	O
moved	O
the	O
Bureau	O
from	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
the	O
Paper	O
Hangings	O
.	O
Then	O
several	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Candle	O
was	O
brought	O
;	O
presently	O
the	O
Desk	O
Part	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
surprizing	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
either	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
never	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bolt	O
was	O
shoved	O
back	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pauncefort	O
came	O
Home	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
locked	O
his	O
Bureau	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
imagined	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
Constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellcock	I-pers
.	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Report	O
of	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
Mr	O
Pauncefort	O
's	O
Sister	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Money	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
searching	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
down	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
clean	O
Shirts	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
In	O
letting	O
down	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
clean	O
Shirts	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Twigger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
only	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
odd	O
half	O
pence	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Shirts	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
when	O
the	O
Drawer	O
was	O
in	O
Flames	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Mr	O
Smith	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Washam	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shirts	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlewoman	O
showed	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
Shirts	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
Fire	O
was	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bureau	O
was	O
all	O
on	O
Fire	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Water	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
quench	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Linnen	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
what	O
Linnen	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Twigger	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
not-moving	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
They	O
searched	O
me	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
hardly	O
used	O
;	O
they	O
denied	O
me	O
all	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Town	O
from	O
Gloucester	O
but	O
five	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
about	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr	O
Gardner	O
,	O
a	O
Minister	O
in	O
Gloucester	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
always	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
the	O
Girl	O
had	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
every	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
civil	O
modest	O
Girl	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
serve	O
Mr	O
Gardner	O
with	O
Coals	O
;	O
his	O
Brother	O
was	O
here	O
all	O
yesterday	O
and	O
to-day	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
,	O
thinking	O
the	O
Trial	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
on	O
to-night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
76.	O
Mary	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bryan	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
77.	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Dressing-Glass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Dressing-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
;	O
the	O
Buckles	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
my	O
Maid	O
and	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
Maid	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs	O
Coates	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
there	O
then	O
,	O
the	O
Looking-Glass	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
Sand	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Fore-Parlour	O
:	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Glass	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Coates	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
only	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
lay	O
between	O
her	O
Maid	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
78.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
August	O
21	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
there	O
happened	O
a	O
Fire	O
at	O
Mr	O
Ladbrook	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Things	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
for	O
Security	O
from	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
moving	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
found	O
on	O
this	O
Thomas	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
;	O
Mr	O
Ladbrook	O
had	O
removed	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
This	O
Spoon	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
a	O
Year	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
J.	O
M.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
before	O
Mr	O
Wroth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
an	O
old	O
Mother	O
of	O
seventy	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
able	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
have	O
Mercy	O
shown	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
79.	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bartrup	I-pers
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bartrup	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Woman	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
Whitecross-Alley	B-place
,	O
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
Small-Beer	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
Gin	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
having	O
the	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
these	O
were	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
they	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Where	O
's	O
my	O
Shirt	O
?	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
taken	O
your	O
Wife	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
her	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
and	O
the	O
Stays	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Gown	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
single	O
Man	O
then	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
80	O
,	O
81	O
,	O
82	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
John	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
open	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Inwood	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
one	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cantaloon	O
Stuff	O
80	O
Yards	O
,	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
22	O
Yards	O
,	O
14	O
Ells	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Remnants	O
of	O
Bays	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Inwood	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Inwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Milk-Alley	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shipwright	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Wife	O
is	O
chiefly	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
Business	O
:	O
July	O
the	O
22d	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
fast	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
barred	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Shutters	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
within	O
reach	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
by	O
a	O
Hand	O
Put	O
thro	O
'	O
that	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
this	O
Anderson	O
the	O
Soldier	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
walking	O
together	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
we	O
met	O
Richard	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
and	O
Hinton	O
;	O
this	O
Anderson	O
mentioned	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
proposed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
Anderson	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Cobler	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Means	O
of	O
his	O
Pinchers	O
,	O
pulled	O
the	O
Groove	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shutters	O
slide	O
upon	O
;	O
I	O
broke	O
the	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Anderson	O
;	O
Anderson	O
and	O
Hinton	O
held	O
open	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
and	O
Studder	O
stood	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Bag	O
;	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
course	O
Sheeting	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Gill	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
was	O
divided	O
between	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
odd	O
6	O
d.	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
Brother	O
Richard	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
it	O
yet	O
:	O
Mrs	O
Gill	O
finding	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
keep	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
returned	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
cried	O
,	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Miller	O
the	O
Thieftaker	O
's	O
Wife	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
my	O
Information	O
,	O
having	O
made	O
myself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Hinton	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
Unwin	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
China	O
and	O
Earthen	O
ware	O
.	O
Unwin	O
.	O
I	O
informed	O
Mr	O
Inwood	O
I	O
thought	O
Richard	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
hearing	O
of	O
this	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
offered	O
himself	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Evidence	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
several	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
clear	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
Evidence	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
then	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
He	O
named	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Crocket	O
and	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
I	O
met	O
Anderson	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Brother	O
and	O
Hinton	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
Mother	O
Rippon	O
's	O
at	O
Epping	O
:	O
I	O
hired	O
some	O
People	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Anderson	O
and	O
Studder	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
themselves	O
Evidences	O
,	O
but	O
Hinton	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
himself	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
save	O
Studder	O
;	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
there	O
is	O
about	O
60	O
of	O
this	O
Crew	O
;	O
Studder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
New	O
Prison	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
Leaders	O
of	O
this	O
Gang	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
hardly	O
stir	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Upwood	I-pers
Constable	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Bays	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Studder	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Anderson	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Thief-takers	O
here	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
swear	O
our	O
Lives	O
away	O
.	O
Inwood	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Marks	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
them	O
.	O
Nathanael	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mother	O
Rippon	O
's	O
at	O
Epping	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Richard	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
saw	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
Hinton	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
prevented	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Studder	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
your	O
Pistols	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
exchanged	O
them	O
with	O
Matthew	O
Mooney	O
*	O
for	O
his	O
Buckles	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Hatter	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
58.	O
p.	O
24	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
Harris	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
very	O
dangerous	O
Man	O
.	O
Hinton	O
.	O
Harris	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Pounds	O
I	O
may	O
serve	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
your	O
Life	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
concerning	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
expect	O
any	O
.	O
[	O
Unwin	O
called	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
;	O
have	O
you	O
received	O
any	O
Money	O
from	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
Relations	O
.	O
Unwin	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Money	O
offered	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
considerable	O
Sum	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Studder	O
offered	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
any	O
ways	O
serve	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Studder	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
all	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Hind	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
Anderson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
Thomas	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
lay	O
his	O
Informations	O
fully	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
mine	O
fuller	O
than	O
his	O
before	O
Colonel	O
Deveil	B-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
Anderson	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
Lie	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Dennel	O
.	O
Hind	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
that	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
produced	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Pistols	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Thursday	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
were	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Marks	O
are	O
rubbed	O
off	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
Anderson	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Cobler	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
keep	O
a	O
Stall	O
,	O
but	O
works	O
for	O
several	O
Masters	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Brother-in-Law	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
Bread	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Brasier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Broad	O
street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
sell	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Brokers	O
there	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Sister	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
cries	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
Mr	O
Unwin	O
,	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
away	O
an	O
innocent	O
Life	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
come	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
served	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
Money	O
my	O
Brother	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
mention	O
'd	O
any	O
particular	O
Sum	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
Fellow	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
sucked	O
at	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
34	O
or	O
35	O
Years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
45	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
looked	O
to	O
be	O
full	O
as	O
old	O
)	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Broad	O
St	O
Giles	O
's	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Unwin	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
that	O
Woman	O
(	O
Anderson	O
's	O
Sister	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
free	O
Dealer	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
pay	O
it	O
at	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
the	O
Husband	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
3	O
l	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
offer	O
any	O
thing	O
concerning	O
taking	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
83.	O
Richard	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Geese	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Duck	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Game	O
Cocks	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Hen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
84.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
85.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
sell	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapened	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
.	O
I	O
fitted	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
this	O
Pair	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
opened	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
have	O
them	O
here	O
?	O
she	O
opened	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
under	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bag	O
tied	O
round	O
her	O
Waste	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stays	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
Bag	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Compton	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
's	O
Wife	O
both	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Stays	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bag	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
86.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
3	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Ring	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Box	O
last	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Box	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
pawned	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
Hart-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grub	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hart-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
she	O
pledged	O
it	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
in	O
several	O
Rings	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
dealt	O
very	O
fairly	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Wedding-Ring	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
87.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pumps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Damask	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
September	O
2	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
88.	O
Martha	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
Hooper	O
deserted	O
my	O
Service	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
said	O
,	O
Mr	O
Miller	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
some	O
Pumps	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
Pair	O
behind	O
a	O
Grate	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Mark	O
is	O
blotted	O
out	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Pumps	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
by	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
her	O
Mistress	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Hooper	O
guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Goldsmith	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
89	O
,	O
90.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Canwell	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Yards	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Thread	O
Lace	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coverley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coverley	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
1.	O
Frances	B-pers
Coverley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Milliner	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
White-Chapel	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapened	O
some	O
Lace	O
,	O
Davis	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
Baby-Cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
designed	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
at	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
(	O
Mr	O
Crawley	O
's	O
)	O
House	O
.	O
This	O
Lace	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Box	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Lace	O
drop	O
from	O
Canwell	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
under	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Davis	O
was	O
at	O
some	O
small	O
Distance	O
from	O
the	O
Lace	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Canwell	O
.	O
Have	O
I	O
not	O
been	O
several	O
Times	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
out	O
Money	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Coverley	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
twice	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
bought	O
Goods	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Canwell	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Davis	O
take	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Coverley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
should	O
rather	O
think	O
Davis	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
like	O
an	O
ill	O
Person	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Lace	O
they	O
cheapened	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
Canwell	O
handled	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
might	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
stood	O
even	O
with	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
(	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Crawley	O
)	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
sitting	O
close	O
together	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Davis	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Lace	O
stuck	O
to	O
Davis	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Part	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Gerrard	O
Crawley	O
.	O
My	O
Cousin	O
Coverley	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
with	O
these	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
unwilling	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
go	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
my	O
Cousin	O
said	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
you	O
two	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
little	O
amazed	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
you	O
shall	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
shortest	O
one	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
Davis	O
)	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Search	O
me	O
,	O
Madam	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Lace	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
outward	O
Garment	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
stuck	O
to	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
from	O
that	O
Side	O
next	O
to	O
Davis	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
opposite	O
Side	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Coverley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
missing	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
must	O
come	O
back	O
.	O
Says	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
What	O
will	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
the	O
Lace	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
Mr	O
Crawley	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
told	O
what	O
we	O
wanted	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Gilham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Canwell	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
is	O
a	O
Lapidary	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Young	I-pers
had	O
known	O
her	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Foxon	I-pers
four	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Woolball	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
have	O
known	O
Canwell	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
*	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Jane	B-pers
Canwell	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
Davis	O
had	O
not	O
one	O
Person	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
,	O
Linnen-Draper	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
remarkable	O
Trial	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
91	O
,	O
92	O
,	O
93.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Ewins	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
called	O
Grace	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
upon	O
Joseph	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
Fear	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
sixteen	O
Metal	O
Spurs	O
,	O
one	O
Cock	O
,	O
and	O
thirty	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Well-Street	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
called	O
Grace	B-place
's	I-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
and	O
heard	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
come	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
presently	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
pass	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
here	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Fowl	O
in	O
my	O
Bag	O
;	O
)	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
Bag	O
under	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
these	O
Spurs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
trifling	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
first	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Fowl	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
:	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
50	O
s.	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
laid	O
it	O
but	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
I	O
begged	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
working	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
hinder	O
me	O
from	O
getting	O
my	O
Living	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
up	O
a	O
Thing	O
like	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
another	O
Word	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
another	O
held	O
up	O
a	O
Thing	O
like	O
a	O
Hanger	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
very	O
particular	O
,	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
come	O
along	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Bags	O
only	O
a	O
Fowl	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
but	O
of	O
little	O
Use	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
saying	O
that	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
flew	O
towards	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Fury	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
said	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
:	O
A	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Cock	O
Spurs	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
'T	O
was	O
Mr	O
Unwin	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
near	O
Well	O
Close-Square	O
,	O
the	O
Spurs	O
are	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
;	O
this	O
wooden	O
Box	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Spurs	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
darkish	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
Lamps	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sized	O
Men	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Daniel	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
middle	O
sized	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Plaue-maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
divert	O
yourself	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
Cock-Match	O
.	O
Daniel	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
use	O
much	O
Company	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
spend	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
as	O
spend	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Shillings	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
met	O
Joseph	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
an	O
Alley	O
near	O
Well-Close-Square	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
to	O
stop	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
we	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
from	O
them	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr	O
Daniel	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Ewins	O
the	O
Irishman	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
what	O
Money	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
22	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
was	O
shared	O
among	O
us	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
sunk	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
-	O
Squire	O
was	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
Body	O
hold	O
up	O
a	O
Pistol	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
