TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
16th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
1743	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIMOTT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
BURNET	O
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Hall	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Catmur	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
George	O
Gillet	O
was	O
sworn	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
ill.	O
William	B-pers
Bilon	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brackley	I-pers
.	O
64	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
light	O
Dun	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
Dun	O
Gelding	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Grounds	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Lands	O
called	O
the	O
Lawn	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Gotburst	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Bucks	O
:	O
The	O
Gelding	O
was	O
at	O
Grass	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
my	O
Seat	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Scrimshaw	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
light	O
Dun	O
Gelding	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	O
in	O
Princess-street	O
,	O
by	O
Leicester-Fields	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
keeps	O
an	O
Inn	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
Sale	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
Father	O
to	O
set	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Way	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
Money	O
:	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
nine	O
Guineas	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
six	O
Guineas	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
stood	O
all	O
Night	O
at	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
:	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
afterwards	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
it	O
was	O
advertis	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Papers	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Esquire	O
Wright	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Servants	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
show	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Thursday	O
after	O
)	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
them	O
directly	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
the	O
Bargain	O
was	O
made	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edgar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
's	O
Son	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
to	O
Mr	O
Scrimshaw	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
Partners	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
Dun	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
very	O
little	O
Difference	O
between	O
a	O
light	O
Dun	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pale	O
Dun	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
received	O
this	O
Horse	O
from	O
Scrimshaw	O
?	O
Mr	O
Wright	O
.	O
My	O
Servants	O
did	O
.	O
-	O
Edgar	O
and	O
Scrimshaw	O
owned	O
they	O
had	O
this	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Servants	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
delivered	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
by	O
Scrimshaw	O
or	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
receive	O
a	O
pale	O
Dun	O
Gelding	O
from	O
Mr	O
Scrimshaw	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
Wright	O
.	O
Scrimshaw	O
.	O
The	O
Gelding	O
that	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
Hollis	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Gelding	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Jertmiah	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
by	O
Scrimshaw	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Portion	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Twenty-one	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
this	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
your	O
Father	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dark	O
Brown	B-pers
Mare	I-pers
,	O
Value	O
7	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collingridge	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
Mr	O
Wright	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
light	O
Dun	O
Gelding	O
,	O
my	O
Servant	O
lost	O
a	O
dark	O
Brown	B-pers
Mare	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Lordship	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
Grounds	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
Lordship	O
of	O
Gotburst	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
lost	O
?	O
Mr	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
Steward	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Servant	O
here	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
Mr	O
Collingridge	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
65.	O
Christian	B-pers
Poland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Blanket	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Titt	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Titt	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
Fortnight	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
of	O
mine	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
show	O
me	O
:	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
Sheet	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
throw	O
this	O
Sheet	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lap	O
upon	O
Mrs	O
Titt	O
's	O
Bed	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Blanket	O
lie	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
Blanket	O
which	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
drop	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
65.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
green	O
Silk	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Short	O
Coat	O
,	O
four	O
Boy	O
's	O
Shirts	O
,	O
four	O
Frocks	O
,	O
6	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Hardwick	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
Cloak	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hardwick	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hardwick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
[	O
Had	O
it	O
been	O
so	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Capital	O
Offence	O
]	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hardwick	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Lap	O
full	O
of	O
Things	O
;	O
but	O
thought	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
mistook	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
not	O
mistrusting	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
soon	O
after	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
Stature	O
of	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Dress	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Mother	O
cleared	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
could	O
know	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
thousand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hardwick	I-pers
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
Things	O
at	O
Mr	O
Carter	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Broad	O
St	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
we	O
lost	O
;	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Saleshop	O
for	O
Women	O
's	O
Apparel	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Things	O
which	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
-	O
Mr	O
Hardwick	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
That	O
good	O
Woman	O
brought	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bargained	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
who	O
said	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Short's-Gardens	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Trader	O
)	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
you	O
sold	O
me	O
last	O
were	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
lose	O
my	O
Money	O
*	O
;	O
so	O
it	O
is	O
for	O
me	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
had	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
a	O
Twelve-month	O
.	O
*	O
No	O
Sale	O
,	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Pawn	O
,	O
or	O
Mortgage	O
,	O
of	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
shall	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
or	O
within	O
two	O
Miles	O
thereof	O
,	O
to	O
any	O
Broker	O
or	O
Pawntaker	O
,	O
shall	O
make	O
any	O
Change	O
or	O
Alteration	O
of	O
the	O
Property	O
.	O
1	O
James	O
i.	O
c.	O
21.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
did	O
come	O
again	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Shorts-Gardens	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
this	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
such	O
an	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
before	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
She	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
pay	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
come	O
into	O
Trouble	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
honestly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dumbleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Osburne	I-pers
,	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
fair	O
dealing	O
Woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
67.	O
John	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Pendarvis	B-pers
Keckwick	I-pers
,	O
December	O
14th	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Tayler	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
mend	O
by	O
Mr	O
Keckwick	O
,	O
I	O
hung	O
them	O
carelesly	O
over	O
the	O
Shop-Door	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatched	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
having	O
no	O
Shoes	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pursue	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
hung	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
catch	O
him	O
,	O
fastened	O
a	O
String	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
nailed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
off	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
for	O
the	O
String	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Breeches	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Cap	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Hat	O
on	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
68	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jam	O
.	O
Mills	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
December	O
22d	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Somerset-House	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
bear	O
a	O
little	O
tight	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
immediately	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
quite	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Shop	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Person	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
,	O
who	O
seemed	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Complexion	O
with	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
that	O
they	O
go	O
in	O
Gangs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
attacked	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
by	O
Force	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
:	O
Mr	O
Blakey	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
between	O
his	O
Feet	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Person	O
near	O
me	O
who	O
could	O
possibly	O
pick	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mr	O
Blakey	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Somerset-House	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Fellow	O
has	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
no	O
body	O
shall	O
come	O
behind	O
you	O
to	O
assault	O
you	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Feet	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
your	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
Mr	O
Mills	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
a	O
Hosier's-Shop	O
,	O
by	O
Somerset	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
insulted	O
by	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
so	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Guard	O
from	O
Somerset-House	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Frasier	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Handkerchief	O
lay	O
very	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
else	O
near	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
possibly	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Fellow	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Yards	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
suspected	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Gang	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
Phoebe	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Time	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
a	O
Comb-maker	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
hard-working	O
,	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
69	O
,	O
70	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Beecher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
January	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Angelo	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
some	O
Stockings	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Friday	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
take	O
one	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
me	O
come	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
stood	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
:	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
some	O
Stockings	O
for	O
themselves	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
Money	O
about	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
than	O
Seven-pence	O
Half-penny	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
71.	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	O
James	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Sheets	O
and	O
two	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Harrington	I-pers
;	O
one	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Lorano	B-pers
Clutterbuck	I-pers
;	O
two	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Rose	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
Rose	O
Eustace	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs	O
Eustace	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Mother	O
bring	O
them	O
Home	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Cathery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Mother	O
deliver	O
the	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
before	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
72.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broxton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pebble	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Rim	O
and	O
Hinge	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jan.	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
Richard	B-pers
Battman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
clean	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
of	O
Errands	O
for	O
Mr	O
Barron	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
this	O
Snuff-box	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
People	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Pinchbeck	O
Mettle	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Deveil	B-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Certificate	O
*	O
produced	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Minister	O
and	O
Church-Wardens	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
George	O
,	O
Hanover-Square	O
,	O
dated	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1730	O
,	O
certifying	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broxton	I-pers
was	O
baptiz	O
'd	O
there	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
]	O
Guilty	O
.	O
*	O
An	O
Infant	O
,	O
infra	O
AEtatem	O
Infantiae	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Seven	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
whatever	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
proving	O
Discretion	O
,	O
may	O
appear	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
be	O
above	O
Seven	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
Twelve	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
commit	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
prima	O
facie	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
adjudged	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
is	O
supposed	O
not	O
of	O
Discretion	O
to	O
judge	O
between	O
Good	O
and	O
Evil	O
;	O
yet	O
if	O
it	O
appear	O
by	O
strong	O
and	O
pregnant	O
Evidence	O
and	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Discretion	O
to	O
judge	O
between	O
Good	O
and	O
Evil	O
,	O
Judgement	O
of	O
Death	O
may	O
be	O
given	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
At	O
Abingdon	O
Assizes	O
,	O
1629	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
between	O
E	O
ight	O
and	O
Nine	O
Years	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
arraigned	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
burning	O
two	O
Barns	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Windsor	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Malice	O
,	O
Revenge	O
,	O
Craft	O
,	O
and	O
Cunning	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Judgment	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bang	O
'd	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
corporal	O
Punishment	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
doing	O
the	O
Boy	O
a	O
great	O
Piece	O
of	O
Service	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
abroad	O
.	O
73.	O
George	B-pers
Spurham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saltwell	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
74.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saltwell	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Saltwell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Hoxton-Square	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mr	O
Harris	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
at	O
Mr	O
Hayley	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
stopped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Shirts	O
and	O
the	O
Spoon	O
were	O
sold	O
out-right	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hayley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Spurham	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
Hat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
;	O
Hudson	O
stood	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
Spurham	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
premunire	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
somebody	O
in	O
Hoxton-Square	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Things	O
behind	O
them	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Saltwell	O
owned	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Spurham	O
.	O
Hudson	O
is	O
clear	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Saltwell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Door	O
crack	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Spurham	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Hand-Basket	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
disturb	O
me	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Hudson	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
run	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
Things	O
till	O
the	O
Evening	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Mistrust	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
They	O
both	O
confessed	O
the	O
having	O
the	O
Things	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
;	O
the	O
Confession	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Spurham	I-pers
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hudson	O
had	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hudson	O
brought	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
supposing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr	O
Saltwell	O
the	O
Owner	O
.	O
Spurham	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
Weeds	O
;	O
and	O
Hudson	O
said	O
,	O
all	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Spurham	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
two	O
Shirts	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
gave	O
Spurham	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
75	O
,	O
76	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Fennell	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
December	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Christmas-Day	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
to	O
Bruton-Street	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
New-Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
standing	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
stood	O
there	O
for	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
o'Night	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
a	O
Soldier	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Penny	O
:	O
The	O
Woman	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
Night-Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
Two	O
other	O
Soldiers	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
three	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
Catherine-street	B-place
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Arm	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Pot	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
my	O
Way	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
wanted	O
to	O
lead	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
again	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
down	O
Catherine-street	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
turned	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
whisper	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
almost	O
against	O
Bridges-street	O
,	O
Bland	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
off	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
laid	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
Bland	O
,	O
called	O
out	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
before	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Bland	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Brand	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
off	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Christmas	O
Eve	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
,	O
together	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Oak	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
a	O
Street	O
over	O
against	O
Somerset-House	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Brand	O
ask	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
be	O
a	O
Penny	O
towards	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
Three	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
provided	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
his	O
Way	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
against	O
Exeter-street	O
End	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hold	O
him	O
fast	O
)	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Fennell	O
was	O
forty	O
Yards	O
off	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
concerted	O
any	O
Scheme	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
neither	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
Fennell	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
my	O
Design	O
of	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Brand	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
off	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Head	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Whispering	O
when	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
parted	O
from	O
us	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
Christmas-Day	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
Bland	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr	O
Blackwell	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Colonel	O
of	O
the	O
Guard	O
,	O
and	O
demand	O
the	O
two-Prisoners	O
whom	O
Bland	O
had	O
discovered	O
as	O
being	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
Brand	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Hat	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
Barracks	O
.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Temple	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Hat	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr	O
Blackwell	O
)	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Fennell	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Bland	O
did	O
propose	O
to	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Hat	O
off	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
a	O
Drink	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
Words	O
;	O
Let	O
us	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Hat	O
off	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
Drink	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
.	O
On	O
Christmas-Day	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Bland	O
was	O
charged	O
by	O
Mr	O
Blackwell	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
while	O
another	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
Bland	O
begged	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
Bridges-Street	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
Mr.	O
Blackwell	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
running	O
up	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Blackwell	O
have	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
Bland	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
:	O
And	O
Brand	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
off	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
Fennell	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Col.	O
Duroy	B-pers
.	O
Brand	O
has	O
been	O
about	O
nine	O
Months	O
entered	O
in	O
my	O
Company	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
:	O
From	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
his	O
Duty	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
his	O
Honesty	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
Lad	O
about	O
19	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
favoured	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
take	O
warning	O
by	O
this	O
.	O
Ever	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Company	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Barracks	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
better	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
knowing	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Behaviour	O
than	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
not	O
confined	O
all	O
Night	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Roll	O
was	O
called	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Fennell	O
has	O
behaved	O
well	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
listed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
April	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
lives	O
:	O
Extremely	O
so	O
;	O
a	O
quite	O
sober	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Serj	O
.	O
W.	O
Temple	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
they	O
listed	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
Rognery	O
or	O
Villainy	O
in	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
.	O
Fennell	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
as	O
honest	O
Men	O
as	O
live	O
.	O
Edw	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
Corporal	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Brand	O
ever	O
since	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
always	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
Fennell	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Elisha	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Brand	O
about	O
nine	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
about	O
eight	O
Months	O
.	O
Brand	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Apartment	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
entrusted	O
with	O
Things	O
of	O
great	O
Value	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Col.	O
Duroy	B-pers
.	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
both	O
their	O
Characters	O
are	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
This	O
happened	O
just	O
on	O
Christmas-Eve	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
drink	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Fennell	O
,	O
Brand	O
and	O
Bland	O
,	O
Russel	O
and	O
Bryan	O
,	O
on	O
Christmas-Eve	O
,	O
till	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Russel	O
,	O
Bryan	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
set	O
out	O
first	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
Fennell	O
came	O
home	O
soon	O
after	O
us	O
.	O
Fennell	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
called	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
Brand	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
'till	O
such	O
time	O
I	O
got	O
ready	O
for	O
Guard	O
.	O
Col.	O
Duroy	B-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
returned	O
as	O
Defaulters	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
answered	O
to	O
their	O
Names	O
upon	O
the	O
calling	O
over	O
the	O
Roll	O
.	O
Mr	O
Cramphorne	O
.	O
Brand	O
came	O
of	O
very	O
honest	O
Parents	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
last	O
March	O
was	O
twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
always	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
silly	O
Fellow	O
to	O
be	O
led	O
into	O
this	O
Scrape	O
.	O
Mr	O
Blackwell	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
[	O
a	O
Circumstance	O
requisite	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
Robbery	O
]	O
when	O
one	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Arm	O
:	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
afraid	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
more	O
so	O
when	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
laid	O
his	O
Arm	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
Brand	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Fennell	O
acquitted	O
.	O
77	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
unknown	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Money-bag	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
35	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
Dec.	O
28	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Dec.	O
28th	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
Waggon	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Eagle	B-place
and	I-place
Child	I-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
between	O
Shoe-Lane	O
and	O
the	O
New-Market	O
.	O
She	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
for	O
Nan	O
,	O
Nan	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
.	O
-	O
Not	O
this	O
Nan	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Nans	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
both	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
Right-Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
her	O
Left	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
one	O
Arm	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
dived	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
into	O
the	O
left	O
Pocket	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
my	O
Shirt	O
out	O
before	O
she	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
both	O
cried	O
out	O
for	O
George	O
,	O
but	O
George	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Soul	O
came	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
she	O
found	O
my	O
Shirt	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Bag	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
35	O
s.	O
She	O
got	O
the	O
Bag	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Bag	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
she	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
part	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
Jerk	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
takes	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
God	O
gave	O
me	O
more	O
Strength	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
cried	O
out	O
for	O
George	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
George	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
her	O
quite	O
down	O
the	O
Alley	O
.	O
And	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
stood	O
three	O
Men	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
by	O
this	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
your	O
Assistance	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
White-Swan-Inn	O
at	O
Holbourn-Bridge	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
Horses	O
were	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
what	O
Drink	O
they	O
would	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
Country	O
Man	O
's	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Tap-house	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
I	O
thanked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
craved	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
dared	O
not	O
tell	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
knocked	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
by	O
her	O
Bullies	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
that	O
Night	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
:	O
And	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
suddled	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
Shirt	O
hung	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
without	O
any	O
Reason	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Pocket	O
was	O
then	O
buttoned	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
would	O
have	O
thought	O
it	O
impossible	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
always	O
lay	O
my	O
Breeches	O
under	O
my	O
Pillow	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Bag	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
assisted	O
me	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
White	O
Fryars	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
at	O
20	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
the	O
Alley	O
with	O
his	O
Shirt	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
New	O
Market	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
Christmas-Day	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
my	O
Husband	O
something	O
for	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
old	O
Gentleman	O
come	O
and	O
pull	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
Eagle	O
and	O
Child	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
indecent	O
;	O
Manner	O
;	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shirt	O
hung	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
Murder	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
hurt	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
any	O
Body	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Beer	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
some	O
Inn	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
hawling	O
her	O
into	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
that	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
Market	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
abundance	O
of	O
Mob	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
murder	O
your	O
Wife	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
their	O
Faces	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
black	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
more	O
remarkable	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
strange	O
,	O
that	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
should	O
want	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Man	O
till	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
Murder	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
among	O
the	O
other	O
Mob	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
which	O
he	O
hawl	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
the	O
Candle	O
is	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
That	O
old	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
in	O
Eagle	O
and	O
Child	O
Alley	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
Christmas	O
Week	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
Women	O
.	O
-	O
Both	O
fair	O
Women	O
;	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
without	O
:	O
(	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
my	O
Husband	O
does	O
,	O
in	O
Eagle	O
and	O
Child	O
Alley	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Mr	O
Pauley	O
's	O
,	O
an	O
Alehouse-keeper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Compasses	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
first	O
under	O
the	O
Lamp	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
People	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Women	O
mov	O
'd	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
Gentleman	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
:	O
I	O
only	O
speak	O
this	O
to	O
show	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Women	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shirt	O
hung	O
a	O
little	O
indecently	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
of	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
immodest	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
thorough	O
Sight	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
say	O
,	O
Do	O
not	O
murder	O
your	O
Wife	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
murder	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
,	O
honest	O
Man	O
!	O
can	O
you	O
deny	O
these	O
Words	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Phillips	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
you	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
help	O
me	O
then	O
?	O
Phillips	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Mob	O
cried	O
,	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
honest	O
Man	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robb	O
'd	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
robb	O
'd	O
!	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Gallon	O
of	O
Beer	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
away	O
to	O
some	O
Place	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Woman	O
he	O
was	O
pulling	O
up	O
the	O
Alley	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
Woman	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
black-guard	O
Boys	O
and	O
Girls	O
:	O
Her	O
Arm	O
looked	O
very	O
big	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
swell	O
'd	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
Woman	O
in	O
Eagle	O
and	O
Child	O
Alley	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
this	O
Hand	O
may	O
rot	O
off	O
if	O
!	O
did	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
:	O
She	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
Service	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
Service	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Judge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
sixteen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
with	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Penny	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
her	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Black	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
teach	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
Fence	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
from	O
her	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
this	O
Year	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
her	O
again	O
with	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
her	O
Mother	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
good	O
Woman	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Behaviour	O
of	O
late	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Church-Warden	O
of	O
St	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
Church-Warden	O
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
Beadle	O
,	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
indeed	O
with	O
her	O
Arm	O
bound	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
never	O
hurt	O
her	O
Arm	O
.	O
Townsend	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
bound	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
Elbow	O
to	O
the	O
Wrist	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
I	O
clasp	O
you	O
with	O
both	O
Arms	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Cripple	O
with	O
one	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
did	O
offer	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
Arm	O
unbound	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
bound	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
bound	O
on	O
Purpose	O
to	O
deceive	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
great	O
Matter	O
of	O
a	O
Wound	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Doctor	O
Lee	O
gives	O
me	O
Stuff	O
for	O
it	O
now	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stir	O
Hand	O
nor	O
Finger	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pickfat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
Holbourn-Hill	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
is	O
become	O
now	O
so	O
notorious	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
more	O
Thieves	O
between	O
our	O
Parts	O
and	O
Deputy	O
Nash	O
's	O
,	O
than	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
Street-Walker	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
.	O
-	O
Plying	O
between	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
decoying	O
and	O
seducing	O
Mankind	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
Phillips	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Compasses	O
in	O
Eagle	O
and	O
Child	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
frequented	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Ill	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
since	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
her	O
Character	O
is	O
very	O
vile	O
,	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
notorious	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
78.	O
Mary	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
out	O
of	O
Westminster-Abbey	B-place
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Dean	B-pers
and	O
Chapter	B-pers
of	I-pers
Westminster	I-pers
,	O
Dec	O
27	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fido	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Choir	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
call	O
Mr	O
Fido	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Robert	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
have	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Common-Prayer	O
Book	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manley	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
,	O
or	O
deny	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Senses	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Dean	O
and	O
Chapter	O
of	O
Westminster	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Dean	O
's	O
Cushion	O
about	O
five	O
Minutes	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
Verger	O
to	O
the	O
Dean	O
and	O
Chapter	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Candles	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Choir	O
Door	O
,	O
waiting	O
for	O
Mr	O
Fido	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
seeing	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
that	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
unwilling	O
I	O
should	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
Book	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
real	O
Want	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
79.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
;	O
on	O
e	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
3	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
for	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
too	O
large	O
for	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
committed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Pew-Opener	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Church-Warden	O
's	O
Pew	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Bingley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Assistant	O
to	O
the	O
Pew-Opener	O
of	O
St	O
Clement	O
Danes	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
Pew-Cleaner	O
or	O
Pew-Opener	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
Servants	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
these	O
three	O
Books	O
,	O
Mr	O
Johnson	O
's	O
,	O
Mrs	O
Reeve	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Jones	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Names	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
torn	O
out	O
,	O
except	O
Mrs	O
Reeve	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
Church-Warden	O
's	O
Pew	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Reeve	O
's	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
three	O
Books	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
three	O
Books	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
eight	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
she	O
sold	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
:	O
And	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
stopped	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
Mr	O
Johnson	O
's	O
:	O
This	O
is	O
Mrs	O
Reeves	O
's	O
:	O
This	O
is	O
Mr	O
Jones	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
so	O
often	O
in	O
my	O
Hands	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
Common-Prayer	O
Book	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
Mrs	O
Wood	O
.	O
my	O
Name	O
being	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Name	O
out	O
without	O
making	O
the	O
Book	O
imperfect	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
three	O
Books	O
out	O
*	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Book	O
.	O
*	O
Stealing	O
any	O
Thing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Church	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
capital	O
Offence	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
,	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
Compassion	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Charge	O
;	O
which	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
these	O
poor	O
Wretches	O
must	O
have	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Turn-slile-Alley	O
,	O
by	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
deal	O
in	O
Books	O
)	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
Book	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Mr	O
Johnson	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
18	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
brought	O
this	O
Book	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mrs	O
Reeve	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs	O
Reeve	O
's	O
Name	O
in	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
Books	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
80	O
,	O
81.	O
Tobias	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Three	O
Farthings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
December	O
29	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
Tobias	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
my	O
Husband	O
has	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Jack	B-pers
Friday	I-pers
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
null	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
says	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
Almighty	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
Says	O
Isaac	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Push	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Waters	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Six	O
pences	O
,	O
and	O
Twelve-pence	O
Three-farthings	O
in	O
Brass	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Substance	O
we	O
had	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Breeches	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Waters	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
thick	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
Thumb	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Cobweb	O
down	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
Waters	O
threw	O
the	O
Breeches	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
your	O
Breeches	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Says	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
!	O
these	O
Men	O
will	O
always	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
keep	O
a	O
Farthing	O
of	O
Money	O
to	O
myself	O
.	O
Waters	O
.	O
Was	O
nobody	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Peggy	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Friday	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
you	O
forc	O
'd	O
in	O
:	O
You	O
have	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Prison-Affair	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
give	O
Leave	O
to	O
bring	O
down	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
of	O
our	O
Ward	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
defend	O
ourselves	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
prompt-up	O
Prosecution	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
Hurst	O
is	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Hurst	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
promis	O
'd	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Drink	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
Six-pences	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
Twelve-pence	O
Three-farthings	O
in	O
Brass	O
,	O
but	O
Copper	O
is	O
the	O
proper	O
Name	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pad	O
.	O
lock	O
upon	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
have	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
two	O
Shillings	O
then	O
:	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
Ned	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
's	O
Prime	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Expression	O
they	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
slept	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
some	O
People	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
waked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
awake	O
:	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
Says	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
You	O
Dog	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
Water	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Handful	O
of	O
Copper	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
stuck	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
either	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
or	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
:	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
repent	O
this	O
I	O
doubt	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
black-guard	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
another	O
Word	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
stick	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Heart	O
;	O
or	O
if	O
you	O
ever	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
threw	O
the	O
Breeches	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
mention	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
till	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Partners	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
spoke	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Keeper	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
afterwards	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr	O
Akerman	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Jack	B-pers
Friday	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
or	O
make	O
with	O
any	O
Thing	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
because	O
they	O
threatned	O
to	O
null	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
Margaret	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
lay	O
upon	O
another	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
in	O
the	O
Women	O
's	O
Ward	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
a	O
Hasp	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
broke	O
one	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Place	O
to	O
fix	O
a	O
Padlock	O
on	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Hasp	O
and	O
Staples	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Akerman	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Complaint	O
made	O
to	O
you	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Akerman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
remember	O
something	O
of	O
Mrs	O
Hurst	O
's	O
complaining	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
being	O
ill	O
us	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
Mr	O
Bold	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
down	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Cells	O
upon	O
this	O
Complaint	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
used	O
ill	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Punishment	O
for	O
their	O
Offences	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
not	O
confined	O
in	O
the	O
Cells	O
where	O
the	O
Criminals	O
are	O
consined	O
?	O
And	O
was	O
I	O
not	O
there	O
ten	O
Days	O
?	O
Akerman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
Days	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
eight	O
Days	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Hearing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
Hurst	O
lies	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
Lock	O
?	O
Akerman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
has	O
now	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Hasp	O
,	O
Staples	O
,	O
and	O
Padlock	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
a	O
Duce-Room	O
,	O
for	O
Persons	O
who	O
are	O
brought	O
from	O
one	O
Goal	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
There	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
Staple	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
this	O
Year	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Hasp	O
now	O
on	O
the	O
Inside	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
Padlock	O
to	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Friday	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
Ned	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
's	O
Room	O
together	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
Isaacs	O
took	O
the	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
Hurst	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
Waters	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
Ward	O
,	O
Waters	O
told	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
11	O
d.	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
Pots	O
of	O
Gin	O
and	O
Small-Beer	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Door	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
jar	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Hurt	O
done	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Hurst	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
complained	O
that	O
her	O
Hand	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
Hurst	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
saw	O
Waters	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Pocket	O
'till	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
Hurst	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
undressed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
almost	O
undressed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
striving	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
had	O
a	O
Hasp	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
Pad-lock	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
was	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Waters	O
.	O
Friday	O
came	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Says	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
Let	O
us	O
see	O
what	O
Prime	O
Hurst	O
has	O
got	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
blew	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
he	O
stabbed	O
Mrs	O
Hurst	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
-	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
Hall	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Candle	O
?	O
Girdler	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
to	O
Jack	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
's	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
Charity-Money	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
us	O
:	O
We	O
are	O
robbed	O
daily	O
and	O
hourly	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Delabrown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Isaacs	O
desire	O
Friday	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
Ned	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
Prime	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
Friday	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
would	O
null	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
fix	O
a	O
Pad	O
lock	O
to	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Delabrown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
:	O
For	O
I	O
lay	O
there	O
one	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
Hurst	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
sastened	O
with	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
Wire	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
Isaacs	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
Isaacs	O
ever	O
robbed	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
-	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
sooner	O
give	O
than	O
take	O
from	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Butterworth	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
always	O
used	O
me	O
with	O
good	O
Manners	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Delabrown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
Isaacs	O
has	O
used	O
my	O
Wife	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
in	O
striking	O
of	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Waters	O
never	O
used	O
me	O
ill	O
in	O
any	O
Shape	O
.	O
-	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
82	O
.	O
+	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Hopwood	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Pountney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Half-Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
Dec.	O
27th	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
my	O
Bureau	O
,	O
which	O
stands	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
unlocked	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
the	O
Walnut-Tree	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Rust	O
upon	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
open	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
unlocked	O
this	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
Story	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
bar	O
it	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
unbar	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
:	O
And	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
married	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Husband	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
who	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
all	O
Night	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
opening	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
pleased	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
these	O
Fellows	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
get	O
them	O
apprehended	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Thatched-House	O
,	O
by	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
Deptford	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
83.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Crank	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Silver-Buttons	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pendrice	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
28th	O
.	O
Pendrice	O
.	O
She	O
lodges	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
Buttons	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Pendrice	O
's	O
Buttons	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
brown	O
Paper	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
84	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cambrick-Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Vanhoorn	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vanhoorn	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
at	O
past	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Bull	O
Inn	O
in	O
Bishopgate-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
lighting	O
me	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Houses	O
from	O
the	O
Bull	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
russled	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
Hand	O
at	O
my	O
left	O
Side-Pocket	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
Thief	O
?	O
The	O
Boy	O
who	O
was	O
lighting	O
me	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
your	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
lighting	O
Mr	O
Vanboorn	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
picked	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
white	O
Handerchief	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
Mr	O
Vanboorn	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Sweep	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bull	O
Inn	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
I	O
lighted	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
my	O
Gate	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mr	O
Vanboorn	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Pocket	O
picked	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
Pockets	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
did	O
charge	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cathery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Horse	O
in	O
Old-Bond	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
out	O
Horses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
weekly	O
Servant	O
,	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
,	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Wood	O
street	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
a	O
Job	O
to	O
Bristol	O
.	O
The	O
poor	O
Fellow	O
has	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
being	O
almost	O
blind	O
.	O
W.	O
Lemmon	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
these	O
six	O
Years	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
Lord	O
Duncannon	O
's	O
Groom	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Humour	O
fell	O
into	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
almost	O
blind	O
.	O
He	O
can	O
hardly	O
see	O
your	O
Lordship	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
goes	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
with	O
People	O
as	O
a	O
Guide	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
those	O
that	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
Macdonald	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
Lord	O
Duncannon	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
say	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Servant	O
at	O
Lord	O
Duncannon	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
85	O
,	O
86	O
,	O
87	O
,	O
88	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Tigh	I-pers
of	O
Chatham	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	B-place
of	I-place
Kent	I-place
,	O
Coachman	O
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hebert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
Peruke-maker	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
of	O
Southwark	B-place
,	O
Pawn-broker	O
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Shearsmith	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
1736	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Margaret	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
did	O
forge	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
or	O
caused	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
willingly	O
act	O
and	O
assist	O
in	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
certain	O
Instrument	O
,	O
partly	O
printed	O
and	O
partly	O
written	O
,	O
and	O
sealed	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
general	O
Release	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Frogget	I-pers
thereunto	O
subscribed	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Frogget	I-pers
of	O
Chatham	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Kent	O
,	O
Ship-wright	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Indictment	O
farther	O
sets	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Secondary	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
.	O
This	O
(	O
the	O
general	O
Release	O
)	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Herbert	O
and	O
Tigh	O
both	O
attended	O
there	O
.	O
Herbert	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
,	O
Whether	O
,	O
upon	O
taxing	O
the	O
Costs	O
,	O
Mr	O
Stokes	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
?	O
And	O
whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
act	O
as	O
Assistant	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
Stokes	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
produced	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
.	O
He	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief-Justice	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
.	O
-	O
Herbert	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Mr	O
Herbert	O
frequently	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
filling-up	O
was	O
his	O
Hand-writing	O
.	O
The	O
Paper	O
was	O
then	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
General	O
Release	B-pers
from	O
George	B-pers
Frogget	I-pers
of	O
Chatham	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Kent	O
,	O
Ship-wright	O
,	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Tigh	I-pers
of	O
Chatham	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
County	O
of	O
Kent	O
,	O
Victualler	O
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Dated	O
the	O
13th	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1742	O
.	O
-	O
Signed	O
George	B-pers
Frogget	I-pers
,	O
And	O
witnessed	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
+	O
his	O
Mark	O
.	O
Owen	O
.	O
Mr	O
Stokes	O
declared	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Herbert	O
appeared	O
at	O
all	O
Motions	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
Herbert	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Owen	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Adams	O
there	O
once	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
last	O
Trinity-Term	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
Court	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Steps	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Phillips	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
-	O
Mr	O
Herbert	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
since	O
the	O
taxing	O
of	O
the	O
Costs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
only	O
Attorney	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Record	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Treasury	O
.	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Judgment	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Tigh	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Taxation	O
,	O
amounts	O
to	O
26	O
l.	O
The	O
Costs	O
were	O
taxed	O
May	O
14	O
,	O
1742.	O
John	B-pers
Burnford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
Tigh	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
G.	O
Frogget	O
and	O
his	O
Attorney	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Taxing	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Bench-Office	O
and	O
that	O
Night	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
together	O
:	O
Herbert	O
then	O
appeared	O
as	O
Tigh	O
's	O
Attorney	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Talk	O
about	O
a	O
General	O
Release	B-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Motion	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
why	O
this	O
Judgment	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
set	O
aside	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
General	O
Release	B-pers
;	O
after	O
this	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Forgery	O
,	O
Mr	O
Frogget	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Wapping	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Phillips	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
shaving	O
at	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
in	O
Cable-Street	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hay	O
field	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
Mr	O
Frogget	O
asked	O
him	O
this	O
Question	O
:	O
Pray	O
where	O
was	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Phillips	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
says	O
Frogget	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
not	O
at	O
such	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
naming	O
the	O
Sign	O
,	O
at	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
,	O
Phillips	O
asked	O
why	O
:	O
Says	O
Frogget	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
tell	O
whether	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
;	O
Frogget	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Company	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
Frogget	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Phillips	O
replied	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
Frogget	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
not	O
as	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
;	O
Look	O
at	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
says	O
Frogget	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Number	O
of	O
People	O
)	O
then	O
says	O
Frogget	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Villain	O
,	O
to	O
swear	O
you	O
saw	O
me	O
receive	O
such	O
a	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
:	O
Says	O
Phillips	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
paid	O
,	O
says	O
Frogget	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
surprizing	O
Thing	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
Cloths	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
Thing	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
Phillips	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sai	O
d	O
too	O
much	O
already	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
more	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
Mr	O
Adams	O
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroken	O
,	O
in	O
Faulcon-Court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
will	O
inform	O
you	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Transactions	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Talk	O
of	O
a	O
Paper	O
that	O
he	O
signed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
strange	O
Thing	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
as	O
to	O
sign	O
such	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Master	O
's	O
Office	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Attorneys	O
cast	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Shearsmith	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
Tigh	O
and	O
Herbert	O
,	O
and	O
Frogget	O
,	O
and	O
Goulder	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Bladen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
King	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
by	O
White-Fryers-Gateway	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Herbert	O
cast	O
the	O
Bill	O
up	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Goulder	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
the	O
Bill	O
to	O
Mr	O
Bladen	O
to	O
cast	O
up	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
casting	O
up	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
Tigh	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
pulled	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Draught	O
upon	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
drew	O
it	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bank	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
it	O
;	O
Herbert	O
says	O
to	O
Goulder	O
,	O
(	O
Frogget	O
's	O
Attorney	O
,	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
design	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
over	O
hasty	O
in	O
making	O
out	O
your	O
Judgment	O
against	O
my	O
Client	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
take	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
should	O
make	O
out	O
an	O
Execution	O
,	O
or	O
bring	O
an	O
Action	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
King	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
Frogget	O
.	O
Goulder	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Sun-Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
two	O
half	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
at	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Frogget	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
taxed	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Tigh	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
Master	O
's	O
Chambers	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
Debt	O
and	O
Costs	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
suffered	O
the	O
Bill	O
to	O
be	O
taxed	O
;	O
Pob	O
,	O
poh	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
value	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
doing	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Release	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
Frogget	O
's	O
Name	O
to	O
the	O
Release	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand	O
Writting	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
Herbert	O
.	O
Was	O
Mr	O
Stokes	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Taxation	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Master	O
.	O
Burnford	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
staid	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
whole	O
Taxation	O
.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
Tigh	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
cautious	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
People	O
are	O
trying	O
for	O
their	O
Lives	O
;	O
you	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Tigh	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Release	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Burnford	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
Tigh	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Voice	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
such	O
Discourse	O
pass	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
granted	O
to	O
be	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
standing	O
together	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Phillips	O
.	O
Burnford	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Burnford	O
.	O
In	O
Half	O
Moon-Court	O
,	O
on	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
for	O
a	O
Livelihood	O
?	O
-	O
Burnford	O
.	O
I	O
officiate	O
as	O
Clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Character	O
never	O
was	O
impeached	O
on	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Tigh	O
.	O
He	O
swears	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Master	O
's	O
Office	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Attorney	O
says	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
but	O
Mr	O
Goulder	O
,	O
and	O
Herbert	O
;	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
find	O
Money	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Burnford	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Oath	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
one	O
Shilling	O
towards	O
the	O
carrying	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Tigh	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
lent	O
Mr	O
Goulder	O
Money	O
.	O
Burnford	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
Mr	O
Goulder	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
Master	O
for	O
Mr	O
Frogget	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
Office	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Taxation	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mr	O
Frogget	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mr	O
Burnford	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
,	O
Mr	O
Stokes	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Herbert	O
attended	O
:	O
We	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
Master	O
's	O
Office	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Tigh	O
,	O
Herbert	O
,	O
Frogget	O
,	O
Burnford	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Bladen	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
King	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
White	O
Fryers	O
,	O
to	O
cast	O
up	O
the	O
Deductions	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Master	O
off	O
the	O
Bill	O
.	O
I	O
cast	O
the	O
Bill	O
up	O
first	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
to	O
Mr	O
Bladen	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Figures	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
cast	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
Mr	O
Bladen	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Costs	O
stood	O
on	O
this	O
Deduction	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
24l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
that	O
Evening	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Alligation	O
signed	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
-	O
Stokes	O
staid	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
at	O
the	O
Office	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
King	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
-	O
Stokes	O
said	O
to	O
Herbert	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
leave	O
the	O
Taxation	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
Concern	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
What	O
passed	O
at	O
King	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
?	O
Goulder	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Costs	O
were	O
cast	O
up	O
,	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
Draught	O
on	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
drew	O
that	O
Draught	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bank	O
refused	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
20l	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
disappointed	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Costs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
Mr	O
Herbert	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Time	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr	O
Frogget	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
Law	O
would	O
allow	O
him	O
.	O
Herbert	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
for	O
your	O
Client	O
's	O
Interest	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Days	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Walks	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Herbert	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
sue	O
out	O
an	O
Execution	O
,	O
or	O
bring	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
Debt	O
upon	O
the	O
Judgment	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
parted	O
:	O
Tigh	O
,	O
Herbert	O
and	O
Bladen	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Temple	O
Hall	O
;	O
Frogget	O
,	O
Burnford	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
went	O
directly	O
up	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
Walks	O
,	O
through	O
Mitre-Court	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Sun-Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
drank	O
two	O
Half-pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
King	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Mr	O
Frogget	O
looked	O
on	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Talk	O
of	O
a	O
Release	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
impossible	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
pull	O
out	O
a	O
Release	O
,	O
when	O
so	O
many	O
People	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
without	O
somebody	O
's	O
seeing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
?	O
Goulder	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mr	O
Stokes	O
,	O
who	O
wished	O
me	O
Joy	O
of	O
my	O
Client	O
's	O
having	O
received	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
surprised	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
wonder	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
a	O
General	O
Release	B-pers
.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
Frogget	O
,	O
Burnford	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Master	O
's	O
Office	O
by	O
Appointment	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
whether	O
Tigh	O
was	O
there	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Herbert	O
,	O
that	O
Stokes	O
said	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
General	O
Release	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Herbert	O
declared	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
yet	O
this	O
Release	O
is	O
all	O
filled	O
up	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
very	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
is	O
filled	O
up	O
by	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Discourse	O
with	O
Tigh	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
avoided	O
their	O
Company	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
when	O
the	O
Release	O
was	O
first	O
produced	O
?	O
Goulder	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
-	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
produced	O
it	O
:	O
My	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
Release	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
handed	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
the	O
Court	O
said	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
Tigh	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
leave	O
the	O
Release	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
shew	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Herbert	O
in	O
Court	O
confessed	O
his	O
drawing	O
the	O
Release	O
.	O
Herbert	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
cast	O
up	O
at	O
King	O
's	O
Coffe-House	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
to	O
Mr	O
Bladen	O
to	O
examine	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
take	O
20	O
Shillings	O
off	O
that	O
was	O
miscast	O
?	O
Goulder	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
Mr	O
Bladen	O
's	O
casting	O
up	O
agreed	O
with	O
ours	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
called	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr	O
Herbert	O
's	O
Hand	O
writing	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
looked	O
the	O
General	O
Release	B-pers
all	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
all	O
the	O
Filling	O
up	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
his	O
Hand-writing	O
:	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
Word	O
Thirteenth	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Hand-writing	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Turn	O
of	O
the	O
T.	O
[	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
was	O
then	O
called	O
to	O
come	O
forth	O
and	O
give	O
Evidence	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
served	O
with	O
a	O
Subpoena	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
Oct.	O
20th	O
)	O
to	O
one	O
Abel	B-pers
Cooks	I-pers
in	O
St	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
cast	O
in	O
a	O
Law	O
Suit	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
in	O
Execution	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
one	O
Shearsmith	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
dead	O
at	O
Norwich	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
somebody	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
into	O
Court	O
to	O
justify	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
very	O
much	O
amiss	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
ask	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Costs	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
bad	O
Way	O
of	O
proceeding	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
Felony	O
without	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Advice	O
.	O
Mr	O
Goulder	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
abundance	O
of	O
Letters	O
from	O
Frogget	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
this	O
(	O
his	O
Name	O
to	O
the	O
General	O
Release	B-pers
)	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Hand-writing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tigh	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Forgery	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
one	O
Shearsmith	O
,	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Judgment	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Forgery	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Suit	O
in	O
the	O
Crown	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
on	O
Frogget	O
's	O
Account	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Frogget	O
sign	O
this	O
General	O
Release	B-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
General	O
Release	B-pers
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
publish	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
no	O
ways	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Forgery	O
:	O
It	O
appears	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
published	O
by	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
conjunction	O
with	O
Mr	O
Stokes	O
.	O
And	O
if	O
this	O
can	O
be	O
alledged	O
against	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
criminal	O
Fact	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
no	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
can	O
be	O
safe	O
in	O
what	O
they	O
do	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
filling	O
up	O
a	O
Deed	O
should	O
subject	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
criminal	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
I	O
recommend	O
this	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Consideration	O
,	O
and	O
submit	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Davenport	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
'till	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
from	O
Gravesend	O
to	O
Chatham	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
Mrs	O
Green	O
in	O
Golden-Square	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Christ	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
a	O
Nurse-keeping	O
and	O
ironing	O
)	O
And	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
White-Fryers	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
Boat	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
ne'er	O
a	O
Boat	O
ready	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
for	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
(	O
Tigh	O
)	O
paying	O
down	O
some	O
Money	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
whom	O
they	O
called	O
Shearsmith	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
follow	O
Frogmill	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
him	O
this	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
Law	O
will	O
ruin	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
Man	O
go	O
out	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
my	O
Wine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Name	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
?	O
Davenport	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
justly	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
of	O
-	O
Frog	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
take	O
up	O
23	O
Guineas	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Name	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
something	O
of	O
Smith	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Shearsmith	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
more	O
Notice	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
;	O
-	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
my	O
Gill	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
were	O
acquainted	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
give	O
Evidence	O
?	O
Davenport	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Davenport	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
Whether	O
I	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
Forgery	O
?	O
And	O
hearing	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
remember	O
a	O
Coachman	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
Gravesend	O
to	O
Chatham	O
with	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
was	O
Tigh	O
.	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
;	O
she	O
takes	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
-	O
then	O
I	O
remembered	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pay	O
a	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Subpoena	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
Was	O
it	O
Summer	O
or	O
Winter	O
?	O
Davenport	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
since	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
Month	O
-	O
or	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
-	O
About	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Green	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
pay	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
carry	O
you	O
to	O
Chatham	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mrs	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
telling	O
me	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
do	O
you	O
what	O
Service	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
begged	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
speak	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Davenport	O
.	O
Our	O
Acquaintance	O
was	O
so	O
slender	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hulbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
at	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
Goat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
that	O
Man	O
Phillips	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Jacobs	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
Table	O
;	O
and	O
Jacobs	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
soon	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
over-against	O
the	O
Fire-place	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
come	O
in	O
:	O
Said	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Mr	O
Frogget	O
.	O
why	O
want	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
Mr	O
Tigh	O
has	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
?	O
Said	O
Frogget	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
now	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
pay	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
