TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
WEDNESDAY	O
June	O
29	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
June	O
30	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
17th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
,	O
1743	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIMOTT	I-pers
,	O
Efq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
ABNEY	O
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Plucknet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gigner	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Amy	B-pers
.	I-pers
Garnault	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Peraro	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cottenbelt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Cranston	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Mallory	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dechamps	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Morran	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Rawlings	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Stovell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrop	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boozshire	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Tredgold	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sandwich	I-pers
.	O
283.	O
Judith	B-pers
Arman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Smoothing-Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
,	O
(	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
)	O
May	O
12	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
she	O
stole	O
these	O
Things	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
accidentally	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
on	O
Whitson-Monday	O
,	O
(	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Days	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
)	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
base	O
Jade	O
as	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Key	O
too	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
for	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Rachael	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
two	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
12	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
these	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
pawned	O
Things	O
frequently	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
284.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Clasp	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
Clock-Maker	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
almost	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
one	O
Morning	O
about	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Clasp	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoons	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
4	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
:	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Clasp	O
for	O
2	O
s	O
-	O
He	O
behaved	O
but	O
very	O
indifferently	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
fourth	O
Time	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
for	O
Fear	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
suddled	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
suddled	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
-	O
Painter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Clasp	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
or	O
some	O
body	O
else	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
or	O
his	O
Confederate	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
285.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St	B-place
Ann	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
ripping	O
,	O
taking	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
(	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1731	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1743	O
,	O
)	O
300	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
belonging	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Seddon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Seddon	I-pers
,	O
their	O
Property	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sarsfield	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
Fellows	O
were	O
taking	O
the	O
Lead	O
off	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Samuel	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Seddon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Soho	B-place
Square	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Storer	O
and	O
Bishop	O
concealed	O
between	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
and	O
the	O
Roof	O
:	O
This	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Lock	O
lay	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
Knife	O
,	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Instrument	O
to	O
unscrew	O
the	O
Nuts	O
of	O
a	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Biudgeon	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
-	O
the	O
Fish	O
and	O
Bell	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles-Street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
-	O
the	O
Salmon	O
and	O
Bell	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
-	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Trap-Door	O
into	O
the	O
Gutter	O
;	O
pulled	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Tiles	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
cut	O
the	O
Lead	O
of	O
the	O
Gutter	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
as	O
much	O
Lead	O
off	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Jeddery	O
for	O
three	O
Farthings	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
gave	O
more	O
-	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
Lead	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Dunghill	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
Day-light	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
we	O
went	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Area	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
a	O
Watchman	O
heard	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
Watchman	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
ourselves	O
over	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
us	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
Lead	O
away	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
only	O
took	O
the	O
Lock	O
off	O
the	O
Door	O
-	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
Way	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Concern	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
Constable	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
Watch	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
and	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
very	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
broke	O
out	O
and	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
considerable	O
Charge	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
another	O
Time	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Bishop	O
in	O
Milford	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
3	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
Area	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
2	O
Fellows	O
a	O
peeping	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
whipt	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
Sarsfield	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Hole	O
between	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
and	O
the	O
Roof	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
This	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lead	O
and	O
this	O
Bludgeon	O
lay	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
fast	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Bishop	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
suddled	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Area	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
threw	O
his	O
down	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
only	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Charge	O
.	O
Bishop	O
.	O
This	O
Knife	O
,	O
File	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
call	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
286.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
600	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
val	O
6	O
l.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
noble	O
John	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
And	O
287.	O
David	B-pers
Luellin	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
Mr	O
Willoughby	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Plumber	O
's	O
Bill	O
,	O
8	O
Hund	O
.	O
3	O
qu	O
.	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
stole	O
from	O
a	O
House	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
,	O
in	O
Great-Russel-Street	B-place
;	O
700	O
Weight	O
was	O
lost	O
about	O
Christmas	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
Lead	O
off	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
January	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
Quantity	O
was	O
about	O
200	O
Weight	O
,	O
in	O
May	O
,	O
off	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
Mr	O
Willoughty	O
means	O
:	O
We	O
took	O
it	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Jeddery	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Church	O
;	O
Luellin	O
bought	O
the	O
first	O
Parcel	O
about	O
Christmas	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
Storer	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
his	O
Cellar-Window	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
Light	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
weighed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
3	O
Farthings	O
per	O
Pound	O
.	O
Luellin	O
.	O
You	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
some	O
Lead	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
believed	O
you	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Bishop	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
Luellin	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
none	O
at	O
3	O
Farthings	O
per	O
Pound	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Penny	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Storer	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
the	O
Man	O
any	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
288.	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
val	O
16	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Property	O
,	O
January	O
1	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
about	O
200	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Closet	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
King-Street	B-place
,	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Williams	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
Hamilton	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
King's-Street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
as	O
much	O
Lead	O
as	O
we	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Widow-Woman	O
in	O
Parker's-Lane	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
-	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Plumber	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Colonel	O
Deveil	B-pers
the	O
first	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
no	O
farther	O
Trouble	O
,	O
I	O
own	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
this	O
Time	O
2	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
darkened	O
the	O
Doors	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
289	O
,	O
290	O
,	O
291.	O
George	B-pers
Treacle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
belonging	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
January	O
21	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Treacle	I-pers
is	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
:	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
House	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Hosier	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenhill	O
;	O
Treacle	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
Chissel	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sink	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Saw	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Sink	O
and	O
the	O
Cistern	O
to	O
Pieces	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
one	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
another	O
to	O
a	O
Plumber	O
's	O
in	O
Castle-Street	O
,	O
by	O
Brokers-Alley	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
it	O
there	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Hundred	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Parcel	O
something	O
above	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
we	O
parted	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
5	O
s.	O
or	O
within	O
a	O
Trifle	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Time	O
,	O
Treacle	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
leaden	O
Pipe	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Hamilton	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
about	O
a	O
Hundred	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
off	O
the	O
Balcony	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Greenhill	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Widow-Plumber	O
in	O
Parker's-Lane	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
divided	O
between	O
Hamilton	O
and	O
I.	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Storer	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenhill	O
,	O
broke	O
a	O
Hole	O
through	O
the	O
Roof	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Gutters	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
about	O
1	O
Hundred	O
and	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Lead	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Widow	O
Jeddery	O
in	O
Middle-Row	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
divided	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Storer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
vile	O
Rogue	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
as	O
that	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Rob	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Greenhill	O
's	O
Houses	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
to	O
the	O
Amount	O
of	O
two	O
Tons	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
set	O
down	O
but	O
one	O
Ton	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
There	O
are	O
three	O
Gutters	O
taken	O
off	O
three	O
Houses	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
off	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
Hosier-Lane	O
End	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wibb	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Servant	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Days	O
before	O
Whitsuntide	O
;	O
he	O
hurt	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Ginger-bread	O
Baker	O
in	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Waite	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
Hamilton	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Grocery	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
and	O
faithful	O
;	O
some	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
since	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
292.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cloth-Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gook	I-pers
,	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
James	O
Lake	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
and	O
Son-in-Law	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gook	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
10	O
Weeks	O
;	O
my	O
Father	O
had	O
missed	O
many	O
Things	O
before	O
.	O
One	O
Day	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
got	O
his	O
own	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
wore	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
threw	O
these	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
an	O
old	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckskin	O
Breeches	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
are	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
never	O
sold	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
Power	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
any	O
Thing	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
four	O
Shillings	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gook	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
both	O
the	O
Leather	O
and	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Gook	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
293.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Chaplin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
May	O
18	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Somering	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Porter	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Lovel	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Feraro	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
Bullinger	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
before	O
she	O
sent	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
erased	O
the	O
Crest	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
File	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
Promises	O
made	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Crest	O
is	O
filed	O
off	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
Spoons	O
lost	O
last	O
Winter	O
.	O
Penelope	B-pers
Bullinger	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
Spoon	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bullinger	O
brought	O
this	O
Spoon	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
only	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
because	O
the	O
Crest	O
was	O
erased	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
loth	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
at	O
last	O
own	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Family	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
compared	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
matched	O
;	O
this	O
Workman	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
verify	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
that	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Spoons	O
were	O
made	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gardiner	O
,	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
pressed	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
confess	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
with	O
my	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
Confession	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
no	O
more	O
man	O
that	O
one	O
.	O
Paine	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gardiner	O
did	O
say	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
an	O
ingenuous	O
Confession	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
all	O
the	O
Interest	O
he	O
could	O
for	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Lady	O
-	O
She	O
made	O
no	O
Confession	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Constab	O
le	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Crest	O
is	O
erased	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
five	O
Years	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
Lovel	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
Dr.	O
Feraro	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
File	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
to	O
file	O
the	O
Tongues	O
of	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooksey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Miles	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Great	O
Russel-Street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
frequently	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
were	O
Things	O
of	O
great	O
Value	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
never	O
missed	O
anything	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
ever	O
did	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coomer	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
294	O
,	O
295	O
,	O
296.	O
James	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburg	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Iron	O
Japan	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Merriton	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Merriton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
these	O
Boy	O
s	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
pretty	O
much	O
;	O
having	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
that	O
Sort	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
turn	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Maid	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Boys	O
were	O
lifting	O
up	O
the	O
Show-Glass	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
:	O
Rutt	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Show-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
Cordwell	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Boxes	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
Cordwell	O
immediately	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
by	O
the	O
Show-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Box	O
down	O
the	O
next	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Cellar-Window	O
-	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Boys	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Fright	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Boy	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Boxes	O
.	O
Cordwell	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
threatned	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
third	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Cordwell	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
when	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
the	O
white	O
Cap	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Show-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Mistress	O
that	O
the	O
Boys	O
were	O
lifting	O
up	O
the	O
Glass	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Boys	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Cordwell	O
had	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Gough	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs.	O
Merriton	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
Value	O
the	O
Box	O
at	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Merriton	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
value	O
it	O
but	O
at	O
6	O
d.	O
Gough	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
11	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
Rutt	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
into	O
13	O
.	O
Cordwell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Gough	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Cordwell	O
Guilty	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
Rutt	O
Guilty	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
297	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
Will	O
,	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ballet	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Ballard	O
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	O
Duck	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
last	O
January	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
between	O
e-Lane	O
and	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
thirty-five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
11.	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
Fol	O
.	O
47.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
who	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
Mary	B-pers
Ballet	I-pers
's	O
House	O
in	O
Thatched-Alley	B-place
in	O
Chick	B-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
showed	O
us	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
us	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
;	O
she	O
acted	O
then	O
as	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
by	O
Force	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Eleven	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
my	O
Pocket	O
inside	O
outward	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sensible	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
:	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
:	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
Knock	O
with	O
her	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Man	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
threatned	O
to	O
throw	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
me	O
down	O
Stairs	O
if	O
I	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
(	O
Yates	O
)	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
in	O
Safety	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
came	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
fitting	O
Alderman	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Constable	O
had	O
her	O
in	O
hold	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
off	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Quilt	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
-	O
there	O
were	O
Eleven	O
Shillings	O
-	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
he	O
searched	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
lying	O
up	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
tallied	O
with	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
to	O
Day	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
used	O
very	O
ill	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
came	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
shall	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
Intention	O
of	O
Lewdness	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
had	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
frightened	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
afraid	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Andrews	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
heard	O
Bess	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
ordered	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
298.	O
Philip	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Michael	I-place
in	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
1/2	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fessey	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fessey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Journeyman	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
2	O
1/2	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
pretended	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
in	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Intention	O
to	O
cheat	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
weighing	O
some	O
Filings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
part	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scale	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
aside	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
cheat	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
Opportunities	O
enough	O
.	O
Fessey	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
by	O
Trade	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
Silver	O
Filings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
weigh	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
weighed	O
right	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Examination	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
wanted	O
2	O
1/2	O
Ounces	O
of	O
weight	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
taxed	O
him	O
pretty	O
closely	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
carried	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
Excuse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
mislaid	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Mistrust	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
299	O
,	O
300.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
.	O
of	B-place
St	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
(	O
together	O
with	O
Judith	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Copperthwait	I-pers
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Copperthwait	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Sen'night	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
Judith	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Companion	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
Women	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
Home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
in	O
Black-Boy	B-place
Alley	I-place
by	O
Chick	B-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Apprehension	O
of	O
Danger	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Judith	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
was	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
some	O
Gin	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
taste	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
proper	O
Place	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
without	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Judith	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
discover	O
myself	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Martha	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
to	O
bring	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Present	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
wanted	O
Nothing	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
called	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
-	O
Ewers	O
and	O
Nash	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
seized	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
1/2	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
odd	O
Half-pence	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
my	O
Reckoning	O
before	O
)	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
boarded	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
me	O
too	O
fast	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Light	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
.	O
Bartlet	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
two	O
Guineas	O
to	O
Long	O
Charles	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
knows	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
Copperthwait	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
from	O
Long	O
Charles	O
.	O
Bartlet	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
Farthing	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
the	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Ewers	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
301.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hoden	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Hayden	B-pers
,	O
(	O
which	O
last	O
is	O
her	O
right	O
Name	O
)	O
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
1/2	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davey	I-pers
,	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Ram-Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
resolute	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Porter	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Thatched-Alley	O
,	O
or	O
Black-Boy-Alley	B-place
,	O
by	O
Chick-Lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
her	O
Sister	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
we	O
might	O
come	O
into	O
their	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
bring	O
Gin	O
for	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
love	O
Gin	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
little	O
small	O
Glass	O
of	O
Anniseed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
small	O
Quantity	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
Glass	O
herself	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
show	O
me	O
a	O
Trick	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
pushed	O
me	O
backward	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
below	O
Stairs	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
from	O
me	O
by	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Half-Crown	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Name	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Three-pence	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Keys	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
that	O
Half-Crown	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
another	O
Half-Crown	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
if	O
I	O
fetched	O
another	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
that	O
too	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
Keys	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
but	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
sooner	O
?	O
Davey	O
I	O
was	O
troubled	O
at	O
the	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afred	O
or	O
exposing	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
People	O
would	O
laugh	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
some	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
a	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
used	O
me	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
her	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
Justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Davey	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
Justice	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Davey	O
.	O
Several	O
People	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
offer	O
or	O
agree	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
upon	O
any	O
other	O
Account	O
,	O
than	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
ask	O
my	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threatned	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
302.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
two	O
Inch	O
Leaden	O
Pipe	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hiron	I-pers
.	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hiron	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
Leaden	O
Pipe	O
from	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
New-Ormond-Street	B-place
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Lead	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goslick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
at	O
the	O
Conduit	O
at	O
Snow-Hill	O
(	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
Lamb	O
's	O
Conduit	O
:	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
some	O
Lead	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Lead	O
from	O
Mr	O
Hiron	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
303	O
,	O
304	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ballet	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Ballard	B-pers
,	O
*	O
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flannigal	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
small	O
Silver	O
Cross	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ballet	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Ballard	O
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Vide	O
ante	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
297.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flannigal	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Holborn-Bridge	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Ballard	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Liquor	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
to	O
be	O
Gin	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
tasted	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
Two-pence	O
half-penny	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
another	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
says	O
Ballard	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
you	O
make	O
us	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
pushed	O
me	O
backward	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
rushes	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
my	O
Shoes	O
off	O
instantly	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Buckles	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
Buckles	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cross	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
Hand	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
that	O
down	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Date	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
used	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
vile	O
Manner	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Watchman	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
dead	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
held	O
it	O
out	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
longer	O
-	O
they	O
stopped	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
leaned	O
upon	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
strove	O
to	O
stifle	O
me	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
Murder	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
they	O
run	O
down	O
Stairs	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
Strength	O
to	O
keep	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Custody	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
any	O
nearer	O
she	O
would	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Ballard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Flannigal	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
was	O
one	O
that	O
assaulted	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
one	O
concerned	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Things	O
from	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Watchman	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
.	O
she	O
hid	O
herself	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
turn-up	O
Bed	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Room	O
-	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
Things	O
I	O
will	O
let	O
you	O
go	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
made	O
Answer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Constable	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
very	O
likely	O
she	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
she	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Watchman	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
hid	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
delivered	O
the	O
Things	O
into	O
your	O
Possession	O
?	O
Flannigal	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
has	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
Constable	O
or	O
a	O
Watchman	O
that	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
back	O
?	O
Flannigal	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
has	O
kept	O
them	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
there	O
?	O
Flannigal	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
Person	O
that	O
stopped	O
my	O
Breath	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
astonished	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Senses	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
upon	O
my	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
my	O
Breath	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
fearce	O
breathe	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
Harris	O
did	O
it	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Person	O
that	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
upon	O
my	O
Breast	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Harris	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
charged	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
first	O
;	O
was	O
there	O
not	O
some-body	O
else	O
discharged	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Flannigal	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
secured	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
but	O
me	O
.	O
Flannigal	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
but	O
these	O
two	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Remainder	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
run	O
over	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
?	O
Flannigal	O
.	O
Harris	O
hid	O
herself	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
Hole	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
Coal-hole	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
pulled	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
others	O
went	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Thatched-Alley	B-place
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
beat	O
pretty	O
hard	O
with	O
my	O
Staff	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Way	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
the	O
Bolt	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
Stairs-Feet	O
,	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
Back	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
burst	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
presently	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
got	O
away	O
over	O
the	O
Houses	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
this	O
lower	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Ballard	O
behind	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Harris	O
lay	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
his	O
Breath	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
and	O
Ballard	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
such	O
Things	O
lost	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
this	O
lower	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Bedstead	O
was	O
turned	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
stood	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
the	O
Bedstead	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
Buckles	O
and	O
the	O
Cross	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Consta	O
ble	O
's	O
Hands	O
;	O
Ballard	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Buckles	O
were	O
found	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
find	O
that	O
my	O
Apron	O
was	O
bloody	O
?	O
Price	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
said	O
your	O
Husband	O
had	O
been	O
beating	O
you	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bothomly	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
or	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
crying	O
out	O
of	O
Murder	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Watchmen	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
believed	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
Harris	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
Ballard	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
below	O
Stairs	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
Ballard	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Things	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
three	O
Watchmen	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Ballard	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Bothomly	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
what	O
Occasion	O
had	O
she	O
to	O
hide	O
herself	O
.	O
Ballard	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Watchmen	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
pulled	O
the	O
Bedstead	O
down	O
the	O
Bed	O
tumbled	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
lay	O
-	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
they	O
are	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
Gore-Blood	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Closet	O
to	O
hide	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
Ballard	O
said	O
,	O
stay	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shall	O
not	O
hurt	O
you	O
.	O
Ballard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Sweat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
myself	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
-	O
though	O
the	O
Bed	O
turns	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
room	O
for	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
lie	O
behind	O
it	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
lived	O
with	O
me	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Months	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
behaved	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Thought	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Harris	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Baby	O
;	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
Parents	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
just	O
honest	O
People	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
;	O
I	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Alley	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
call	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
was	O
beating	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
Ballard	O
was	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
some	O
Years	O
(	O
about	O
7	O
Years	O
ago	O
)	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
Wrong	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Ballard	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Harris	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
305.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
of	B-place
St	I-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
unfinished	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
This	I-pers
is	O
my	O
Gown	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
came	O
and	O
tole	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
Cloak	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs	O
Cope	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Reason	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
Reason	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
her	O
in	O
Great	O
Russel	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
trifling	O
Excuse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
me	O
any	O
Damage	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
Recompence	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
this	O
Gown	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
This	O
is	O
Mrs	O
Deane	O
's	O
Gown	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
to	O
alter	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Dresser	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Gown	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
would	O
come	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
done	O
out	O
of	O
Spight	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
another	O
Nation	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
306	O
.	O
+	O
Daniel	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Feathers-Tavern	B-place
,	O
over-against	O
St	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
half	O
way	O
down	O
the	O
Tavern-Passage	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
Twitch	O
at	O
my	O
Right-Hand	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
immediately	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Fellow	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
Strand	O
into	O
St	O
Clements	O
Church	O
yard	O
.	O
and	O
raised	O
a	O
Cry	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
turning	O
the	O
West	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
but	O
others	O
continued	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
crossed	O
St	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
within	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Feathers-Tavern	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
exactly	O
like	O
the	O
Man	O
by	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
from	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
Cloath	O
on	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
Night	O
about	O
9.	O
or	O
a	O
after	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
two	O
Friends	O
at	O
the	O
Feathers	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Larder	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Larder	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
half	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
before	O
that	O
Fellow	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
very	O
high	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
down	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
with	O
an	O
A	O
in	O
Black-Ink	O
at	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
stand	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
a	O
Fart	O
for	O
any	O
Body	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
saucy	O
before	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
Rose-Tavern	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Feathers-Tavern	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
last	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
something	O
after	O
9	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
by	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Feathers-Tavern	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
Feathers-Tavern	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
of	O
myself	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
Soul	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Harbin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
my	O
Coach	O
at	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
round	O
between	O
the	O
Pole	O
of	O
my	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Roberts	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
ble	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
Mr	O
Roberts	O
stopped	O
him	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
behind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Harbin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
should	O
he	O
be	O
caught	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Feathers-Tavern	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
unlikely	O
I	O
should	O
run	O
Mile	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bring	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
307.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Ann	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
two	O
Dimity	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
2	O
Bodies	O
of	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Lawn	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
*	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bureau	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
lay	O
asleep	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
the	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
*	O
Mrs	O
Marsh	O
is	O
called	O
Spinster	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Widow	O
;	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
single	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
Spinster	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
Servant	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
Company	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Gown	O
on	O
Purpose	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
This	O
was	O
denied	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
]	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Halls	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
Body	O
of	O
a	O
Shift	O
into	O
pawn	O
the	O
27th	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
14	O
Years	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
pretended	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
belonged	O
to	O
Plays	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
Singing	O
,	O
and	O
Dancing	O
upon	O
the	O
Ropes	O
,	O
and	O
dresses	O
sometimes	O
in	O
Mens	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
High-Holbourn	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
Gown	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
for	O
something	O
that	O
fitted	O
her	O
better	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
try	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
without	O
buying	O
it	O
outright	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
another	O
Gown	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
to	O
boot	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d	O
for	O
this	O
Apron	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
Dutch	O
Woman	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Marsh	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
carrying	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
my	O
Lodging	O
and	O
Board	O
;	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Company	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
308	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Maccartney	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
old	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
June	O
24	O
Evan	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
at	O
Mrs	O
East	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
East	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
about	O
six	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Williams	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Palm	I-pers
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Knee	O
,	O
asked	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
309	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cask	O
with	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Rum	O
Shrub	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
James	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
Bar	O
after	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Casks	O
under	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
some	O
Assistance	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	O
Christian	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
my	O
Mistress	O
scream	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
stunn	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
rob	O
them	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
my	O
knocking	O
her	O
or	O
her	O
Maid	O
down	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
310	O
,	O
311	O
,	O
Griffith	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
.	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Callico	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
;	O
one	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Callico	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Callico	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Malkin	I-pers
.	O
June	O
7.	O
Mary	B-pers
Malkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Woods-Close	B-place
,	O
and	O
take	O
in	O
Washing	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Things	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Griffith	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Marvin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs	O
Malkin	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
(	O
Merrick	O
)	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
hindermost	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
white	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
like	O
Linnen	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
kept	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Eyes	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
;	O
and	O
Merrick	O
threw	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lap	O
into	O
the	O
Channel	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
Davis	O
in	O
my	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Causeway	O
he	O
threw	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lap	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
me	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
push	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
belonging	O
to	O
Spencer	O
's	O
Breakfasting-House	O
;	O
that	O
Man	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
:	O
we	O
then	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
Merrick	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
know	O
.	O
Merrick	O
.	O
Ask	O
what	O
Cloaths	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
then	O
.	O
Marvin	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
grey	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
Apron	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Cloaths	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
Apron	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Merrick	O
throw	O
some	O
Linnen	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
behind	O
the	O
Turnpike-House	O
;	O
and	O
Wakely	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wakely	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Collector	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
blue	O
Aprons	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Poulterers	O
;	O
and	O
Merrick	O
threw	O
the	O
Linnen	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs	O
Malkin	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Bundle	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Dear	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
collar	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Davis	O
running	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
Linnen	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
William	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Theif	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs	O
Malkin	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
run	O
;	O
and	O
Mr	O
Marvin	O
pursued	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Linnen	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
Merrick	O
run	O
into	O
my	O
Lord	O
Cobham	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Linnen	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
Mr	O
Marvin	O
and	O
Davis	O
up	O
to	O
Sadlers	O
Wells	O
;	O
Marvin	O
and	O
Flowers	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
throw	O
away	O
the	O
Linnen	O
:	O
Davis	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
loth	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
Mr	O
Marvin	O
cried	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
pursuing	O
Davis	O
;	O
and	O
Davis	O
cried	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Do	O
not	O
stop	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
running	O
after	O
two	O
Boys	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
pushed	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Stall	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
push	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Davis	O
running	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
some	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Apron	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
;	O
when	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
Mr	O
Marvin	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
no	O
Body	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Causeway	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Dog	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
stopping	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
no	O
Harm	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Linnen	O
that	O
Davis	O
threw	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
Flowers	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
took	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Ass	O
Field	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Davis	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
2	O
Boys	O
who	O
had	O
thrown	O
down	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Stall	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
nothing	O
amiss	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
stop	O
me	O
for	O
then	O
?	O
the	O
rest	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Merrick	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
2	O
Men	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
robbed	O
somebody	O
of	O
some	O
Linnen	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
only	O
running	O
after	O
2	O
Boys	O
who	O
had	O
thrown	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Stall	O
down	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
live	O
at	O
Brentford	O
Richard	O
Hippesley	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
Old	O
Brentford	O
:	O
Merrick	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Weeks	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
have	O
left	O
me	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
stay	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
has	O
some	O
Relations	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
for	O
me	O
sometimes	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Months	O
.	O
Hippesley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Boy	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
Weeks	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Parkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
Day	O
after	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
trusted	O
with	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Plate	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
wronged	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
carry	O
Coals	O
for	O
the	O
Prince	O
,	O
and	O
stack	O
his	O
Wood	O
:	O
There	O
has	O
been	O
Plate	O
lay	O
about	O
in	O
Plenty	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
touched	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fetherston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Davis	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
;	O
-	O
he	O
made	O
Pies	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
.	O
Never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
312.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Glass	O
Salts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
Glass	O
Cruit	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
And	O
313.	O
Ann	B-pers
Boone	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Haynes	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
May	O
28	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Brone	O
's	O
is	O
a	O
noted	O
House	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Good	O
,	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
always	O
carried	O
their	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
that	O
Burk	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lent	O
him	O
3	O
d	O
upon	O
them	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
me	O
?	O
Gardiner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bonne	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
4	O
Salts	O
and	O
a	O
Cruit	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lent	O
the	O
Boy	O
3	O
d	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
she	O
returned	O
me	O
the	O
Salts	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
not	O
be	O
harmed	O
if	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
Truth	O
;	O
he	O
showed	O
me	O
the	O
Shop	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
us	O
along	O
to	O
Boone	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Salts	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
returned	O
upon	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
3	O
d.	O
which	O
she	O
lent	O
the	O
Boy	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Boone	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
3	O
d	O
for	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
3	O
Pence	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
them	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
leave	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
3	O
Pence	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
twice	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Boone	O
these	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
her	O
-	O
She	O
takes	O
in	O
Quilting	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Boone	O
these	O
29	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
doing	O
a	O
bad	O
Action	O
-	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
Yorkshire	O
Woman	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Scotsman	O
.	O
Ann	O
Young	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Joel	B-pers
Whiteford	I-pers
,	O
Philippa	B-pers
Whiteford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
have	O
known	O
her	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Burk	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Boone	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
314	O
.	O
+	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pybee	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ias	O
Hayfield	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
Matthias	B-pers
Hayfield	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
12	O
Yards	O
through	O
Newgate	B-place
I	O
missed	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Minutes	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
just	O
at	O
my	O
Elbow	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
coarse	O
Cloth	O
Apron	O
on	O
,	O
rolled	O
up	O
over	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
hold	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
under	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
directly	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
asted	O
if	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
Magistrate	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
recommend	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Owen	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
beadles	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Constable	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
last	O
Monday	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
:	O
The	O
Constable	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
attending	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Necessity	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
Bread	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
excuted	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Way	O
of	O
getting	O
his	O
Bread	O
;	O
I	O
resolved	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
common	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Hayfield	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
but	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
you	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
315	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Macklean	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Macklearan	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ferne	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ferne	I-pers
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
up	O
into	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
New-Market	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Holbourn-Bridge	B-place
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Minute	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
sure	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
between	O
15	O
and	O
16	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
316.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
val	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Clasps	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
val	O
2	O
d.	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chissel	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
3	O
Shirts	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Canvas	O
Trowsers	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Hose	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Boy	O
's	O
Hat	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
and	O
Wallet	O
val	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Turnkey	O
of	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
Gate	O
with	O
this	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
I	O
find	O
that	O
he	O
apprehended	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
a	O
Mob	O
pursuing	O
him	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
told	O
me	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Lodge	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Goal	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
presently	O
,	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
a	O
Vessel	O
down	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Man	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Vessel	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
me	O
who	O
knew	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Outside	O
of	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
serve	O
him	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
sooner	O
than	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
lose	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
poor	O
distressed	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Boy	O
's	O
coming	O
after	O
some	O
loose	O
Boys	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
farther	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
than	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
under	O
Consinement	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
this	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Mob	O
at	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
imagined	O
were	O
coming	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Turnkey	O
's	O
Habitation	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Boy	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Person	O
likely	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
Things	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
this	O
Parcel	O
belongs	O
to	O
a	O
poor	O
Miller	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
of	O
Money	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
raise	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
must	O
be	O
lost	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
bid	O
me	O
bring	O
the	O
Things	O
into	O
the	O
Lodge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Things	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
?	O
Kingston	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
loose	O
Boy	O
that	O
comes	O
after	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
surprised	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Lodge	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
Mr	O
Cox	O
it	O
was	O
proper	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Things	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
too	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
could	O
come	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Time	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
away	O
clandeslinely	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
one	O
Mast	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Boat	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Under-Turnkey	O
,	O
my	O
Business	O
is	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Rats	O
and	O
Mice	O
.	O
Cox	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Carrier	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
with	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
help	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
gather	O
up	O
some	O
Wheat	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
burst	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
's	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Mistrust	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
Thief	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Son	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
Mr	O
Lingard	O
,	O
in	O
Mint	O
street	O
,	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Son	O
was	O
gone	O
with	O
Arthur	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Percival	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
my	O
Boy	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Casey	O
delivered	O
the	O
Wallet	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Age	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Crime	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
Corporal	O
Punishment	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
immediately	O
.	O
317.	O
John	B-pers
Hendrick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Botolph-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Mascal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
some	O
Ship	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
left	O
his	O
Ship	O
ever	O
since	O
Christmas	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
follows	O
Thieving	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
:	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
pitied	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
licked	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
this	O
Time	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
about	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
stuffed	O
into	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
318.	O
John	B-pers
Kirkbridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Christopher	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustian	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Sale-Shop	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
Mr	O
Hall	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Hall	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
9	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Beer-house	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Eleven	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
6	O
Months	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
and	O
Sheers	O
,	O
in	O
Giles	B-pers
How	I-pers
's	O
Possession	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Giles	B-pers
How	I-pers
is	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
How	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
his	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
319.	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Yates	B-pers
,	O
other	B-pers
wise	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le-bon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Cotton	O
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
one	O
blue	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
Stuff	O
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
white	O
Tabby	O
Stays	O
,	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Stockings	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shift	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
,	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
one	O
Cannister	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
6	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
June	O
22	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
my	O
Apartment	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford	B-place
Market	I-place
)	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
a	O
Bill	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
empty	O
Parlours	O
below	O
Stairs	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
reading	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
wants	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
Body	O
there	O
to	O
an	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
consider	O
able	O
Time	O
(	O
the	O
House	O
is	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
Tenement	O
,	O
it	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr	O
Thredgold	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
)	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Does	O
not	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
stay	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
my	O
Friend	O
said	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
may	O
be	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Lane	O
of	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Mistress	O
,	O
or	O
Madam	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ever	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
her	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
,	O
with	O
both	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
hold	O
her	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Apartment	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
no	O
Harm	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
my	O
empty	O
Entry	O
,	O
therefore	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
Harm	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
he	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
bundling	O
up	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Matter	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Goods	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
see	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
one	O
Hand	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Thing	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Gowns	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
produced	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
which	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
Wheeler	O
)	O
the	O
next	O
Thing	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Knee-Buckle	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Fellow	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
Shoe	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
now	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
farther	O
doubt	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
held	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
:	O
she	O
desired	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Publican	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
return	O
me	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
I	O
own	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
any	O
Body	O
-	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
expose	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
your	O
Goods	O
and	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
she	O
only	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
Money	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Silver	O
among	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
other	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
withdraw	O
from	O
the	O
Folk	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Apartment	O
again	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
thinking	O
she	O
would	O
return	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
believing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
large	O
Sum	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Mob	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
the	O
Silver	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Money	O
)	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
People	O
I	O
had	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
hold	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
me	O
from	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Entry	O
;	O
I	O
pushed	O
her	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Thief	O
might	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
other	O
Money	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
spent	O
my	O
Money	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
delivered	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Reason	O
of	O
my	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
secured	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
kept	O
her	O
long	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
Assistance	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Door	O
might	O
be	O
shut	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Mob	O
from	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
tie	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
Money	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
four	O
Shillings	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
Money	O
than	O
this	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
Shillings	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
pulled	O
out	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
six	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
begged	O
and	O
prayed	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
:	O
have	O
Leave	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
safe	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
;	O
one	O
Thing	O
I	O
forgot	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
first	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
her	O
throw	O
down	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
that	O
Key	O
opened	O
my	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Key	O
locked	O
and	O
unlocked	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Drawers	O
swept	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
8	O
Keys	O
more	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Street-Door	O
Key	O
,	O
Keys	O
for	O
Chamber-Doors	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Keys	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Council	O
to	O
plead	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
disappointed	O
*	O
in	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Milliner's-Shop	O
in	O
Convent	O
Garden	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Smith	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
my	O
Name	O
is	O
unhappily	O
Yates	O
or	O
Holmes	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Law	O
allows	O
not	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
Counsel	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
on	O
any	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
yet	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
many	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
never	O
the	O
worse	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
did	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
very	O
strange	O
,	O
to	O
allow	O
a	O
Man	O
this	O
Assistance	O
,	O
in	O
Defence	O
of	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
and	O
deny	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Life	O
lies	O
at	O
Stake	O
.	O
See	O
Preface	O
to	O
the	O
Collection	O
of	O
State	O
Trials	O
,	O
6	O
Vol	O
.	O
Fol	O
.	O
and	O
Whitelocke	O
's	O
Memorials	O
,	O
p.	O
433	O
.	O
*	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
called	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Smith	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
Bundle	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
Appearance	O
of	O
a	O
Bundle	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Market	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
call	O
Mr	O
Norman	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mrs	O
Wheeler	O
have	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
