TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
December	O
7	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
8	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
9	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
12	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
17th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Robert	B-pers
Westley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
1	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.Cooper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1743	O
,	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WESTLEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Charters	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Veck	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wacklett	I-pers
,	O
Parmenias	O
Moore	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hallifax	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Forwood	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Shuttleworth	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stepleton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Mourgue	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Bladwell	B-pers
Peyton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Sellers	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Skylight	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Segalas	I-pers
,	O
November	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
right	O
Name	O
is	O
Scarlett	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
72	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Segalas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Gunsmith	O
in	O
Green-street	B-place
by	O
Leicester	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
one	O
Day	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
telling	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Fortune	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
)	O
she	O
told	O
my	O
Wife	O
she	O
had	O
good	O
Fortune	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
very	O
lucky	O
in	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Planet	O
was	O
at	O
hand	O
(	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
Words	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Treasure	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
a	O
deceased	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soul	O
of	O
that	O
Person	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
Rest	O
till	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
160	O
or	O
260	O
Guineas	O
besides	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Silver	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Closet	O
and	O
over-heard	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
)	O
she	O
asked	O
my	O
Wife	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
lend	O
her	O
20	O
s.	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
20	O
s.	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
20	O
s	O
?	O
My	O
Wife	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Diamond	O
Ear-Rings	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
20	O
s.	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
:	O
My	O
Wife	O
gave	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
Salt	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrapped	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
with	O
the	O
Salt	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
staid	O
it	O
would	O
spoil	O
the	O
Thing	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
good	O
Fortune	O
and	O
not	O
mine	O
;	O
for	O
by	O
Virtue	O
of	O
this	O
the	O
Stones	O
were	O
to	O
rise	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Treasure	O
would	O
appear	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
by	O
themselves	O
:	O
My	O
Wife	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
steal	O
her	O
Ear-Rings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
troubled	O
with	O
an	O
evil	O
Sprit	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Faith	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
seemed	O
mistrustful	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
mistrustful	O
the	O
Planet	O
would	O
be	O
spoiled	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
slip	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
changed	O
the	O
Packet	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Paper	O
instead	O
of	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Ear-Rings	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
Buttons	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
struggling	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
dropped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
found	O
between	O
her	O
Finger	O
and	O
Thumb	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Salt	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
Paper	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
a	O
false	O
Thing	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Segalas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
facing	O
our	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
Quarrel	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
Madam	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
old	O
Clothes	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
no	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
lucky	O
Planet	O
in	O
your	O
Face	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
your	O
Fortune	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
Coffee	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Law	O
Suit	O
depending	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
must	O
make	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
come	O
another	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
say	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
Holy	O
Ghost	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
proposed	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Paper	O
that	O
was	O
never	O
wrote	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
her	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
divided	O
it	O
into	O
three	O
Parts	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
Salt	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
some	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
Virtue	O
of	O
that	O
Salt	O
the	O
Mould	O
was	O
to	O
rise	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
Guineas	O
she	O
mentioned	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
besides	O
broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
Silver	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
20s	O
.	O
that	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
against	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
me	O
make	O
that	O
Bargain	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
20	O
s.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-Rings	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
cost	O
me	O
3	O
Guineas	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Almighty	O
God	O
,	O
Father	O
,	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
Holy	O
Ghost	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
this	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
Almighty	O
prosper	O
what	O
we	O
are	O
a	O
going	O
upon	O
:	O
Then	O
she	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
say	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Prayer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
fall	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
Knees	O
and	O
say	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Prayer	O
three	O
Times	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Virtue	O
of	O
this	O
the	O
Mould	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
was	O
to	O
rise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
the	O
Treasure	O
.	O
I	O
stepped	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Fancy	O
the	O
Woman	O
wanted	O
to	O
steal	O
my	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
bored	O
a	O
Hole	O
through	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
watch	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
deal	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
slip	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
changed	O
the	O
Parcel	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
look	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Paper	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
Buttons	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
Husband	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Diamond	O
Ear-Rings	O
are	O
here	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
spoke	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
scandalous	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
and	O
cursed	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Skirmish	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
force	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
David	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
Shilling	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Steel	O
set	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
,	O
being	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Stay-Hook	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
privately	B-pers
from	I-pers
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Nov.	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
in	O
last	O
December	O
Sessions	O
for	O
a	O
Street	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
obtained	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Pardon	O
.	O
See	O
Page	O
15	O
.	O
Trial	O
26.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
was	O
Sev'night	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
Side	O
,	O
the	O
String	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
about	O
my	O
Waist	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
immediately	O
miss	O
your	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
felt	O
something	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
Husband	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
-	O
My	O
Pocket	O
was	O
given	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Savoy	O
Gate	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
cried	O
out	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
from	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Side	O
down	O
the	O
Savoy	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
a	O
Man	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
in	O
his	O
Sight	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
or	O
Moon-light	O
.	O
Heath	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
15	O
Months	O
at	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
dark	O
as	O
a	O
Dungeon	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
he	O
takes	O
a	O
false	O
Oath	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Good	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Corporal	O
in	O
the	O
Guards	O
.	O
)	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Hill	O
from	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Brother	O
Soldier	O
,	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
third	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Guards	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Pocket	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
say	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
?	O
Good	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
Brother	O
Soldier	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
Robert	O
Johnson	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Savoy	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Frock	O
stoop	O
down	O
and	O
snatch	O
something	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
's	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
my	O
Pocket	O
is	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Pocket	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
David	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
le	O
Strand	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callimanco	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
French	O
Psalm	O
Book	O
with	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Clasp	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
and	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Hebert	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
her	O
Person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
27	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Hebert	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
Sev'night	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
almost	O
facing	O
Exeter	B-place
Change	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
three	O
Coaches	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tall	O
thin	O
Man	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
whitish	O
Frock	O
like	O
a	O
Livery	O
Frock	O
stooped	O
down	O
and	O
stole	O
my	O
Pocket	O
from	O
my	O
Side	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
my	O
Things	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Jer	O
.	O
Briggs	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
which	O
belong	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hebert	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Michael	B-pers
Swart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Till	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
26	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
29th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sweeping	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Money-Till	O
drop	O
,	O
I	O
stepped	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Counter	O
:	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
I	O
want	O
a	O
Roll	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
the	O
Till	O
down	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
without	O
your	O
touching	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
touched	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
Till	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
touching	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Till	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
's	O
place	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Till	O
;	O
it	O
locks	O
four	O
Inches	O
under	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
should	O
see	O
the	O
Key	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Till	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
touching	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Till	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
half	O
Pence	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Master	O
or	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
Michael	O
and	O
John	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tatlow	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
12	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tatlow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
,	O
seeing	O
some	O
Things	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
some	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Loin	O
of	O
Mutton	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
Apron	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
prodigious	O
fuddled	O
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
two	O
People	O
more	O
in	O
Liquor	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
lay	O
drunk	O
in	O
the	O
Wash	O
house	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Maid	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoon	O
might	O
be	O
bundled	O
up	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
6.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
earthen	O
Mug	O
tipped	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Brignall	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Brignall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
Mugs	O
.	O
My	O
Man	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
went	O
often	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
secrete	O
myself	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Days	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
upon	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Stairs	O
and	O
secreted	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Way	O
was	O
clear	O
he	O
unlocked	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
Door	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Mug	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
backward	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Hole	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
perceived	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
Some	O
Time	O
after	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
knock	O
it	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Hole	O
covered	O
over	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
a	O
Villain	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Damage	O
I	O
had	O
sustained	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
that	O
Evening	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hid	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
dark	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lay	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
Body	O
coming	O
in	O
prevented	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
my	O
Master	O
caught	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
strange	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
let	O
me	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
nothing	O
should	O
be	O
said	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
denied	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Henry	B-pers
Barter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Heathcote	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Millar	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
Valentine	O
Vernon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
an	O
Ammunition	O
Shirt	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Jemmerson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Cath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Cicely	B-pers
Eckley	I-pers
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
others	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
seventy	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O
H	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Eagle-Court	B-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
kept	O
by	O
a	O
Sheriff	O
or	O
a	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Court	O
Officer	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
up	O
an	O
eighteen-penny	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
five	O
Minutes	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
got	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
seventy	O
Pounds	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
-	O
The	O
Moment	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
eighteen	O
Pence	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
above	O
two	O
Minute	O
's	O
after	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
who	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
Chamber	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
Money	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
others	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Question	O
asked	O
then	O
-	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
some	O
Body	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Embling	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
fir	O
Timber	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
16	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lyne	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
proved	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Timber	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shoulder	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
of	O
Great	B-place
Stanmore	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
1	O
piece	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
piece	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Check	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
.	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Kent	O
at	O
Old	O
Windsor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
lifted	O
for	O
a	O
Marine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
covenanted	O
Servant	O
.	O
This	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
at	O
common	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
11.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Romaine	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
14	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Romaine	I-pers
.	O
Oct.	O
14	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
4	O
Shirts	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
called	O
Avery	O
Farm	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
Linen	O
over	O
a	O
Bank	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropped	O
the	O
Linen	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
12.	O
Penelope	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Silver	O
Coin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
3	O
1/4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Distiller	O
;	O
Nov.	O
13	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Till	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
Time	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
stepped	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
right	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mistress	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
examine	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
bulky	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
Business	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
13.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
16	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
just	O
below	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
we	O
drank	O
three	O
Pints	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
condescended	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
absconded	O
-	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Fleming	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
Face	O
and	O
her	O
Voice	O
;	O
I	O
challenged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
her	O
Mother	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
show	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
gives	O
you	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
Maker	O
's	O
Name	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
Kipling	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
her	O
Mother	O
offered	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Crowns	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
six	O
Months	O
by	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Girl	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
dutiful	O
to	O
her	O
Mother-in-law	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother-in-law	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Girl	O
,	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
Care	O
of	O
three	O
Children	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Warwickshire	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
but	O
six	O
Months	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
14.	O
John	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
Oct.	O
25	O
.	O
Captain	O
Murray	O
.	O
On	O
October	O
25	O
or	O
26	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
Play	I-place
-house	I-place
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
my	O
Chair	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whip	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chairman	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Rose	O
Tavern	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Passage	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
about	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
white	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
has	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
me	O
then	O
if	O
you	O
says	O
me	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
Murray	O
.	O
Because	O
you	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
Fellows	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
came	O
to	O
rescue	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Party	O
of	O
the	O
Guard	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
a	O
Rescue	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Captain	O
Murray	O
's	O
Chairmain	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
justly	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
behind	O
me	O
or	O
before	O
me	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Carrol	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
Chair	O
Poles	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Chair	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Chair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Pocket	O
was	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
that	O
far	O
thest	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
next	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Carrol	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
fairly	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
of	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Play	B-pers
-house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
that	O
Evening	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
kick	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Pick-pocket	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
used	O
by	O
these	O
Fellows	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
Hardship	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
House	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
England	O
within	O
these	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Gray	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Captain	O
cried	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
pick	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Gray	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ind	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Chairman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
plying	O
in	O
the	O
Rose	O
Passage	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
commonly	O
ply	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Captain	O
Murray	O
cry	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
up	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
stopped	O
himself	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Captain	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pushed	O
into	O
the	O
Rose	O
Tavern	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
received	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Eye	O
with	O
a	O
Brickbat	O
,	O
though	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
Guard	O
of	O
the	O
Play-house	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
hundreds	O
of	O
Stones	O
and	O
Brickbats	O
seen	O
lying	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
:	O
They	O
flew	O
so	O
that	O
People	O
thought	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
his	O
Brains	O
beat	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Murray	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
with	O
an	O
S	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
15.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Quart	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Tennant	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
28	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Copper	O
Funnels	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
half	O
Gallon	O
Pewter	O
Measure	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
18	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Holgate	I-pers
took	O
the	O
Quart	O
Tankard	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Cloak	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Tennant	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
in	O
White-Cross	O
Street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
16.	O
Jane	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Webb	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dynes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dynes	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dynes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
at	O
the	B-place
Angel	I-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
in	O
Wood-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
-	O
The	O
third	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
weighing	O
twenty	O
nine	O
Ounces	O
eighteen	O
Penny	O
Weight	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Tankard	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bar	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
had	O
the	O
Gown	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
an	O
Old-Clothes	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
Gown	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hoped	O
she	O
should	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Paterson	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Tankard	O
was	O
handed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
return	O
,	O
till	O
an	O
Officer	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
by	O
Force	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Dynes	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
into	O
Rose-Alley	O
in	O
White-cross	O
Street	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Alley	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
more	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
White-cross	O
Street	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dynes	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
one	O
Mary	O
Staton	O
's	O
in	O
Staining-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Master	O
into	O
Staining-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
all	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
;	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
Tankard	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
17.	O
Julius	B-pers
Dunt	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Doo	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Leather	O
Pouch	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
Nov.	O
17	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Doo	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
Side	O
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
Parish	I-place
School	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
by	O
who	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Mile	O
End	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
ringing	O
my	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Stepney	O
Parish	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
Parish	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
threw	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
over	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
my	O
Mouth	O
:	O
They	O
took	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
three	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Half-pence	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
Night	O
for	O
Letters	O
)	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
four	O
Shillings	O
more	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
was	O
frightful	O
enough	O
-	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Pouch	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
out	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
understood	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Julius	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
-	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
my	O
Pouch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Porch	O
belonging	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Spinckes	I-pers
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
November	O
17	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
James	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Robbing	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
Julius	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Wells	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
-	O
We	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
Man	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Silver	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
the	O
Postman	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
;	O
Leech	O
said	O
he	O
knows	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
over	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
Julius	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
took	O
some	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pouch	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
attacked	O
him	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Julius	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Pouch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
throw	O
it	O
into	O
Whitechapel	O
Goal	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
got	O
was	O
three	O
Shillings	O
and	O
two	O
Pence	O
Half	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
Half-pence	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Shilling	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Leech	O
had	O
a	O
Shilling	O
's	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Shilling	O
's	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Pence	O
Half-penny	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
trumped	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Thief-Taker	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
so	O
disguised	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stirrop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
eight	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
Weeks	O
;	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Indies	O
I	O
never	O
locked	O
up	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Rogue	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Supernumerary	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Wells	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
any	O
Business	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
four	O
Years	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
Snaresbrook	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Forest	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
abuse	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Mercy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saved	O
his	O
Life	O
-	O
*	O
*	O
This	O
may	O
be	O
probable	O
,	O
for	O
Spinckes	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
Leech	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
+	O
18.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Leath	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Southall	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Sept.	O
13	O
.	O
his	O
Property	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Sept.	O
13	O
.	O
his	O
Property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Aylesbury	O
in	O
the	O
Stage-Coach	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lawyer	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
who	O
had	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
Pistol	O
:	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
Hat	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
cross	O
the	O
Wrist	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Lawyer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
an	O
one	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
half	O
Pence	O
-	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Hat	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
Money	O
from	O
every	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
us	O
a	O
good	O
Journey	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
off	O
towards	O
London	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
Ladies	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Dress	O
was	O
I	O
in	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
loose	O
white	O
Duffel	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Rug-Coat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
same	O
Waistcoat	O
you	O
have	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Horse	O
had	O
I	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
A	O
dark	O
bay	O
Horse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Marks	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Horne	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Person	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Aylesbury	O
Coach	O
,	O
September	O
13	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
on	O
this	O
Side	O
Southall	O
;	O
he	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
Lawyer	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
Mr.	O
Herne	O
's	O
Brains	O
out	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Lawyer	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Mr.	O
Herne	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
or	O
8	O
s.	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
collected	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
Money	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Herne	O
's	O
Money	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
Ladies	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
direct	O
his	O
Discourse	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Lawyer	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
him	O
the	O
200	O
l.	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
Mistake	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
Lawyer	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
my	O
Hands	O
to	O
convince	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Dyer	O
by	O
Trade	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
what	O
Money	O
you	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
you	O
that	O
already	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Take	O
Notice	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Ladies	O
Money	O
first	O
.	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
throw	O
a	O
Purse	O
into	O
his	O
Hat	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Herne	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
Herne	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
my	O
upper	O
Coat	O
buttoned	O
or	O
unbuttoned	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
loose	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
coloured	O
Horse	O
had	O
I	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
Horse	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
dark	O
bay	O
Colour	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
had	O
any	O
Marks	O
.	O
Ellis	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
horseback	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
Miles	O
on	O
this	O
Side	O
Southall	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
in	O
him	O
what	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
common	O
in	O
Travellers	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
too	O
much	O
Notice	O
of	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
several	O
impertinent	O
Questions	O
:	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
Master	O
a	O
Lawyer	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Welshman	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Discourse	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
a	O
Mile	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
I	O
lost	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
Toast	O
at	O
Southall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coach	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
Master	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Potter	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Ladies	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
complaining	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dark	O
cropt	O
Horse	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Chashunt	O
,	O
a	O
Quaker	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
had	O
been	O
pursuing	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
riding	O
by	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
his	O
Dress	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
rode	O
through	O
the	O
Town	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Dress	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
Cap	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
on	O
an	O
old	O
Hat	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
net	O
worth	O
six	O
Pence	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
and	O
pursue	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
myself	O
Mile	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Wickmore-Hill	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
Miles	O
from	O
Heathcomb	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
from	O
Missinglam	O
,	O
I	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
on	O
Horseback	O
had	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
hurt	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Common	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
to	O
a	O
Girl	O
said	O
sure	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
,	O
for	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
changed	O
my	O
took	O
a	O
Pistol	O
under	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
took	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
had	O
not	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
pretended	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
some	O
Beer	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
and	O
the	O
Butcher	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
Opposition	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
out	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pockets	O
were	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
Pistol	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
Powder	O
only	O
;	O
I	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Missingham	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
very	O
much	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
away	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Whip	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
very	O
quietly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
without	O
tying	O
him	O
?	O
Pugh	O
.	O
Yes	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
ride	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
Missingham	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
he	O
robbed	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
their	O
Pardon	O
;	O
he	O
sai	O
d	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
at	O
my	O
Lady	O
Mordington	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
committed	O
.	O
-	O
Holland	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
Birth	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
Trooper	O
or	O
Dragoon	O
in	O
the	O
Horse	O
Service	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
these	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Complaint	O
of	O
him	O
-	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Certificate	O
from	O
the	O
and	O
Church	O
Wardens	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
with	O
Regard	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
*	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
begged	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Mercy	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Potter	O
begged	O
leave	O
to	O
inform	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Fortune	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Coach-Box	O
muffled	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
robbed	O
any	O
Body	O
upon	O
the	O
Coach-Box	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
believed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
by	O
falling	O
into	O
bad	O
Company	O
at	O
my	O
Lady	O
Mordington	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
obliged	O
to	O
prosecute	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
his	O
Country	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
favourable	O
Circumstances	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
join	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Request	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
Life	O
.	O
10.	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Crocked	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Teakettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
staying	O
for	O
her	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Teakettle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
concealed	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20	O
,	O
21.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Glass	O
Beads	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
come	O
from	O
Rotterdam	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
Glass	O
Beads	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
as	O
the	O
Seller	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Bundles	O
of	O
green	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
white	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
for	O
eight	O
Pence	O
per	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
again	O
for	O
nine	O
Pence	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Son	O
to	O
one	O
over	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
mistook	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
Beads	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
landed	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Sort	O
at	O
Botolph	O
Wharf	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
Person	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
sell	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Property	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
confirmed	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
present	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Property	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
22	O
,	O
23.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Sheets	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
And	O
Jane	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
24.	O
George	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spatula	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
Sharret	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
Allen	B-pers
Sharret	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Instrument	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
call	O
a	O
Spatula	O
)	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Stair	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
here	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
-	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
Spatula	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Irving	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
who	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
for	O
Pocket	O
Expences	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
Lunatick	O
these	O
twelve	O
Months	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
A	O
Person	O
appeared	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
as	O
a	O
Packer	O
for	O
Alderman	O
Bernard	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lodge	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
Lectures	O
at	O
Doctor	O
Taylor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grocock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Bars	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
two	O
Steel	O
Punches	O
,	O
two	O
Chissels	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pease	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
25	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pease	O
a	O
Blacksmith	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
these	O
Things	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
informed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
challenged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
corporal	O
Punishment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Oct.	O
23	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
(	O
a	O
King	O
's	O
Watchman	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
a	O
Merchant	O
to	O
watch	O
a	O
Lighter	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Skuttle	O
Hole	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Bed	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
little	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Sugar	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
(	O
Constable	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Mate	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
industrious	O
Man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
27.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Barefoot	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Diamond	O
on	O
the	O
Pendant	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Duhammel	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
,	O
1741	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Duhammel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
or	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1741	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
sent	O
his	O
Watch	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
advertised	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Person	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
Jacob	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
Person	O
was	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vanhop	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Barefoot	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
since	O
married	O
one	O
Miller	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Richards	O
,	O
Jacobs	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
twenty	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
employed	O
one	O
Harris	O
a	O
Thief-taker	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
get	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
Years	O
ago	O
last	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Rag-Fair	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
second-hand	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
a	O
Jew	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Chap	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
try	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Father	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Levi	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
;	O
my	O
Father	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
Son	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
you	O
had	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
middle	O
sized	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Diamond	O
on	O
the	O
Pendant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Diamond	O
on	O
the	O
Button	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
they	O
fix	O
a	O
String	O
to	O
this	O
Watch	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
wanting	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Son	O
Abraham	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
to	O
be	O
disposed	O
of	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
get	O
a	O
Penny	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Levi	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
his	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
Son	O
in	O
the	O
Hebrew	O
Language	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
that	O
Watch	O
is	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
very	O
handsome	O
Diamonds	O
.	O
Seeing	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Duhammel	O
's	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Rickards	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Thieves	O
came	O
about	O
us	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Duhammel	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
too	O
short	O
of	O
coming	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
-	O
She	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
17	O
Guineas	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Diamond	O
on	O
the	O
Pendant	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
the	O
Button	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Ring	O
wanting	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lovi	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
(	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
Gold	O
repeating	O
Watch	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Diamond	O
upon	O
the	O
Button	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
upon	O
the	O
Pendant	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Ring	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
In	O
November	O
,	O
1741	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
with	O
two	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
showed	O
me	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Chance	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Chap	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
satisfy	O
you	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
offered	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dubammel	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
thirty	O
Guineas	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Harris	O
who	O
kept	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
You	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
this	O
Practice	O
.	O
Oh	O
!	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
that	O
by	O
Jesus	O
God	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
is	O
their	O
Irish	O
way	O
of	O
talking	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Dubammel	O
I	O
could	O
inform	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
so	O
many	O
Thieves	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Rag-Fair	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
knocked	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Berry	O
was	O
a	O
Thief-taker	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Court	O
while	O
her	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
Berry	O
.	O
She	O
wants	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
discover	O
who	O
the	O
Persons	O
are	O
,	O
that	O
come	O
in	O
her	O
Behalf	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
like	O
herself	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Rickards	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
murdered	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
as	O
peaceable	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
quietly	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
stripped	O
her	O
naked	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
her	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
every	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
extend	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
concealed	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
that	O
narrowly	O
;	O
we	O
cut	O
the	O
very	O
Beds	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
now	O
-	O
She	O
never	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Child's-Coat-Maker	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cable	O
Street	O
;	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
Clothes	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
Things	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
challenged	O
for	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
just	O
and	O
fair	O
of	O
her	O
-	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
Stay-maker	O
,	O
and	O
buys	O
and	O
sells	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
Goods	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
the	O
Fair	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
dive	O
into	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
enough	O
to	O
do	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
say	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Berry	O
.	O
What	O
Character	O
has	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carlow	I-pers
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
She	O
buys	O
such	O
Things	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
all	O
buy	O
these	O
Things	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
them	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
Characters	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
deal	O
that	O
way	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
in	O
stolen	O
Things	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Carlow	O
has	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
Thieves	O
about	O
her	O
always	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
get	O
these	O
Things	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Barefoot	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Case	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Box	O
(	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
Hannah	B-pers
Copestakes	I-pers
privately	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Minetray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
Felony	O
Hannah	B-pers
Copestakes	I-pers
was	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
*	O
convicted	O
)	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
9	O
*	O
See	O
last	O
September	O
Sessions	O
,	O
Trial	O
424	O
,	O
Page	O
249.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Menitray	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Hannah	B-pers
Copestakes	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Muston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
Hannah	B-pers
Copestakes	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
sold	O
my	O
Watch	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Muston	I-pers
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Copestakes	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
29.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
one	O
Penny	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
Sevennight	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
George	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
by	O
Fleet-Ditch	B-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
forced	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
loth	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
something	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
went	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
just	O
to	O
the	O
Stairs	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Message	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
Liquor	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pushed	O
her	O
away	O
several	O
times	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
pick	O
my	O
Pocket	O
then	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
for	O
more	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
held	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
-	O
She	O
clapped	O
her	O
Hands	O
upon	O
both	O
my	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Minute	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
Hand	O
upon	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
saved	O
that	O
:	O
They	O
called	O
out	O
several	O
Names	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
immediately	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sharrock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
frightened	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
ten	O
Years	O
old	O
might	O
have	O
managed	O
me	O
-	O
That	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
change	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
Six-pence	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
the	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
any	O
nearer	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
than	O
only	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
that	O
you	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
her	O
Side	O
nor	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
held	O
you	O
?	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
in	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
my	O
Oath	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
drunk	O
these	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
(	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
George	O
Alley	O
;	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
Sevennight	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
just	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
good	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
go	O
in	O
Arm	O
and	O
Arm	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
Arm	O
in	O
Arm	O
together	O
-	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
notorious	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Man	O
complain	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
complain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Character	O
does	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bear	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
the	O
good	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
-	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
Servant	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
bad	O
House	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
good	O
Woman	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
being	O
laid	O
to	O
her	O
Charge	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
Husband	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
in	O
creditable	O
Families	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
rightly	O
considered	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
your	O
Lordship	O
or	O
I	O
either	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bassett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
eleven	O
Years	O
ago	O
at	O
my	O
Lady	O
Kelly	O
's	O
in	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
last	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Plumber	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Fanstick-Maker	O
in	O
Wild	O
Street	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
Fellow-Servants	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
Fellow-Servant	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Blundell	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Grocer	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
Street	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
Manner	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
one	O
Phillips	O
,	O
a	O
Printer	O
,	O
in	O
Wine-Office	O
Court	O
.	O
-	O
Bradford	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
George	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
civil	O
sober	O
Woman	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
30.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Callin	I-pers
in	O
the	O
same	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Callin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Highgate	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Parrot	O
to	O
a	O
Lady	O
,	O
whose	O
Husband	O
was	O
Surveyor	O
General	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
in	O
New	O
England	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Highgate	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
a	O
Corner	O
a	O
Woman	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
(	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Thing	O
full	O
of	O
Brandy	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
Measure	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
carried	O
me	O
up	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
some	O
odd	O
Expressions	O
,	O
and	O
falls	O
back	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
tumbles	O
me	O
o	O
'	O
Top	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
feel	O
you	O
;	O
no	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
feel	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
feel	O
no	O
Body	O
;	O
why	O
?	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
You	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
poxed	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
pox	O
her	O
nor	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
feel	O
me	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Cup	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
again	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
to	O
trust	O
them	O
with	O
,	O
as	O
believing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
two	O
English	O
half	O
Crowns	O
more	O
,	O
an	O
English	O
Shilling	O
,	O
two	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
(	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
Brandy	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
paid	O
your	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
Cousin	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
down	O
-	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
carried	O
me	O
in	O
:	O
They	O
opened	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapped	O
her	O
Arms	O
round	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
carried	O
me	O
in	O
took	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
one	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Six-pence	O
;	O
she	O
opened	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
my	O
left	O
Pocket	O
inside	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
slipped	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
right	O
Pocket	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
some	O
Papers	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
keep	O
my	O
Papers	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
delivered	O
me	O
my	O
Papers	O
again	O
:	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
plundered	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
a	O
Girl	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
six	O
Minutes	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
prodigiously	O
frightened	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
make	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Constable	O
about	O
six	O
Minutes	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
the	O
Coachman	O
*	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
twenty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
used	O
to	O
Sterling	B-pers
Money	I-pers
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Sum	O
cleverly	O
,	O
either	O
then	O
,	O
or	O
now	O
-	O
*	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Sharrock	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
was	O
Sev'night	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Coachman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Young	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
Callin	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
fearful	O
of	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
three	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
Pence	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
living	O
Woman	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
die	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
hurt	O
her	O
in	O
any	O
Shape	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Caution	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Mercy	O
.	O
+	O
31.	O
Mary	B-pers
Corker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Carnaby	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carnaby	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Hartshorn-Lane	B-place
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Women	O
standing	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turned	O
me	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
(	O
though	O
she	O
never	O
was	O
my	O
Fellow-Servant	O
)	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
pulled	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
feel	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
Occasion	O
for	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Fob	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
her	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Constable	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
promised	O
me	O
(	O
that	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
)	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
down	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
something	O
hard	O
under	O
her	O
Armpit	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
hanged	O
if	O
you	O
go	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
carried	O
you	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Souchon	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
green	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Job	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
23	O
.	O
33.	O
John	B-pers
Hume	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Job	O
Matthew	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White-chapel	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Davis	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Porter	O
)	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
there	O
with	O
some	O
Tea	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
Body	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
two	O
Fellows	O
called	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Parcel	O
left	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Headborough	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
see	O
,	O
whether	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
Hume	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Parcel	O
;	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
the	O
Parcel	O
you	O
wait	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Headborough	O
,	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
being	O
stolen	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
Davis	O
comes	O
strutting	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Where	O
are	O
these	O
two	O
Thieves	O
that	O
wait	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
see	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
confounded	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Sweat	O
dropped	O
down	O
from	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
William	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
Goods	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Rickards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
small	O
Parcel	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
large	O
Parcel	O
of	O
a	O
Smuggler	O
.	O
I	O
weighed	O
a	O
Cannister	O
of	O
Soucbon	O
Tea	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suspected	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Account	O
I	O
keep	O
with	O
the	O
Officer	O
of	O
Stock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
about	O
two	O
Pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
wanting	O
:	O
The	O
Lid	O
of	O
the	O
Cannister	O
was	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Ounces	O
lay	O
loose	O
upon	O
the	O
Lid	O
of	O
the	O
Cannister	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
some	O
Body	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
Tea	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
strong	O
Flavour	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
of	O
this	O
Sort	O
of	O
Tea	O
run	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
positive	O
it	O
is	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Tea	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
I	O
met	O
in	O
New	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bohea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Green	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
for	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
Job	O
Matthew	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Linen	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
says	O
a	O
Leather	O
one	O
:	O
This	O
Fellow	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Letter	O
when	O
I	O
hired	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Okey	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
buy	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Tea	O
of	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
in	O
New	O
Gravel-Lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
or	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
-	O
about	O
two	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bargained	O
for	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
one	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
taking	O
the	O
Paper	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
opened	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
Davis	O
saw	O
it	O
opened	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
Coachman	O
to	O
Justice	O
Strong	O
of	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
four	O
Years	O
Coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Weller	O
of	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
34.	O
Ann	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
2	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Yard	O
at	O
the	B-place
Three	I-place
Queens	I-place
on	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
Green	I-place
about	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hurder	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Turnmill-Street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hurder	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hurder	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
this	O
good	O
honest	O
Man	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
that	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Words	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
scold	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
without	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
half	O
Crown	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
without	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
us	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
us	O
all	O
the	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Black-guards	O
he	O
could	O
think	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
and	O
abused	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
Pot	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
Hole	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
B	O
-	O
d	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
lustier	O
Man	O
than	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
force	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35.	O
William	B-pers
Rinklesworth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dignan	I-pers
,	O
November	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
36.	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Stockley	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
four	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-Strainer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Knee-Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
Silver	O
Sleeve-Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
five	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ruddell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ruddell	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ruddell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
my	O
Bedchamber	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bob	B-pers
Wig	I-pers
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
absconded	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
and	O
Joiner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
his	O
Wife	O
out	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
her	O
Things	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Wig	O
behind	O
her	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
with	O
the	O
Wig	O
on	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
for	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
barbarously	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
ten	O
thousand	O
Pardons	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
should	O
make	O
me	O
amends	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Ruddell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
six	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
which	O
my	O
Husband	O
has	O
mentioned	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
my	O
Knee	O
against	O
it	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
burst	O
open	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Headborough	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Pecks	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
Tavern	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Ruddell	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt-seller	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe	O
Buckles	O
,	O
one	O
Knee	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
Shirt	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Corner	O
Cupboard	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
37	O
,	O
38.	O
John	B-pers
Yearby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowles	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Cotton	O
Gowns	O
,	O
three	O
Flannel	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
five	O
Aprons	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
one	O
Ticken	O
Apron	O
,	O
one	O
Dimitty	O
Cap	O
,	O
three	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
39.	O
Susan	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
Yearby	O
cried	O
and	O
owned	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowles	I-pers
in	O
robbing	O
me	O
;	O
Dowles	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
Thompson	O
owned	O
the	O
buying	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
Edwards	O
six	O
Shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Apron	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
Wild	O
,	O
the	O
Headborough	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Thompson	O
owned	O
the	O
buying	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
is	O
my	O
Uncle	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
November	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Yearby	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Unkle	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
helped	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Pales	O
and	O
received	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Jemmy	O
Thomson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
both	O
got	O
out	O
o	O
'	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Fire	O
to	O
dry	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
looked	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
should	O
give	O
us	O
six	O
Shillings	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
paid	O
us	O
the	O
Money	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Yearby	O
and	O
Dowles	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomson	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Shirt	O
and	O
one	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
;	O
one	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
;	O
one	O
Shift	O
and	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
3	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
Washing	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
sometimes	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
42.	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
four	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
September	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
Waggon	O
belonging	O
to	O
Sir	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Trial	O
402	O
.	O
Page	O
233.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
stooping	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Cheese	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
