TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
WEDNESDAY	O
September	O
7	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
8	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
9	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
12	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
17th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
1743	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIMOTT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
DENISON	O
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Wheat	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Sherburne	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Malpas	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lupton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hornblower	I-pers
,	O
Solomon	B-pers
Pelliter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bundy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boone	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Thoyts	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gatlon	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Oseland	I-pers
,	O
Enoch	B-pers
Grigg	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
368.	O
Charles	B-pers
Maddison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Napkin	O
and	O
Cap	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
;	O
two	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Donsur	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
Damask	O
Clout	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
pledging	O
some	O
Stockings	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Outside	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Parcels	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
his	O
Feet	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
pledged	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
different	O
Persons	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
sell	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
369	O
.	O
+	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hartshorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
three	O
Pieces	O
ditto	O
,	O
36	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
at	O
Mary-bone	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Money	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Closet	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
had	O
been	O
wrenched	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
was	O
turned	O
upside	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
sat	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Box	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
further	O
examined	O
,	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Copper	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sealed	O
up	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
who	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Head	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
the	O
Devil	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
wrenched	O
the	O
Box	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Sweetman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
acquaint	O
her	O
Master	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
Master	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Glove	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Inches	O
under	O
Ground	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Copper-hole	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
hoped	O
her	O
Master	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wrenched	O
the	O
Box	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
Case-Knife	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Capps	I-pers
.	O
Constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr	O
Gough	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
threatning	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
not	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
clean	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
this	O
Man	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
cried	O
in	O
a	O
lamentable	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
her	O
Master	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Copper-hole	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
beheved	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Devil	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
Servant	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
about	O
Ten	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
follow	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
.	O
Stairs	O
all	O
Hours	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
upon	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
last	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Money	O
be	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
Pieces	O
there	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
this	O
Money	O
for	O
Favours	O
.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
offered	O
,	O
or	O
gave	O
her	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
370	O
.	O
+	O
Jacob	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
unfinished	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
18	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Haberdashers	O
,	O
and	O
Stuff-Shop	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Maker	O
;	O
this	O
Gown	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
somebody	O
snatch	O
the	O
Gown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Coleby	I-pers
.	O
Just	O
as	O
the	O
Clock	O
struck	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
Holborn	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Coleby	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lad	O
running	O
by	O
with	O
something	O
whitish	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positively	O
sure	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
know	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Thousand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
proved	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Gown	O
which	O
was	O
delivered	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
Buck	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
*	O
Tho	O
'	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
so	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
as	O
to	O
some	O
within	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
to	O
exempt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
Clergy	O
,	O
in	O
Favour	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
such	O
Statutes	O
are	O
construed	O
strictly	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
of	O
Shop-lifting	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
all	O
held	O
,	O
the	O
Felony	O
must	O
be	O
of	O
such	O
Goods	O
are	O
are	O
usually	O
sold	O
in	O
such	O
Shop	O
;	O
This	O
Gown	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
therefore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
capitaliy	O
convicted	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Value	O
had	O
been	O
proved	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
371.	O
Ann	B-pers
Haskins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Legborn	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gostelow	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Gostelow	I-pers
.	O
July	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
caught	O
you	O
now	O
:	O
These	O
five	O
Keys	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Key	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Kitchen-door	O
;	O
the	O
Keys	O
do	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Gostelow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
set	O
the	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
before	O
to	O
conceal	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
Coats	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
her	O
Coats	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
the	O
Keys	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
were	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Glass	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
it	O
hung	O
.	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Nutting	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
372.	O
Ann	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Debanks	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
29	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Debanks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Cloak	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
my	O
Chamber	O
:	O
She	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
Mr	O
Stringer	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Debanks	I-pers
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Cloak	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
at	O
Stringer	O
's	O
for	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
she	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
Brother	O
would	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
Debanks	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
373	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Yards	O
and	O
three	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Mecklin	O
Lace	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arabella	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
.	O
Arabella	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
:	O
I	O
live	O
over-against	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
was	O
within	O
;	O
my	O
Man	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Parlour	O
where	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Lace	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Order	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
for	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mecklin	O
Lace	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
Price	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
Breadth	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
two	O
Pieces	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
14	O
s.	O
per	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
another	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
clapped	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
is	O
dearer	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
20	O
s.	O
per	O
Yard	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
was	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
bad	O
better	O
take	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
11	O
s.	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
directly	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
at	O
first	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
another	O
Box	O
;	O
it	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
stopped	O
by	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
kept	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
as	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Lace	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Maltus	O
Paine	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
little	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lace	O
Merchant	O
;	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
small	O
Information	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
has	O
another	O
Indictment	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Thing	O
that	O
brought	O
this	O
to	O
light	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
Piece	O
in	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Reputation	O
and	O
Character	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
five	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
Property	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
possible	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
your	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Piece	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
that	O
you	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
know	O
whose	O
this	O
is	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
-	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
maker	O
that	O
was	O
making	O
Wiggs	O
for	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
lent	O
him	O
five	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
-	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
Lace	O
-	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
surprized	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
under	O
any	O
Confusion	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
my	O
Business	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
give	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
-	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Piece	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
.	O
Aug.	O
11	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
's	O
Shop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
had	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O
that	O
Question	O
?	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
about	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
Great	O
Russel	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
Now	O
,	O
says	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
spoiled	O
all	O
your	O
Innocency	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
run	O
away	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
innocent	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Maiden-Lane	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Day	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Perriwig-maker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
traffick	O
'd	O
Wigs	O
for	O
Lace	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
my	O
Name	O
was	O
Day	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Name	O
is	O
Earl	O
.	O
Hull	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Mason	O
's	O
,	O
whose	O
Property	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Town	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
heard	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
Mrs	O
Morris	O
's	O
Lace	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
Lace	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
Day	O
,	O
at	O
Reading	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Fair	O
;	O
I	O
r	O
apped	O
Goods	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
travelled	O
the	O
Countries	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
Perriwigs	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Perriwig-maker	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Caps	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
good	O
Business	O
when	O
he	O
travelled	O
the	O
Countries	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ayloffe-street	O
now	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Pen	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
twelve	O
Months	O
next	O
Michaelmas-Day	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Perriwig-maker	O
,	O
and	O
travels	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
my	O
House	O
very	O
often	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
sent	O
them	O
again	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wickers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Gate	O
by	O
the	O
Seven-Dials	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Cases	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
Opportunities	O
to	O
wrong	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
very	O
readily	O
have	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Ayloffe-street	O
,	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
travel	O
the	O
Countries	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trevors	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Earl	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
about	O
three	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Perriwig-maker	O
and	O
Hosier	O
too	O
;	O
he	O
sells	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
one	O
Fair	O
to	O
another	O
-	O
he	O
trafficks	O
one	O
thing	O
for	O
another	O
-	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
regular	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Family	O
.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Court	O
Officer	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
Kind	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
374	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Day	O
,	O
was	O
(	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
)	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
and	O
1/2	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
called	O
Corded	O
Mecklin	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
49	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
Joyce	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
first	O
Floor	O
in	O
Mr	O
Pearce	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
Lace	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mecklin	O
Lace	O
,	O
of	O
about	O
10	O
s.	O
per	O
Yard	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
Nine	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
Ten	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
seemed	O
not	O
to	O
understand	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
another	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Piece	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Piece	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
above	O
his	O
Price	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
clapped	O
his	O
other	O
Hand	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
imagine	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Piece	O
up	O
again	O
that	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
About	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
afterwards	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
I	O
missed	O
five	O
Pieces	O
more	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
six	O
Yards	O
three	O
Quarters	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
six	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
that	O
were	O
but	O
Remnants	O
;	O
then	O
was	O
I	O
dubious	O
,	O
whether	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Servants	O
had	O
not	O
stole	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
ingenuous	O
in	O
shewing	O
me	O
what	O
Laces	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Piece	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Piece	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
then	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Lace	O
went	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
since	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Piece	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
at	O
first	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
shew	O
this	O
particular	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
to	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
opened	O
two	O
Boxes	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
-	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
Piece	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
-	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Laces	O
over	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
them	O
over	O
again	O
till	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Maltus	O
Paine	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Mason	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
telling	O
my	O
Wife	O
of	O
her	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
in	O
losing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Lace	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
in	O
two	O
Pieces	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
one	O
or	O
both	O
may	O
be	O
your	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
Lace	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
this	O
Piece	O
;	O
this	O
Piece	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
another	O
Piece	O
of	O
about	O
thirteen	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
too	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
four	O
Yards	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
several	O
Questions	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
such	O
satisfactory	O
Answers	O
,	O
that	O
really	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
gave	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Evidence	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
stop	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
bring	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
somebody	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
Mr	O
Paine	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
he	O
run	O
bravely	O
?	O
Hull	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
most	O
stoutly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
Business	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Moore	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
sometimes	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
kept	O
a	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Turk's-Head	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
375	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Day	O
,	O
was	O
(	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
)	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Yards	O
and	O
1/2	O
of	O
Mecklin	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
English	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gubbins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
John	B-pers
Gubbin	I-pers
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Catherine-street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
looked	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
right	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
two	O
Ladies	O
at	O
Richmond	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
some	O
Time	O
ago	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
sold	O
some	O
Lace	O
to	O
two	O
Ladies	O
that	O
live	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
those	O
Ladies	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
desired	O
Mrs	O
Gubbins	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
at	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
;	O
my	O
Mistress	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Boxes	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
fault	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
too	O
dear	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
one	O
Excuse	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
hid	O
her	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
;	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
at	O
12	O
s.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
their	O
Opinion	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
Half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Upon	O
putting	O
the	O
Laces	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
broad	O
Mecklin	O
Lace	O
,	O
four	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
English	O
Lace	O
.	O
Some	O
Time	O
after	O
that	O
hearing	O
somebody	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
Lace	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Mason	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
,	O
and	O
laid	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
Pieces	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
376	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Mulberry	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St	B-place
Michael	I-place
in	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Plimpton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Plimpton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Moses	B-pers
Polock	I-pers
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Polock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
Mr	O
Plimpton	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Mr	O
Plimpton	O
directly	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
Mr	O
Plimpton	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
377.	O
Michael	B-pers
Pennyfeather	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
10	O
.	O
William	O
Hill	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
weekly	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
honest	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Sixpences	O
into	O
the	O
Till	O
on	O
Purpose	O
to	O
catch	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
concealed	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
unlock	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
some	O
Money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Shillings	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
we	O
have	O
seen	O
enough	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
me	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kippax	I-pers
.	O
I	O
marked	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
(	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Sixpences	O
)	O
but	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
some	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
afterwards	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
378.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Nicholas	I-place
Olaves	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Haughton	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
ten	O
Plates	O
from	O
Mr	O
Haughton	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropped	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Poverty	O
drove	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
379	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Hanns	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
Mr	O
Pearson	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
over	O
Hounslow-Heath	B-place
,	O
in	O
an	O
one	O
Horse	O
Chaise	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Chaise	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr	O
Pearson	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
borrow	O
some	O
Money	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	O
Pearson	O
not	O
minding	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
again	O
sharply	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
borrow	O
some	O
Money	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Mr	O
Pearson	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Watch	O
-	O
He	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
very	O
high	O
close	O
to	O
Mr	O
Pearson	O
's	O
Ear	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
Horseback	O
-	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
put	O
your	O
Hand	O
into	O
your	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
have	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
cocked	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
towards	O
my	O
Face	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Person	O
with	O
him	O
who	O
dropped	O
a	O
black	O
Crape	O
over	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Chaise	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
cocked	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Face	O
was	O
bare	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Five	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
immediately	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
that	O
Day	O
Sev'nnight	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
about	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
Man	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
acquainted	O
my	O
Fellow-Sufferer	O
,	O
Mr	O
Pearson	O
,	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
George	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
-	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
)	O
between	O
Marybone	O
and	O
Paddington	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Pearson	O
came	O
quite	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
Pearson	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
drank	O
two	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Pipes	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
without	O
saying	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
were	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
seem	O
any	O
ways	O
shy	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
drinking	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
the	O
first	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
looked	O
a	O
little	O
Shy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
looked	O
hard	O
at	O
Mr	O
Pearson	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
coloured	O
Coat	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Surrout	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
close	O
bodied	O
Coat	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
ordinary	O
thread-bare	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
Holes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
narrow	O
brimm	O
'd	O
Hat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Coat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
July	O
9.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
stopped	O
on	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
of	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
Joke	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
he	O
spoke	O
pretty	O
sharply	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Chaise	O
with	O
my	O
Whip	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
have	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
dropped	O
a	O
Crape	O
over	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
Friend	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
Handful	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
we	O
are	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Servants	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
airing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
have	O
aired	O
us	O
very	O
handsomely	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
my	O
Companion	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
you	O
are	O
richer	O
than	O
we	O
are	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
false	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
our	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
theirs	O
;	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Sev'nnight	O
following	O
,	O
my	O
Mate	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
by	O
half	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
says	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
Beer	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Hanns	O
's	O
House	O
-	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Mate	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
Seven-Dials	O
from	O
Hounslow	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
ten	O
Miles	O
.	O
Q	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
a	O
Man	O
can	O
ride	O
that	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
According	O
as	O
the	O
Horse	O
is	O
-	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
wet	O
with	O
Sweat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Colour	O
was	O
the	O
Horse	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Five	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
turned	O
of	O
Six	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
were	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
sure	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
in	O
George-Yard	O
by	O
Grosvenor	O
square	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
hired	O
Horses	O
of	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
;	O
for	O
one	O
Day	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
never	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
kept	O
very	O
good	O
Hours	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Horse	O
that	O
very	O
Day	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Sorrel	B-pers
Horse	I-pers
that	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Pearson	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
coloured	O
Horse	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
well	O
skilled	O
in	O
Horses	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
or	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
;	O
Mr	O
Bowles	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
some	O
secret	O
Expedition	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bowles	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Discourse	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
that	O
?	O
Bowles	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
pretty	O
hard	O
;	O
at	O
this	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Business	O
he	O
went	O
about	O
very	O
well	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
an	O
anonymous	O
Letter	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Name	O
Pearson	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Mr	O
Pearson	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Watch	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
on	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
engraved	O
on	O
the	O
Outside	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
[	O
Neither	O
the	O
Letter	O
sent	O
to	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
,	O
nor	O
another	O
received	O
by	O
Pearson	O
,	O
could	O
be	O
read	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
deny	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Garden	O
,	O
by	O
Drury-Lane	O
End	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
we	O
h	O
ad	O
Beans	O
and	O
Bacon	O
for	O
Dinner	O
,	O
he	O
dined	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
seven	O
-	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
half	O
an	O
Anchor	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
I	O
owed	O
him	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
Anchor	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
3	O
l.	O
for	O
both	O
[	O
The	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
Anchor	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Receipt	O
in	O
full	O
]	O
-	O
It	O
bore	O
Date	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
-	O
we	O
drank	O
Beer	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Bumbo	O
-	O
we	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
below	O
Stairs	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
!	O
Newbury	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Receipt	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
Reason	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
dined	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mr	O
Newbury	O
's	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
Horse	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
-	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
a	O
lightish	O
Bay	O
or	O
Sorrel	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Man	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
intimate	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Chandler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Peter's-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
dined	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
?	O
Burden	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
seven	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
Beans	O
and	O
Bacon	O
for	O
Dinner	O
-	O
we	O
drank	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
Water	O
and	O
Brandy	O
-	O
we	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
Mr	O
Newbury	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
House-keeper	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
had	O
several	O
Hampers	O
of	O
Wine	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Brewer	O
who	O
serves	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
drew	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
sixteen	O
Years	O
,	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
considerable	O
Farmer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rented	O
a	O
Farm	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
about	O
16	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
now	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
Months	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
spirituous	O
Liquors	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
well	O
.	O
-	O
Fuller	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
comfortable	O
Living	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
Bread	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
Father	O
lived	O
there	O
some	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Freer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
served	O
him	O
with	O
Coals	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
Half	O
a	O
Mile	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Graham	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Paddington	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Foreman	O
to	O
Mr	O
Barret	O
,	O
of	O
Brentford	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Master	O
Brick-maker	O
,	O
and	O
Landlord	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
pay	O
my	O
Men	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
am	O
is	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
about	O
thirty	O
of	O
Mr	O
Barret	O
's	O
Men	O
are	O
obliged	O
to	O
use	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
near	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
his	O
Character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
very	O
good	O
Business	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
could	O
maintain	O
himself	O
handsomely	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
desired	O
Col.	O
Deveil	B-pers
,	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
Newbury	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
first	O
Witness	O
)	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
that	O
Question	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
declare	O
that	O
Mr	O
Newbury	O
is	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
most	O
infamous	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
believed	O
in	O
any	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
380	O
.	O
+	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
381	O
,	O
382	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Michael	I-place
,	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Coker	I-pers
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
one	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
myself	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
[	O
His	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
]	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
called	O
the	O
Curtain	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
and	O
I	O
broke	O
off	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
the	O
furthest	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
two	O
Wiggs	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
forced	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
:	O
Robert	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
went	O
into	O
Gutter-Lane	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Candle	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
,	O
-	O
(	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
a	O
jew	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
absconded	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
till	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
for	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
a-piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
wicked	O
Fellow	O
to	O
rob	O
your	O
Father	O
?	O
Richard	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
.	O
Peake	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
several	O
in	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
discovered	O
this	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
July	O
31	O
)	O
and	O
impeached	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Clay	O
most	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
prodigiously	O
fuddled	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
fenuble	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
after	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
recover	O
himself	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
upon	O
an	O
Expedition	O
of	O
this	O
Kind	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Coster	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Grimston	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
Clay	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
young	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Coupee	I-pers
says	O
,	O
that	O
Clay	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Person	O
as	O
ever	O
she	O
desires	O
to	O
deal	O
with	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Bowland	I-pers
says	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
known	O
Peake	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
five	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
has	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
for	O
16	O
Years	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Lad	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Peake	O
in	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
Womb	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
always	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
383.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
*	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
one	O
Quart	O
Bottles	O
,	O
full	O
of	O
White	O
Wine	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
eighteen	O
large	O
Candles	O
.	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Jul	O
,	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
October	O
1740	O
.	O
No	O
459	O
,	O
p.	O
255.	O
William	B-pers
Blackhall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Cooper	O
to	O
Mr	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
about	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
July	O
26	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Mr	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Vault	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
21	O
Quart	O
Bottles	O
of	O
White-Wine	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
large	O
Cellar	O
Candles	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Jew	O
)	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
July	O
25	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Fenchurch	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Iron	O
.	O
lifted	O
a	O
Plank	O
up	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
twenty-one	O
Bottles	O
of	O
White	O
Wine	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
the	O
Wine	O
and	O
the	O
Candles	O
for	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Alvares	O
,	O
a	O
jew	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Plank	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
watching	O
.	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
we	O
put	O
the	O
Plank	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	B-pers
.	I-pers
-	O
I	O
never	O
accused	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
two	O
Jews	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
impeached	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
?	O
Pass	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Fido	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
is	O
a	O
Framework-knitter	O
and	O
Cap-maker	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
bore	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
just	O
Lad	O
.	O
-	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Pump-Court	O
by	O
Devonshire-square	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Bishopgate	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
Stockings	O
to	O
fit	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
Pass	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
is	O
his	O
Whore	O
.	O
-	O
Green	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Thing	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Pass	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
26th	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
married	O
that	O
very	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Pass	O
's	O
Wedding	O
about	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
Clay	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
two	O
more	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
have	O
troubled	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
clear	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
.	O
Pass	O
said	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Consinement	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
troubled	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Concern	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
,	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
Aaron	B-pers
Polock	I-pers
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
asking	O
Pass	O
concerning	O
his	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
got	O
a	O
Penny	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
384.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cullin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
,	O
August	O
29	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr	O
Emmery	O
's	O
in	O
Artillery	O
lane	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
Sev'nnight	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Mistres	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
somebody	O
behind	O
the	O
Curtain	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
what	O
does	O
any	O
Body	O
do	O
in	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Room	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hearing	O
me	O
crying	O
out	O
bitterly	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
hush	O
Jenny	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shirt	O
.	O
John	O
Hill	O
After	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
200	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
this	O
Shirt	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
[	O
Edward	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
]	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
barbarous	O
young	O
Fellows	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
what	O
we	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
385.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
3	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Remnent	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Remnent	I-pers
proved	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Lead	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Essex-street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Lead	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
386.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Worley	I-pers
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Worley	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Stew-pans	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rastel	I-pers
proved	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr	O
Worley	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
387.	O
Ann	B-pers
Warbee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Mob	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
388.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Silk	O
dyed	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
six	O
Bobbins	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Pound	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Spragg	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
July	O
3	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
Bobbins	O
(	O
with	O
Silk	O
upon	O
them	O
)	O
with	O
Mr	O
Dyer	O
's	O
Mark	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
Mary	B-pers
Colloway	I-pers
's	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
suspecting	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr	O
Dyer	O
,	O
who	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
his	O
Servant	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Bobbins	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Silk	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
389.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harford	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
Gown	O
to	O
make	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Williams	O
's	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
it	O
would	O
fit	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
tried	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
two	O
Hours	O
following	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
Mrs	O
Williams	O
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
she	O
threatened	O
to	O
kick	O
me	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Gown	O
then	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
consent	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
try	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Gentlewoman	O
(	O
Mrs	O
May	O
)	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
this	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
for	O
just	O
such	O
another	O
fat	O
arsed	O
Creature	O
as	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
Word	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
indeed	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
served	O
the	O
Warrant	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
have	O
the	O
Gown	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
the	O
Gown	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
own	O
Gown	O
fetched	O
and	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
She	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Teeth	O
out	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
390.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Napkin	O
and	O
Clout	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
for	O
some	O
Quilting	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
;	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
there	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
2nd	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Quilter	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Glover	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
two	O
Trades	O
,	O
besides	O
what	O
you	O
learned	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Clout	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Clout	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
391.	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
John	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
Cambridge	O
,	O
Aug.	O
13	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wolley	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Dunkin	I-pers
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
between	O
his	O
Shirt	O
and	O
his	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Hands	O
were	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cod-piece	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Lumpers	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Family	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
and	O
two	O
Children	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
392	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Danson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
in	O
January	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Danson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
fine	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Parlour	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
before	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Styles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Hemp-dresser	O
in	O
Tothill-Fields	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Place	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
about	O
100	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Apron	O
tied	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
Home	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
393.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gritton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Toote	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
394.	O
Bacon	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dolphin	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
395.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Ounces	O
of	O
frost	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
.	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
Silver-Spinner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
spun	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Gold-frost	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
a	O
Shop	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
Quill	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
five	O
Ounces	O
;	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
left	O
his	O
Work	O
that	O
Morning	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
among	O
Mr	O
Sharp	O
's	O
Boys	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
very	O
orderly	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
in	O
Barbican	O
for	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
d.	O
1/2	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
Ounces	O
and	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
wt	O
.	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Ounce	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
burnt	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Silversmith	O
:	O
but	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
fair	O
Market	O
Price	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
burnt	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
burn	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
burnt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
very	O
well	O
know	O
new	O
Goods	O
from	O
old	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Name	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Though	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
the	O
full	O
Price	O
,	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
buying	O
such	O
Things	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
.	O
Panton	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
as	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
signify	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
396	O
,	O
397.	O
Mary	B-pers
Danks	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Damsel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Yards	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
8	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
398.	O
Johanna	B-pers
Kemmet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Coral	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
with	O
six	O
Silver	O
Bells	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Corral	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
cost	O
me	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Coral	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Silver	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
very	O
well	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
advis	O
'd	O
Mr	O
Clifton	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
cautious	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
dealt	O
,	O
left	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
indicted	O
himself	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
399.	O
Philip	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
25	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Spoon	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wakelyn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
this	O
Spoon	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
a	O
Crest	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
her	O
Name	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
ten	O
Months	O
as	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Recommendation	O
of	O
Sir	O
Watkin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
Time	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
his	O
Friends	O
have	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Characters	O
in	O
Wales	O
.	O
-	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Brewer	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
18	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
entrusted	O
with	O
50	O
or	O
60	O
l.	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Cousin	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
is	O
about	O
22	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eighteen	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Family	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
whole	O
Generation	O
are	O
so	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
400.	O
Christian	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Proctor	I-pers
,	O
*	O
of	O
St	O
Ann	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leghorn	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Cranbourne-Alley	O
;	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
Interposition	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
appearing	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
P.	O
199	O
,	O
No	O
325	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Green	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
Cranbourne-Alley	O
,	O
by	O
Leicester-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
too	O
large	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
another	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
a	O
Hat	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pinned	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
to	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
none	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
Sixpence	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
to	O
carry	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
As	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
Green	O
said	O
,	O
Oh	O
,	O
you	O
Hussey	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
my	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
just	O
now	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
401	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Hanks	O
of	O
Brass	O
Wire	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fossick	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Fowkes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
Fossick	O
lost	O
fifteen	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Wire	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Tub	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sieve-maker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Pound	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Brass	O
Wire	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Price	O
I	O
give	O
is	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
such	O
small	O
Quantities	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
me	O
more	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
fetched	O
this	O
Parcel	O
of	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
must	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
are	O
but	O
Mr	O
Fossick	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
that	O
draw	O
this	O
Sort	O
of	O
Wire	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
to	O
Mr	O
Fossick	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Iron	O
Candlesticks	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
this	O
Wire	O
to	O
Mr	O
Mills	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Birmingham	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
the	O
Pound	O
and	O
Quarter	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Wire	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
into	O
my	O
Charge	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
more	O
impudent	O
than	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
Mr	O
Ellis	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
Wire	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Brass	O
Wire-Drawer	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
bad	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Birmingham	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
broke	O
a	O
Bit	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
keep	O
a	O
Sample	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
Case	O
he	O
should	O
hear	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
since	O
the	O
Man	O
broke	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Wire	O
does	O
not	O
look	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
above	O
three	O
Months	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
positively	O
sure	O
that	O
this	O
Wire	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
but	O
Mr	O
Fossick	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
402.	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
*	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
Cambrick	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s	O
five	O
Cambrick	O
Stocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Cambrick	O
Night	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
One	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felony	O
,	O
Dec	O
.	O
Sessions	O
,	O
1739.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Sir	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Waggon	O
Load	O
of	O
Goods	O
carried	O
down	O
to	O
Sir	O
Jonathan	O
's	O
Seat	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
;	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
missed	O
when	O
the	O
Waggon	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Hamper	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Butler	O
pack	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
Sheets	O
from	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Doody	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
[	O
The	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
]	O
I	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
went	O
to	O
St	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
a	O
Fowl	O
,	O
(	O
Norman	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
us	O
then	O
)	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
Fowl	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
dressed	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pretends	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
dress	O
it	O
for	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
spent	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
Gin	O
at	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
-	O
they	O
kept	O
a	O
little	O
Gin-shop	O
,	O
and	O
harboured	O
nothing	O
but	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
it	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
Yards	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Wine	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Cafe-Knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Drawer	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Hamper	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
cut	O
the	O
Hamper	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Linnen	O
out	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
Norman	O
opened	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
our	O
Shares	O
,	O
among	O
us	O
four	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
one	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
discovered	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pawned	O
three	O
Sheets	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owes	O
us	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
now	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
a-piece	O
.	O
Q	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
here	O
?	O
Doody	O
.	O
But	O
once	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
against	O
one	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Havril	I-pers
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
.	O
+	O
Dec	O
.	O
Sessions	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
See	O
Trial	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Page	O
9	O
.	O
Q	O
Does	O
the	O
Carrier	O
set	O
up	O
his	O
Waggon	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Inn	O
in	O
St	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
?	O
Carr	O
He	O
sets	O
up	O
in	O
Smithfields	O
;	O
the	O
Waggon	O
stood	O
all	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
the	O
Crown-Inn	O
is	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Hog-lane	O
in	O
St	O
Giles	O
's	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
carry	O
the	O
Fowl	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
mine	O
?	O
Doody	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
or	O
your	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
pays	O
the	O
Rent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Linden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sat	O
out	O
at	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Waggon	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Crown-Inn	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
-	O
All	O
the	O
whole	O
Load	O
was	O
Sir	O
Jonathan	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
hired	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
Q	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
because	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
just	O
sure	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
under	O
do	O
it	O
than	O
over	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Pardien	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
three	O
Sheets	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Norman	O
-	O
she	O
always	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
was	O
Norman	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bring	O
some	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
-	O
his	O
Mother	O
fetched	O
them	O
out	O
-	O
his	O
Mother	O
asked	O
12	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
12	O
s.	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
creditable	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
made	O
no	O
Scruple	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Mark	B-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
C	I-pers
.	O
and	O
the	O
Cloth	O
is	O
like	O
ours	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Sheets	O
.	O
-	O
Ward	O
.	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
Sir	O
Jonathan	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Mark	O
.	O
Doody	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Shirts	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
picked	O
the	O
Letters	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
fine	O
Needle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
were	O
the	O
Marks	O
taken	O
.	O
Doody	O
.	O
Cut	O
of	O
the	O
Gussets	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
.	O
-	O
Ward	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
were	O
marked	O
on	O
the	O
Gussets	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
Skirts	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
those	O
Shirts	O
were	O
marked	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
use	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
pawn	O
Things	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
his	O
own	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
civil	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Fruiterer	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Market	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
these	O
sixty	O
Years	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
threescore	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
or	O
thirteen	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
Gardeners	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
Matthias	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gawthorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vanryse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
Years	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
committing	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Barney	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
opposite	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
Leg-Alley	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
403.	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Culver	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Culver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fenchurch-street	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
down	O
Grace-church	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
under	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
he	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
run	O
down	O
Old	O
Bethlehem	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
ask	O
Pardon	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bonfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
's	O
right	O
Hand	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
a	O
Lamp	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
404	O
.	O
+	O
Susanna	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hyrons	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hyrons	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
Home	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
Leicester-Fields	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
she	O
would	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Creed-lane	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Shrub	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Liquor	O
then	O
)	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
kiss	O
her	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Hyrons	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
missing	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
push	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
manner	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
described	O
her	O
Person	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Door	O
is	O
shut	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Creed-lane	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
lighted	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
in	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Watch	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
longer	O
with	O
her	O
above	O
Stairs	O
than	O
while	O
we	O
drank	O
the	O
Liquor	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
Minutes	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Waistcoat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
we	O
drank	O
the	O
Liquor	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
beating	O
my	O
Rounds	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
One	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
come	O
two	O
Minutes	O
sooner	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
prevented	O
his	O
being	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Watchman	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
House	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
cried	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
Rogue	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
call	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
break	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
she	O
knows	O
me	O
well	O
enough	O
,	O
she	O
need	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Nap	O
of	O
Sleep	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
Things	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
close	O
shut	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr	O
Owen	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
Jobb	O
for	O
him	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
any	O
Beer	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Let	O
us	O
do	O
Business	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Madam	O
and	O
her	O
Partner	O
coming	O
by	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
11	O
;	O
thinks	O
I	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
has	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
gone	O
into	O
that	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Windows	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
Bawdy-houses	O
generally	O
are	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
pushed	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Robbery	O
swore	O
against	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
keep	O
you	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
a	O
Man	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Wife	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
your	O
Wife	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mind	O
your	O
Wife	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
Plague	O
in	O
Hell	O
did	O
you	O
never	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
go	O
by	O
you	O
ten	O
Times	O
a	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Time	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
out	O
till	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
Night	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
in	O
due	O
Time	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
after	O
that	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
without	O
my	O
knowing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
Key	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Kelly	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
commonly	O
leave	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
mend	O
a	O
Slit	O
in	O
her	O
Shoe	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
She	O
sells	O
Fruit	O
.	O
Patrick	O
Wall	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
us	O
Good-morrow	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
about	O
seven	O
.	O
Ann	O
Wall	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
late	O
Hours	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
405.	O
James	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pace	I-pers
July	O
29	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mr	O
William	B-pers
Gyles	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Founder	O
in	O
Shoe	O
Lane	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
brought	O
some	O
Shruff	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Clippings	O
of	O
Copper	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
three	O
Pound	O
,	O
nine	O
Ounces	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pace	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
happened	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
Shruff	O
at	O
Mr	O
Gyles	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
particular	O
Marks	O
he	O
swears	O
to	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pace	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
swears	O
to	O
about	O
half	O
the	O
Quantity	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Pace	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Years	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
406	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
India	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Great	B-place
Russel	I-place
street	I-place
into	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
or	O
feel	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
charged	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
Pardon	O
,	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
own	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
young	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
yellow	O
India	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
another	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
described	O
it	O
by	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
made	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
right-hand	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
close	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
seemingly	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
positively	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
The	O
Handkerchief	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
found	O
within	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Distance	O
of	O
Ten	O
Yards	O
from	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
excus	O
'd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
407	O
.	O
+	O
Silvester	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
called	I-pers
John	I-pers
Connor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
17th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
did	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
procure	O
William	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
a	O
Subject	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
foreign	O
Prince	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
without	O
Licence	O
first	O
had	O
and	O
obtained	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Sign	O
Manual	O
;	O
in	O
Contempt	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Laws	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
evil	O
Example	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
the	O
Indictment	O
further	O
charged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Silvester	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
8th	O
Day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
hire	O
,	O
and	O
retain	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
Silver	O
Coin	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
to	O
