TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
23d	O
and	O
THURSDAY	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
17th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Westley	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1744	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WESTLEY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BURNET	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENISON	O
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Legg	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baynham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Shipman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Colvill	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Huggett	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Increase	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
.	O
+	O
140.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Hensman	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
12	O
silver-handled	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
12	O
silver-handled	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver-handled	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver-handled	O
fork	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Deseret	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
EliZ	B-pers
GOODWIN	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Deseret	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
Amey	O
Deseret	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
after	O
tea	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
this	O
young	O
gentlewoman	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
GOODWIN	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
of	O
what	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
shirts	O
and	O
her	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
nine	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
silver-handled	O
knives	O
,	O
thirteen	O
forks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Deseret	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
discharged	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
in	O
our	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
body	O
but	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
supposed	O
her	O
husband	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Deseret	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
your	O
goods	O
again	O
?	O
Deseret	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
the	O
pint	O
mug	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
place	O
to	O
lock	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
let	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
could	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
without	O
her	O
knowledge	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
owned	O
since	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
three	O
spoons	O
in	O
Christmas	O
week	O
.	O
ELIZ	O
.	O
GOODWIN	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
she	O
carried	O
out	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
Christmas	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
,	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
?	O
GOODWIN	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
she	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
must	O
take	O
them	O
?	O
GOODWIN	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Medlicot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
28th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
goes	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
brought	O
three	O
spoons	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
crest	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
spoons	O
?	O
or	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
Embassador	O
for	O
a	O
debt	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
afterwards	O
who	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
believed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
herself	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
,	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
wherever	O
she	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
herself	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
lived	O
in	O
very	O
creditable	O
families	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
creditable	O
good	O
families	O
,	O
with	O
great	O
people	O
,	O
both	O
here	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
country	O
(	O
Holland	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
know	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
God	O
Almighty	O
take	O
my	O
soul	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
thing	O
,	O
indeed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
three	O
spoons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
141.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Templeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Filks	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Filks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bedford	B-place
Arms	I-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
;	O
Mrs.	O
Dyley	O
brought	O
the	O
spoon	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
engraved	O
round	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
Bedford	O
Arms	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Dyley	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
spoon	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
writing	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
writing	O
round	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
142.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Malcher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Slade	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Goodman	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
stairs	O
to	O
be	O
dirty	O
with	O
somebody	O
's	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
traced	O
the	O
steps	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
feet	O
,	O
that	O
somebody	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
rooms	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
a	O
closet	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Goodman	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Malcher	I-pers
.	O
Hearing	O
somebody	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
hung	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
concealed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
lying	O
partly	O
upon	O
a	O
box	O
and	O
partly	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
breeches	O
under	O
them	O
.	O
Slade	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
upon	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
peg	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
they	O
fall	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Box	O
?	O
Bowler	O
.	O
Not	O
very	O
well	O
-	O
They	O
might	O
fall	O
upon	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
-	O
The	O
box	O
stood	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
peg	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
impossible	O
they	O
could	O
fall	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
described	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
peg	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
sea	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
served	O
three	O
years	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
got	O
four	O
to	O
serve	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
escape	O
a	O
press-gang	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
habit	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
pressed	O
.	O
Bowler	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
dress	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
livery	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
sailors	O
waiting	O
to	O
press	O
me	O
?	O
This	O
was	O
denied	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dalby	O
,	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dalby	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
who	O
lives	O
there	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
in	O
the	O
Hope	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
entrusted	O
with	O
plate	O
and	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
143.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Colechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rammell	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rammell	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
-	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
saw	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
his	O
shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
he	O
from	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Rammell	O
.	O
Not	O
an	O
inch	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
144.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
and	I-place
Bird	I-place
Cage	I-place
in	O
Woodstreet	B-place
;	O
last	O
Shrove	O
Tuesday	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
two	O
plates	O
off	O
a	O
dresser	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
things	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
caught	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Blakemore	I-pers
.	O
The	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Norman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
in	O
comes	O
this	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
looking	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
shelves	O
and	O
viewing	O
the	O
pewter	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
cocks	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
breast	O
like	O
pewter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
two	O
plates	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
those	O
plates	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Norman	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
theirs	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
plates	O
of	O
the	O
maid	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
them	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
slice	O
of	O
meat	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
maid	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
that	O
neighbourhood	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Punch	O
Bowl	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
your	O
bosom	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
words	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Blakemore	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
plates	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
meat	O
.	O
Blakemore	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Norman	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
mix	O
the	O
plates	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
145.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
of	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
20	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
the	O
Farrier	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
lay	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
informed	O
them	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pursued	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
Great	O
Moregate	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
way	O
up	O
into	O
an	O
inn	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
Gate	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
theirs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
iron	O
?	O
Wade	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
iron	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
bar	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
146.	O
John	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Fleet	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
another	O
man	O
's	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
's	O
coat	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
bill	O
is	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
search	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
147.	O
Richard	B-pers
Durose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Colechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
of	O
nutmegs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
17	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
Grocer	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
nutmegs	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
give	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
those	O
nutmegs	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
bring	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
protested	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
a	O
nutmeg	O
these	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
chocolate-maker	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
for	O
me	O
)	O
for	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
lose	O
his	O
work	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
some	O
nutmegs	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
charge	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
begged	O
my	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
done	O
so	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Oram	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
somewhere	O
by	O
the	O
Turnstile	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
to	O
whom	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
nutmegs	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
these	O
nutmegs	O
?	O
Oram	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
60	O
or	O
70	O
pound	O
weight	O
in	O
a	O
cask	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
cellar-door	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
down	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
your	O
character	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
Oram	O
.	O
Before	O
this	O
thing	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
fellow	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
thousand	O
weight	O
of	O
chocolate	O
for	O
me	O
last	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
thousand	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
five	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
offered	O
the	O
nutmegs	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
chocolate	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
148.	O
Jane	B-pers
Aspley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Wood	O
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
aprons	O
,	O
the	O
petticoat	O
,	O
stockings	O
and	O
shoes	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wood	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
my	O
gown	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
for	O
six-pence	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
apron	O
,	O
stockings	O
and	O
shoes	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
gate-house	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
afterwards	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
my	O
gown	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
apron	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
A	O
lodger	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
house	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
149.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bladder	O
of	O
six	O
pound	O
of	O
hogs	O
lard	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Burroughs	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
a	O
bladder	O
of	O
hogs	O
lard	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
mysel	O
f.	O
He	O
looked	O
me	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
send	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
:	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
guilty	O
person	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
person	O
and	O
clothes	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
Black	O
Boy	O
Alley	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
probably	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
scolding	O
and	O
fighting	O
together	O
:	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
wife	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
hearing	O
some	O
girls	O
singing	O
of	O
ballads	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
prove	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
balled-singers	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
150	O
.	O
+	O
Isabella	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Matthias	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Miles	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
without	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Matthias	O
's	O
maid-servant	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
peep	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
supposed	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
observe	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
151.	O
Richard	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Stratford	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
pestle	O
and	O
mortar	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Crane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
five	B-place
bells	I-place
at	O
Bow	B-place
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
my	O
mistress	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
pestle	O
and	O
mortar	O
off	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Higgs	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
mortar	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pestle	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
ale	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
running	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
hold	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
152	O
.	O
+	O
Margaret	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Haddock	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
bagnio	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
between	O
Hungerford	O
and	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
caught	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
pocket	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
before	O
her	O
hand	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
put	O
your	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
together	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
together	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
before	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Just	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
all	O
about	O
14	O
s.	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
pieces	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
all	O
shillings	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ne'er	O
a	O
six-pence	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
full	O
change	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
some	O
money	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spent	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
had	O
you	O
spent	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
nine	O
pence	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nine	O
pence	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Very	O
little	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
open	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
retrieve	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
taken	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
kept	O
her	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
offer	O
me	O
three	O
pence	O
at	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
oblige	O
you	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
so	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Jennings	O
.	O
By	O
virtue	O
of	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
pull	O
me	O
and	O
haul	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
By	O
virtue	O
of	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
spending	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
more	O
.	O
Jennings	O
.	O
By	O
virtue	O
of	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
false	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
what	O
pretence	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Did	O
she	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
pick	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
space	O
of	O
time	O
was	O
there	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
transaction	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
thereabout	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pick	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
she	O
pick	O
you	O
up	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
She	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
with	O
one	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
searched	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
searched	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
proposed	O
searching	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
half	O
guineas	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
by	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
three	O
pence	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
gate-way	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
his	O
three	O
pence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
spending	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
bitch	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
153.	O
Edward	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
eight	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Inglish	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Inglish	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
halfpence	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
blamed	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
looked	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
eight	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
punch	O
bowl	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
from	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
upon	O
this	O
?	O
Inglish	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Edward	O
Wall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Headborough	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Inglish	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
half-pence	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cupboard	O
in	O
Inglish	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
punch-bowl	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Malton	I-pers
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
on	O
that	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
154.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cleaver	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Abraham	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
called	O
Brewhouse-Yard	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
an	O
iron	O
cork-skrew	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
pen-knife	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
3.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
Jan.	O
being	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Ship-Tavern	B-place
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	B-place
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Burr-street	B-place
(	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
person	O
with	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
)	O
passing	O
through	O
Brewhouse-Yard	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
overtaken	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
run	O
after	O
,	O
by	O
four	O
lusty	O
young	O
fellows	O
,	O
who	O
bid	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
carried	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
light	O
(	O
they	O
run	O
after	O
me	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
pace	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
at	O
first	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
press-gang	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
up	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
pass	O
by	O
)	O
the	O
man	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
ready	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
light	O
out	O
as	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
readily	O
finding	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
knocked	O
the	O
man	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
fell	O
and	O
broke	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
one	O
stood	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
stood	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
had	O
pistols	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
the	O
light	O
being	O
out	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
pistols	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
rifled	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pen-knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tobacco-stopper	O
and	O
cork-skrew	O
;	O
they	O
detained	O
me	O
near	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
used	O
me	O
with	O
more	O
roughness	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
demanded	O
a	O
watch	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
me	O
very	O
narrowly	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
tavern	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
taken	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Justice	O
Dennet	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
had	O
Francis	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
before	O
him	O
under	O
examination	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
Justice	O
Dennet	O
,	O
for	O
knocking	O
down	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
hearing	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
that	O
person	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Sherlock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
voice	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
than	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
was	O
so	O
soon	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
Sherlock	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
impeached	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
upon	O
this	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
Sherlock	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
went	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
got	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
privateers	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
ago	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Street	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
well	O
dressed	O
,	O
genteel	O
,	O
young	O
fellows	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
dress	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
He	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
size	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
young	O
,	O
and	O
active	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
any	O
concern	O
in	O
attacking	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
or	O
third	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
mistaken	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
committed	O
that	O
robbery	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Robert	B-pers
Rocket	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Neagle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Cleaver	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
pursued	O
him	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Brewhouse-yard	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
new	O
Hermitage	O
Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
first	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
Rocket	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
overtook	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
knocked	O
the	O
man	O
down	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
shoved	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Neagle	O
was	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
Rocket	O
at	O
his	O
right-hand	O
,	O
and	O
Cleaver	O
at	O
his	O
left	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
rifled	O
him	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
Cleaver	O
and	O
Rocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
take	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
divided	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
all	O
in	O
six-pences	O
,	O
but	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
pen-knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tobacco-stopper	O
and	O
cork-screw	O
in	O
one	O
;	O
Neagle	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
o'night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Minories	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
gave	O
Cleaver	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
hanger	O
out	O
of	O
pledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
stopped	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
over	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
Neagle	O
stepped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
a	O
gentleman	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
all	O
four	O
go	O
there	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
four	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
over	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
Neagle	O
and	O
Rocket	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
because	O
Neagle	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
(	O
Rocket	O
and	O
Cleaver	O
)	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
gold	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fight	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
++	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
cloak	O
on	O
,	O
muffled	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
cold	O
night	O
)	O
Neagle	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
rascal	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
strike	O
the	O
gentleman	O
for	O
?	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
you	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
stunned	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
three	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
our	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
affair	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
my	O
escape	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
part	O
,	O
because	O
no	O
harm	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
++	O
Mr.	O
Willoughby	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
so	O
't	O
is	O
probable	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
witness	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
or	O
them	O
upon	O
such	O
an	O
account	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
+	O
.	O
+	O
He	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Pidgeon	O
,	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
evidence	O
,	O
as	O
appears	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Trial	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
place	O
did	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
We	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Charles	O
Street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
the	O
first	O
robbery	O
you	O
committed	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
robbery	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pidgeon	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
.	O
Cleaver	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
without	O
danger	O
of	O
being	O
pressed	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
waiting	O
to	O
rob	O
one	O
Esquire	O
Wynn	O
;	O
but	O
missing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
indeed	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
with	O
that	O
gentleman	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wynn	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
getting	O
some	O
liquor	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
this	O
Rocket	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
out	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
without	O
company	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
pressed	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
these	O
three	O
persons	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
tell	O
in	O
particular	O
where	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Minories	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Rocket	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
Neagle	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
shillings	O
apiece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
hanger	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
;	O
and	O
Neagle	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain	O
and	O
Shovel	O
in	O
Thames	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
passed	O
at	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
tried	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
they	O
say	O
is	O
taken	O
,	O
is	O
brought	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
better	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
155	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Cleaver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Pidgeon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pidgeon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
St.	B-place
Catharine	I-place
's	I-place
into	O
Burr	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
standing	O
and	O
laughing	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
passed	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
ship	O
I	O
belonged	O
to	O
:	O
I	O
answered	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
their	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
walked	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
officer	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
:	O
They	O
rifled	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Pidgeon	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
first	O
per	O
son	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
The	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Willoughby	O
sent	O
to	O
acquaint	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
prison	O
,	O
Sherlock	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire-side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pitched	O
upon	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
light	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
robbed	O
?	O
Pidgeon	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
light	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
took	O
me	O
for	O
her	O
father	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
stamped	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Oh	O
lah	O
,	O
Oh	O
lah	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
?	O
Then	O
he	O
that	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
shoot	O
the	O
girl	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Neagle	O
,	O
Cleaver	O
and	O
Rocket	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Jerusalem	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Square	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
upon	O
such	O
an	O
affair	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
coward	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
they	O
should	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Bishopsgate	O
Street	O
,	O
drank	O
some	O
slip	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
Stepney	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
boy	O
with	O
a	O
link	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
other	O
peopl	O
e	O
,	O
we	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
worth	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
captain	O
Pidgeon	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
a	O
captain	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
in	O
Holland	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
mate	O
of	O
a	O
merchant-man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
certainly	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
first	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
Neagle	O
and	O
Rocket	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
ship	O
?	O
Cleaver	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
.	O
-	O
No	O
body	O
attacked	O
him	O
but	O
them	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
there	O
a	O
guinea	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Cleaver	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
Cleaver	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
neither	O
.	O
-	O
Neagle	O
and	O
Rocket	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
Neagle	O
and	O
Rocket	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
stopped	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
standing	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
two	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
We	O
spent	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
a	O
night-house	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
had	O
you	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
but	O
seventeen-pence	O
half-penny	O
.	O
-	O
Rocket	O
might	O
keep	O
the	O
guinea	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
Cleaver	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
spending	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Cleaver	O
then	O
?	O
Sherlock	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
buy	O
some	O
barley-sugar	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
for	O
his	O
cold	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
indeed	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
knock	O
at	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
door	O
a	O
stone's-throw	O
off	O
:	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Newgate	O
Market	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
striking	O
and	O
abusing	O
people	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pastry-cook	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
barleysugar	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
home	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
+	O
156	O
,	O
157.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
and	O
Edmund	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
twenty	O
three	O
bottles	O
of	O
Hungary	O
water	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
and	O
robbed	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Wych-Street	B-place
,	O
of	O
twenty	O
three	O
bottles	O
of	O
Hungary	O
water	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Petty	O
seized	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
parcel	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
parcel	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
Smith	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
a	O
stick	O
of	O
an	O
uncommon	O
size	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
repeated	O
many	O
oaths	O
,	O
which	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
Petty	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
parcel	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
help	O
!	O
I	O
recovered	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
Smith	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
and	O
finding	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
stronger	O
than	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
pretty	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
somebody	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
Petty	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
secured	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
make	O
any	O
excuse	O
in	O
the	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
no	O
excuse	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
your	O
goods	O
again	O
.	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
has	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
first	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
they	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
Did	O
not	O
they	O
tell	O
you	O
they	O
were	O
Excise	O
Officers	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
hear	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Excisemen	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
they	O
say	O
so	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
they	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Excise-men	O
,	O
or	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Excise-Office	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
your	O
parcel	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
they	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
least	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
they	O
produce	O
their	O
deputations	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
remember	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
then	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pelleret	O
's	O
in	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
Hungary	O
water	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Sandys	O
,	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
tea	O
,	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
tea	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
you	O
in	O
mind	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
not	O
they	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
ask	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
besides	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Miles	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
.	O
This	O
bundle	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
?	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
Petty	O
did	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Wych-street	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
crowd	O
at	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nightingale	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
Smith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
Petty	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
again	O
.	O
Another	O
Excise-Officer	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
)	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
light	O
of	O
this	O
Petty	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
step	O
out	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Petty	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
deputations	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
They	O
pretended	O
to	O
snew	O
some	O
deputation	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
's	O
Clerk	O
.	O
Smith	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Excise-Officer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
parcel	O
as	O
run	O
goods	O
-	O
Petty	O
denied	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
-	O
They	O
offered	O
to	O
produce	O
deputations	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
did	O
produce	O
any	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
swore	O
directly	O
contrary	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
say	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
justly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
they	O
differed	O
in	O
their	O
accounts	O
?	O
Tell	O
us	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
remember	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Petty	O
deny	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Justice	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
robbery	O
;	O
and	O
directed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
prefer	O
a	O
bill	O
at	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
PRISONERS	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
Attorney	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
back-side	O
of	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
,	O
Mr	O
Nightingale	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
run-goods	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Nightingale	O
say	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
molest	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
a	O
robbery	O
against	O
you	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
by	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
the	O
back-side	O
of	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
go	O
in	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Nightingale	O
,	O
demand	O
to	O
see	O
their	O
deputations	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
tell	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
Excise-Officers	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Excise-Officers	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
Council	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
before	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
neither	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
19th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Nightingale	O
came	O
together	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Nightingale	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
might	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
Nightingale	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
window	O
himself	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Excise-Officers	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
some	O
run	O
tea	O
;	O
Nightingale	O
was	O
for	O
sending	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
Smith	O
bid	O
Petty	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
Petty	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Nightingale	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
Excise-Officers	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Nightingale	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
heard	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
prosessed	O
themselves	O
to	O
be	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
their	O
deputations	O
.	O
A	O
worthy	O
Alderman	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
known	O
Petty	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
knowledge	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
believes	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
incapable	O
of	O
committing	O
a	O
dishonest	O
or	O
an	O
unjust	O
act	O
.	O
Justice	O
Engier	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
known	O
Petty	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
believes	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
for	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
person	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
just	O
,	O
fair	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
granted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
their	O
indictment	O
.	O
158.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
her	O
male	O
bastard	O
child	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
necessary	O
house	O
filled	O
with	O
excrement	O
and	O
other	O
filth	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
choaked	O
and	O
suffocated	O
,	O
and	O
thereof	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
159.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
six	O
silver	O
clasps	O
for	O
stocks	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
dimithy	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pin	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
till	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
watches	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
watches	O
,	O
and	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
watches	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Stringer	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
's	O
,	O
another	O
Charles	B-pers
Day	I-pers
's	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
pledged	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
metal	O
one	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
business	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
(	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
an	O
account	O
)	O
were	O
offered	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
sustian	O
to	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
into	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
is	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
cut	O
out	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
waistcoats	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bowers	O
,	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
acquaint	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
pledge	O
this	O
large	O
metal	O
watch	O
for	O
eight	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Stringer	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Colonel	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
show	O
you	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
Stringer	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
watch	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Lady	O
Mordington	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
gaming	O
table	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Colonel	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
who	O
waits	O
at	O
the	O
gaming	O
table	O
,	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
watch	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
waistcoats	O
were	O
shown	O
before	O
the	O
Colonel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
his	O
accomplices	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
four	O
pound	O
a-piece	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
dipped	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
about	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
gaming-table	O
;	O
some	O
silver	O
clasps	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
rings	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Stringer	O
said	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Stringer	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
pledge	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
for	O
eight	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
him	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Bowers	O
.	O
Nothing	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
Mr.	O
Stringer	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Bowers	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
three	O
pound	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
gold	O
one	O
.	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
all	O
the	O
persons	O
in	O
who	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
:	O
Those	O
two	O
watches	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
were	O
produced	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
the	O
metal	O
watch	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bowers	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
eight	O
pound	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
The	O
silver	O
watch	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
broke	O
the	O
minute	O
hand	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Pmy	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
how	O
many	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
there	O
are	O
in	O
those	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
the	O
lining	O
and	O
buttons	O
are	O
his	O
.	O
Stringer	O
.	O
The	O
lining	O
and	O
the	O
buttons	O
are	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
coals	O
and	O
wood	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
lived	O
a	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
carrying	O
out	O
coals	O
and	O
wood	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
months	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
three	O
months	O
since	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cantillion	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Armitage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
parish	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
sold	O
coals	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
myself	O
with	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
?	O
Armitage	O
.	O
I	O
moved	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
house	O
into	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
of	O
mine	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
drawer	O
himself	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
myself	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
forty	O
pound	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
very	O
safe	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
fellow	O
.	O
-	O
Renton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
consented	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
160	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
*	I-pers
Doody	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
of	O
flowered	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
evidence	O
against	O
Thomas	B-pers
Havril	I-pers
tried	O
in	O
December	O
Sessions	O
,	O
1742.	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
Trial	O
13	O
.	O
Page	O
9.	O
and	O
also	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
last	O
September	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Sir	O
Jonathan	O
Cope	O
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Trial	O
402	O
.	O
Page	O
233.	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
last	O
December	O
Session	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Trial	O
42	O
.	O
Page	O
15.	O
Richard	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
eating-house	O
over-against	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
my	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
flowered	O
lawn	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
somebody	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
pretty	O
quick	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q.	O
Where-abouts	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
he	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
for	O
my	O
mother	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
knocking	O
for	O
somebody	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
mother	O
wash	O
clothes	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
neither	O
know	O
him	O
nor	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
161.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
162	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
gold	O
coin	O
called	O
thirty	O
six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
36	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
lawful	O
money	O
of	O
Great-Britain	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Sibilla	B-pers
Hetherington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
Sibilla	O
Hetherington	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
church	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
four	O
thirty	O
six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
guineas	O
and	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
upwards	O
of	O
forty	O
pound	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
as	O
working	O
for	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
this	O
money	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
trunk	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
nails	O
were	O
drawn	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
trunk	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
represented	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Hetherington	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Hetherington	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
us	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
There	O
is	O
thirty	O
pound	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
[	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
shown	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
four	O
thirty	O
six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
guines	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
what	O
pieces	O
are	O
yours	O
?	O
Hetherington	O
.	O
These	O
four	O
thirty	O
six	O
shillings	O
pieces	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
is	O
a	O
crooked	O
piece	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
guineas	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
alike	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
163	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keate	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
two	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pound	O
of	O
bohea	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
two	O
pound	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
.	O
Yesterday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shutter	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
thrown	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
cannisters	O
with	O
two	O
pound	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
upon	O
a	O
shelf	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
till	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
four	O
pence	O
in	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
shutters	O
up	O
myself	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
pin	O
which	O
goes	O
through	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
turning	O
the	O
pin	O
round	O
the	O
key	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
catch	O
;	O
and	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
and	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
cannisters	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
on	O
Addle	O
Hill	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Thomas	O
Street	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
smugglers	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Alderman	O
's	O
beadle	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
were	O
laid	O
under	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Canfield	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
till	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
or	O
upwards	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
court	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
lives	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
live	O
,	O
who	O
sells	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
beg	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
up	O
Addle	O
Hill	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
gin	O
,	O
which	O
some	O
smugglers	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
lived	O
by	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
promise	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
again	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
cannisters	O
with	O
tea	O
,	O
some	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
sugar	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
will	O
bring	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
scrape	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
fairly	O
by	O
these	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
neither	O
should	O
he	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
should	O
hear	O
of	O
somebody	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
those	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Canfield	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
joiner	O
and	O
carpenter	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
shop-mate	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
directly	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
your	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
your	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
Prosecutor	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
smugglers	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
he	O
gone	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Canfield	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
farthest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
off	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Canfield	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
at	O
farthest	O
three	O
stones	O
throw	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
About	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Guild-Hall	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
would	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
-	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
sacking	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
in	O
this	O
bag	O
[	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
Cave	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
bag	O
,	O
this	O
spoon	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
with	O
two	O
E	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
B.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
may	O
it	O
be	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lives	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
stones	O
throw	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
have	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
given	O
by	O
some	O
smugglers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Canfield	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
smuggler	O
's	O
goods	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
tea	O
was	O
in	O
cannisters	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Canfield	O
tasted	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
say	O
was	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
vinegar	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Druitt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gun-lock	O
maker	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
then	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
164.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Collett	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
sev'night	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
was	O
surrounded	O
by	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
women	O
,	O
who	O
forced	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Love	B-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
in	O
George	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bade	O
me	O
strip	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
fetch	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
who	O
should	O
knock	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
stripped	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
up	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
she	O
with	O
you	O
before	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
that	O
forced	O
me	O
into	O
bed	O
.	O
They	O
left	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
they	O
forced	O
me	O
into	O
bed	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
bed	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
it	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
breeches	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
bolster	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
six-pence	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
papers	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
all	O
you	O
had	O
in	O
your	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
I	O
had	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
brought	O
up	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
away	O
to	O
another	O
woman	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
breeches	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buttons	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sleeves	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
up	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
who	O
were	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
stung	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
breeches	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
some	O
people	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
got	O
some	O
assistance	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
only	O
the	O
woman	O
whom	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
six-pence	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
six-pence	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
them	O
to	O
hard	O
labour	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
pretends	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
brought	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
the	O
Alderman	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
were	O
hurried	O
up	O
by	O
2	O
dozen	O
women	O
.	O
Cox	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
by	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
Women	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
a	O
market	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
about	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
call	O
out	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
stopped	O
my	O
mouth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
run	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
complain	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
those	O
people	O
who	O
were	O
nearest	O
you	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
ready	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
women	O
with	O
abusing	O
and	O
robbing	O
you	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
Not	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
order	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
be	O
pawned	O
for	O
your	O
convenience	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
Hebborn	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
at	O
night	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
'S	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Amps	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Swan-Alley	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
clear-stearcher	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
linen	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
to	O
clean	O
-	O
We	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
sup	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
eat	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
after	O
supper	O
,	O
it	O
began	O
to	O
rain	O
hard	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
bed	O
at	O
your	O
service	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Catheral	I-pers
.	O
Saturday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Amps	O
's	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
from	O
nine	O
till	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
supper	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Amps	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Amps	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
your	O
wife	O
?	O
Amps	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
able	O
to	O
support	O
her	O
without	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
forced	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
you	O
be	O
there	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
that	O
Alley	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Cox	O
.	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
165.	O
Richard	B-pers
Blay	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
fifteen	O
Mocha	O
stone	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
166.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
167	O
,	O
168	O
,	O
Winifred	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Mayers	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Mayers	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
jeweller	O
,	O
Soloman	B-pers
Mayers	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
jeweller	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Mayers	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
fourth	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
15th	O
year	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
George	O
,	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christopher	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
ward	O
of	O
Bread	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
did	O
unlawfully	O
conspire	O
,	O
combine	O
,	O
and	O
consult	O
together	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
laceman	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
by	O
unlawful	O
and	O
deceitful	O
ways	O
and	O
means	O
,	O
to	O
cheat	O
and	O
defraud	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
,	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Winifred	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
having	O
four	O
East-India	O
bonds	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
N	O
11453	O
,	O
dated	O
Sep.	O
30	O
,	O
1708.	O
which	O
is	O
set	O
forth	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Company	O
,	O
trading	O
to	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
12179	O
,	O
dated	O
June	O
22	O
,	O
1711	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
15106	O
,	O
dated	O
July	O
22	O
,	O
1712	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
16388	O
,	O
dated	O
Nov.	O
16	O
,	O
1713.	O
which	O
are	O
set	O
forth	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
united	O
Company	O
of	O
Merchants	O
of	O
England	O
trading	O
to	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
East-India	O
Company	O
having	O
given	O
due	O
and	O
publick	O
notice	O
in	O
the	O
London	O
Gazette	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1729.	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
and	O
discharge	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
bonds	O
,	O
that	O
bond	O
ceased	O
to	O
carry	O
any	O
further	O
interest	O
from	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
then	O
next	O
ensuing	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Company	O
having	O
given	O
the	O
like	O
notice	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1730.	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
and	O
discharge	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
bonds	O
,	O
those	O
also	O
ceased	O
to	O
carry	O
any	O
further	O
interest	O
from	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
then	O
next	O
ensuing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
1730.	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
continually	O
to	O
the	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
there	O
remained	O
due	O
and	O
payable	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Company	O
,	O
over	O
and	O
above	O
the	O
principal	O
sums	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
on	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
bonds	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
96	O
l.	O
for	O
interest	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
said	O
four	O
bonds	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
the	O
said	O
Winifred	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
falsely	O
,	O
freudulently	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
and	O
deceitfully	O
declare	O
,	O
affirm	O
,	O
and	O
assert	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
that	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
such	O
publick	O
notices	O
,	O
had	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
petition	O
of	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Winifred	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
at	O
a	O
General	O
Court	O
by	O
them	O
holden	O
,	O
ordered	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
four	O
bonds	O
should	O
carry	O
interest	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
likewise	O
assert	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
then	O
due	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Company	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
four	O
bonds	O
,	O
the	O
full	O
sum	O
of	O
665	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
falsely	O
and	O
deceitfully	O
entice	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
to	O
pay	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Winifred	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
sum	O
of	O
665	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
which	O
sum	O
he	O
,	O
giving	O
credit	O
and	O
belief	O
to	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
declarations	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
actually	O
pay	O
into	O
the	O
proper	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Winifred	O
,	O
as	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
due	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Company	O
,	O
on	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
purchase	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
bonds	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
and	O
means	O
whereof	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
did	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
pay	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Winifred	O
169	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
more	O
than	O
was	O
really	O
due	O
;	O
and	O
thereby	O
the	O
said	O
Winifred	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
fraudulently	O
obtain	O
from	O
,	O
cheat	O
and	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
of	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
169	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
deceit	O
,	O
fraud	O
and	O
demage	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
in	O
contempt	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
laws	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
evil	O
example	O
of	O
all	O
others	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
the	O
bonds	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
proved	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
East-India	O
Company	O
's	O
bonds	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Secretary	O
to	O
the	O
East-India	O
Company	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
minutes	O
of	O
the	O
proceedings	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
minute	O
made	O
at	O
a	O
General	O
Court	O
holden	O
the	O
