TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
18th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Westley	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1744	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WESTLEY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENISON	O
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whipham	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Prue	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Niccoll	I-pers
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
.	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Calloway	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnett	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
352	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Letitia	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
;	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Goving	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
Letitia	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
my	O
niece	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
walking	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
towards	O
Kilburn	B-place
;	O
she	O
saw	O
three	O
boys	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
aunt	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
those	O
boys	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
they	O
are	O
but	O
boys	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
only	O
mushrooning	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
2	O
cloaks	O
upon	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
them	O
upon	O
our	O
backs	O
for	O
the	O
wind	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
right	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
the	O
cloaks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
anything	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
your	O
breast	O
?	O
Pennington	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
delive	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
any	O
pistol	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
gentleman	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
boys	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
rode	O
after	O
them	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
aunt	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
walking	O
towards	O
Kilburn	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
three	O
rogues	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
aunt	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
boys	O
a	O
mushrooning	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
that	O
my	O
aunt	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
here	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
nothing	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
stuff	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
her	O
breast	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
deliver	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
gentleman	O
on	O
horseback	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
the	O
cloaks	O
?	O
Goring	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
had	O
robbed	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
nigh	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
hold	O
when	O
the	O
gentleman	O
called	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
myself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
gentleman	O
say	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
directly	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
you	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
breath	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
any	O
farther	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
taking	O
a	O
little	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
accidentally	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
into	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
offered	O
White	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Headborough	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
two	O
more	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mrs.	O
Pennington	O
say	O
,	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
she	O
had	O
sworn	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
sworn	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
so	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
indeed	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
more	O
grace	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
353.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
4	O
d	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
9	O
d.	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
5	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Sindry	I-pers
,	O
August	O
14	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
little	O
thought	O
this	O
boy	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
age	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cried	O
and	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Aris	O
in	O
Baldwin's-Gardens	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
swept	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Aris	I-pers
.	O
This	O
boy	O
has	O
been	O
bringing	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
ever	O
since	O
March	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
his	O
mother	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
knows	O
what	O
I	O
say	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
-	O
Henley	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
mother	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
never	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
any	O
thing	O
these	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
about	O
eight	O
*	O
old	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
Children	O
under	O
nine	O
years	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
may	O
of	O
some	O
acts	O
that	O
imply	O
malice	O
in	O
themselves	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
354.	O
William	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
dishes	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
missed	O
some	O
pewter	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
emissaries	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Church-Lane	O
end	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
355	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Cheworth	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
59	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chairman	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
night	O
cellar	O
by	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
sixpence	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
and	O
60	O
guineas	O
;	O
though	O
I	O
swore	O
but	O
to	O
59	O
guineas	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
change	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
snuff	O
box	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
keeps	O
it	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
5	O
guineas	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
purse	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
45	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
snuff	O
box	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Haddock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
we	O
forced	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
we	O
came	O
about	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Haddock	O
's	O
purse	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
45	O
guineas	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wished	O
she	O
had	O
gone	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Flanders	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Haddock	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Haddock	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
might	O
know	O
me	O
though	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
,	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
privately	O
stealing	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
356	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
21	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Loxley	I-pers
,	O
July	O
21st	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Loxley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
Cups	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
put	O
6	O
guineas	O
into	O
a	O
purse	O
(	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
15	O
guineas	O
before	O
,	O
25	O
crown	O
pieces	O
and	O
6	O
half	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
put	O
this	O
purse	O
into	O
a	O
gown	O
sleeve	O
,	O
under	O
some	O
gowns	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
bedchamber	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
27	O
guineas	O
more	O
lay	O
visible	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
touched	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
into	O
the	O
drawer	O
and	O
missed	O
this	O
purse	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
concerning	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
a	O
little	O
confounded	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
wondered	O
I	O
should	O
mistrust	O
her	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
herself	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
let	O
other	O
people	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
)	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
drawer	O
the	O
key	O
did	O
not	O
easily	O
unlock	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
taken	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
key	O
found	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
opened	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Loxley	I-pers
said	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
chamber	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
remained	O
untouched	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
357	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
August	O
4th	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Swan-Alley	B-place
in	I-place
East-Smithfield	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lives	O
within	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
doors	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
sister	O
's	O
by	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Fence	O
*	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
were	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
except	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
child	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
The	O
cellar	O
,	O
the	O
drinking	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
kitchen	O
,	O
are	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
floor	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
4	O
foot	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
tankard	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
run	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
tankard	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
half	O
his	O
shirt	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
retaken	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
A	O
Fence	O
is	O
a	O
Receiver	O
of	O
stolen	O
goods	O
.	O
358.	O
Mary	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
perriwig	O
,	O
2	O
s	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Alvares	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stedder	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
lower	O
window	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alvares	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Clapton	B-place
,	O
towards	O
the	O
highway	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
shuffling	O
something	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
pursued	O
her	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
rod	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
behind	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
shirt	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
's	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alvare	O
's	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
over	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
chairwoman	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
robbed	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Hyans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shirt	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shirt	O
.	O
The	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
359.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Wheelwright	I-pers
,	O
August	O
10	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Wheelwright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bedchamber	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grubb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
gown	O
to	O
me	O
August	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
her	O
size	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
mistress	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
inquired	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
360	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Stratford	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
lamb	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nunnelly	I-pers
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nunnelly	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
lamb	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
of	O
mine	O
at	O
Stratford	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lamb	O
and	O
the	O
skin	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Potter	O
's	O
the	O
Constable	O
at	O
Bow	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
skin	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
mark	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
country	O
mark	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
lamb	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
field	O
by	O
Stratford	O
turnpike	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Boot	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
field	O
killing	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
sheep	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
perceiving	O
me	O
come	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
run	O
over	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
fields	O
before	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
who	O
ran	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
hatchet	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
lay	O
down	O
the	O
hatchet	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
his	O
hatchet	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stand	O
by	O
the	O
lamb	O
-	O
The	O
lamb	O
was	O
dead	O
and	O
warm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
skin	O
stripped	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
lamb	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
since	O
;	O
the	O
lamb	O
was	O
given	O
away	O
in	O
our	O
town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
skin	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
then	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
skin	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
16th	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lamb	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
head	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
skin	O
was	O
half	O
off	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Boot	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
killing	O
a	O
lamb	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Stratford	O
to	O
bring	O
some	O
beasts	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
market	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
several	O
market	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lamb	O
almost	O
dead	O
in	O
a	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
killed	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
as	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
361.	O
Lowry	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	O
of	O
White	B-place
Friers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
spoon	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lilly	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
Job	O
Lilly	O
.	O
This	O
Spoon	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
good	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
some	O
violence	O
used	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
't	O
is	O
stolen	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
this	O
boy	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
lad	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
spoon	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
him	O
too	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
let	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
a	O
journeyman	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
spoon	O
lie	O
about	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
journeyman	O
Baker	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
my	O
running	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
sixpence	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
three	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
if	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
me	O
all	O
my	O
life	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
362.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Talloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Powson	I-pers
,	O
September	O
3	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Powson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
pewter	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Powson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
hand-basket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
whether	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
lived	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
directly	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
pewter	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
pewter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
363.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Janes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Barthalomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
shop	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
ribbon	O
:	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
liking	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
another	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
cut	O
her	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
a	O
brown	O
ribbon	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
stooping	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
paper	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
ribbon	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
gentlewoman	O
who	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
left	O
side	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
watched	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
then	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
ribbon	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
why	O
should	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
being	O
night	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
determined	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
ribbon	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sladen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
ribbon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
fetched	O
her	O
back	O
-	O
The	O
ribbon	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
ever	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
ribbon	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Sladen	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
lay	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
midwife	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
got	O
all	O
my	O
women	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bembrick	I-pers
,	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Armourer	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Worth	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
364	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
July	O
21	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Leadenhall	B-place
Market	I-place
and	O
deal	O
in	O
lace	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
lace	O
for	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
some	O
;	O
(	O
she	O
held	O
her	O
apron	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
clandestine	O
manner	O
doubled	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
up	O
and	O
concealed	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
left	O
hand	O
that	O
held	O
her	O
apron	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
apron	O
covered	O
her	O
hand	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
lace	O
in	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
draw	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
afford	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
you	O
bid	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
design	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
buy	O
any	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
design	O
you	O
shall	O
steal	O
any	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
:	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
examination	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
dropped	O
the	O
lace	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
happened	O
to	O
slide	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
the	O
lace	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cut	O
off	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
leave	O
my	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sent	O
the	O
ring	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
accept	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
as	O
a	O
pledge	O
:	O
but	O
some	O
people	O
who	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
their	O
persuasion	O
she	O
did	O
charge	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
true	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
It	O
's	O
all	O
true	O
that	O
she	O
says	O
,	O
every	O
word	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
transgressing	O
the	O
law	O
in	O
putting	O
the	O
affair	O
up	O
,	O
till	O
my	O
neighbours	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gilstrop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
33	O
years	O
,	O
almost	O
from	O
her	O
cradle	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
has	O
known	O
her	O
eighteen	O
years	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
said	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
to	O
her	O
parents	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
ancient	O
people	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
365	O
,	O
366.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
holland	O
frock	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
dimitty	O
skirt	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
stay	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
laced	O
cap	O
,	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
Castle-Street	B-place
near	I-place
Rag-Fair	I-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
broke	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
away	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
Collet	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
confessed	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
-	O
Randall	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
old	O
clothes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Collet	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
wished	O
me	O
good	O
luck	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
two	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Fair	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
lap	O
full	O
of	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
before	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
deposed	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
confession	O
freely	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
every	O
particular	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
wrote	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
read	O
in	O
evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
freely	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
July	O
9	O
,	O
1744	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
.	O
``	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
faith	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
``	O
John	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
when	O
``	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
``	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
about	O
``	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
``	O
the	O
money	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
promised	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
ever	O
made	O
her	O
any	O
such	O
promise	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
declared	O
he	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
concerning	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
what	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
hang	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
West	I-pers
who	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Collet	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Studder	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
After	O
Studder	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Studder	O
is	O
as	O
guilty	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
and	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
flew	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
boxing	O
his	O
ears	O
and	O
abusing	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
367	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Hamlet	O
of	O
Bethnal-Green	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
15	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Grove	B-place
Street	I-place
in	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
stop	O
me	O
and	O
have	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
weapon	O
?	O
Sewell	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
an	O
ordinary	O
little	O
penknife	O
which	O
lay	O
open	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
-	O
It	O
lay	O
cross	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
15	O
d.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
fright	O
me	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
harm	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
some	O
money	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
then	O
left	O
us	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
some	O
way	O
from	O
us	O
we	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
us	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Sewell	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
robbed	O
her	O
of	O
15	O
d.	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
weapon	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
a	O
stick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Mary	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
say	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
fright	O
me	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sewell	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
stick	O
?	O
Sewell	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
the	O
knife	O
-	O
'T	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
beyond	O
Bishop	O
Bonner	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
run	O
before	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
green	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
swore	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
.	O
Sewell	O
and	O
Jackson	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
then	O
a	O
green	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
a	O
woollen	O
cap	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sewell	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
present	O
the	O
knife	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Sewell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
held	O
it	O
open	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
These	O
2	O
gentlewomen	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Weston	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
one	O
Capt	O
.	O
Luckerby	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
carried	O
home	O
my	O
work	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
fellow	O
run	O
along	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Price	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
running	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
run	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
sain	O
have	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
believe	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
these	O
gentlewomen	O
,	O
they	O
swore	O
hard	O
and	O
fast	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
six-pence	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
.	O
368.	O
John	B-pers
Bothaw	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
pounds	O
of	O
Mace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hayter	I-pers
,	O
merchant	O
,	O
August	O
10	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
act	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
at	O
the	O
water-side	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
this	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Plaistow	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
White's-yard	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
William	O
Gold	O
burne	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
dark	O
gate-way	O
by	O
Galley-Key	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
box	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
:	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
15	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mead	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Addison	O
at	O
the	O
water-side	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
desired	O
the	O
box	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
him	O
favour	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Bothaw	O
,	O
receive	O
mery	O
while	O
you	O
can	O
-	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
reply	O
,	O
You	O
black-guard	O
dog	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
is	O
it	O
of	O
yours	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
whom	O
I	O
saw	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
rug	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
:	O
And	O
some	O
people	O
will	O
scandalize	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
being	O
a	O
thief-taker	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
want	O
no	O
reward	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
sitting	O
with	O
others	O
and	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
;	O
and	O
got	O
information	O
concerning	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
hers	O
in	O
White's-yard	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
her	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
waited	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
hours	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hayter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
boxes	O
of	O
mace	O
sent	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Queen	O
of	O
Hungary	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
N	B-pers
.	I-pers
3.	O
the	O
other	O
N	B-pers
.	I-pers
4.	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
Those	O
boxes	O
were	O
landed	O
near	O
the	O
custom-house	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hayter	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
21	O
pound	O
Dutch	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
19	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
entered	O
3	O
small	O
pieces	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hayter	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
lye	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boxes	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimott	I-pers
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
asked	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
box	O
that	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
sealed	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
seal	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Colburne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
26	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Pertt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
all	O
his	O
life-time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
369.	O
Mary	B-pers
Noah	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	I-place
Spittle-Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunnalston	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
370	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
smith	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
100	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
smith	O
)	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
some	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
's	O
iron	O
by	O
his	O
way	O
of	O
working	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
as	O
if	O
a	O
board	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Edward	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
come	O
to	O
Tom	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
something	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
,	O
past	O
three	O
o'clock	O
and	O
a	O
rainy	O
morning	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
3	O
times	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
took	O
something	O
every	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
's	O
shop	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
may	O
be	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
3	O
months	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
rooms	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
somebody	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
a	O
proper	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
might	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
371.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Dyas	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Dyas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	B-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
conveniency	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
me	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
place	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
treated	O
her	O
with	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
drams	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stockal	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
lent	O
her	O
18	O
d.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Fott	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutrix	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Clothes	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
gown	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hat	O
upon	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
money	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
372.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dichens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
whip	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brotherton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
dropped	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sensible	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
spurs	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
Kent	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
horseback	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
boots	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
boots	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spurs	O
were	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Beaning	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brotherton	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
boots	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
boots	O
?	O
Beaning	O
.	O
The	O
spurs	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
boots	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
then	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
2	O
whip	O
too	O
.	O
Benning	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
the	O
whip	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
spurs	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
the	O
spurs	O
with	O
the	O
boots	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
pulled	O
off	O
the	O
boots	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
hedge	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
a	O
man	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
boots	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
a	O
hedge	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
hedge	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
373.	O
Sophia	B-pers
Cudan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stedley	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Stedley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
The	O
gown	O
and	O
stays	O
were	O
rolled	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Stedley	O
lodges	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
body	O
was	O
above	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Stedley	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
something	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
without	O
the	O
Key	O
?	O
for	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
her	O
till	O
Mrs.	O
Stedley	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
threatened	O
me	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
kept	O
on	O
detained	O
her	O
)	O
and	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Stedley	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Mrs.	O
Stedley	O
's	O
daughter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stay	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stedley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
meet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Bawick-street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
or	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
374	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
scarlet	O
duffile	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
blue	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scarlet	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
August	O
16	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
rent	O
the	O
ground-floor	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Henley	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
these	O
goods	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
but	O
one	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
neighbours	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
saw	O
any	O
body	O
carry	O
any	O
clothes	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
2	O
young	O
fellows	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
at	O
the	O
new	O
bridge	O
at	O
Westminster	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
two	O
such	O
men	O
with	O
clothes	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
horse-guards	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
him	O
a	O
house-breaking	O
dog	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
wife	O
sells	O
fruit	O
at	O
the	O
horse-guards	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Fryer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wellwisher	O
to	O
a	O
soldier	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
horse-grenadier	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
impressed	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
The	O
Waterman	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
the	O
men	O
over	O
with	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
he	O
carried	O
over	O
with	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
clothes	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
particulars	O
of	O
the	O
clothes	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
?	O
Fryer	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
this	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
another	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
new	O
stairs	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
oars	O
to	O
Pepper-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
clothes	O
loose	O
upon	O
their	O
arms	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
scarlet	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
tucked	O
into	O
his	O
bosom	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fryer	O
's	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
I	O
saw	O
with	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
Fryer	O
.	O
This	O
answers	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
my	O
clothes	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Galley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
.	O
He	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
barber	O
and	O
periwig-maker	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Yalden	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
journey-work	O
at	O
other	O
places	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Wallington	I-pers
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
from	O
his	O
birth	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Player	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
4	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
375.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
sauce-pan	O
and	O
cover	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
candlestick	O
,	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parkes	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
Alex	O
Carless	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
down	O
a	O
large	O
sauce	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
maid	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
sauce-pan	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Doborah	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
sauce-pan	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
petticoat	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
376	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Billings	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
price	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Witney	I-pers
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Witney	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
from	O
Layton	B-place
Buzzard	I-place
in	I-place
Bedford-shire	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
about	O
14	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
one	O
Cowling	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
He	O
delivered	O
me	O
the	O
gelding	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Cowling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
gelding	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
rapping	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
stole	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
wet	O
night	O
or	O
a	O
dry	O
night	O
?	O
Witney	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
showery	O
night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
brought	O
this	O
horse	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
booked	O
and	O
tolled	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
chopped	O
him	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cowling	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
ride	O
the	O
horse	O
about	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
bought	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
2	O
guineas	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swinstead	I-pers
proved	O
Mr.	O
Witney	O
's	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Northamptonshire	O
to	O
a	O
brother	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Hockley	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
rained	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
it	O
could	O
.	O
There	O
stood	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
people	O
under	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
well	O
set	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
me	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
as	O
to	O
purchase	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
a	O
horse	O
.	O
However	O
I	O
purchased	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
saddle	O
for	O
43	O
s.	O
-	O
I	O
bought	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
in	O
Dunstaple	O
under	O
the	O
gate-way	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bull	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
at	O
the	O
Cherry	O
Tree	O
in	O
Kentish-Town	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
4	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
last	O
March	O
:	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
hedge	O
and	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
5	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
2	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
turnpike	O
road	O
by	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
hay-making	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
2	O
nights	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
work	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Joyce	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Plough	O
,	O
between	O
this	O
and	O
Wormley-Green	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
pretty	O
flush	O
of	O
money	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
?	O
Joyce	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
was	O
flush	O
of	O
money	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
40	O
s.	O
Joyce	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
wife	O
pawned	O
her	O
clothes	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
above	O
40	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
was	O
known	O
by	O
us	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
kept	O
late	O
hours	O
,	O
or	O
used	O
to	O
spending	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
376	O
.	O
+	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hamstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Paulet	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
him	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
striking	O
him	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
neck	O
,	O
back	O
,	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
stomach	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
blows	O
he	O
received	O
upon	O
those	O
parts	O
several	O
mortal	O
bruises	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
August	O
23	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Pawlet	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
,	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
a	O
publick-house	O
at	O
West-End	B-place
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
victuals	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
tired	O
with	O
his	O
work	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
possible	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
tired	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
work	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
play	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
his	O
work	O
?	O
Hind	O
.	O
A	O
Bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
-	O
After	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
said	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
disputed	O
it	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
lie	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
lie	O
again	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
answer	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
five	O
shillings	O
that	O
he	O
beat	O
him	O
in	O
three	O
minutes	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
lay	O
him	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
money	O
pulled	O
out	O
:	O
however	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
stripped	O
very	O
fairly	O
and	O
fought	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
received	O
the	O
first	O
two	O
falls	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
fall	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
rather	O
the	O
worst	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
shake	O
hands	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
and	O
welcome	O
-	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
sick	O
and	O
vomited	O
:	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Slann	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
victuals	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
pretty	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
sitting	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
tired	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
made	O
answer	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
he	O
be	O
tired	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
work	O
was	O
but	O
play	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
work	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
a	O
thousand	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
bricks	O
two	O
story	O
high	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
They	O
contradicted	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
deceased	O
the	O
lie	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
lie	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
they	O
talked	O
of	O
laying	O
a	O
wager	O
about	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
by	O
consent	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
three	O
falls	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
fall	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
together	O
sideways	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
rather	O
the	O
worst	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
any	O
wound	O
he	O
received	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
Churchwarden	O
said	O
the	O
Coroner	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
prosecute	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
appear	O
for	O
the	O
parish	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Kelleck	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	O
Russel-Street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
vast	O
quantity	O
of	O
blood	O
in	O
the	O
cavity	O
of	O
the	O
abdomen	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
proceeded	O
from	O
an	O
eruption	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
blood	O
vessels	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
wounds	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
must	O
from	O
the	O
shock	O
of	O
the	O
fall	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
capital	O
vessels	O
in	O
the	O
cavity	O
of	O
the	O
abdomen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
body	O
was	O
quite	O
in	O
a	O
diseased	O
state	O
before	O
this	O
accident	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
skull	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
contusion	O
upon	O
the	O
brain	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
clear	O
and	O
safe	O
.	O
One	O
lobe	O
of	O
the	O
lungs	O
was	O
quite	O
adhered	O
to	O
the	O
pleura	O
and	O
was	O
quite	O
emaciated	O
(	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
occasioned	O
by	O
this	O
fall	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
adhesion	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
lobe	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
.	O
377	O
.	O
+	O
Moses	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Hobdell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
cane	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hobdell	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
drinking	O
pretty	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
set	O
myself	O
down	O
any	O
where	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
either	O
upon	O
a	O
bench	O
or	O
a	O
stone	O
by	O
Exeter-Exchange	B-place
:	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
came	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
surprize	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
asleep	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
fellows	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
which	O
stunned	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
my	O
cane	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
by	O
force	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
knocked	O
you	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
?	O
Hobdell	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
fellows	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
cane	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Hobdell	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
struggled	O
for	O
my	O
cane	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
cane	O
that	O
I	O
valued	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
watch	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
murdered	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
bad	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
upon	O
that	O
work	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Yll	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Hobdell	O
cried	O
out	O
thieves	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
but	O
they	O
all	O
escaped	O
except	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
[	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
thick	O
stick	O
produced	O
about	O
a	O
foot	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
long	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
leg	O
of	O
a	O
form	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
Yoxell	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
's	O
distance	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
bad	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
premanire	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
378	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Tollman	I-pers
,	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Burridge	O
and	O
Tollman	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
home	O
with	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
goods	O
upon	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Anchor	O
in	O
Dudgy-Lane	B-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
Somerset-House	I-place
;	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
basket	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
young	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
three	O
halfpence	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
basket	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
more	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
come	O
through	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
-	O
I	O
staid	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
the	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
basket	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
pot	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
dram	O
of	O
gin	O
:	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
liquor	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
for	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
just	O
taste	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
upon	O
my	O
legs	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
9	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
received	O
9	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
at	O
the	O
Civet	O
Cat	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
paid	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
these	O
three	O
glasses	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
could	O
be	O
above	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
-	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
my	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
women	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
They	O
rose	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
up	O
your	O
basket	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
got	O
my	O
basket	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
-	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
if	O
she	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
one	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
waterman	O
,	O
thieves	O
!	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
thrown	O
sixpence	O
into	O
the	O
boat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
waterman	O
seize	O
them	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
them	O
away	O
[	O
rowed	O
away	O
]	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
boat	O
and	O
rowed	O
after	O
them	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
lighters	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
boats	O
faitened	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
rowed	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
on	O
shore	O
I	O
jumped	O
upon	O
a	O
lighter	O
,	O
got	O
on	O
shore	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
all	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Constable	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
her	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
her	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
small	O
silver	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
might	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
near	O
me	O
after	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
sit	O
on	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
touch	O
you	O
after	O
you	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
reckoning	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
women	O
in	O
custody	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
got	O
on	O
shore	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
keep	O
them	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
go	O
voluntarily	O
with	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
you	O
did	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
we	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
others	O
took	O
my	O
part	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
mob	O
me	O
off	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
took	O
her	O
did	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
you	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
She	O
laughed	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
380	O
,	O
381	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bucklimes	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brampton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Sept.	O
8	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brampton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
night	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Swan-Tavern	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
home	O
and	O
turning	O
up	O
Norton	B-place
Falgate	I-place
,	O
the	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
heavy	O
loaden	O
,	O
(	O
because	O
I	O
walked	O
heavy	O
and	O
sluggish	O
)	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
Barbican	O
(	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
)	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
they	O
seemed	O
willing	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
:	O
with	O
that	O
Roach	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
of	O
my	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
walked	O
behind	O
.	O
We	O
walked	O
along	O
Hog-Lane	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Baker	O
and	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
Roach	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
finding	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
:	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
turned	O
from	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
to	O
Roach	O
and	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
skuffled	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
-	O
I	O
lost	O
8	O
s.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
that	O
pocket	O
23	O
or	O
24	O
s.	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
I	O
had	O
3	O
guineas	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
secured	O
Roach	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
paper	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
Roach	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
odd	O
money	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
in	O
that	O
pocket	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
Brampton	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
pocket	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
or	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
13	O
s.	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
-	O
A	O
watchman	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
went	O
home	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
lost	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
Newton	O
you	O
are	O
heavy	O
loaden	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Brampton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brampton	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
he	O
paid	O
twenty	O
six	O
guineas	O
to	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Brampton	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
broomstick	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
lads	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Hog-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
master	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
heavy	O
loaden	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Brampton	O
says	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
Roach	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
arm	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Baker	O
and	O
Basket	O
in	O
Hog-Lane	O
;	O
then	O
Brampton	O
said	O
,	O
hollo	O
,	O
Newton	O
!	O
the	O
fellow	O
has	O
got	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
broomstick	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
knock	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
move	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
money	O
fell	O
down	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
pretty	O
artfully	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
both	O
tumbled	O
over	O
together	O
.	O
Bucklimes	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
still	O
held	O
Roach	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
Bucklimes	O
seeing	O
I	O
had	O
managed	O
him	O
,	O
held	O
this	O
stick	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
knock	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
down	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
shilling	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
shillings	O
found	O
afterwards	O
-	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
Brampton	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
money	O
chink	O
after	O
Brampton	O
told	O
you	O
his	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
dropped	O
out	O
of	O
Roach	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
money	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
tenter	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
King	O
Street	O
.	O
Roach	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
money	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brampton	O
and	O
examined	O
his	O
pockets	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Roach	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Roach	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
I	O
met	O
you	O
at	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Hog-Lane	O
.	O
-	O
Bricknell	O
(	O
Constable	O
)	O
.	O
This	O
note	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Roach	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shilling	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
near	O
him	O
-	O
The	O
watchmen	O
were	O
searching	O
him	O
when	O
this	O
paper	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
Mr.	O
Brampton	O
fall	O
down	O
?	O
Brampton	O
.	O
Not	O
till	O
after	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Purdue	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Roach	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
draws	O
draught	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
Weavers	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
Walker	O
)	O
left	O
work	O
but	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brampton	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stogden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Weaver	O
-	O
Roach	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Bucklimes	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
fellow	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moulton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Roach	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
worked	O
together	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
Bucklimes	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Roach	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Roach	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Bucklimes	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
382	O
.	O
+	O
Eleanor	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
eight	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Guy	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
Guy	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
hired	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
she	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
doors	O
were	O
all	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
four	O
horses	O
and	O
four	O
men	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
tollhouse	O
at	O
Putney-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
aprons	O
,	O
caps	O
and	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
more	O
caps	O
than	O
one	O
on	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
cap	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
new	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
made	O
the	O
other	O
unmade	O
,	O
these	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
work	O
basket	O
;	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
toll-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
likewise	O
my	O
cap	O
,	O
apron	O
,	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
clogs	O
and	O
cloak	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
woman	O
should	O
tell	O
me	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
turn	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
sold	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bartlow	O
-	O
A	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
spoons	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bartlow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
2	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
odd	O
trifling	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
questioned	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
mother	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
to	O
bury	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
selling	O
her	O
things	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
2	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
383	O
,	O
384	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Parding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Carolina	B-pers
Banham	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
necklace	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
a	O
coral	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeve-buttons	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buttons	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
38	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
August	O
17	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
Fruit	O
.	O
Five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
cherries	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
2	O
children	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
My	O
biggest	O
girl	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mother	O
,	O
Betty	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
and	O
Carolina	B-pers
Banham	I-pers
have	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
King-Street	O
by	O
Guild-hall	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
drank	O
3	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
.	O
Pugh	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
?	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
body	O
here	O
has	O
robbed	O
you	O
:	O
and	O
Banham	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
lie	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
have	O
robbed	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
owned	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
golden	O
guinea	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
have	O
the	O
gowns	O
upon	O
their	O
backs	O
now	O
)	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
cost	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
apiece	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
2	O
spoons	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Tyson	O
's	O
,	O
facing	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
church	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
by	O
their	O
direction	O
.	O
They	O
owned	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
my	O
coral	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Peters	O
in	O
the	O
borough	O
;	O
(	O
Banham	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Peters	O
melted	O
it	O
down	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
buttons	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
bridge-foot	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Stafford	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tyson	O
,	O
facing	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
church	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
(	O
especially	O
Pugh	O
)	O
coming	O
with	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
delivering	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
3	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
lead	O
more	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
Pugh	O
guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
Banham	O
guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
385	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
periwig	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Revd	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Divinity	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lockall	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1st	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lockall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gloucester-Street	B-place
.	O
The	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
-	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
gone	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
offer	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
caught	O
him	O
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
came	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
the	O
people	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
nodded	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
any	O
nearer	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
pretty	O
near	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
presented	O
his	O
pistol	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
He	O
presented	O
his	O
pistol	O
at	O
every	O
one	O
he	O
met	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
discover	O
his	O
accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harrington	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Lockall	O
's	O
house	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
after	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
church	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
stood	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
short	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
head	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
observe	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
walked	O
very	O
soberly	O
towards	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
boy	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lockall	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
one	O
turned	O
one	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
other	O
corner	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
minutes	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Cox	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
?	O
Lockall	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
you	O
?	O
Was	O
you	O
not	O
pursued	O
immediately	O
and	O
taken	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
wig	O
and	O
gloves	O
into	O
an	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lockall	O
's	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
wig	O
.	O
Lockall	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
Dr.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
wig	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
386	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Caryl	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
February	O
19	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Caryl	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
in	O
Windsor-Court	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-Lane	I-place
.	O
-	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
too	O
late	O
:	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Bow-Street	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
getting	O
in	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
this	O
woman	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Baker	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
Jury	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Caryl	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
into	O
Windsor-Court	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lie	O
alone	O
?	O
Caryl	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
candle	O
away	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
liquor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
or	O
two	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
had	O
some	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
till	O
near	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
breeches	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
to	O
look	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
light	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Caryl	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
here	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
concerning	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
lighted	O
me	O
up	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
by	O
her	O
confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
-	O
She	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
had	O
pledged	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
pledged	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
387	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
burdet	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
linnen	O
gown	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
12	O
d.	O
six	O
ells	O
of	O
dowlas	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
half	O
of	O
guinea	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
August	O
21	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
nurse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
by	O
my	O
bedside	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Garland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
in	O
Whitecross-Street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Blunt	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
pocket	O
with	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
)	O
a	O
new	O
shift	O
and	O
six	O
ells	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
hid	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
her	O
