TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
18th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Westley	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1744	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WESTLEY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lodge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Breed	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Somers	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boozshire	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sandwith	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Tredgold	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Stovell	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
.	O
296.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pinder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
as	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
periwig	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sidney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
periwig	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
May	O
12	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sidney	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
bailiffs	O
waiting	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
hese	O
goods	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
two	O
vigs	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
in	O
Middle	O
Row	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
wig	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Orbury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Orbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
wig	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
Whitsontide	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
for	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
once	O
before	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
is	O
a	O
barber	O
and	O
perriwig	O
maker	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
business	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
separate	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
goes	O
into	O
a	O
skettle	O
ground	O
,	O
off	O
the	O
hinges	O
:	O
he	O
orders	O
me	O
sometimes	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
a	O
cobler	O
's	O
stall	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
bailiffs	O
being	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
bailiffs	O
were	O
waiting	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Sidney	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
hinges	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
myself	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
the	O
razors	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
wig	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
297.	O
Judith	B-pers
Septon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
four	O
pound	O
of	O
hair	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
,	O
May	O
4	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair	O
cloth	O
maker	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
last	O
May	O
was	O
twelvemonths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
last	O
May	O
she	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
hair	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
:	O
she	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Coombs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
hair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
?	O
Archibald	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
son	O
worked	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
knows	O
it	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wrought	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
hair	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
tale	O
or	O
tidings	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
Whitsun	O
Monday	O
,	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Coombs	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
goal	O
that	O
one	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Nimble	I-pers
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
whether	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
accuse	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
hair	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
's	O
to	O
make	O
sale	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
piece	O
?	O
Jacob	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
piece	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
assure	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Jacob	O
.	O
To	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
truth	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
-	O
My	O
mistress	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coombs	O
's	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
she	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coombs	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
it	O
directly	O
-	O
it	O
weighed	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hundred	O
and	O
seven	O
pounds	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nitchel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stone	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
spun	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
pence	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
brought	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
298	O
,	O
299.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mynet	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mynet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
off	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
a	O
purse	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
with	O
these	O
women	O
?	O
Mynet	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Mynet	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
very	O
early	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
bed-fellow	O
that	O
night	O
but	O
your	O
wife	O
?	O
Mynet	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
no	O
wife	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Mynet	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
these	O
women	O
were	O
tumbling-upon	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Mynet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
middlingly	O
in	O
drink	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
remember	O
this	O
?	O
Mynet	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
very	O
well	O
remember	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
Dixon	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
office	O
in	O
the	O
lost	O
above	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
you	O
by	O
force	O
?	O
Mynet	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
who	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
this	O
ring	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
her	O
smock	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
untied	O
her	O
smock	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Mynet	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
ring	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Townley	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
money	O
upon	O
her	O
?	O
Townley	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
-	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
was	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
countryman	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
slight	O
brass	O
ring	O
off	O
her	O
finger	O
and	O
pretended	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
ring	O
that	O
Mynet	O
gave	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
countryman	O
[	O
Mynet	O
]	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
Sullivan	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
woman	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
Mynet	O
found	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
between	O
the	O
cieling	O
of	O
the	O
vault	O
and	O
the	O
tiling	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Dixon	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Townley	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
to	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
-	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
was	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
lost	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
office	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Sullivan	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
Dixon	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
action	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
Dixon	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
short	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
ring	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
ring	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
by	O
force	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
laid	O
this	O
indictment	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
capital	O
offence	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
300	O
.	O
+	O
Jane	B-pers
Ansley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
;	O
five	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
shirts	O
and	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Scot	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
aunt	O
Hannah	B-pers
Maddison	I-pers
put	O
her	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
proved	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
aunt	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
stealing	O
them	O
:	O
she	O
confessed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Skevington	O
's	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
to	O
be	O
pawned	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Skevington	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
shirt	O
that	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
aunt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
debt	O
of	O
it	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
excuse	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
remaining	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
guineas	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
in	O
clothes	O
:	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
acknowledge	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Scot	O
's	O
drawers	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Scot	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
drawers	O
.	O
Christiana	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
-	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
drawers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
from	O
what	O
place	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
Her	O
aunt	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
took	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
herself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
behave	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
Very	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
natured	O
creature	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
her	O
aunt	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
money	O
and	O
good	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
loss	O
is	O
but	O
trifling	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
301.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Trotter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
dimitty	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
cambrick	O
mobs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
six	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
flower	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
tinder	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
snuffers	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
June	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
that	O
same	O
Abraham	B-pers
Trotter	I-pers
took	O
down	O
both	O
my	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
window	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
brasses	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
shutters	O
were	O
open	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
us	O
?	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
frightened	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
safe	O
there	O
then	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
along	O
;	O
then	O
Richard	O
Downs	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
my	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
directed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
some	O
men	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
dunny	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
now	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Powis	O
:	O
yes	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
favourable	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Powis	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
shutters	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
no	O
harm	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
Mrs.	O
Powis	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
gown	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
home	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Powis	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
say	O
,	O
make	O
haste	O
down	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
thief	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
hatch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
brasses	O
were	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
says	O
Mrs.	O
Powis	O
,	O
oh	O
you	O
rogue	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
stripped	O
my	O
house	O
of	O
almost	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
angry	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Powis	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
hurt	O
you	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
frightened	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
directed	O
Downs	O
and	O
her	O
where	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Powis	O
's	O
husband	O
used	O
to	O
employ	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
I	O
thought	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Powis	O
to	O
beg	O
a	O
few	O
greens	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
answering	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
almost	O
starved	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
some	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
my	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
buried	O
a	O
child	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
of	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
earned	O
but	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
for	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
302.	O
Charles	B-pers
Billingsly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
.	O
The	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
joining	O
to	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
one	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howston	O
a	O
silversmith	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mordaunt	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
errand	O
boy	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
our	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
opportunity	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
confessed	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	O
)	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
sash	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
corner	O
cupboard	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Howston	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
master	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
impudence	O
to	O
send	O
another	O
boy	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mordaunt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
2	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
Green	O
a	O
cobler	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
usual	O
for	O
a	O
cobler	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
spoon	O
as	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
owns	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
w	O
ent	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
mother	O
who	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Billingsly	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
eight	O
years	O
old	O
-	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
303	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Everett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Tolke	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Tolke	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Monument	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
company	O
of	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
those	O
people	O
were	O
there	O
for	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
wives	O
of	O
those	O
persons	O
who	O
are	O
gone	O
to	O
Flanders	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
there	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
a	O
hand	O
at	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
*	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
this	O
pocket	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
apron	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
feet	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
by	O
Bishopsgate	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
vile	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
undutifully	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
followed	O
this	O
practice	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
left	O
hand	O
near	O
three	O
pounds	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
out	O
of	O
tenderness	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
lay	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
and	O
mother-in-law	O
were	O
always	O
vile	O
people	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
drove	O
to	O
this	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
304.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hellier	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
.	O
These	O
pewter	O
plates	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
for	O
sale	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hellier	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
14th	O
instant	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
till	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
mistrusting	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
turned	O
up	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Holder	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
cloak	O
she	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
305.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hung	O
my	O
gown	O
out	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Trust	I-pers
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
she	O
did	O
deliver	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
because	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
gown	O
was	O
blown	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
forswear	O
yourself	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Shropshire	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Trust	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
Seeing	O
her	O
whisk	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
stole	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
hung	O
upon	O
the	O
line	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
's	O
gown	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
and	O
her	O
mistress	O
both	O
together	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
has	O
taken	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
gown	O
indeed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
making	O
hay	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Winchester	O
.	O
The	O
gown	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
sat	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
several	O
people	O
whether	O
any	O
body	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
306.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
straw	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
May	O
22d	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
window	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
cloaks	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
pretty	O
early	O
,	O
because	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
we	O
get	O
up	O
at	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
o'clock	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
milking	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
heard	O
somebody	O
and	O
that	O
disturbed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
Almighty	O
bless	O
you	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
little	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Causton	I-pers
my	O
Carrier	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
pawned	O
one	O
cloak	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stringer	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chambers	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
for	O
15	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Causton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
Kate	O
,	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
and	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
fair	O
means	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
by	O
foul	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
untied	O
her	O
apron	O
three	O
times	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
cloak	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
hang	O
'd	O
in	O
Hyde-Park	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
shot	O
in	O
Hyde-Park	O
.	O
Stringer	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
pardon	O
,	O
I	O
mistook	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
307.	O
Mary	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bible	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
book	O
called	O
The	O
Preparation	O
for	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
clogs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Strangeways	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
Strangeways	O
Pearson	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wing	I-pers
.	O
My	O
master	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
or	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
books	O
were	O
what	O
my	O
master	O
valued	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
two	O
books	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
cap	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
cradle	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
herself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mistress	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
well	O
sensible	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
Pearson	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
books	O
I	O
own	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
308	O
,	O
309.	O
Edward	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
*	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Wandon	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
but	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Andrew	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
from	O
the	O
Red	B-place
Cow	I-place
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
in	O
Saturday	O
's	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Bannister	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
Bannister	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
three	O
times	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Bates	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
[	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
tankard	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Vane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
Bannister	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
after	O
the	O
horse	O
market	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
being	O
up	O
early	O
was	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
nap	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
gentlemen	O
who	O
had	O
three	O
tankards	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
beer	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
turned	O
about	O
to	O
drink	O
it	O
.	O
Bannister	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Robert	O
Hall	O
the	O
drover	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
ask	O
for	O
drovers	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
o'night	O
?	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
come	O
at	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
fetched	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lighted	O
his	O
pipe	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
Bannister	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
the	O
woman	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Vane	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
but	O
Bannister	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
taken	O
the	O
tankard	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
pipe	O
which	O
Bannister	O
had	O
just	O
lighted	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
his	O
beer	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
this	O
tankard	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
out	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
constables	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
:	O
as	O
to	O
Moody	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
Bannister	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
oath	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
constables	O
came	O
in	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
dubious	O
of	O
drawing	O
any	O
beer	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Bannister	O
I	O
cried	O
for	O
joy	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
rogue	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
stole	O
our	O
tankard	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
wicked	O
creature	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
silver	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
butler	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
rogue	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
of	O
getting	O
my	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
would	O
ruin	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
might	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Moody	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
some	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
forget	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
gone	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
found	O
the	O
bottom	O
and	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Bates	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
Bannister	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Bates	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
pardon	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
informed	O
so	O
by	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Bannister	O
.	O
You	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
how	O
can	O
she	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Vane	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
tankard	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
n't	O
please	O
your	O
honour	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
said	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
together	O
.	O
Vane	O
.	O
I	O
come	O
here	O
to	O
do	O
justice	O
to	O
God	O
and	O
man	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
beer	O
for	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
but	O
Bannister	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
too	O
much	O
remarks	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
calling	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
be	O
mistaken	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
usual	O
for	O
people	O
on	O
a	O
market	O
day	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
smoke	O
a	O
pipe	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
has	O
sell	O
out	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
so	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
Seven	O
Stars	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
old	O
clothes	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
June	O
both	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Moody	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
damask	O
shoes	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
silver	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
bits	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
either	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
a	O
cup	O
or	O
a	O
tankard	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
silver	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
sell	O
old	O
clothes	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
recommended	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
apt	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
angry	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
Bannister	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
bought	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
little	O
bits	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
paper	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
plate	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
it	O
surprised	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
believed	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
pieces	O
that	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
examined	O
the	O
plate	O
bit	O
by	O
bit	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
butler	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
it	O
,	O
Bannister	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
blame	O
any	O
person	O
for	O
being	O
careful	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
stay	O
and	O
see	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
your	O
plate	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
not	O
weights	O
enough	O
to	O
weigh	O
it	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
weighed	O
an	O
ounce	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
ounces	O
weighed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
an	O
ounce	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
ounces	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
ounces	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
neighbours	O
told	O
us	O
we	O
should	O
stop	O
the	O
thief	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
boy	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Moody	O
at	O
one	O
Buckmaster	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
by	O
Prescot	O
Street	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Bannister	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
being	O
a	O
confederate	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
Bannister	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
for	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
We	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
tankard	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
(	O
Headborough	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
two	O
thieves	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Buckmaster	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Sturt	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
maid	O
(	O
Sarah	B-pers
Vane	I-pers
)	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
jumped	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
joyful	O
,	O
she	O
cried	O
for	O
joy	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Bannister	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
rogue	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
fix	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
the	O
person	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
talked	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
?	O
Handcock	O
.	O
She	O
jumped	O
for	O
joy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
upon	O
the	O
first	O
appearance	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
stopping	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Bannister	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
butler	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
knew	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
by	O
chance	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
who	O
are	O
both	O
silversmiths	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Bannister	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
early	O
that	O
morning	O
with	O
my	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Moody	O
.	O
Bannister	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
silver	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sturt	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
Bannister	O
.	O
The	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
something	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
hawker	O
and	O
dealer	O
in	O
goods	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Moody	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wandon	I-pers
otherwise	O
Bannister	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
310	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Quarendon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
blue	O
tabby	O
night	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
yellow	O
burdet	O
night	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
four	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
edged	O
with	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
night	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
,	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Baker	B-place
and	I-place
Basket	I-place
in	O
Hog	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
sash	O
window	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
chamber	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
was	O
thrown	O
up	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
This	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
flustration	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
understood	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
at	O
Norton	O
Folgate	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
entered	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
key	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
pull	O
out	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
goods	O
there	O
?	O
Stratford	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Tenter	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
white	O
quilt	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
bed	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
window	O
was	O
fast	O
down	O
at	O
past	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
pardon	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
mistook	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
close	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
the	O
window	O
fastened	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
an	O
iron	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fastened	O
that	O
myself	O
-	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
iron	O
that	O
turns	O
round	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Stratford	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
fastening	O
is	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Stratford	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
nut	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
turn	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
takes	O
so	O
little	O
hold	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
use	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
screw	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
hook	O
to	O
catch	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
sash	O
?	O
Stratford	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
hook	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
could	O
latch	O
it	O
?	O
Stratford	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
low	O
was	O
the	O
sash	O
down	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
quite	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
My	O
aunt	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
of	O
thieves	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elkins	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
proper	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
belonging	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
.	O
Quarendon	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
?	O
With	O
that	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
taking	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
loth	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Stratford	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
white	O
quilt	O
,	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
caps	O
;	O
the	O
white	O
quilt	O
Mr.	O
Stratford	O
brought	O
back	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
bed	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
shirt	O
marked	O
R.	O
S.	O
N.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
washing	O
tub	O
wet	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
shirt	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
caps	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Stratford	O
's	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
voluntarily	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
back	O
wall	O
by	O
the	O
tenter	O
ground	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
window	O
without	O
a	O
window	O
shutter	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
shed	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
pushed	O
his	O
finger	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
lifted	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
pushed	O
it	O
up	O
far	O
enough	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
out	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
quilt	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
these	O
things	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
;	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
or	O
third	O
drawers	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
about	O
half	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
dyer	O
's	O
bag	O
,	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
again	O
,	O
dropped	O
the	O
bag	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shed	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
bag	O
by	O
the	O
mouth	O
,	O
dropped	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
jumped	O
down	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
through	O
the	O
next	O
dyer	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
home	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Elkins	I-pers
(	O
constable	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
hussled	O
a	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
care	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
till	O
morning	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Elkins	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
searched	O
him	O
yet	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
talked	O
of	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
watch	O
upon	O
the	O
shelf	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Stratford	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
opened	O
a	O
drawer	O
with	O
a	O
key	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
sealed	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
quilt	O
away	O
?	O
Page	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
there	O
?	O
Page	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Stratford	O
.	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
quilt	O
?	O
Stratford	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
when	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
yellow	O
burdet	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
linen	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
gowns	O
are	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
.	O
This	O
cap	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
shirt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
washing	O
tub	O
.	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Stratford	O
's	O
cap	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
call	O
some	O
witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
dyer	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
just	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
several	O
masters	O
of	O
the	O
trade	O
that	O
I	O
keep	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
always	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Another	O
witness	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
whereever	O
he	O
lived	O
and	O
where-ever	O
he	O
worked	O
,	O
for	O
whatever	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
always	O
bore	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bonnet	I-pers
.	O
He	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
wronged	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
child	O
,	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
if	O
his	O
master	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
appeared	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
more	O
goods	O
than	O
he	O
has	O
wronged	O
these	O
people	O
of	O
.	O
-	O
Prior	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
his	O
parents	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
people	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
-	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
was	O
extraordinary	O
good	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
honourable	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
two	O
small	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
poor	O
mother	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
was	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
it	O
's	O
being	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
any	O
more	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
than	O
her	O
aunt	O
told	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
her	O
aunt	O
came	O
home	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
cloak	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
shut	O
then	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
as	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
311	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Quarendon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pippin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Sleymaker	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
shalloon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pippin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Sleymaker	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
;	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
coffoy	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
coffoy	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Chamberlain	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
April	O
9.	O
Chamberlain	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
apprentice	O
with	O
Messieurs	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Pippin	O
,	O
and	O
Sleymaker	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
partners	O
in	O
the	O
dyers	O
trade	O
in	O
Hog	B-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
the	O
9th	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
fashion	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
Lee	O
,	O
which	O
hung	O
up	O
at	O
my	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
of	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
s	O
of	O
mine	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
with	O
R.	O
W.	O
scratched	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
that	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
nail	O
in	O
the	O
wall	O
by	O
the	O
bedside	O
)	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
scarlet	O
coffoy	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
cloth	O
coat	O
full	O
trimmed	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
May	O
hearing	O
a	O
person	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
Norton	O
Folgate	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
know	O
him	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Elkins	O
the	O
officer	O
said	O
we	O
must	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
scarlet	O
coffoy	O
breeches	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
knee-buckles	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
seat	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
hang	O
his	O
watch	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
-	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
went	O
without	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
heard	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
so	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
bed	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
very	O
genteelly	O
without	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watches	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
The	O
windows	O
were	O
open	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
open	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
shut	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
by	O
breaking	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
's	O
watch	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
.	O
The	O
tenth	O
of	O
May	O
hearing	O
this	O
person	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
they	O
talked	O
of	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
lay	O
something	O
upon	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
laying	O
the	O
watch	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
claimed	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
searching	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
key	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scarlet	O
breeches	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
seat	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fetched	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
clothes	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
when	O
the	O
gentleman	O
who	O
owns	O
the	O
other	O
watch	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
till	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
both	O
snore	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
asleep	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
tore	O
the	O
shalloon	O
down	O
off	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
dye-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
312.	O
John	B-pers
Prentice	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catharine	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cullin	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cullin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
ballast	O
lighter	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
iron	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
iron	O
we	O
raise	O
the	O
ballast	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
fix	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
gunnel	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
caught	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
handing	O
the	O
iron	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
B	O
-	O
d	O
lay	O
hold	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
gentleman	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
irons	O
were	O
an	O
outside	O
standard	O
and	O
an	O
inside	O
standard	O
.	O
Cullin	O
.	O
Clark	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
protected	O
by	O
the	O
Trinity	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sleeping	O
in	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
taking	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
lighter	O
's	O
scutter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
uncle	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
reputation	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bley	O
.	O
Clark	O
.	O
His	O
uncle	O
wo	O
n't	O
come	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
rogue	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wo	O
n't	O
trouble	O
himself	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
313.	O
Mary	B-pers
Imbey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Uxbridge	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mastin	I-pers
,	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mastin	I-pers
.	O
May	O
19	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
drying	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
aprons	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
town	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Lynch	O
with	O
the	O
linen	O
apron	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
hid	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mastin	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
person	O
she	O
thought	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
about	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
apron	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
other	O
among	O
some	O
grass	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
covered	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
apron	O
herself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
I	O
did	O
own	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
being	O
frightened	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
314.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
June	O
22	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
wash	O
and	O
iron	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
silver	O
spoon	O
last	O
Friday	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
lodgers	O
said	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
has	O
my	O
cap	O
has	O
your	O
spoon	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hutchins	O
for	O
eight	O
shillings	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
twenty	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
things	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
She	O
never	O
pawned	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
confessed	O
it	O
innocently	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Millesham	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
than	O
come	O
into	O
any	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
closet	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
please	O
to	O
forgive	O
me	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
will	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
again	O
to	O
no	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
child	O
,	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
Live	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
315	O
,	O
316	O
,	O
317	O
,	O
318.	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Monroe	I-pers
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catharine	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
dimitty	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
calico	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
three	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meriton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
outhouse	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meriton	I-pers
,	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
And	O
319	O
,	O
320.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
*	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
+	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
John	O
Johnson	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
receiving	O
thirty	O
guineas	O
and	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
which	O
Mary	O
Matthews	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Congleton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
January	O
Sessions	O
1742-3	O
.	O
Page	O
59	O
,	O
Trial	O
90	O
and	O
91	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
arraigned	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
hold	O
up	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
convict	O
me	O
before	O
my	O
time	O
?	O
I	O
can	O
hold	O
up	O
my	O
hand	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
question	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
how	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
tried	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
God	O
and	O
my	O
country	O
,	O
two	O
better	O
persons	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
tried	O
by	O
.	O
+	O
Jane	O
Johnson	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
May	O
Sessions	O
1743	O
,	O
upon	O
two	O
indictments	O
for	O
receiving	O
goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
against	O
her	O
than	O
an	O
accomplice	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
felonies	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
May	O
Sessions	O
1743	O
.	O
Page	O
175	O
,	O
Trial	O
266.	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
trial	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meriton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
thirty	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
knocking	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
people	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
my	O
vessel	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
that	O
young	O
gentleman	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
[	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
a	O
boy	O
about	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
]	O
He	O
immediately	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
us	O
where	O
his	O
confederates	O
were	O
,	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
called	O
the	O
blind	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nobody	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
two	O
dead	O
fowls	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
stolen	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
towards	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
watch-house	O
we	O
took	O
these	O
three	O
girls	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
there	O
?	O
Meriton	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
five	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
[	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
]	O
Take	O
that	O
man	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
putting	O
into	O
his	O
head	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Badham	O
[	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
Meriton	O
.	O
The	O
tea	O
spoons	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
girls	O
pockets	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
You	O
say	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Meriton	O
.	O
I	O
mistook	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
You	O
will	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
out-house	O
and	O
dwelling-house	O
join	O
together	O
?	O
Meriton	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
yard	O
between	O
the	O
out-house	O
and	O
the	O
forehouse	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
sworn	O
to	O
a	O
cock	O
and	O
a	O
hen	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knows	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
swear	O
you	O
lost	O
a	O
cock	O
and	O
a	O
hen	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
swear	O
so	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Meriton	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
swore	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
[	O
found	O
]	O
these	O
clothes	O
.	O
Meriton	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
will	O
make	O
that	O
appear	O
presently	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
those	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
?	O
Meriton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
ironed	O
these	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
to	O
be	O
hardened	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
Martin	O
came	O
and	O
stole	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
?	O
Lambert	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
own	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
Johnson	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
constable	O
-	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
received	O
out	O
of	O
Johnson	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
thieves	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
run	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
green	O
stocking	O
:	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
a	O
turning	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
goods	O
into	O
the	O
porch	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
crying	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
channel	O
,	O
but	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Amstead	I-pers
took	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
begged	O
Mr.	O
Meriton	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
in	O
that	O
gang	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
thieving	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Badham	I-pers
.	O
Captain	O
Meriton	B-pers
sent	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
taken	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Swan	O
Alley	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
deceived	O
us	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
show	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
appeared	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
somebody	O
round	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
back	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
her	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
then	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
assistants	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
our	O
due	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
shirt	O
unmade	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
plates	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
Johnson	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
I	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
Badham	O
.	O
You	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
you	O
was	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
wife	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Q.	O
Recollect	O
what	O
answer	O
he	O
gave	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Badham	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
run	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
house	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
into	O
the	O
Hay-field	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
secure	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
?	O
Badham	O
.	O
We	O
secured	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
desire	O
he	O
would	O
ask	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Martin	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
contradict	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
denied	O
himself	O
?	O
Badham	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
what	O
you	O
wanted	O
?	O
Badham	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
wanted	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Meriton	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
what	O
answer	O
did	O
I	O
make	O
?	O
Meriton	O
.	O
You	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
He	O
will	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
what	O
signifies	O
my	O
asking	O
questions	O
when	O
he	O
denies	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
Johnson	O
(	O
to	O
Badham	O
)	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
declare	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
?	O
Badham	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
,	O
indeed	O
you	O
did	O
,	O
indeed	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
goods	O
by	O
the	O
vault	O
door	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
vault	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
with	O
only	O
one	O
petticoat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
liberty	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
hay	O
field	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
either	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
up	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
she	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
can	O
fight	O
a	O
battle	O
,	O
)	O
she	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
like	O
an	O
ox	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
foul	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
her	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
shoved	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
it	O
opened	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
stout	O
fellows	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
rustical	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
she	O
came	O
along	O
very	O
quietly	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Amstead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Con	O
stable	O
to	O
Johnson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
key	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
run	O
round	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
.	O
I	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fore	O
room	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
was	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
hay	O
field	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
run	O
up	O
who	O
had	O
received	O
stolen	O
goods	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shove	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
came	O
up	O
she	O
came	O
quietly	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
thoroughfare	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
?	O
Amstead	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
belonging	O
to	O
Johnson	O
's	O
house	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
vault	O
door	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
fast	O
?	O
Amstead	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
passage	O
with	O
about	O
50	O
houses	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
any	O
person	O
might	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
will	O
consider	O
this	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Badham	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
?	O
Badham	O
.	O
The	O
minute	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Now	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
first	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Amstead	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
let	O
Badham	O
in	O
,	O
had	O
Johnson	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
then	O
or	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
?	O
Amstead	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Carter	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
press	O
gang	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
there	O
's	O
any	O
goods	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
ask	O
the	O
boy	O
[	O
Martin	O
]	O
whether	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Ask	O
Martin	O
whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
these	O
girls	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Bernard	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
.	O
Martin	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Meriton	O
had	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
more	O
than	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
girls	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
received	O
these	O
goods	O
from	O
Martin	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Johnson	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
-	O
Copeland	O
and	O
Monroe	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
particularly	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
Esther	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
;	O
Martin	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
Capt	O
.	O
Meriton	O
's	O
wall	O
or	O
pales	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
these	O
girls	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
give	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
somebody	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
persons	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Meriton	O
being	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Copeland	O
,	O
Monroe	O
and	O
Buck	O
,	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
Johnson	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
boy	O
confessed	O
it	O
mighty	O
publickly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Johnson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
and	O
a	O
ship	O
mate	O
of	O
his	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
ticket	O
for	O
the	O
Winchester	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
time	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
call	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
pressed	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Execution	O
Dock	O
;	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
lock	O
at	O
all	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lodgers	O
all	O
go	O
through	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Was	O
I	O
sick	O
in	O
bed	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
ailing	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
sweat	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Plumberee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
to	O
Johnson	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Smith	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
several	O
jobbs	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
something	O
for	O
me	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
Smith	O
's	O
shop	O
but	O
does	O
not	O
now	O
:	O
he	O
pays	O
his	O
rent	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
was	O
not	O
secure	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
closed	O
up	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
window	O
or	O
window	O
shutter	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
great	O
strong	O
board	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
make	O
rasps	O
for	O
the	O
Bakers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
make	O
them	O
better	O
than	O
ordinary	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Ironmongers	O
,	O
because	O
if	O
I	O
sell	O
to	O
them	O
I	O
must	O
sell	O
at	O
a	O
low	O
price	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
only	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Bakers	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
price	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lockeridge	I-pers
.	O
Johnson	O
works	O
at	O
rasp	O
making	O
and	O
file	O
cutting	O
,	O
sometimes	O
he	O
works	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
sometimes	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
within	O
these	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Monroe	I-pers
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
receiving	O
the	O
goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
When	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
you	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
321.	O
Archer	B-pers
Hard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
books	O
bound	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
silver	O
clasps	O
,	O
one	O
the	O
book	O
of	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
.	O
May	O
2	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
brother-in-law	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
Bible	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
enquiry	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
pledge	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Old	O
Street	O
Road	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
He	O
s	O
aid	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Balls	O
in	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
ever	O
deny	O
before	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
that	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
book	O
there	O
?	O
Plummer	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
book	O
in	O
a	O
fortnight	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
?	O
Plummer	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
returned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
straits	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Blue	O
Balls	O
in	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
book	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
earlier	O
in	O
May	O
than	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
speaks	O
of	O
)	O
and	O
asked	O
12	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
book	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
lay	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
bury	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
bringing	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
put	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
out	O
of	O
compassion	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
more	O
than	O
another	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
seven	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pledge	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
he	O
was	O
indicted	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Plummer	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
brother	O
have	O
patience	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
you	O
every	O
farthing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
pulling	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
accounts	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
After	O
my	O
brother	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Barnes	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
at	O
my	O
work	O
till	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
when	O
my	O
brother	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
pawn	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Smith	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
borrowed	O
this	O
book	O
of	O
my	O
sister	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
my	O
brother	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
lay	O
dead	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
beg	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
sister	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
if	O
my	O
brother	O
would	O
have	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
.	O
Plummer	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hinder	O
my	O
wife	O
from	O
coming	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
want	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
shilling	O
or	O
two	O
you	O
may	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
fellow	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
should	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
spare	O
nothing	O
to	O
separate	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
honest	O
in	O
all	O
cases	O
since	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Buckland	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
character	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
Mary	O
Butler	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
322	O
,	O
323	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Cater	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Cater	I-pers
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cater	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
down	O
Barbican	B-place
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
no	O
man	O
or	O
woman	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
blew	O
out	O
a	O
candle	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
home	O
to	O
light	O
me	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
(	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
put	O
her	O
apron	O
against	O
my	O
mouth	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
resist	O
he	O
would	O
stab	O
me	O
,	O
whereof	O
[	O
whereupon	O
]	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
six	O
single	O
shillings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
then	O
Sarah	O
Cox	O
untied	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
drawed	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
off	O
my	O
shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
run	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
untie	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
while	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
took	O
it	O
off	O
your	O
neck	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
calm	O
night	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
calm	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
one	O
person	O
from	O
another	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
Yes	O
very	O
easily	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
light	O
did	O
you	O
discern	O
them	O
by	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
he	O
blew	O
my	O
candle	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
their	O
faces	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
relation	O
of	O
theirs	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
examined	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
first	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
herself	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
other	O
persons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
for	O
this	O
fact	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
particular	O
fact	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
how	O
far	O
she	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Justice	O
had	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
singly	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
untied	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
confession	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
something	O
wrote	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
marks	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
coming	O
along	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
or	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
[	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
]	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
[	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
]	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
apron	O
before	O
his	O
mouth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
The	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
then	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
She	O
untied	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
who	O
stood	O
behind	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
light	O
did	O
you	O
discern	O
this	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
discerned	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lamps	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
lamp	O
thereabouts	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
Yes	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
clear	O
night	O
I	O
stopped	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
William	O
Cox	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
whether	O
he	O
ever	O
saw	O
me	O
before	O
?	O
Cater	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
harm	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
woman	O
before	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
vile	O
jade	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobbinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Willoughby	O
a	O
Press	O
maker	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
Mr.	O
Cater	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Willoughby	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
heard	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
Swan-alley	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
three	O
Jolly	O
Butchers	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
endeavour	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
generally	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
skittle	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dangerous	O
attempt	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
brought	O
home	O
myself	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
had	O
lately	O
worked	O
for	O
a	O
Hog	O
Butcher	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Tidsell	O
(	O
who	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
come	O
hither	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
Cox	O
's	O
credit	O
was	O
good	O
enough	O
to	O
borrow	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
pay	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
this	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
suspect	O
what	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
tell	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
that	O
lent	O
out	O
money	O
at	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
week	O
that	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
Cox	O
?	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
too	O
little	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pot	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
drank	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
some	O
people	O
said	O
he	O
looked	O
a	O
little	O
white	O
)	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
bring	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Joiner	O
's	O
hatchet	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
stirred	O
a	O
step	O
I	O
would	O
lay	O
his	O
head	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
Tidsell	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
called	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
Tidsell	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
what	O
these	O
whores	O
would	O
bring	O
you	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
rogue	O
as	O
this	O
;	O
Cox	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
