TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
18th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1744	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HENRY	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ABNEY	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Drayton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sargent	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Podgar	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Bricknell	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Oakeman	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Skeats	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Rouchead	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Jane	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Audrey	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
November	O
12th	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
And	O
Ann	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Audrey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
pound	I-place
to	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
followed	O
me	O
from	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
hugged	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
neck	O
and	O
insisted	O
I	O
should	O
stay	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
honest	O
wife	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
in	O
any	O
shape	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
an	O
entry	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
had	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
company	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Watchman	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
watch	O
again	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
in	O
Brown	O
's	O
Gardens	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
because	O
she	O
promised	O
me	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
watch	O
again	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Drum-major	O
in	O
Colonel	O
Haughton	B-pers
's	O
Company	O
at	O
Gibraltar	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
spend	O
10	O
s.	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
cause	O
any	O
uneasiness	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
o'clock	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
Ann	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
Ann	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
say	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Audrey	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
thief	O
that	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Philpot	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
designing	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
me	O
in	O
liquor	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
-	O
She	O
never	O
denied	O
the	O
having	O
it	O
from	O
first	O
to	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Philpot	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Audrey	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dun	O
bar's	O
's	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
my	O
cousin	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
any	O
relation	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Audrey	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
way	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
any	O
Kin	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Audrey	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
no	O
kin	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
pretend	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Brown	O
's	O
Gardens	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
and	O
Butler	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
(	O
Butler	O
lives	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
rag	O
shed	O
)	O
about	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
Jane	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
came	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
Butler	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
Butler	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
deliver	O
the	O
watch	O
into	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
Gentlemens	O
hands	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
she	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
unreasonable	O
thing	O
to	O
suppose	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
lend	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
upon	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Butler	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
return	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
matters	O
easy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
?	O
Barron	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
Butler	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
fetched	O
,	O
and	O
Butler	O
delivered	O
the	O
watch	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
when	O
Philpot	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
impudent	O
.	O
Butler	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
.	O
Philpot	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
me	O
say	O
I	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Barron	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Audrey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dunbar	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Philpot	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
your	O
brother	O
's	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
again	O
-	O
she	O
came	O
voluntarily	O
.	O
Butler	O
was	O
very	O
sulky	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
but	O
little	O
.	O
Philpot	O
said	O
to	O
Butler	O
,	O
Deliver	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
Philpot	O
said	O
,	O
Hussy	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
Said	O
Jane	O
,	O
Christopher	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
Ann	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
go	O
,	O
but	O
keep	O
her	O
till	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
Philpot	O
came	O
voluntarily	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
shewed	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
of	O
keeping	O
it	O
-	O
we	O
are	O
related	O
to	O
Philpot	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
birth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
suspected	O
of	O
any	O
theft	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
cousin	O
Tom	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
watch	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dunbar	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Tommy	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
have	O
another	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
your	O
watch	O
for	O
a	O
trifle	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
lose	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
times	O
were	O
very	O
dubious	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Butler	O
.	O
Next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Kit	O
Audrey	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Butler	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
Philpot	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
leave	O
your	O
watch	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dunbar	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
3.	O
Ann	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
(	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
24	O
yards	O
.	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Merrifield	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Merrifield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
the	O
Fleet	B-place
Market	I-place
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
pnted	O
linen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
our	O
porter	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looking	O
at	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
she	O
drew	O
two	O
pieces	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
uppermost	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
James	B-pers
Galloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
,	I-place
Silver-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
October	O
30	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
spoon	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
My	O
man	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
James	O
has	O
got	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
spoons	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
silver	O
spoons	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
stole	O
this	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
customers	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sadler	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
spoons	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
letters	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
this	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
with	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
purse	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hayloft	O
,	O
upon	O
such	O
a	O
beam	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
-	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Yorkshire	O
boy	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
ride	O
one	O
up	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
with	O
a	O
silk	O
string	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Peter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1731	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1744	O
.	O
did	O
steal	O
one	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
chapel	O
,	O
called	O
Spring	B-place
Garden	I-place
chapel	I-place
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Southwell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Humphry	O
Littleales	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Southwell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
Spring-Garden	B-place
,	O
by	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
iron	O
rail	O
lost	O
from	O
his	O
chapel	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
stone-work	O
;	O
the	O
stone	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
iron	O
rail	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
bar	O
in	O
the	O
range	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
-	O
About	O
three	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
which	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Horse	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
throw	O
something	O
down	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
centry	O
at	O
the	O
Pay	O
Office	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
running	O
along	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
:	O
hearing	O
the	O
watch	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
at	O
Scotland-Yard	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
drawn	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hammer	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
the	O
gate	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Ann	B-pers
Peach	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
eight	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
cambrick	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb	B-place
near	O
Turnstile	B-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
steak	O
broiled	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
had	O
been	O
wetting	O
some	O
linen	O
for	O
ironing	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
rolled	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
cloth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
your	O
wife	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
missing	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
a	O
steak	O
to	O
be	O
broiled	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
compassion	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
penny	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
a	O
bundle	O
that	O
lay	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
here	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
:	O
Then	O
she	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
favourable	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Leekey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Malard	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
holland	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
cambrick	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
holland	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Malard	I-pers
;	O
a	O
holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Purey	B-pers
Castor	I-pers
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cambrick	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Malard	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Malard	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
open	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Purey	O
Castor	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Malard	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
blind	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
's	O
feet	O
,	O
one	O
person	O
's	O
foot	O
upon	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
upon	O
the	O
rails	O
before	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
dusk	O
,	O
hardly	O
dark	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Castor	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
some	O
linen	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Uptabake	I-pers
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Leekey	O
about	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Jeweller	O
by	O
trade	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
enclosure	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
discern	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
face	O
almost	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
narrow	O
street	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Mallard	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
Leekey	O
saw	O
some	O
linen	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
called	O
us	O
back	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
blind	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
linen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
tied	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
Robinson	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
opened	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dog	O
barking	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
disturb	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
's	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
likewise	O
by	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
Lawrence	O
and	O
Lomax	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
She	O
bought	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
equally	O
divided	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Cane	O
before	O
?	O
Uptabake	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
knew	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
money	O
by	O
thieving	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
any	O
things	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
ask	O
us	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
asked	O
us	O
wha	O
t	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
these	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
more	O
than	O
we	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
knew	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
little	O
enough	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
white	O
gown	O
,	O
some	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
waistcoat	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mary	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
follow	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
her	O
business	O
was	O
to	O
sell	O
fish	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
dealt	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Cane	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Leekey	O
and	O
Robinson	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10	O
,	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Leekey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Gibb	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
laced	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Gibb	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
April	O
17	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gibb	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Uptabake	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Gibb	O
,	O
at	O
Hick's-hall	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
sworn	O
upon	O
a	O
book	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Scotchman	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
conscience	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
by	O
holding	O
up	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
scratched	O
off	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
One	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
within	O
these	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
months	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibb	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
we	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
forced	O
open	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
gowns	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
laced	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
she	O
looked	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
50	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
4	O
l.	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
always	O
willing	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
enough	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
knew	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
little	O
enough	O
:	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
endeavouring	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
to	O
stifle	O
my	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Uptabake	O
.	O
About	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
months	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
or	O
week	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
dark	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
upon	O
this	O
indictment	O
but	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Leekey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Lebone	I-place
(	O
together	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
ruby	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
medal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
an	O
India	O
damask	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
calimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
September	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Sept.	O
19	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
in	O
money	O
and	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
half	O
guineas	O
among	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
,	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
most	O
valuable	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
bugle	O
worked	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Uptabake	I-pers
.	O
On	O
a	O
wednesday	O
or	O
thursday	O
night	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
Croydon	O
fair	O
,	O
Leekey	O
,	O
Robinson	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
jar	O
;	O
Leekey	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Robinson	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
bugle	O
box	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
Leekey	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
chin	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
bought	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
-	O
Robinson	O
carried	O
the	O
candle	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
leave	O
a	O
candle	O
there	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
burnt	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
stuck	O
upon	O
some	O
drawers	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
the	O
candle	O
.	O
Uptabake	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
chiefly	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
were	O
half	O
guineas	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
rings	O
,	O
a	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
things	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
.	O
Leekey	O
.	O
They	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
separated	O
;	O
their	O
hearing	O
one	O
another	O
corroborates	O
one	O
another	O
's	O
evidence	O
.	O
Uptabake	O
.	O
We	O
broke	O
the	O
shell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
silver	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Cane	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
equally	O
divided	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
we	O
shared	O
,	O
Leekey	O
and	O
Robinson	O
went	O
to	O
Croydon	O
Fair	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
and	O
pair	O
-	O
Robert	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
was	O
equally	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Leekey	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
the	O
information	O
?	O
Uptabake	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
.	O
Leekey	O
and	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Cane	O
,	O
guilty	O
as	O
an	O
accessary	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Leekey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Convent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
five	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
ten	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Leekey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lomax	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
castors	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
castor	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
six	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
castors	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
these	O
two	O
indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
fifty-nine	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
three	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
bohea	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
Kensington	B-place
Gate	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
raining	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Turnham	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Richardson	O
left	O
these	O
goods	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
bringing	O
them	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
wooden	O
horse	O
that	O
I	O
carry	O
my	O
lamps	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
thence	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lamplighter	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
advertised	O
with	O
two	O
guineas	O
reward	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
near	O
the	O
Packhorse	O
on	O
Turnham	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lace	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
theft	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
warrant	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
with	O
all	O
her	O
heart	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
the	O
lace	O
publickly	O
to	O
sale	O
at	O
Kensington	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
showing	O
the	O
things	O
publickly	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
selling	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Kensington	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
setting	O
on	O
the	O
pole	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
lace	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
basket	O
full	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
good	O
luck	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
King	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Kensington	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
gift	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
luck	O
than	O
I	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
-	O
she	O
sells	O
pins	O
and	O
thread	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
opened	O
her	O
basket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
headlace	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
Scot	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
box	O
upon	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
tipped	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
the	O
wink	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
want	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
?	O
she	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
lace	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
Park-Wall	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
William	B-pers
Skipper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
As	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Broomer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Goldsbury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pound	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
3	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Macsall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
breeches	O
full	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
porter	O
on	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
sometimes	O
for	O
two-pence	O
or	O
three-pence	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
can	O
get	O
six-pence	O
another	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
an	O
empty	O
lighter	O
?	O
Mascall	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
hogshead	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
loose	O
tobacco	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
very	O
good	O
hands	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19.	O
David	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Rann	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Rann	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Malpas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cried	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Malpas	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pledge	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
asking	O
him	O
various	O
questions	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
account	O
being	O
but	O
slender	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
cried	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rann	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
James	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
curry	O
comb	O
and	O
brush	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sudger	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sudger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Swan-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
eyes	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sudger	I-pers
's	O
evidence	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Roffe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Thresher	I-pers
,	O
October	O
31	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
shift	O
off	O
my	O
line	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
shift	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Farmborough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
good	O
woman	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
She	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
hard	O
of	O
hearing	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hilliard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shift	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Humphry	B-pers
Collison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
japan	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
31	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
cups	O
and	O
six	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
46	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
box	O
with	O
counters	O
for	O
the	O
game	O
called	O
quadrille	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prestage	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Collison	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Bedford-Row	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Road	I-place
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
my	O
jaw	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
tongue	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
speaking	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
blinded	O
my	O
eyes	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
keys	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
somebody	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
bit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
hit	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
espied	O
this	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
paved	O
stones	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
?	O
Collison	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
first	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
trunk	O
:	O
this	O
key	O
in	O
particular	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Collison	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fraser	O
's	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
robbed	O
Collison	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Road	O
,	O
by	O
Red-lion-street	O
.	O
Hill	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
looks	O
;	O
Gascoign	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
hit	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
We	O
hit	O
him	O
but	O
one	O
blow	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
John	O
Hill	O
hit	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
coffee	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
with	O
them	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
Will	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
it	O
formerly	O
was	O
a	O
brandy-shop	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
thieving	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fraser	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
delivered	O
them	O
up	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
years	O
-	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
together	O
-	O
Gascoign	O
brought	O
me	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
Gascoign	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Jack	O
Adams	O
's	O
Alley	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
)	O
Gascoign	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
near	O
me	O
almost	O
all	O
his	O
life-time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Gascoign	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
been	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
you	O
money	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
money	O
-	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
hard	O
ware	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Hare-street	O
,	O
in	O
Cold-bath-fields	O
;	O
and	O
these	O
fellows	O
used	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
John	O
Hill	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
voluntarily	O
surrendered	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
information	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
sooner	O
,	O
only	O
these	O
rouges	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
surrender	O
yourself	O
to	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
To	O
one	O
Quaite	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
bailiff	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
proper	O
person	O
to	O
surrender	O
yourself	O
to	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
took	O
Hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
Hill	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
frightened	O
you	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
afraid	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
Hill	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
surrendered	O
my	O
self	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
made	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
do	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
did	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
-	O
Prestage	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
with	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Peacock	O
's	O
.	O
Miles	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
John	O
Hill	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fraser	O
's	O
to	O
take	O
Hill	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
Hill	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Hill	O
acknowledged	O
Waters	O
,	O
Gascoign	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
several	O
robberies	O
;	O
-	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
Waters	O
made	O
the	O
discovery	O
)	O
and	O
Hill	O
desired	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
intercede	O
with	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
promised	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
an	O
ample	O
discovery	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
Hill	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
Waters	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Hill	O
has	O
impeached	O
both	O
you	O
and	O
Gascoign	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
impeach	O
nine	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
a	O
brandy-house	O
and	O
coffee-house	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Quaite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
Waters	O
,	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Hill	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
Waters	O
at	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
24	O
,	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
*	I-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
Quaite	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
linen	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
is	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
John	O
Hill	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Quaite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Road	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
one	O
man	O
stopped	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Hollo	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
?	O
Quaite	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
this	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Quaite	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
before	O
eight	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Hill	O
,	O
by	O
name	O
,	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
stick	O
cross	O
my	O
and	O
nose	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
me	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
half-pence	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
stick	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
action	O
[	O
the	O
produced	O
a	O
pretty	O
large	O
bludgeon	O
.	O
]	O
There	O
were	O
John	O
Hill	O
,	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
Gascoign	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
,	O
you	O
bitch	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
woman	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
your	O
will	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
take	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
Gascoign	O
clapped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
you	O
going	O
about	O
?	O
Quaite	O
.	O
To	O
buy	O
a	O
tin	O
kettle	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
several	O
nights	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
those	O
men	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
?	O
Quaite	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
been	O
after	O
them	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
your	O
husband	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Quaite	O
.	O
He	O
heard	O
me	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
were	O
George	B-pers
Quaite	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Tring	I-pers
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
directed	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Road	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
?	O
Quaite	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
receive	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
?	O
Quaite	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Quaite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
assist	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
officers	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
to	O
Francis	B-pers
Quaite	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
thief-taking	O
?	O
Francis	B-pers
Quaite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
send	O
your	O
wife	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
?	O
Quaite	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
then	O
?	O
Quaite	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
in	O
that	O
road	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
John	O
Hill	O
,	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
,	O
Gascoign	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
John	O
Hill	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Quaite	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
getting	O
it	O
presently	O
,	O
old	O
Hill	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
so	O
long	O
about	O
?	O
and	O
John	O
Hill	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
old	O
Hill	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
directly	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
Only	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
!	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
as	O
John	O
Hill	O
's	O
father	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
otherwise	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
ever	O
rob	O
with	O
you	O
before	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
Not	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
robberies	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
-	O
we	O
robbed	O
one	O
man	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
by	O
the	O
alms-houses	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
old	O
Hill	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
drinking	O
;	O
though	O
he	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
us	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
his	O
son	O
did	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
we	O
went	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
us	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
ourselves	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
very	O
night	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Quaite	I-pers
and	O
his	O
son	O
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
and	O
Haines	O
the	O
Thief-takers	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
on	O
purpose	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
lodgers	O
,	O
for	O
't	O
is	O
full	O
of	O
lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
persons	O
they	O
wanted	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Quaite	O
came	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
my	O
wife	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
tin	O
kettle	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
God	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
a	O
brass	O
one	O
.	O
After	O
these	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
pray	O
shall	O
I	O
come	O
in	O
for	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
come	O
in	O
for	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
robbed	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
?	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
these	O
eight	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
bread	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
better	O
than	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
often	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
A	O
Painter	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
thirty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
school-fellow	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
pains-taking	O
man	O
.	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
John	O
Hill	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
26	O
,	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
medal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
October	O
17	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
alms-houses	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	B-place
by	O
the	O
Sun-Inn	B-place
,	O
three	O
persons	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Waters	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Porto-bello	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
particularly	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
John	O
Hill	O
in	O
company	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
old	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
there	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
Waters	O
produced	O
my	O
knife	O
and	O
perriwig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
the	O
hat	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
Waters	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
says	O
that	O
young	O
Hill	O
hit	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
old	O
Hill	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
knock	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
you	O
so	O
long	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
knocked	O
me	O
about	O
very	O
much	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bloody	O
condition	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Sun-Inn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
these	O
people	O
taken	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Joseph	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
your	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
we	O
stopped	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
by	O
the	O
alms-houses	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Porto-Bello	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
hit	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
prove	O
that	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
there	O
as	O
sure	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
proof	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Dorrington	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
glass	O
bottle	O
filled	O
with	O
a	O
spirituous	O
liquor	O
called	O
geneva	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
halfpence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Dorrington	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
17	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dorrington	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	B-place
by	O
four	O
people	O
-	O
there	O
were	O
old	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
Gascoign	O
;	O
Gascoign	O
pointed	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
old	O
Hill	O
?	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
your	O
life	O
?	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
meet	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
conversation	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
your	O
life	O
to	O
be	O
told	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
any	O
otherwise	O
than	O
as	O
Waters	O
told	O
you	O
?	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
No	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
off	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
was	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
tobacco	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
men	O
were	O
they	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
?	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
or	O
a	O
short	O
man	O
?	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
much	O
about	O
my	O
size	O
[	O
a	O
middle	O
size	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
an	O
old	O
man	O
?	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
turned	O
of	O
fifty	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
description	O
that	O
Dorrington	O
gives	O
of	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
is	O
pretty	O
just	O
,	O
he	O
wears	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
middle	O
sized	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
turned	O
of	O
fifty	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
that	O
age	O
?	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Only	O
from	O
what	O
the	O
evidence	O
said	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Gascoign	O
?	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
John	O
Hill	O
,	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
,	O
Gascoign	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
his	O
breeches	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
drinking	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
from	O
another	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
John	O
Hill	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
eighteen-pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
on	O
this	O
indictment	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Quinsby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Alddergate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
horn	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
knee	O
buckle	O
,	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
stock	O
,	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
four-pence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Petticoat	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
stock	O
and	O
stock	O
buckle	O
off	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
four-pence	O
halfpenny	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
broken	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
old	O
houses	O
which	O
are	O
uninhabited	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
I	O
believe	O
for	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
waked	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
broken	O
house	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
stock	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
my	O
snuff	O
box	O
and	O
a	O
knee	O
buckle	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
beating	O
my	O
rounds	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
candle	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
light	O
it	O
and	O
welcome	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Watchman	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
coming	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
here	O
;	O
for	O
Jemmy	O
is	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
without	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
you	O
may	O
get	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Robertson	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
cold	O
morning	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
watchman	O
have	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
filled	O
a	O
cup	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
another	O
dram	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
another	O
three	O
halfpence	O
left	O
.	O
When	O
that	O
was	O
drank	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
for	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
the	O
knee	O
buckle	O
and	O
snuff-box	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
odd	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
in	O
the	O
empty-house	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
she	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
this	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dalby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
18	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
nurse	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
back	O
alley	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
open	O
-	O
She	O
burst	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
a	O
louder	O
noise	O
than	O
a	O
pistol	O
can	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
listened	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
feet	O
go	O
cross	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
a	O
jar	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
going	O
in	O
for	O
fear	O
there	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
men	O
with	O
their	O
cutlasses	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bounced	O
out	O
upon	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
an	O
hundred	O
,	O
a	O
brazen	O
faced	O
jade	O
:	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
off	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
second	O
piece	O
came	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
had	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
these	O
shirts	O
out	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
stove	O
and	O
the	O
wall	O
:	O
nobody	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
somebody	O
's	O
feet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Henry	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Orgars	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
bohea	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
brush	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
three	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
26	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
porter	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
with	O
some	O
empty	O
casks	O
to	O
an	O
inn	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
another	O
parcel	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
for	O
some	O
old	O
Ropes	O
in	O
a	O
lumber	O
hole	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
tea	O
in	O
three	O
papers	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
about	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
tea	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
hoard	O
of	O
somebody	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
God	O
knows	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
R	O
W	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
cross	O
between	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
position	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
moved	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
through	O
a	O
sash-window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
from	O
behind	O
a	O
partition	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
the	O
candle	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
partition	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
bag	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
's	O
hats	O
,	O
three	O
papers	O
of	O
tea	O
and	O
a	O
hard	O
brush	O
;	O
the	O
hats	O
were	O
marked	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea	O
had	O
the	O
marks	O
I	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
papers	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
begged	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Perne	I-pers
These	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
lumber	O
hole	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
marks	O
that	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
papers	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
marking	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
press	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
his	O
bed-side	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
three	O
Papers	O
and	O
the	O
brush	O
,	O
and	O
moving	O
some	O
boxes	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
hats	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
some	O
servant	O
had	O
hid	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
formerly	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
justices	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Somerset	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
certificate	O
of	O
his	O
behaviour	O
there	O
[	O
a	O
certificate	O
under	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
minister	O
and	O
church	O
wardens	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
admitted	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
in	O
Evidence	O
]	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
his	O
master	O
Cross	O
would	O
speak	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
Dost	O
thou	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
speak	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
thy	O
behalf	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
please	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Cross	O
.	O
This	O
poor	O
creature	O
was	O
recommended	O
into	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
single	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
understand	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
,	O
I	O
humbly	O
hope	O
the	O
court	O
will	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33	O
,	O
34	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Perkins	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Artwell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
Nov.	O
25	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Artwell	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
sunday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
dined	O
at	O
the	O
glass-house	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
boat	O
load	O
of	O
people	O
and	O
landed	O
at	O
Black	O
Friers	O
;	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
Shoe-Lane	B-place
whether	O
these	O
people	O
struck	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
God	O
knows	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
by	O
three	O
women	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
women	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
opened	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
stock	O
off	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
throtled	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
those	O
two	O
women	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
directly	O
-	O
the	O
farthest	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
[	O
Jackson	O
,	O
]	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
their	O
names	O
,	O
how	O
should	O
I	O
know	O
their	O
names	O
?	O
this	O
gentleman	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Capel	O
]	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
them	O
off	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
distinguish	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
How	O
should	O
I	O
see	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
throtled	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
women	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
women	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
nobody	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
seem	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
jest	O
:	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
neither	O
drunk	O
nor	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
set	O
with	O
the	O
watchmen	O
till	O
four	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
drinking	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
stock	O
and	O
stock	O
buckle	O
you	O
lost	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
your	O
neck	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
bustle	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
No	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
up	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
collar	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Q.	O
Shoe-lane	O
is	O
a	O
dark	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
night	O
.	O
Artwell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
place	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
moon-shining	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pipemaker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Liquorpond	O
Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
sure	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
By	O
her	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
certainly	O
see	O
her	O
face	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
how	O
could	O
I	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
face	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
?	O
Coun	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
time	O
you	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
staid	O
till	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
Yes	O
-	O
I	O
drank	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
in	O
company	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
likely	O
then	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
drinking	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
you	O
were	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
Artwell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
show	O
you	O
my	O
arms	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
now	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Capel	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
man	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
murdered	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
women	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Williamson	O
stood	O
by	O
with	O
the	O
stock	O
and	O
stock-buckle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
stock	O
and	O
stock	O
buckle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
stock	O
?	O
Capel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
stock	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buckle	O
dropped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stock	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Artwell	O
?	O
Capel	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Williamson	O
do	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Capel	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Williamson	O
touch	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
sister	O
's	O
-	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
houses	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
picked	O
the	O
stock	O
and	O
stock-buckle	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
and	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
hers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Williamson	O
offer	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
stock	O
again	O
?	O
Capel	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
women	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Capel	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
woman	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
another	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
.	O
And	O
please	O
your	O
honour	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
usual	O
time	O
of	O
our	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
uproar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Artwell	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
stock	O
and	O
buckle	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
Jackson	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Jackson	O
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
mentioned	O
Williamson	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
to	O
our	O
houseman	O
,	O
she	O
belongs	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
ill	O
same	O
;	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
find	O
her	O
:	O
for	O
she	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Moll	O
Perkins	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
often	O
answers	O
to	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Willia	O
mson	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
this	O
countryman	O
[	O
Capel	O
]	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Artwell	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Williamson	O
?	O
Abel	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
sister	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Horne	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
Liquorpond	O
Street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Capel	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
women	O
upon	O
Artwell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knocked	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Perkins	O
?	O
Abel	O
.	O
Only	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Moll	O
Perkins	O
?	O
Abel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
-	O
the	O
watchman	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Moll	O
Perkins	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sells	O
hearts	O
and	O
livers	O
about	O
streets	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
beadle	O
ask	O
Jackson	O
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
two	O
persons	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honour	O
of	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Ward	B-pers
Beadles	I-pers
to	O
Alderman	O
Hoare	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
night	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
watch	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
exceeding	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
Jackson	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
upon	O
some	O
demur	O
made	O
a	O
mistake	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
never	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
but	O
her	O
sister	O
went	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
what	O
charge	O
he	O
gave	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
A	O
street	O
robbery	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
know	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
Constable	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Artwell	O
swore	O
hard	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
consider	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
us	O
whether	O
Williamson	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
mentioned	O
the	O
two	O
following	O
names	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
wrote	O
down	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
says	O
,	O
that	O
Jane	B-pers
Norbury	I-pers
and	O
Pat	O
Bristow	O
,	O
alias	O
Little	O
Pat	O
,	O
were	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Jackson	O
declared	O
that	O
Williamson	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
stock	O
produced	O
in	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
before	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
there	O
?	O
Stanton	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
circumstances	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
bring	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
will	O
speak	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
Rayment	O
Large	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Watchman	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Artwell	O
came	O
very	O
drunk	O
into	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
stock	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
look	O
into	O
your	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
the	O
stock	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
stock	O
produced	O
in	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
before	O
Williamson	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Large	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
stock	O
and	O
buckle	O
are	O
not	O
worth	O
six	O
pence	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
brass	O
buckle	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Stanton	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
knew	O
Williamson	O
?	O
Stanton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
girl	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
hay	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
Selling	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
livers	O
and	O
lights	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
sheeps-heads	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Beadle	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
the	O
loose	O
order	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Boston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Williamson	O
near	O
thirty	O
years	O
,	O
almost	O
from	O
her	O
birth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
good	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
sells	O
livers	O
and	O
lights	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
baked	O
heads	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Church-warden	O
last	O
year	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
three	O
other	O
persons	O
unknown	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Welldy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Welldy	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
about	O
15	O
minutes	O
after	O
9	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
passed	O
me	O
in	O
Old	O
Bethlehem	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
posts	O
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
close	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
little	O
dog	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
drew	O
a	O
knife	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
immediately	O
let	O
my	O
puddings	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
threatened	O
to	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
fellow	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
take	O
that	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
black-boy-alley	O
boys	O
are	O
not	O
taken	O
yet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Welldy	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
lame	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
held	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
the	O
moon	O
shone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lamps	O
were	O
lighted	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
lamps	O
facing	O
Bethlehem-gate	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
rails	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
and	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
the	O
money	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
being	O
abused	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
?	O
Welldy	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
reddish	O
beard	O
on	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
me	O
last	O
Sunday	O
,	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
present	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
are	O
examining	O
.	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
withdraw	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
discover	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
directly	O
?	O
Welldy	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
an	O
hundred	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Welldy	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Lloyd	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
lame-footed	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
pick-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
for	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
14	O
years	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Welldy	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
who	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
believed	O
they	O
knew	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
under	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
me	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
37.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Madringham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hubert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridges-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
.	O
-	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
abroad	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
having	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
have	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
few	O
trifles	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Deveil	I-pers
's	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
person	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hubert	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Figure-maker	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
deliver	O
liver	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
from	O
under	O
a	O
floor	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
in	O
Swan-yard	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
where	O
Thomas	B-pers
Madringham	I-pers
lodged	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Deveil	I-pers
's	O
.	O
-	O
Madringham	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Madringham	I-pers
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38	O
.	O
+	O
Lucy	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
cambrick	O
caps	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cambrick	O
tucker	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cambrick	O
ruffles	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
checquered	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
1st	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
girl	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
live	O
a	O
fortnight	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
mere	O
charity	O
,	O
and	O
respect	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
live	O
there	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
place	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
dressed	O
herself	O
in	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
pillow	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
clothes	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
produced	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39	O
.	O
+	O
Abraham	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Isabella	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
tin-box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
Sep.	O
17	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
desire	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Harvey	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Kilbourn	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
Paddington	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
-	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
garter	O
:	O
my	O
cousin	O
Harvey	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
ale	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
drink	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
My	O
cousin	O
drank	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
cousin	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
far	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Kilbourn	O
to	O
pay	O
16	O
Shillings	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Waters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
your	O
cousin	O
that	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
-	O
I	O
paid	O
three	O
pence	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
drank	O
,	O
my	O
cousin	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
us	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
cousin	O
parted	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
to	O
London	O
:	O
when	O
my	O
cousin	O
parted	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
me	O
safe	O
to	O
Kilbourn	B-place
;	O
I	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
my	O
way	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
no	O
company	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
field	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
highway	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
is	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
highway	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
considerable	O
distance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
or	O
did	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
He	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
and	O
sixteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
anything	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
lewdness	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
For	O
lewdness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
robbed	O
you	O
then	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
lewd	O
fellow	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
debauch	O
you	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
entrusted	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Dean	O
's	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
thief	O
.	O
You	O
thought	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
rob	O
you	O
of	O
your	O
virtue	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
so	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
pistol	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
pistol	O
or	O
stick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
put	O
you	O
into	O
any	O
fear	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
otherwise	O
than	O
being	O
rude	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littlewood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
this	O
woman	O
into	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
garter	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Littlewood	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
-	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
share	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
?	O
Littlewood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Kilbourn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
accept	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
her	O
safe	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
told	O
you	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlady	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Blaker	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Berridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
one	O
Blaker	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
robbery	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Littlewood	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
fighting	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
fighting	O
booth	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
some	O
people	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
improper	O
place	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
rescued	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
will	O
be	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
when	O
the	O
fight	O
is	O
over	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
spoil	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
diversion	O
,	O
nor	O
spoil	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Littlewood	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
let	O
them	O
part	O
the	O
money	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Blaker	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Littlewood	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
thought	O
it	O
dangerous	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
booth	O
said	O
,	O
push	O
;	O
Littlewood	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
so	O
fast	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
that	O
Crispin	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Rawhole	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
interrupt	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Crispin's-day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Broughton	O
's	O
booth	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
with	O
several	O
men	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
knew	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
