TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
19th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
C.	O
NUTT	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
1745	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ABNEY	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLING	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Meriton	I-pers
,	O
Elmer	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Multon	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Oldner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Luttman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
Ernest	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Perrit	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Seacall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Blackgrove	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hambridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealling	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
17	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
about	O
15	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
:	O
My	O
Wife	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
13	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
a	O
36	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
,	O
five	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
a	O
Punch-Ladle	O
,	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
eight	O
Razors	O
and	O
two	O
Wigs	O
,	O
My	O
Man	O
went	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
About	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
again	O
:	O
The	O
Constable	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Conversation	O
with	O
him	O
afterwards	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
your	O
Money	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
your	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
of	O
Trinity	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
this	O
Boy	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Gate	O
of	O
our	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
such	O
Boy	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
this	O
Boy	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
this	O
Punch	O
Ladle	O
,	O
a	O
Portugal	O
36	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
and	O
the	O
Guineas	O
and	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
two	O
Perriwigs	O
and	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Razors	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mears	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Race	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
November	O
4	O
.	O
Q.	B-pers
James	I-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
At	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	B-place
near	O
Whitechapel	B-place
Church	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
wanted	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
lie	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
even	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
with	O
my	O
Soldier	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Hot-Pot	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Soldier	O
was	O
upon	O
Duty	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
my	O
Till	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Keys	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Till	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Spoon	O
gone	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
suspect	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Rickards	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
mine	O
within	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
an	O
it	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
Name	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
value	O
it	O
at	O
one	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
Hat	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jasper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
:	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Till	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
?	O
He	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
the	O
Hat-Lining	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Perfect	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hawkin	O
's	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
bare	O
Foot	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
tells	O
wrong	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
nor	O
walk	O
bare	O
Foot	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Work	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
over-against	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
that	O
Handkerchief	O
than	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
Hat	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
as	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Witness	O
here	O
;	O
the	O
Regiment	O
is	O
march	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
Scotland	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
my	O
Footman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Draught	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
,	O
my	O
Son-in-Law	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Draught	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Banker	O
,	O
ordering	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
two	O
20	O
l.	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
the	O
two	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
and	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Cash	O
for	O
the	O
Draught	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Million-Bank	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
Notes	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Chamber	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Purse	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Buroe	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Bed-Chamber	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
over-Night	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
know	O
my	O
Orders	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Toy-Shop	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
Dressing-Table	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Order	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Buroe	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Purse	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Studs	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
Purse	O
inside-out	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
Money	O
and	O
Notes	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Note	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
this	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
two	O
Studs	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Purse	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Notes	O
in	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
but	O
one	O
Bank	O
Note	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Note	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Look	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
?	O
Well	O
,	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
diligently	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
mistrust	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Neale	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
slip	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
putting	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
Purse	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
)	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
thought	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
Draught	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
.	O
The	O
Bearer	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
exchange	O
two	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
Bank	O
Note	O
does	O
exactly	O
correspond	O
with	O
the	O
Bank	O
Note	O
then	O
given	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
enter	O
the	O
Number	O
,	O
Date	O
and	O
Sum	O
of	O
every	O
Note	O
coming	O
in	O
or	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
This	O
Note	O
being	O
stolen	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
it	O
by	O
our	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
correspond	O
with	O
the	O
Number	O
,	O
Date	O
and	O
Sum	O
of	O
the	O
Entry	O
thereof	O
paid	O
unto	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
's	O
Draught	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
right	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
second	O
Letter	O
of	O
my	O
Name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whom	O
receiv	O
'd	O
you	O
this	O
Note	O
?	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
.	O
From	O
a	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
's	O
Clerk	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
.	O
Q.	O
Madam	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand-writing	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
own	O
Hand-writing	O
.	O
Hinckley	O
Phipps	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Linnen-Draper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
bought	O
Cloth	O
of	O
my	O
Man	O
to	O
the	O
Amount	O
of	O
2	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
presented	O
the	O
Bill	O
to	O
my	O
Man	O
and	O
desired	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
truly	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
for	O
so	O
little	O
Money	O
being	O
laid	O
out	O
:	O
But	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
Man	O
run	O
down	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Note	O
.	O
But	O
my	O
Servant	O
returning	O
,	O
tells	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
immediately	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Sands	O
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
speaking	O
broad	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Scoth	O
Hair	O
Merchant	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
for	O
the	O
Bank-Note	O
12	O
l.	O
in	O
Hair	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
well	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
Merchant	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Snuff-colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Waistcoat	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Colour	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
Wig	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Clerk	O
asked	O
him	O
some	O
Questions	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
Story	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
related	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Boar	O
at	O
Turn-Stile	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Degree	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
steady	O
Countenance	O
and	O
an	O
Air	O
of	O
Honesty	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
my	O
Service	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Scruple	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
along	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
lives	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
describing	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
they	O
thought	O
the	O
Description	O
answer	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Matthews	O
's	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Dr.	O
Jurin	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Note	O
?	O
Hinckley	O
Phipps	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Number	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
may	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Testimony	O
to	O
swear	O
;	O
yet	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
at	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
's	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
Bank-Note	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
of	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
for	O
two	O
Hours	O
together	O
at	O
Dr.	O
Jurin	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
saw	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
steady	O
Countenance	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
like	O
before	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
bought	O
Irish	O
Cloth	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
2	O
d.	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Bank	O
Bill	O
for	O
Change	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
in	O
the	O
Counting-House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
Note	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
did	O
buy	O
the	O
Cloth	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Phipps	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Note	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
it	O
stopt	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Clerk	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
This	O
Note	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Phipps	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
stopt	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
bring	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
make	O
out	O
his	O
Claim	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Phipps	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Secretary	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Phipps	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
some	O
Hair	O
to	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Change	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
's	O
.	O
This	O
Note	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
:	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Possession	O
ever	O
since	O
:	O
Shew	O
it	O
to	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Note	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
our	O
Book	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
stopt	O
in	O
Payment	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
whom	O
enter	O
'd	O
?	O
Blackwell	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Secretary	O
's	O
Clerk	O
:	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
enter	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Books	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Cashier	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
signed	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
very	O
well	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
Note	O
with	O
another	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Frock-pocket	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
at	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
your	O
Mistress	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Goods	O
?	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
these	O
nine	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
in	O
Newport	O
Market	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Skeen	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Huff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Huff	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
my	O
Husband	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
Wheelwright	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
great	O
Wheel	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
Home	O
very	O
much	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
threatned	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
was	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
broad	O
and	O
long	O
;	O
he	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Diaculum	O
,	O
and	O
scraped	O
some	O
Lint	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Plaister	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
Sheet	O
under	O
his	O
Leg	O
:	O
He	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Sleep	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
Light-headed	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
among	O
the	O
Wheelwrights	O
a	O
Confederacy	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Combination	O
;	O
and	O
these	O
were	O
those	O
that	O
threatned	O
both	O
Master	O
and	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
doubled	O
their	O
Fists	O
;	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Skeen	I-pers
had	O
before	O
threatned	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
that	O
these	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
borrow	O
'd	O
18d	O
.	O
and	O
spent	O
a	O
Shilling	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
them	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
his	O
Adze	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
William	O
Hales	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
your	O
Man	O
cut	O
himself	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Plaister	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
said	O
t'other	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Huff	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Skeen	I-pers
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
declared	O
all	O
this	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
his	O
Death-Red	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
wilful	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
your	O
Husband	O
's	O
being	O
press	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Soldier	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Huff	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Wheelwright	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
press	O
'd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
)	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
should	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Soldier	O
:	O
Several	O
Oaths	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
my	O
Maid	O
said	O
that	O
Huff	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
to	O
Huff	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
you	O
cut	O
yourself	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
his	O
Leg	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
Brandy	O
and	O
fine	O
Sugar	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
hard	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
my	O
Death	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
finish	O
my	O
Work	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Hours	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
live	O
to	O
see	O
another	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
that	O
God	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
right	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
accidentally	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
heard	O
rash	O
Words	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
two	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
)	O
say	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
cur	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
to-Day	O
.	O
William	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
cur	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
working	O
to-Day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
at	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
who	O
did	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
threaten	O
'd	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
work	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
Combination	O
to	O
raise	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
their	O
Wages	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
soon	O
cause	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
Work	O
.	O
Q.	B-pers
Philip	I-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Philip	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
No	O
farther	O
than	O
what	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
said	O
unto	O
me	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
of	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
one	O
(	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
was	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
seem	O
'd	O
glad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
your	O
Man	O
cut	O
himself	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
apprehend	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
accidental	O
.	O
Q.	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Stephens	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
?	O
Henry	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
Humour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
all	O
go	O
for	O
Soldiers	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Talk	O
of	O
their	O
Exercise	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
Humour	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Skeen	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
joking	O
about	O
going	O
to	O
Flanders	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
Beer	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Pot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
Friends	O
before	O
the	O
Stroke	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
them	O
after	O
the	O
Wound	O
and	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Henry	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Skeen	I-pers
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
5.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newberry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Counsel	I-pers
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
August	O
28	O
,	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Newberry	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Counsel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
or	O
near	O
Exeter-Exchange	B-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
.	O
I	O
must	O
confess	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
Eight	O
or	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Counsel	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Eldest	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
The	O
young	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Night	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
About	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
And	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
met	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Exeter-Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
a-whoring	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Manner	O
was	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
familiar	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
They	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Coat-Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
by	O
the	O
Lamps	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Coat-Pocket	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
Blow	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
gave	O
her	O
40	O
Shillings	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Discourse	O
was	O
there	O
between	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
her	O
and	O
you	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
all	O
about	O
picking	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Sometime	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
Watch	O
)	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Reward	O
for	O
them	O
that	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
the	O
Mother	O
gave	O
40	O
Shillings	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Not	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
by	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
None	O
but	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
cost	O
me	O
four	O
Guineas	O
at	O
second	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
four	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
worth	O
?	O
Can	O
you	O
pawn	O
or	O
sell	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
a	O
Watch	O
as	O
this	O
,	O
for	O
more	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Indeed	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
Judge	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
Watches	O
.	O
-	O
Barnes	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
advertise	O
his	O
Watch	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
'till	O
this	O
young	O
one	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
that	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
something	O
else	O
besides	O
your	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Leaden	O
shilling	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
I	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
an	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
this	O
Newberry	O
:	O
She	O
is	O
the	O
Husband	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
Having	O
the	O
Warrant	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Rolton	I-pers
]	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
's	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
your	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
open	O
'd	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Name	O
is	O
Stone	O
,	O
which	O
Name	O
somebody	O
had	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
craze	O
out	O
:	O
We	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
Woman	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Son	O
's	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Daughter	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Elizabeth	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
when	O
she	O
made	O
the	O
Information	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Pain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
advertis	O
'd	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
The	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
stolen	O
and	O
bargain	O
'd	O
for	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
The	O
28th	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
Watch	O
)	O
serv	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
little	O
Bag	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Elizabeth	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
?	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldier	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Go	O
and	O
pawn	O
this	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
more	O
Money	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
has	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ear-rings	O
:	O
She	O
wants	O
to	O
swear	O
a	O
Street-Robbery	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Susanna	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Watch	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mother	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
buy	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Watch	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
pinn	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
seen	O
'till	O
I	O
see	O
my	O
Child	O
's	O
Face	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
desire	O
to	O
understand	O
clearly	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
advertis	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Lost	O
the	O
28th	O
(	O
August	O
)	O
bought	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
29th	O
and	O
advertis	O
'd	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
?	O
A.	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
read	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
reading	O
it	O
she	O
fell	O
a-crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Mind	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
Watch	O
)	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Counsel	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
do	O
what	O
she	O
would	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Swimbowl	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Newberry	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Son	O
had	O
been	O
extravagant	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
lay	O
in	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
remember	O
him	O
.	O
Well	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
:	O
If	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
whole	O
40	O
Shillings	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Meat	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
kiss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
Thing	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
part	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Pounds	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
Pearce	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Water	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
selling	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Son	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
remember	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
five	O
Years	O
Apprentice	O
:	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
sixteen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
in	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Watshoe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newberry	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Newberry	I-pers
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
95	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
a	O
Sash-maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
many	O
Times	O
lost	O
Lead	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
suspicious	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Plummer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bate	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
great	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Lead	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bate	O
comes	O
one	O
Day	O
and	O
tells	O
me	O
of	O
Lead	O
that	O
was	O
bought	O
of	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
in	O
Grub-Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
.	O
He	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stephenson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stephenson	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
Reason	O
the	O
Master	O
told	O
(	O
desired	O
)	O
the	O
Plummer	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
The	O
young	O
Man	O
sold	O
the	O
Weights	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
sell	O
you	O
them	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
last	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Weights	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Brass	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Perquisites	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
no	O
further	O
Questions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
A	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Our	O
Master	O
gives	O
13	O
s.	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
these	O
Pieces	O
are	O
the	O
Journeymen	O
's	O
Perquisites	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
any	O
Person	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
of	O
a	O
Pin	O
's	O
Point	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	B-place
call	I-place
'd	I-place
the	I-place
Restoration	I-place
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
East	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bring	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hatch-Way	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
Ship	O
lie	O
?	O
East	O
.	O
It	O
lay	O
at	O
King	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Stairs	I-place
near	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
)	O
in	O
an	O
Apron	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Bundle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Sea-faring	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
works	O
by	O
the	O
Day	O
.	O
-	O
Rickson	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
twice	O
with	O
Bundles	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
carried	O
any	O
Tobacco	O
ashore	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hocker	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hocker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Fustain	O
Frock	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
Coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
came	O
down	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
Clark	O
,	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
Things	O
down	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Could	O
say	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
were	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Girl	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
this	O
Girl	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Day	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Picther	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
very	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Lodging	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
Money	O
.	O
This	O
Gardner	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
away	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Lodging	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Watchman	O
would	O
be	O
about	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
Clothes	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
two	O
Shifts	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
she	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
Brown	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
with	O
her	O
but	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Gardner	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
Gardner	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
sick	O
Woman	O
,	O
until	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Coroner	O
had	O
sat	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
this	O
Gown	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
This	O
strip	O
'd	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
by	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Ditty	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Gown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
more	O
?	O
Daniel	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
sign	O
'd	O
her	O
Confession	O
at	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
opening	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Brown's-Gardens	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
stripp	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
ty	O
'd	O
round	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
or	O
dying	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
warm	O
yet	O
;	O
she	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
was	O
stripp	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
Gown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
She	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
leather	O
Boddice	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Woman	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
;	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Man	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
This	O
Gardner	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
this	O
Gown	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
to	O
wash.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Mary	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Horsewhip	O
,	O
November	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
William	O
Green	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	B-place
in	O
Monmouth-Street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Whip	O
lay	O
in	O
one	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
About	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Noon	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Girl	O
comes	O
and	O
tells	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
Charge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
did	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
three	O
Sheets	O
and	O
Whip	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
an	O
Apron	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Servant	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
last	O
Month	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Bar	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
very	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Body	O
inticed	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Colstone	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
She	O
is	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Shirt	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bowler	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Monmouth-Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Bowler	O
's	O
Shirt	O
?	O
Colstone	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Bit	O
of	O
Blue	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bowger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Monmouth-Street	O
;	O
I	O
sell	O
and	O
buy	O
Linnen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
buy	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Bowger	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
of	O
her	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
would	O
have	O
sworn	O
to	O
another	O
Shirt	O
;	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Colstone	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Shirt	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowler	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
Hole	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
's	O
Irish	O
Cloth	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
almost	O
new	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
about	O
last	O
June	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
may	O
such	O
a	O
Shirt	O
as	O
this	O
be	O
worth	O
?	O
Colstone	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
worth	O
Ten	O
or	O
Eleven	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
exactly	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
Master	O
bought	O
a	O
whole	O
Piece	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
nothing	O
farther	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Amey	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
6	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
George	B-place
in	O
New	B-place
Prison	I-place
Walk	I-place
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Mug	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chimney	O
Corner	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
five	O
Minutes	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
directly	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Woman	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
selling	O
Mufles	O
;	O
the	O
Minute	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Mufles	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecure	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Mug	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
about	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
into	O
the	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
feel	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
it	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
very	O
Mould	O
in	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
[	O
Here	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
troublesome	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
called	O
Names	O
,	O
as	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
ch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
wanted	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Husband	O
a	O
Cuckold	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
aloud	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
crazy	O
Woman	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Woman	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
Chare-Woman	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
look	O
'd	O
after	O
me	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Lyings-in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
:	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
out-of-the-Way	O
sometimes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Senses	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
young	O
Child	O
sucking	O
at	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
and	O
takes	O
in	O
washing	O
.	O
Rosamond	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
these	O
six	O
Years	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
Pounds	O
:	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
ty	O
'd	O
down	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lofty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Thief	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
drink	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Senses	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
East	I-pers
Clendon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cloth-Fair	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
12	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
reckon	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
14.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Goose	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Priestly	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
George	B-pers
Priestly	I-pers
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
George	B-pers
Priestly	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Goose	O
,	O
a	O
[	O
dead	O
one	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
worth	O
?	O
George	B-pers
Priestly	I-pers
.	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
R.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
George	B-pers
Priestly	I-pers
.	O
He	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
and	O
walk	O
'd	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
Goose	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Priestly	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
before	O
an	O
Alderman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
Priestly	O
lost	O
his	O
Goose	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Said	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
his	O
Friends	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
*	O
.	O
15.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Skep	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	O
Bibby	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
hardly	O
24	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
Thief	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Evidence	O
in	O
last	O
May	O
Sessions	O
against	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
a	O
notorious	O
Thief	O
,	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
Sarah	B-pers
Soames	I-pers
,	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
Number	O
iv	O
.	O
Page	O
107	O
.	O
Trial	O
202	O
Also	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Sessions	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stavenaugh	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Howel	O
.	O
See	O
Session	O
Paper	O
,	O
Number	O
v.	O
Page	O
147	O
,	O
Trial	O
264	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
convicted	O
on	O
her	O
Evidence	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
likewise	O
been	O
Evidence	O
against	O
little	O
Boys	O
,	O
her	O
Accomplices	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Skep	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
Business	O
are	O
you	O
of	O
?	O
Richard	B-pers
Skep	I-pers
.	O
Music	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
the	O
City-Waits	O
,	O
of	O
Faringdon-Ward	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
Coat	O
upon	O
the	O
Closet-Door	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Hours	O
to	O
refresh	O
myself	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
again	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
my	O
Coat	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
three	O
Shillings	O
and	O
a	O
Penny	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
)	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
fetch	O
my	O
Hautboy	O
.	O
-	O
Butcher	O
.	O
The	O
Coat	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
seven	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whose	O
Coat	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Sister	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Brother	O
's	O
Coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
Sister	O
?	O
-	O
Butcher	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
pawn	O
'd	O
Things	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
Sister	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
William	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Cocoa	O
,	O
at	O
Bear-Key	B-place
,	O
November	O
11	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
had	O
stolen	O
some	O
Cocoa	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
this	O
William	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lap	O
three	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Cocoa	O
at	O
Bear-Key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
another	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Lap	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
the	O
Person	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
that	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Lap	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Nail	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
open	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
nam	O
'd	O
Ned	O
and	O
Sal	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
Ned	O
and	O
Sal	O
would	O
come	O
(	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
)	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
and	O
carry	O
off	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
of	O
one	O
Hogshead	O
the	O
Head	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
gone	O
besides	O
what	O
we	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
a	O
Nail	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
talk	O
of	O
opening	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
with	O
that	O
Nail	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
another	O
Person	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Nail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
;	O
now	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
in	O
your	O
Judgement	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
many	O
Pounds	O
Weight	O
you	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a	O
Pound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
David	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
David	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
the	O
Cocoa	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
safe	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
(	O
Hogshead	O
)	O
found	O
open	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Boy	O
,	O
that	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
:	O
The	O
(	O
the	O
Cocoa	O
)	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
Lap	O
by	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
my	O
Time	O
to	O
a	O
Chimney-Sweeper	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Tobias	B-pers
Burne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
from	O
Bear-Key	B-place
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
Nov.	O
11	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
myself	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Bear-Key	O
Buildings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Manner	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
following	O
my	O
Man	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Man	O
coming	O
down	O
between	O
one	O
Story	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Story	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
Sugar	O
?	O
I	O
must	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
an	O
Apron	O
hung	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
:	O
There	O
it	O
is	O
:	O
And	O
in	O
that	O
Bag	O
was	O
the	O
Sugar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
Want	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
English	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
West-India	O
Merchant	O
's	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Mills	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Stocking	O
full	O
of	O
Sugar	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Stocking	O
full	O
of	O
Sugar	O
between	O
his	O
Thighs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
Want	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
deny	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Job	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
cried	O
out	O
for	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
Reason	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Sugar	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Bargain	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
first	O
the	O
Man	O
asked	O
20	O
d.	O
but	O
took	O
14	O
d.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Sugar	O
off	O
of	O
Brewer	B-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
,	O
computed	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
October	O
23	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Millborn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
of	O
Oct.	O
was	O
working	O
at	O
Brew-house	O
Key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Millborn	O
.	O
A	O
Land-Waiter	O
.	O
Jones	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Lighter	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
cast	O
my	O
Eye	O
into	O
the	O
Lighter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
was	O
it	O
then	O
?	O
Millborn	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
Noon	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
filling	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
his	O
Coat-pocket	O
,	O
with	O
Sugar	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
taking	O
Sugar	O
from	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
heave	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
hide	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Tarpaulin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
the	O
Tarpaulin	O
up	O
?	O
Millborn	O
.	O
The	O
Tarpaulin	O
lay	O
loose	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
rumpled	O
all	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Lighter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
him	O
to	O
move	O
the	O
Coat	O
?	O
Millborn	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
moved	O
the	O
Tarpaulin	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
Coat	O
)	O
under	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
cover	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Millborn	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
order	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Millborn	I-pers
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Sugar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Sugar	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Did	O
it	O
match	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Sugars	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Millborn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Sugars	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
different	O
Merchants	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Black	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
Land-Waiter	O
sent	O
one	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
:	O
Says	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
something	O
;	O
look	O
under	O
the	O
Tarpaulin	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Jones	O
's	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Sugar	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Heartly	I-pers
.	O
Jones	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
Coat	O
that	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
in	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
like	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
his	O
Coat	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
that	O
at	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cutter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Jones	O
.	O
Plummer	O
I	O
knew	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
four	O
Years	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
:	O
He	O
brought	O
up	O
his	O
Children	O
very	O
prettily	O
;	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
our	O
Market	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Spital-Fields	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
10	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
an	O
Apartment	O
of	O
mine	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Blemish	O
in	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
good	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
every	O
one	O
what	O
he	O
dealt	O
for	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
To	O
James	B-pers
Pentitbu	I-pers
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Pentithu	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
Years	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Gaming	O
or	O
Swearing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
18	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bears	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Characters	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pentney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
has	O
been	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Children	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
and	O
a	O
Bun	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Valentine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
three	O
Years	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19.	O
Richard	B-pers
Eve	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Bread	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pagett	I-pers
,	O
October	O
24	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pagett	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Man	O
out	O
with	O
Bread	O
,	O
one	O
Half-Peck	O
,	O
11	O
Quarterns	O
,	O
five	O
Thee-Penny	O
and	O
two	O
Two-Penny	O
Loaves	O
.	O
About	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
my	O
Man	O
comes	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Basket	O
and	O
Bread	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
the	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Duke's-Place	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Basket	O
and	O
Bread	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Basket	O
and	O
Bread	O
upon	O
this	O
Man	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
Basket	O
of	O
Bread	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
Duke's-Place	O
is	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
often	O
sell	O
Bread	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
Duke's-Place	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
Market	O
for	O
Bread	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
shall	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
for	O
this	O
Bread	O
?	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
Quarterns	O
,	O
Three-penny	O
and	O
Two-penny	O
Loaves	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
20	O
d.	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
took	O
18	O
d.	O
for	O
Basket	O
and	O
Bread	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
Quarterns	O
for	O
Three-pence	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Three-penny	O
Loaves	O
for	O
five	O
Farthings	O
a	O
Piece	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heart	I-pers
.	O
This	O
young	O
Man	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	B-place
Head	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Basket	O
was	O
pitched	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
;	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knowing	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
oftentimes	O
Bread	O
sold	O
in	O
Duke's-Place	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
strike	O
down	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
ca	O
n't	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
:	O
This	O
young	O
Man	O
challenges	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
lays	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
says	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Said	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mason	O
's	O
Hand	O
Jack	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Whitro	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
16	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Whitro	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
by	O
Trade	O
a	O
Cabinet-Maker	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Mason	O
's	O
Hand-Jack	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
to	O
weigh	O
a	O
great	O
Weight	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
did	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knockt	O
it	O
to	O
Pieces	O
at	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Cog	O
and	O
Plate	O
,	O
for	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
which	O
weighed	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
at	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Pound	O
came	O
to	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Whitro	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
it	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
in	O
Crooked	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Part	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
for	O
three	O
Farthings	O
a	O
Pound	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
buying	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Relations	O
nor	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
19	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
this	O
Sutton	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
ours	O
is	O
a	O
Car-Yard	O
,	O
in	O
Moor-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
Sight	O
a	O
Matter	O
of	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
later	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
thinking	O
of	O
the	O
Iron	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
this	O
24	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
How	O
had	O
he	O
it	O
?	O
Fuller	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
lost	O
Streaks	O
and	O
Horseshoes	O
,	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
Tire-Streaks	O
for	O
our	O
Cart	O
Wheels	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
this	O
Iron	O
at	O
London	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
one	O
Richardson	O
's	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
Defence	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
that	O
Purpose	O
,	O
but	O
asked	O
a	O
thousand	O
Pardons	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Green	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Dec.	O
5	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
Pocket	O
Yesterday	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
Left	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
charged	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
forward	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
punished	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tago	I-pers
.	O
She	O
has	O
lived	O
nine	O
Months	O
in	O
my	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Britain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Long	O
Pains-taking	O
Woman	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
will	O
drink	O
a	O
little	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
;	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Passage	O
in	O
or	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
seventeen	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Sept.	O
8	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
cause	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
suffered	O
very	O
much	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
in	O
Bolt	B-place
in	O
Tun	B-place
Court	I-place
in	O
Fleet-Street	B-place
:	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
follow	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
between	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
safe	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
homewards	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
within	O
about	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
of	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Brooks	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Rogue	O
and	O
a	O
Villain	O
:	O
And	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
turn	O
to	O
look	O
unto	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
second	O
Blow	O
he	O
cut	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
Place	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Blows	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
seventeen	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
my	O
House	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
Visit	O
against	O
my	O
Will	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
About	O
Eleven	O
or	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cried	O
out	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Appraiser	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
lend	O
Money	O
upon	O
Goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
knockt	O
you	O
down	O
:	O
Was	O
you	O
quite	O
sober	O
then	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
but	O
Part	O
of	O
two	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Children	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
struck	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
you	O
Rogue	O
and	O
Villain	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
seventeen	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Wig	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
Door	O
:	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Bolt-in-Tun	O
Inn	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
Inn	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
found	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
safe	O
Place	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Counter	O
?	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
lame	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
Leg	O
shorter	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
40	O
l.	O
to	O
cure	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Cure	O
too	O
.	O
-	O
Chainey	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
one	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
in	O
Bolt-in-Tun	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
comes	O
down	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
comes	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
Dog	O
,	O
your	O
Names	O
is	O
Brooks	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
Dog	O
,	O
who	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
Scoundrel	O
?	O
I	O
stepp	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
quarrel	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
Word	O
begat	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
Fighting	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walk	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Bolt-in-Tun	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
his	O
Wig	O
came	O
off	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Villain	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
17	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
.	O
Nothing	O
more	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Chainey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
.	O
-	O
Molloy	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
just	O
put	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
say	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Step	O
of	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Chainey	O
with	O
a	O
Pipe	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
knock	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
naked	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
naked	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
being	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Friend	O
ill	O
us	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
?	O
And	O
I	O
am	O
about	O
10	O
Yards	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
I	O
was	O
naked	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
Gold	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
17	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
.	O
I	O
still	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chatney	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Molloy	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Weaver	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
'Squire	O
Turner	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
)	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Porter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Washer-Woman	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
Washing	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Molloy	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Cap	O
helping	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
myself	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
althought	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
17	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Dowell	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
Reason	O
,	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
Brooks	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
destroy	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
naked	O
Hanger	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Woman	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dangerous	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Dowell	O
.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
speaking	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman-Thief	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Brooks	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
he	O
lent	O
22	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
going	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Gate-Way	O
Quarrel	O
?	O
Dowell	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
or	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Voice	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Brooks	O
was	O
roul	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
dawb	O
'd	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
Molloy	O
ask	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
Brooks	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Chainey	O
say	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
your	O
Wig	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
a-Doors	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
17	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Flamboy	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
light	O
it	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
holping	O
Dog	O
:	O
The	O
Neighbours	O
were	O
all	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
none	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
five	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
17	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Money	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Uproar	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
were	O
afraid	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Hanger	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
made	O
several	O
Notches	O
and	O
Cuts	O
in	O
the	O
Wood	O
of	O
the	O
Bedstead	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
persuade	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
his	O
going	O
to	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
honourably	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Mony	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
a	O
Gentleman-Thief	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
further	O
than	O
hearing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bolt	O
in	O
Tun	O
Inn	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
twenty	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Roul	O
and	O
a	O
Tumble	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
or	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
he	O
had	O
gotten	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
sent	O
Home	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
Chamberlain	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
Cook	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
Brooks	O
)	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
myself	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
any	O
Shape	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Molloy	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
ha	O
n't	O
you	O
lost	O
something	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
seventeen	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
What	O
Character	O
does	O
he	O
bear	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
and	O
justly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
unto	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
Customer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Brooks	O
come	O
and	O
search	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
People	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Beds	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
search	O
every	O
Room	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
together	O
Night	O
and	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
what	O
Business	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
Abroad	O
on	O
board	O
that	O
Ship	O
which	O
the	O
Lieutenant	O
of	O
was	O
shot	O
for	O
Cowardice	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
was	O
so	O
troublesome	O
to	O
search	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
another	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Ferdinando	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
one	O
Sunday	O
in	O
November	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Molloy	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Green-Dragon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
gotten	O
the	O
F	O
-	O
at	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
.	O
At	O
the	O
Green-Dragon	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
Spite	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
spoke	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
David	B-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
Mr.	O
F	O
-	O
.	O
Cumberland	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
Months	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Midshipman	O
in	O
the	O
Anglesea	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
an	O
Estate	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
strict	O
Honesty	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Substance	O
.	O
-	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hutton	O
of	O
Gainsborough	O
has	O
given	O
him	O
several	O
Dranghts	O
upon	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
an	O
Estate	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
200	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Trader	O
,	O
and	O
traded	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
.	O
After	O
such	O
a	O
Cloud	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
appearing	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
his	O
Innocence	O
was	O
manifested	O
with	O
peculiar	O
Glory	O
,	O
and	O
Gladness	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
every	O
Countenance	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
Consequence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
honourably	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
granted	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
24.	O
William	B-pers
Bur	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
.	O
John	O
-	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
He	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
a	O
Room	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
Lodging	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
last	O
March	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
up	O
an	O
Alley	O
and	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
thorough-fare	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
last	O
March	O
,	O
whereas	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
last	O
Christmas	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
dead	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
William	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Woollcomber	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
last	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
want	O
any	O
Worsted	O
?	O
And	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
fasten	O
'd	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
about	O
my	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Tongue	O
he	O
put	O
down	O
my	O
Throat	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
a	O
nasty	O
Fellow	O
,	O
I	O
bit	O
his	O
Tongue	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
and	O
Locket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
New-Inn-Yard	O
,	O
she	O
in	O
Cock-Lane	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
this	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
light	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
you	O
so	O
badly	O
?	O
Russel	O
.	O
I	O
bit	O
his	O
Tongue	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
rude	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
of	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Oath	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dimple	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
last	O
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
Worsted	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Irish	O
Worsted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
say	O
something	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
round	O
her	O
Neck	O
and	O
buss	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
get	O
withinside	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
round	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
indeed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
teaz	O
'd	O
so	O
.	O
-	O
Bromley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
10	O
Years	O
;	O
my	O
Business	O
is	O
a	O
Weaver	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Woollcomber	O
;	O
he	O
makes	O
Worsted	O
to	O
fell	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
about	O
this	O
Bracelet	O
,	O
has	O
heard	O
that	O
this	O
Women	O
is	O
a	O
bad	O
Woman	O
in	O
several	O
Shapes	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
say	O
unto	O
Men	O
,	O
Lend	O
me	O
your	O
Tougue	O
,	O
and	O
buss	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
charg	O
'd	O
another	O
Person	O
with	O
this	O
Bracelet	O
.	O
Bromley	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
declare	O
the	O
Truth	O
.	O
That	O
Gentlewoman	O
would	O
have	O
sent	O
my	O
Daughter	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
one	O
Bell	O
,	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Necklace	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
comes	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Father	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
go	O
of	O
the	O
Errand	O
,	O
what	O
Harm	O
is	O
there	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
But	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Reason	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Papist	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Trouble	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Weaver	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Worsted-Weaver	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Weaver	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
for	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
found	O
him	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charge	O
Bell	O
with	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
Necklace	O
)	O
Yesterday	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
?	O
Bright	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
bought	O
Goods	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
is	O
her	O
Character	O
for	O
Chastity	O
?	O
Bright	O
.	O
Give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
Vulgar	O
Report	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Things	O
of	O
her	O
that	O
are	O
not	O
commendable	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
her	O
Dealings	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neagle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
shooting	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
October	O
10	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
Ever	O
since	O
the	O
first	O
March	O
that	O
I	O
march	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Ensign	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
march	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Train'd-Bands	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
common	O
Man	O
for	O
some	O
House-Keeper	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
out	O
Militia	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
made	O
their	O
firing	O
,	O
their	O
regular	O
firings	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
loaded	O
?	O
There	O
were	O
36	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
12	O
in	O
a	O
Rank	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
loaded	O
?	O
And	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
almost	O
fronting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
six	O
Yards	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
and	O
Wadding	O
hit	O
against	O
my	O
Coat	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
fir	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
last	O
Rank	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
third	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
both	O
Right	O
Hand	O
and	O
Left	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
loaded	O
?	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
Rank	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
loaded	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
Stephens	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
loaded	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
3d	O
and	O
4th	O
Time	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
Officers	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
4th	O
Time	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Present	O
and	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
you	O
now	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
any	O
Hurt	O
or	O
Harm	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
Thing	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
has	O
been	O
stold	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
your	O
Exercise	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
Blows	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oak	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
?	O
Oak	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
Hat	O
in	O
the	O
Vinegar-Field	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Head	O
off	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
what	O
Hurt	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
his	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
Word	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Stephens	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
shoot	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Times	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
Four	O
Times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Thing	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Gun	O
?	O
Did	O
it	O
make	O
a	O
Report	O
?	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
he	O
shot	O
;	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
Dispute	O
before	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Piece	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Line	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
two	O
Shirts	O
.	O
-	O
.	O
He	O
stole	O
a	O
Livery	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Stable	O
in	O
Saville-Row	B-place
,	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
:	O
The	O
Man	O
catched	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
?	O
-	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
Livery	O
Coat	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
-	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Coachman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
water	O
my	O
Horses	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Back	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
a	O
Smuggler	O
?	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
very	O
Coat	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Bassett	I-pers
2	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Train	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
Hours	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Primrose-Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
and	O
my	O
Family	O
in	O
Disorder	O
:	O
He	O
run	O
