TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
18th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1745	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiseham	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Rice	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hennel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ribright	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Keep	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collett	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Osman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hett	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Huggett	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Increase	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
.	O
+	O
299.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
leathern	O
purse	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
thimble	O
,	O
val	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
silver	O
pocket	O
piece	O
,	O
val	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
gloves	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Portugal	O
gold	O
coin	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
Fourteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pound	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
August	O
3th	O
.	O
Mary	O
Pound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
nights	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
London	O
with	O
my	O
stockings	O
and	O
shift	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
pressed	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
submit	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
would	O
all	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
wrong	O
you	O
of	O
three	O
pound	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
gave	O
me	O
but	O
36	O
s.	O
for	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
pieces	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
(	O
constable	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Aug	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
's	O
shift	O
and	O
stockings	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Deveil	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
these	O
two	O
rings	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tucker	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dispute	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
pawned	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pound	O
's	O
silk	O
purse	O
with	O
about	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pound	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
three	O
pound	O
twelve	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tucker	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
this	O
purse	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
this	O
leathern	O
purse	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
17	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Pound	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
three	O
pound	O
twelve	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
take	O
these	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
in	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Wright	O
)	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
this	O
purse	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Gibson	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Shug	O
lane	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
talked	O
about	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
doubt	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
three	O
pound	O
twelve	O
shilling	O
piece	O
to	O
take	O
twenty	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
four	O
pence	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owing	O
for	O
things	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
weighed	O
the	O
piece	O
against	O
another	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
thirty	O
six	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
pretty	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
for	O
that	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
rings	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
3	O
in	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
money	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
.	O
These	O
two	O
rings	O
were	O
placed	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
parcels	O
of	O
goods	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
26	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
change	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
Then	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
another	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
nine	O
shillings	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutrix	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
transportation	O
.	O
300.	O
Jane	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Cathorne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
checked	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
20	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
And	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
judge	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
nights	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
from	O
n	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
before	O
justice	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
good	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
the	O
pawning	O
of	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Read	O
knew	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
301.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyrs	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
cambrick	O
mobs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cambrick	O
ruffles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d	O
and	O
a	O
necklace	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
3	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
person	O
.	O
On	O
saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Nottingham	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
Monday	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
those	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ram	O
Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
Nottingham	O
waggon	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
thinking	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	O
Oldcastle	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
there	O
hearkening	O
to	O
the	O
musick	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
thing	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
after	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
some	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gilner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
Mrs	O
Cooper	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
302.	O
Ann	B-pers
Danks	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bercill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Whitchurch	I-pers
,	O
July	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
303	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
August	O
9	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Toyshop	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
difficult	O
in	O
choosing	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
turned	O
up	O
her	O
apron	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
it	O
were	O
four	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
304	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Sign	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Angel	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Sept.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
all	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
friends	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
from	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
till	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
publick	O
room	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
George	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
fellow	O
servants	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
but	O
just	O
delivered	O
the	O
tankard	O
into	O
George	O
Fell	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
known	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drinking	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
They	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
from	O
two	O
o'clock	O
till	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
given	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
About	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
tankard	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
just	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
George	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
to	O
seek	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
tankard	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
pardon	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
cooper	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	B-pers
Tap	I-pers
-house	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Mary	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
fine	O
servant	O
to	O
stay	O
here	O
all	O
this	O
afternoon	O
(	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Bamber	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
Bow	O
coach	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
so	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
all	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
our	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
Mary	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
Mary	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
draw	O
me	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
pewter	O
tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
reply	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
draw	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
pewter	O
tankard	O
?	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
fellow	O
servants	O
can	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
those	O
men	O
:	O
the	O
maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
tankard	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
maid	O
bring	O
the	O
silver	O
tankard	O
up	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
little	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
little	O
room	O
by	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
followed	O
her	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mary	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
,	O
which	O
shall	O
have	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Fell	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
candle	O
is	O
blown	O
out	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
:	O
presently	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
can	O
I	O
do	O
?	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
sometimes	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
at	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pawnbrokers	O
to	O
try	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
marked	O
R.C.S	O
.	O
the	O
man	O
seemed	O
in	O
a	O
surprise	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
surprise	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
surprise	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
that	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
's	O
tankard	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
girl	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
trouble	O
myself	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
should	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
about	O
8	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
tankard	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
customer	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
sister	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Skinner	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
8	O
l.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
brewer	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
whose	O
tankard	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
sister	O
's	O
tankard	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
lend	O
her	O
so	O
much	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
40	O
s.	O
for	O
her	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
her	O
six	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
time	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
's	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
's	O
servant	O
maid	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
company	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
little	O
room	O
by	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
upon	O
some	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
six	O
guineas	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
305.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitchurch	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
Aug.	O
5th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
306	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
307.	O
Mary	B-pers
Macklaughlin	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
night	O
or	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
.	O
Jeffs	O
and	O
Martin	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
come	O
at	O
,	O
we	O
tried	O
at	O
several	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Dove	O
Court	O
,	O
by	O
Leather	O
Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
Jeffs	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
oppose	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
head	O
off	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
latch	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Jeffs	O
turned	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
something	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
;	O
Martin	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
run	O
for	O
?	O
or	O
something	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ribbed	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
Martin	O
off	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Macklaughlin	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Mason	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Thomas	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Little	O
Moll	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
five	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
us	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
gave	O
us	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Martin	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
.	O
Macklaughlin	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
308.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
chain	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Portinier	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
8th	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Portinier	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
looked	O
under	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
engaged	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Coal	O
Yard	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Dare	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Dare	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
Pope	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
chain	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
(	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
first	O
committed	O
for	O
correction	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
watch	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
chain	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dare	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
something	O
pushed	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
watch	O
kicked	O
against	O
my	O
foot	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bruise	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
in	O
it	O
having	O
a	O
new	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
on	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
309	O
.	O
310	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watland	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
Harrateen	O
curtains	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
vallens	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
ladle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pewter	O
chamber	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pewter	O
porringers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
saucepan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
July	O
28th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Sawyer	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
shutters	O
were	O
cut	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bolts	O
knocked	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
?	O
Watland	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Gray	O
's	O
in	O
Essex	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
dreamed	O
an	O
ugly	O
dream	O
,	O
that	O
somebody	O
had	O
her	O
gown	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
windows	O
nailed	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
every	O
thing	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Crockett	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Jones	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
lived	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
bring	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
kettle	O
and	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
rattled	O
.	O
They	O
left	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
some	O
sheets	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
twelve	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
bring	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
then	O
?	O
Crockett	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
carry	O
these	O
things	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Crockett	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
window	O
shutters	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
open	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
window	O
shutters	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
complaint	O
to	O
the	O
neighbours	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
Watland	O
always	O
desired	O
us	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
eye	O
to	O
his	O
windows	O
whenever	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
)	O
one	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
bedaubed	O
with	O
mud	O
.	O
The	O
neighbours	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
have	O
taken	O
out	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Jones	O
went	O
to	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Salmon	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
who	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
the	O
Lane	O
;	O
so	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Salmon	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
dish	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
bed	O
a	O
large	O
spike	O
nail	O
,	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
,	O
[	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
pick	O
lock	O
keys	O
]	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Watland	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
out	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
confessed	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Unwin	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
Watland	O
's	O
house	O
open	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Jones	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
(	O
Crockett	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
information	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
Richard	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
was	O
hanged	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Unwin	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
roguish	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
Crockett	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Jones	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
without	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
trouble	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
[	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
spike	O
nail	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
chissel	O
]	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
time	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
the	O
things	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Watland	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
that	O
Jones	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
his	O
constant	O
practice	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
to	O
pick	O
pockets	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
isle	O
of	O
the	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pass	O
by	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
rightly	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
Isle	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
name	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
name	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
Elmore	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
church	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Moore	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
hurt	O
a	O
man	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
poor	O
.	O
Jones	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Moore	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
311.	O
James	B-pers
Leppard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Aug.	O
12th	O
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
a	O
hogshead	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
at	O
Butolph	O
's	O
wharf	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
some	O
tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hogshead	O
:	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
never	O
so	O
little	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Hartley	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
foreigner	O
that	O
works	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
porter	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
works	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
ill	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Buckeridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thirteen	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
fruit	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tatem	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gangsman	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
for	O
the	O
merchants	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landwaiters	O
are	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
We	O
put	O
the	O
goods	O
into	O
the	O
warehouses	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
turn	O
out	O
right	O
we	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
deficiency	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
every	O
thing	O
answerable	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
daily	O
and	O
hourly	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
frequently	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
deceive	O
me	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
just	O
and	O
true	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tatem	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tinkler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
3	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
as	O
my	O
own	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
to	O
change	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
intrust	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
clear	O
.	O
Hartley	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
wonder	O
that	O
these	O
gangsmen	O
speak	O
for	O
these	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
encourage	O
thieving	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
put	O
them	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clack	I-pers
.	O
(	O
A	O
constable	O
upon	O
the	O
keys	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
reputed	O
pilferer	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
one	O
employed	O
by	O
these	O
gangsmen	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
sweep	O
for	O
the	O
soot	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
what	O
they	O
can	O
thieve	O
or	O
steal	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
some	O
lemon	O
porters	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
tobacco	O
lay	O
under	O
some	O
planks	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
Hartley	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hogshead	O
.	O
Hartley	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hogshead	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whose	O
property	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
merchants	O
than	O
one	O
concerned	O
in	O
that	O
ship	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
312.	O
Richard	B-pers
Westfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
August	O
3	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clack	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
hook	O
the	O
tackle	O
to	O
the	O
hogsheads	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
bring	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
,	O
at	O
Wiggins	B-place
's	I-place
key	I-place
:	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
hogsheads	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
who	O
broke	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
coopers	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
coopers	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
truth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
deny	O
it	O
?	O
Clack	O
.	O
They	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
begged	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
And	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
sheet	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
313.	O
John	B-pers
Swinton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
of	O
Scotch	O
cloth	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Tyson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
apt	O
to	O
stay	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
come	O
so	O
early	O
home	O
as	O
my	O
hours	O
required	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
think	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
money	O
dishonestly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
his	O
trunk	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
opened	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
reluctancy	O
,	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
Scotch	O
cloth	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
it	O
be	O
mine	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
your	O
trunk	O
?	O
I	O
looked	O
on	O
it	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
with	O
characters	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
lay	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
brushing	O
my	O
clothes	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
in	O
my	O
trunk	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
fall	O
down	O
into	O
it	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
.	O
Q.	O
Excepting	O
this	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Cartwright	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
given	O
to	O
drinking	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
strict	O
hand	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
the	O
defence	O
he	O
does	O
now	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
Cartwright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
quite	O
new	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
314	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
Sarah	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
coming	O
by	O
Bayswater	O
,	O
near	O
Kensington	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
(	O
it	O
rained	O
prodigious	O
hard	O
.	O
)	O
A	O
person	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
a	O
crape	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
crape	O
over	O
it	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
his	O
crape	O
aside	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
came	O
each	O
way	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
none	O
.	O
He	O
damned	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
give	O
him	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
demanded	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
7	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
off	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
we	O
drove	O
after	O
him	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
drive	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
stood	O
upright	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
highwayman	O
,	O
a	O
highwayman	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
rode	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
how	O
long	O
time	O
did	O
they	O
take	O
him	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
sight	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
pull	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
knew	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
hoped	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
the	O
lady	O
whether	O
she	O
knows	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
your	O
face	O
,	O
the	O
crape	O
was	O
aside	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
crape	O
he	O
had	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
that	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Price	O
's	O
evidence	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
informed	O
it	O
was	O
needless	O
to	O
relate	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
myself	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
our	O
respective	O
homes	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Tyburn	O
turnpike	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
highwayman	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
rained	O
violently	O
hard	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
on	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
track	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
ride	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
was	O
surprised	O
to	O
hear	O
somebody	O
so	O
near	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
my	O
horse	O
rode	O
before	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
immediately	O
stop	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
after	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
horse	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
came	O
down	O
together	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
and	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
we	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hue	O
and	O
cry	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
he	O
must	O
answer	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
.	O
He	O
struggled	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
robbery	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
soon	O
now	O
,	O
so	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
and	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
.	O
In	O
leading	O
him	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
two	O
women	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
trifle	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
of	O
about	O
18	O
d.	O
or	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thank	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
White-hart	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
women	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
call	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
loaded	O
with	O
shot	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
and	O
some	O
brass	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
rings	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
tie	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
breeches	O
for	O
the	O
rings	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
holes	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
might	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
lining	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
unbuttoned	O
the	O
knees	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
they	O
dropped	O
out	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
evidence	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
given	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
true	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
pistol	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
unfortunate	O
unhappy	O
fellow	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
extravagant	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
nor	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
wrong	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
were	O
ill	O
and	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
drove	O
to	O
necessity	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
fan	O
maker	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
paid	O
me	O
pounds	O
for	O
work	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
followed	O
the	O
trade	O
till	O
it	O
grew	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
live	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
other	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
other	O
business	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
to	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
a	O
vine	O
vault	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
within	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
in	O
putting	O
up	O
a	O
sign	O
in	O
Bridges	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
that	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
another	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bigs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
journey-man	O
then	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
fanstick	O
making	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
ago	O
?	O
Bigs	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Deshorough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
thirteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
pretty	O
conversant	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Deshorough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
accounted	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perriwig	O
maker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
our	O
acquaintance	O
he	O
was	O
reckoned	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
honestest	O
men	O
that	O
we	O
knew	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Streng	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
for	O
whatever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
fifteen	O
years	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
person	O
speak	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
begged	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
all	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
committed	O
.	O
315.	O
Ephraim	B-pers
John	I-pers
Mansell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
razors	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
books	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Walham	B-place
Green	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
twelve	O
razors	O
and	O
six	O
books	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
twelve	O
books	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
you	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
excellently	O
well	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
the	O
cross	O
examination	O
)	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodge	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
these	O
razors	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
lend	O
him	O
any	O
razors	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
on	O
this	O
account	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
razors	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
razors	O
at	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
schoolmaster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
scholars	O
did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
have	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
had	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
scholars	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
has	O
so	O
many	O
scholars	O
would	O
steal	O
a	O
few	O
old	O
razors	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
?	O
Blunt	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Mansell	I-pers
made	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
razors	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
's	O
son	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
one	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
shaving	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
razors	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
razors	O
at	O
Davis	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
razor	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
bit	O
broke	O
off	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
blade	O
in	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
handle	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
unacquainted	O
with	O
the	O
proceedings	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
excuse	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
rules	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
razor	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
I	O
borrowed	O
some	O
razors	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
October	O
)	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
razors	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
old	O
razors	O
,	O
take	O
what	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
three	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
oil	O
to	O
set	O
them	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
as	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
that	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
never	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
razor	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
or	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
thing	O
that	O
we	O
whet	O
knives	O
upon	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
razors	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
My	O
daughter	O
carried	O
those	O
things	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
's	O
over	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mansell	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
things	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Ford	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
seven	O
books	O
,	O
three	O
razors	O
,	O
a	O
hammer	O
and	O
a	O
flower	O
tub	O
Mr.	O
Burgess	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Mansell	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Mansell	O
would	O
insist	O
upon	O
his	O
innocence	O
and	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
does	O
he	O
bear	O
?	O
Burgess	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
reputation	O
and	O
justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Richard	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
?	O
Burgess	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
malicious	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
loves	O
to	O
be	O
litigious	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
(	O
the	O
Headborough	O
)	O
Blunt	O
was	O
3	O
times	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
the	O
warrant	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mansell	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
warrant	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
execute	O
the	O
warrant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mansell	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
should	O
fall	O
into	O
such	O
hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
His	O
character	O
from	O
all	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
steal	O
old	O
razors	O
and	O
old	O
books	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
two	O
years	O
over	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
such	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
any	O
advantage	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
serve	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cope	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
better	O
character	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
than	O
Mr.	O
Mansell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
his	O
bail	O
.	O
Blunt	O
said	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
Mr.	O
Mansell	O
's	O
fault	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Mansell	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
character	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
be	O
his	O
bail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
any	O
razors	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
no	O
more	O
stole	O
the	O
razors	O
than	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
has	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
's	O
character	O
is	O
as	O
indifferent	O
an	O
one	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
can	O
have	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
prosecution	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mansell	O
was	O
honourably	O
acquitted	O
.	O
316.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Susanna	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
cambrick	O
half	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
goods	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
by	O
our	O
own	O
workmen	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
stopped	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
four	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
8	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
property	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
her	O
six	O
shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
sister	O
's	O
.	O
Seeing	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
confusion	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
my	O
boy	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
sister	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
sister	O
's	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
more	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Randall	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Randall	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
intercede	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Randall	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
left	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wadland	I-pers
's	O
service	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Randall	O
's	O
service	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
linen	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
gentlemens	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Randall	O
's	O
to	O
live	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
she	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
yours	O
?	O
Crisp	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
no	O
body	O
can	O
stain	O
the	O
family	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
this	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
her	O
sister	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
317.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dolman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mackie	I-pers
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
August	O
5	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
early	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
us	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
stay	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
half-pence	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
shilling	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Robin	B-pers
Mackie	I-pers
.	O
If	O
your	O
Lord-ship	O
pleases	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
story	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
There	O
she	O
stands	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
but	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
herself	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
her	O
husband	O
to	O
kiss	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
stopped	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
buss	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
bussing	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
half	O
pence	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
vexed	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
asleep	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
by	O
seeing	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
for	O
then	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
alley	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
with	O
a	O
bloody	O
apron	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
drams	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
buckles	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
awake	O
or	O
asleep	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
master	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
lodging	O
house	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
people	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
318	O
.	O
+	O
Philip	B-pers
Devine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
complete	O
sets	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
2d	O
,	O
3d	O
and	O
4th	O
vol	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Roman	O
history	O
,	O
By	O
Ozell	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
400	O
sheets	O
,	O
being	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
vol	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
200	O
books	O
of	O
the	O
4th	O
vol	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Blayer	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	O
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Blayer	I-pers
.	O
These	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
warehouse	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carne	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
room	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
warehouse	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
chap	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
thirteen	O
bundles	O
out	O
of	O
47	O
.	O
I	O
discovered	O
it	O
first	O
by	O
this	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
sent	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
muffatees	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Avery	O
to	O
be	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
home	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
paper	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
In	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
this	O
paper	O
in	O
loose	O
sheets	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
pence	O
farthing	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
common	O
price	O
for	O
waste	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
three	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
from	O
November	O
till	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Carne	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Blayer	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
that	O
paper	O
:	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
,	O
was	O
returned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carne	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Deveil	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
his	O
wife	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
sold	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
ruined	O
and	O
undone	O
forever	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
carver	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carne	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Mr	O
Blayer	O
brought	O
this	O
cargo	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
warehouse	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
pile	O
always	O
remained	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
scooped	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blayer	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Carne	O
here	O
is	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
paper	O
left	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
but	O
thirteen	O
bundles	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
hundred	O
weight	O
to	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
hundred	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
eleven	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ninn	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
worked	O
piece	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
him	O
25	O
or	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
employ	O
him	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
work	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ninn	I-pers
.	O
My	O
servant	O
bought	O
two	O
parcels	O
of	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hundred	O
weight	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
third	O
of	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hundred	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
parcels	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Blayer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
thirteen	O
bundles	O
to	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
for	O
32	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
which	O
makes	O
my	O
whole	O
loss	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
that	O
computation	O
,	O
amount	O
to	O
85	O
l.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carne	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
sheets	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
or	O
into	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
never	O
so	O
little	O
a	O
thing	O
openly	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
stole	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Godwin	O
Prime	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
)	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
devil	O
possessed	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
paper	O
by	O
piece-meal	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Crane	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Blayer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
employ	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
goods	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
stealing	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Blayer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Carne	I-pers
,	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
capital	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
319	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
(	O
together	O
with	O
-	O
Hawthorn	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
seven	O
doe	O
skins	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
twelve	O
skins	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
quilted	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
wooden	O
pail	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
curtain	O
rod	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
either	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
at	O
night	O
or	O
the	O
10th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
fast	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
doe	O
skins	O
were	O
worth	O
at	O
least	O
10	O
l.	O
This	O
bed	O
gown	O
of	O
mine	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Carr	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
only	O
offered	O
me	O
this	O
bed	O
gown	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
old	O
things	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
320	O
.	O
+	O
Monica	B-pers
Branning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Grayley	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
alley	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
inside	O
and	O
an	O
outside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
chain	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Grayley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
and	O
plaistrer	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Sparks	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Phoenix	O
Street	O
,	O
Spittle	O
Fields	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
neighbourly	O
club	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Buttermilk	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	I-place
cross	I-place
Phoenix	I-place
Street	I-place
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
[	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
]	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
buss	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
hands	O
round	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
(	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
printed	O
linen	O
gown	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
)	O
she	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
upon	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
leave	O
my	O
prize	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
slippery	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
blow	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
my	O
two	O
hands	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
took	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
clerk	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
till	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
some	O
goods	O
for	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
Grayley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
sad	O
creature	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Grayley	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
your	O
gown	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Grayley	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
face	O
very	O
plain	O
in	O
Buttermilk	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Grayley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
dark	O
and	O
light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
return	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Grayley	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
complain	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Grayley	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Grayley	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
madam	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
Only	O
in	O
publick	O
company	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
soner	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
wondered	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
cross	O
the	O
back	O
with	O
his	O
cane	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
for	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Grayley	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
about	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
declare	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
cross	O
the	O
back	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
pushed	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
company	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
except	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
Grayley	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
what	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
in	O
liquor	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
Indeed	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
belief	O
,	O
neither	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
nor	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
sober	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
was	O
drunk	O
and	O
lay	O
cross	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
chairs	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
she	O
takes	O
in	O
dubbling	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
out	O
frequently	O
with	O
heavy	O
loads	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
creature	O
she	O
would	O
hardly	O
work	O
so	O
hard	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
She	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
things	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
work	O
was	O
slack	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
child	O
have	O
lived	O
a	O
day	O
upon	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
Leg	O
of	O
Beef	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
these	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
her	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
there	O
is	O
money	O
for	O
taking	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marioge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Headborough	O
's	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Christ	O
Church	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
very	O
often	O
we	O
are	O
disturbed	O
by	O
people	O
in	O
that	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
never	O
a	O
lamp	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
the	O
fair	O
thing	O
by	O
every	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
speaking	O
in	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Sparks	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
dark	O
ugly	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
difficult	O
to	O
distinguish	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
face	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
lamp	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
knocked	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
321	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Locker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
two	O
cambrick	O
caps	O
laced	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Buchannan	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
31	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
a	O
little	O
below	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
bundle	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
goods	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Buchannan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Charles	O
Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
works	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
called	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
that	O
bundle	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
that	O
bundle	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
Madam	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
immediately	O
charge	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thompson	O
)	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bedford	O
Bury	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Thompson	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Thompson	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
young	O
fellows	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
?	O
Blackwell	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
?	O
Blackwell	O
.	O
Just	O
below	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
from	O
those	O
fellows	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Mrs.	O
Thompson	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
pretty	O
hard	O
?	O
Blackwell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
reel	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
watch	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
Blackwell	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Blackwell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
blow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
light	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Blackwell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
quite	O
moon	O
light	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
,	O
there	O
happened	O
a	O
little	O
quarrel	O
against	O
my	O
stand	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
there	O
was	O
watch	O
called	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
[	O
Thompson	O
]	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
had	O
his	O
wig	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
for	O
charging	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
hand	O
against	O
her	O
belly	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
taking	O
his	O
ht	O
.	O
I	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
resolute	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
or	O
she	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
madam	O
Thompson	O
delivered	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hat	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
wig	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
escapes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
women	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
women	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
lad	O
finding	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
run	O
after	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
my	O
assistance	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
*	O
.	O
They	O
never	O
talked	O
of	O
losing	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
retaken	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
talked	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
and	O
losing	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
*	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
strange	O
that	O
the	O
constable	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
would	O
appear	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
hoped	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
this	O
Watchman	O
will	O
be	O
enquired	O
into	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
ordered	O
you	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
liberty	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
their	O
beds	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
confined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
they	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
confined	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
Because	O
they	O
brought	O
friends	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
Why	O
they	O
swore	O
very	O
hard	O
and	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
there	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
the	O
boy	O
do	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
charged	O
with	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
his	O
parents	O
these	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
they	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
taylor	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
was	O
unhandsome	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
honest	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
[	O
the	O
boy	O
is	O
about	O
eighteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Ford	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
holder	O
to	O
a	O
painter	O
-	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
youth	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
or	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
no	O
other	O
then	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
inned	O
to	O
cheat	O
or	O
defraud	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
employed	O
by	O
a	O
pa.	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Blackwell	O
)	O
After	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
charged	O
Mrs.	O
Thompson	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
away	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Thompson	O
made	O
answer	O
;	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
with	O
the	O
slap	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
lose	O
the	O
thing	O
than	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
mob	O
said	O
,	O
knock	O
the	O
Scotch	O
bitch	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
child	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Blackwell	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
come	O
back	O
than	O
lose	O
your	O
own	O
life	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
lose	O
your	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Round-house	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
women	O
make	O
their	O
escapes	O
from	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Prior	O
.	O
Going	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
322	O
.	O
+	O
Judith	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechape	I-place
l	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Susannah	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Waters	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Norman	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ford	B-pers
Bolley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
July	O
15th	O
.	O
Ford	O
Bolley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
July	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
Moses	B-place
and	I-place
Aaron	I-place
's	I-place
Alley	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechape	I-place
l	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
What	O
Business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Bolley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Jeweller	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	O
Britain	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
Jeweller	O
at	O
Ratcliff	O
Cross	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
later	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
that	O
Alley	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
women	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
surrounded	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
or	O
some	O
edged	O
tool	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
she	O
cut	O
me	O
cross	O
the	O
nose	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
they	O
stopped	O
my	O
mouth	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
they	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
(	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
alley	O
crow	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
dispersed	O
since	O
the	O
alley	O
has	O
been	O
take	O
up	O
.	O
)	O
Then	O
they	O
dragged	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Moses	O
an	O
Aaron	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
stripped	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
8	O
s.	O
my	O
jewels	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
ear	O
rings	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
instructions	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
here	O
?	O
Bolley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
has	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
jewels	O
?	O
Bolley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
ever	O
saw	O
my	O
face	O
before	O
?	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
recollect	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
her	O
face	O
again	O
?	O
Bolley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
exactly	O
against	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
particular	O
person	O
[	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
]	O
and	O
2	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
by	O
the	O
sight	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
lamp	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Bolley	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
alley	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
thieftakers	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
employed	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
poor	O
creatures	O
before	O
,	O
besides	O
myself	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
this	O
account	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Bolley	O
)	O
Whose	O
house	O
was	O
you	O
carried	O
into	O
?	O
Bolley	O
.	O
Into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Black-Boy	O
alley	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
these	O
creatures	O
she	O
brings	O
to	O
be	O
witnesses	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
North	I-pers
*	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
robbing	O
that	O
man	O
?	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
by	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
oath	O
of	O
Ford	O
Bolley	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
six	O
gold	O
rings	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
discharged	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
Sessions	O
at	O
the	O
goal	O
delivery	O
,	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
North	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
robbed	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
this	O
Susanna	O
Gray	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
there	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
North	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
there	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Bolley	O
]	O
came	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Susanna	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
and	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
say	O
whether	O
you	O
ever	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Bolley	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
North	O
,	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
witnesses	O
were	O
committed	O
by	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Kalisall	I-pers
[	O
He	O
was	O
called	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Ford	O
Bolley	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
jeweller	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
goods	O
together	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
persons	O
of	O
credit	O
ready	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
323	O
,	O
324	O
.	O
+	O
Winifred	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
purse	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
14	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
14	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
done	O
?	O
Thornton	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
called	O
the	O
Hayfield	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
lane	O
by	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
pipe	O
,	O
and	O
smoaked	O
my	O
pipe	O
of	O
tobacco	O
.	O
This	O
Winifred	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
landlady	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
drank	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pledged	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
opposite	O
against	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
;	O
then	O
Jane	O
Johnson	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
rosa	O
solis	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
rosa	O
solis	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
some	O
Irish	O
name	O
I	O
think	O
;	O
-	O
usqucbaugh	O
,	O
ay	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
they	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
where	O
this	O
Winifred	O
Ward	O
lay	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
side	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
had	O
another	O
quartern	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
worked	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
then	O
this	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
sat	O
by	O
me	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
chamber	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
doors	O
higher	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
:	O
a	O
chamber	O
where	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
has	O
carried	O
many	O
an	O
one	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
led	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
chamber	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
sat	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
tasted	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
Winifred	O
Ward	O
hugged	O
me	O
and	O
kissed	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
roll	O
there	O
,	O
Then	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
?	O
Thornton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
immediately	O
after	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
your	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
house	O
?	O
Thornton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
complaint	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
Jane	O
Johnson	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
sat	O
along	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
?	O
Thornton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
325	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
