TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
18th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1745	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HENRY	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ABNEY	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
.	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chester	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Scrooby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brush	I-pers
,	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Train	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Redshaw	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Oseland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Thoyts	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Theodorick	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gatton	I-pers
,	O
Enoch	B-pers
Grigg	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Brayne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
.	O
256	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
*	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
December	O
Sessions	O
(	O
with	O
his	O
son	O
John	O
Hill	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
executed	O
)	O
upon	O
indictments	O
for	O
highway	O
robberies	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Part	O
I	O
.	O
Page	O
8	O
.	O
Trial	O
24	O
.	O
Page	O
9	O
.	O
Trial	O
27.	O
and	O
Page	O
10	O
.	O
Trial	O
29.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
White	B-place
Hart	I-place
in	I-place
Golden	I-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
At	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
tankard	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
hot	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
ale	O
and	O
gin	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
company	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
thrust	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
very	O
creditable	O
gentlemen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
days	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
the	O
tankard	O
again	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
tankard	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
tankard	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
move	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
bench	O
to	O
the	O
table	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
from	O
the	O
table	O
to	O
the	O
bench	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
old	O
clothes	O
which	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
My	O
neighbour	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
tankard	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
with	O
the	O
old	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
working	O
goldsmith	O
in	O
the	O
snuff-box	O
way	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
played	O
six	O
games	O
at	O
draughts	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Ellis	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Crosby	O
Plummer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
tankard	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
next	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
old	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
clothes	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
tankard	O
too	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
moved	O
the	O
tankard	O
several	O
times	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Plummer	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
man	O
I	O
saw	O
have	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
clothes	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
or	O
loose	O
?	O
Plummer	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
loose	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Tilley	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
here	O
before	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
?	O
Tilley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
appear	O
here	O
about	O
last	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
here	O
for	O
?	O
Tilley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
his	O
friends	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
to	O
testify	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sufficient	O
number	O
of	O
persons	O
here	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
tried	O
for	O
?	O
Tilley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
there	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
his	O
tried	O
here	O
?	O
Tilley	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
son	O
of	O
his	O
tried	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
executed	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Old	O
Street	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
little	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
Old	O
Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
twice	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
before	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
in	O
Baldwin	O
's	O
Gardens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
there	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
before	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
master	O
or	O
a	O
journeyman	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
honesty	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
done	O
very	O
honestly	O
by	O
me	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
here	O
before	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
appeared	O
for	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tandy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
lodge	O
with	O
you	O
now	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
lodge	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Tandy	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
hours	O
did	O
he	O
keep	O
?	O
Tandy	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
he	O
kept	O
very	O
good	O
hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
?	O
Tandy	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
accused	O
with	O
carrying	O
this	O
tankard	O
away	O
in	O
his	O
garments	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
after	O
this	O
in	O
a	O
mean	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
half-pence	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Tandy	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
or	O
thereabout	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
tankard	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
going	O
away	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
immediately	O
upon	O
his	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Who	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
last	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
went	O
out	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
257.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
horizontal	O
sun-dial	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
gardener	O
to	O
'Squire	O
Hedges	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
May	O
this	O
sun-dial	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
pedestal	O
in	O
a	O
gravel	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Sanders	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
founder	O
in	O
Shoe	O
Lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
dial	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
cock	O
[	O
the	O
gnomon	O
]	O
was	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
arms	O
were	O
erased	O
out	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sanders	O
.	O
Had	O
it	O
a	O
gnomon	O
upon	O
it	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
garden	O
?	O
Sanders	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
a	O
gnomon	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Gregory	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Gregory	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
as	O
old	O
brass	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
nine	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
peny	O
;	O
it	O
weighed	O
thirteen	O
pounds	O
two	O
ounces	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
knocker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
Gregory	O
.	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
old	O
pewter	O
and	O
old	O
brass	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
country	O
dealer	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
up	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
probably	O
have	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
Tunbridge	O
ware	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
dealt	O
that	O
way	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Legg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
gardener	O
to	O
Squire	O
Hedges	O
under	O
Mark	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
dial	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
fixed	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
at	O
breakfast	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Legg	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
(	O
mathematical	O
instrument	O
maker	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
made	O
this	O
dial	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hedges	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
up	O
myself	O
;	O
the	O
arms	O
are	O
erased	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
name	O
was	O
engraved	O
so	O
deep	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
that	O
off	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
endeavouring	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
neat	O
one	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hedges	O
gave	O
me	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Highgate	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
gardener	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
either	O
of	O
those	O
two	O
men	O
[	O
Sanders	O
and	O
Legg	O
]	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Neither	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blincoe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
business	O
?	O
Blincoe	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
with	O
Tunbridge	O
ware	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
sell	O
any	O
?	O
Blincoe	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
my	O
dame	O
used	O
to	O
deal	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
character	O
?	O
Blincoe	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
his	O
settlement	O
?	O
Blincoe	O
.	O
His	O
settlement	O
is	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
Blincoe	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
in	O
Islington	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lain	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
.	O
Blincoe	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
lain	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
settlement	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
lodging	O
is	O
where	O
I	O
come	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
Chancery	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
house	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
any	O
family	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
lies	O
in	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
now	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
travel	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
return	O
every	O
night	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
sometimes	O
he	O
staid	O
away	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
travels	O
about	O
the	O
country	O
with	O
wooden	O
ware	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
razor	O
maker	O
in	O
Middle	O
Row	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
the	O
country	O
with	O
an	O
elderly	O
woman	O
who	O
sold	O
turnery	O
ware	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
almost	O
ninety	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
past	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
business	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
them	O
travel	O
with	O
goods	O
?	O
Tovey	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
travel	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
carry	O
goods	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Tovey	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
dishonestly	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
258.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4.	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
shop	O
in	O
Monmouth	B-place
street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
change	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
leave	O
to	O
tie	O
it	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
you	O
seem	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
According	O
to	O
my	O
information	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
not	O
done	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
your	O
Lordship	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
will	O
please	O
to	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
mended	O
these	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
Mrs.	O
Girdler	O
's	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hasser	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Rotherhith	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Mantua	O
maker	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
pretty	O
,	O
modest	O
and	O
virtuous	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
manner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Hasser	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
herself	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
handsom	O
manner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
employed	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
business	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
helped	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
handsom	O
manner	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
several	O
families	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
259.	O
Rose	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
cambrick	O
laced	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
May	B-pers
27th	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
brother	O
Dawson	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Shewell	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
[	O
the	O
gowns	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Shewell	I-pers
and	O
Rachael	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
proved	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Agnew	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dawson	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
last	O
Monday	O
morning	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
house	O
for	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Mrs.	O
Dawson	O
found	O
a	O
shaving	O
cloth	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
gow	O
ns	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
Berwick	O
street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
gowns	O
were	O
wet	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
three	O
caps	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Rose	O
Robinson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
mistress	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
ticket	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
were	O
pawned	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
mistress	O
's	O
handwriting	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
260.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Connell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Merle	I-pers
Delerant	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10th	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Merle	I-pers
Delerant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Half	O
Moon	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Merle	O
Delerant	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
master	O
and	O
man	O
both	O
lodge	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
master	O
?	O
Merle	O
Delerant	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
marine	O
service	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
spoons	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
I.	O
M.	O
D.	O
my	O
surname	O
is	O
Merle	O
Delerant	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kincade	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
spoons	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
?	O
Kincade	O
.	O
He	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
gentleman	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
letters	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Merle	O
Delerant	O
speaks	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
letters	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
?	O
Kincade	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
the	O
letters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Kincade	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
two	O
pence	O
an	O
ounce	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
would	O
give	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
to	O
hang	O
up	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Peter	B-pers
Delander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
book	O
entitled	O
,	O
The	O
reports	O
of	O
the	O
learned	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Hobart	I-pers
knight	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
five	O
other	O
books	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6th	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
books	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
.	O
George	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cover	O
these	O
books	O
with	O
a	O
brown	O
linen	O
apron	O
in	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
shop	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
I	O
believe	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Grand	O
jury	O
have	O
not	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
bill	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
262	O
,	O
263	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Collyer	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
April	O
20th	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
at	O
the	B-place
Bell	I-place
and	I-place
Magpye	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
evening	O
the	O
mug	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
free	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
bolted	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
maid	O
was	O
charging	O
the	O
prisoners	O
with	O
conveying	O
the	O
mug	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
denied	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
lose	O
the	O
mug	O
?	O
Creed	O
I	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
One	O
Swan	O
gateway	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Kyte	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
filled	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Kyte	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
count	O
the	O
tankards	O
and	O
mugs	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
table	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
sat	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
coat	O
[	O
Collyer	O
]	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
(	O
my	O
master	O
has	O
seven	O
silver	O
tankards	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
mugs	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoners	O
the	O
silver	O
mug	O
to	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
?	O
Kyte	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
a	O
pewter	O
pot	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
Collyer	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
silver	O
mug	O
afterwards	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
beer	O
in	O
.	O
Collyer	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Farmer	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
woman	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
set	O
the	O
mug	O
down	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
other	O
people	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
Kyte	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
the	O
mug	O
down	O
before	O
you	O
.	O
Farmer	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
ever	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
or	O
offer	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Kyte	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
pewter	O
pot	O
stood	O
down	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
poured	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
mug	O
into	O
the	O
pewter	O
pot	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kennell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
ale	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
a	O
pewter	O
pot	O
.	O
Collyer	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
cloth	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
fillet	O
of	O
veal	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
dirty	O
bag	O
?	O
Upon	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
trowels	O
of	O
mortar	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
behind	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
cross	O
bunn	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
minute	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
they	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
mug	O
to	O
fill	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Creed	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
Founders	O
arms	O
in	O
Founders	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
back	O
again	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
down	O
the	O
One	O
Swan	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
mug	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
close	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
wheel	O
spur	O
covered	O
with	O
mud	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
it	O
a	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Pollard	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
had	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
hanged	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Creed	O
's	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
his	O
name	O
round	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Collyer	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
maid	O
not	O
to	O
frighten	O
herself	O
about	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
satisfied	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
when	O
the	O
watchmen	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Creed	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
innocents	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
watchmen	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
without	O
any	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
mug	O
after	O
Kennell	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
Kyte	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
Collyer	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
mug	O
to	O
fill	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Charles	B-pers
Collyer	I-pers
about	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
sometimes	O
a	O
labourer	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
goes	O
to	O
sea	O
;	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Shrewsbury	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
and	O
belongs	O
to	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
for	O
a	O
worldly	O
man	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Collyer	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
.	O
-	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
was	O
reckoned	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
,	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Creed	O
.	O
This	O
witness	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
bail	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
keep	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
Magpye	O
next	O
week	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
264.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stavenaugh	I-pers
*	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
checked	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27th	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
lived	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
in	O
Shoe	O
lane	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
and	O
cotton	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Goddard	O
[	O
the	O
present	O
Prosecutrix	O
]	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
is	O
transported	O
.	O
See	O
sessions	O
paper	O
Number	O
4.	O
page	O
107	O
trial	O
202	O
.	O
[	O
Mrs.	O
Goddard	O
being	O
a	O
Frenchwoman	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
understanding	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Mrs.	O
Goddard	O
said	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Moor	B-place
street	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Seven	I-place
Dials	I-place
,	O
that	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
lost	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
checked	O
linen	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
shop	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
ancient	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
sight	O
bad	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
[	O
a	O
girl	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
]	O
About	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Cobler	O
[	O
John	O
Price	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
sessions	O
and	O
transported	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Soames	I-pers
[	O
convicted	O
last	O
sessions	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
goods	O
]	O
and	O
myself	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
by	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
an	O
apron	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
old	O
gentlewoman	O
[	O
Mrs.	O
Goddard	O
]	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
checks	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
which	O
Howell	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
round-about	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Soames	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
let	O
them	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
our	O
shares	O
.	O
She	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
from	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
smother	O
the	O
old	O
gentlewoman	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
smother	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
To	O
throw	O
a	O
cloth	O
over	O
her	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stuck	O
a	O
fork	O
into	O
my	O
leg	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Soames	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Collin	O
's	O
in	O
Fetter	O
lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
frequently	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
people	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
forced	O
to	O
swear	O
this	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
checks	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
sometime	O
by	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
thief	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
afterwards	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
checks	O
being	O
described	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
takes	O
in	O
pawns	O
for	O
a	O
halfpeny	O
worth	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
market	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
people	O
carry	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
will	O
give	O
more	O
upon	O
them	O
than	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
brought	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
Bibby	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
her	O
mother	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
to	O
offer	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
mother	O
.	O
Bibby	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
mother	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
harbours	O
children	O
to	O
run	O
them	O
:	O
my	O
child	O
has	O
gone	O
a	O
thieving	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
transported	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Bibby	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
horse-whip	O
to	O
pieces	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
concern	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Bibby	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
goal	O
,	O
swore	O
and	O
cursed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
information	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
wrongfully	O
;	O
and	O
Bibby	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
cast	O
five	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
cast	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
life	O
this	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
some	O
clothes	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
.	O
Bibby	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Bibby	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
you	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
confined	O
for	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
confined	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
.	O
Bibby	O
has	O
come	O
and	O
insulted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
wrongfully	O
;	O
and	O
Bibby	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
hanged	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
hanged	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
Biggs	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
convicted	O
five	O
people	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Bibby	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Biggs	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Bibby	O
.	O
This	O
Sarah	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
*	I-pers
kept	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Black	O
Boy	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
harboured	O
thieves	O
.	O
She	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Phillis	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Booker	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
tried	O
this	O
sessions	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
she	O
had	O
charged	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
265.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spike	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Masters	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
instant	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spike	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
watch	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Friend	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
.	O
I	O
very	O
little	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
handsomly	O
and	O
well	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
my	O
servant	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
servant	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Lord	O
Bollingbroke	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
my	O
Lord	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
brother	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
brother	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
whose	O
name	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
your	O
brother	O
is	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
odd	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
:	O
he	O
shall	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
brother	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
!	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
plain	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
Lord	O
Bollingbroke	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Master	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Masters	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
drawer	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
for	O
some	O
months	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
downright	O
country	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
266	O
,	O
267	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
Spittlefields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jane	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
in	O
an	O
entry	O
or	O
passage	O
in	O
Flower	B-place
and	I-place
Dean	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
in	O
or	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
my	O
girl	O
was	O
playing	O
about	O
Spittle	O
Square	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
picked	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
Flower	O
and	O
Dane	O
Street	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
gown	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Dockery	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
your	O
child	O
's	O
gown	O
?	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
By	O
their	O
own	O
confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
they	O
owned	O
the	O
stealing	O
that	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
other	O
children	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
your	O
child	O
?	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
Six	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
last	O
January	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
passage	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
knew	O
the	O
place	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dockery	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
night	O
[	O
24	O
May	O
]	O
towards	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
gown	O
from	O
that	O
child	O
[	O
Metcalf	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
of	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Dockery	O
.	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
overagainst	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
gown	O
I	O
lent	O
money	O
on	O
.	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
gown	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
gown	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
Metcalf	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
girl	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
play	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
stripped	O
the	O
child	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Brown	O
[	O
a	O
girl	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
]	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Metcalf	O
pulled	O
the	O
gown	O
off	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Dockery	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
such	O
a	O
child	O
as	O
that	O
have	O
money	O
upon	O
goods	O
?	O
Dockery	O
.	O
Because	O
her	O
mother	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
with	O
things	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marrioge	I-pers
(	O
Constable	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
child	O
lost	O
the	O
gown	O
on	O
Friday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dockery	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
entered	O
as	O
on	O
Saturday	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
pity	O
that	O
these	O
pawnbrokers	O
are	O
suffered	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	O
Metcalf	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Safford	I-pers
in	O
an	O
alley	O
or	O
entry	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
street	O
called	O
Wingfield	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
in	O
or	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Safford	I-pers
,	O
May	O
23	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
268	O
,	O
269	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bickley	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bickley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
Bickley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
pawned	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
for	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
silversmith	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
unless	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
came	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Bickley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Bickley	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
King	O
Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Bickley	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mother	O
Stout	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
her	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
bragging	O
at	O
a	O
ginshop	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
Mother	O
Stout	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
send	O
for	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
send	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Fox	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
where	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
270.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
;	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
,	O
May	O
14	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
excused	O
her	O
partly	O
for	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
let	O
her	O
remain	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
brother	O
come	O
from	O
sea	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
pawned	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
sister	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
continued	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
quite	O
off	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
shifts	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
dimitty	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
long	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
calico	O
apron	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
in	O
excuse	O
?	O
Platt	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
designed	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
shirts	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Crofton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
shifts	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
?	O
Crofton	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
her	O
any	O
questions	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
has	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
produced	O
several	O
things	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawned	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
271.	O
John	B-pers
Rennerson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
three	O
pint	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Berriman	I-pers
,	O
May	O
25	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Berriman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Crowder	B-place
's	I-place
Well	I-place
Alley	I-place
in	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
Street	I-place
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
last	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
expedition	O
I	O
could	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
wanted	O
some	O
anniseed	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
any	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
half	O
peny	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
rattle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
things	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
there	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
nobody	O
else	O
could	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
indeed	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
chink	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
persons	O
running	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
lie	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
inadvertently	O
being	O
fuddled	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
that	O
man	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
for	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
272	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
*	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
general	O
goal	O
delivery	O
holden	O
at	O
Abingdon	O
in	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Berks	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
18th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
before	O
James	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
then	O
one	O
other	O
Baron	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
their	O
fellows	O
Justices	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
assigned	O
to	O
deliver	O
his	O
goal	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Country	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
therein	O
being	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
in	O
Reading	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Berks	O
,	O
labourer	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
due	O
course	O
of	O
law	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
tried	O
,	O
and	O
convicted	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
same	O
Justices	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
that	O
County	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
15th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
George	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Stratfield	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
County	O
,	O
one	O
cock	O
turkey	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
hen	O
turkey	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
two	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
live	O
cocks	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
18	O
d.	O
seven	O
live	O
hens	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
chickens	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lannoy	I-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
his	O
crown	O
and	O
dignity	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
by	O
the	O
foresaid	O
Justices	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
assigned	O
to	O
deliver	O
his	O
goal	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
County	O
of	O
Berks	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
therein	O
being	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
conveniently	O
might	O
be	O
,	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Colonies	O
and	O
Plantations	O
in	O
America	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
statute	O
in	O
such	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
the	O
record	O
thereof	O
doth	O
more	O
fully	O
appear	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
18th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
without	O
any	O
lawful	O
cause	O
was	O
at	O
large	O
within	O
this	O
kingdom	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	O
of	O
Portsoken	O
in	O
London	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
term	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
his	O
crown	O
and	O
dignity	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
in	O
such	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
wounding	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
of	O
Portsoken	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Burgess	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
produced	O
the	O
certificate	O
of	O
his	O
conviction	O
and	O
order	O
for	O
transportation	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
certify	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
general	O
goal	O
delivery	O
for	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
holden	O
at	O
Abingdon	O
in	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Berks	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
18th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
George	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
before	O
James	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
then	O
one	O
other	O
Baron	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
their	O
fellows	O
Justices	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
assigned	O
to	O
deliver	O
his	O
goal	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Country	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
therein	O
being	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
in	O
Reading	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Berks	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
by	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
County	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
15th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
George	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Stratfield	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
County	O
,	O
one	O
cock	O
turkey	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
hen	O
turkey	O
price	O
2	O
s.	O
seven	O
live	O
hens	O
price	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
chickens	O
,	O
price	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lannoy	I-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
then	O
and	O
there	O
prayed	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
to	O
be	O
allowed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Justices	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
goal	O
delivery	O
,	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
conveniently	O
might	O
be	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
plantations	O
in	O
America	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
computed	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
conviction	O
.	O
Signed	O
Thomas	B-pers
Multhoe	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
of	O
Assise	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Berks	O
.	O
April	O
21	O
,	O
1745.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
in	O
Reading	O
goal	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Abingdon	O
the	O
summer	O
assizes	O
in	O
July	O
1742	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
three	O
years	O
next	O
July	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sheriffs	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Reading	O
goal	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
Abingdon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
tried	O
for	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Henry	B-pers
Lannoy	I-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
some	O
cocks	O
and	O
hens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
him	O
and	O
thirteen	O
more	O
who	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
miles	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
from	O
Reading	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
confined	O
then	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
irons	O
and	O
handcuffed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
them	O
off	O
:	O
he	O
carried	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bazzils	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
get	O
away	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
thirteen	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
day-light	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
day-light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
then	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
horseback	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
persons	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
him	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
him	O
till	O
day-light	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
irons	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threatened	O
our	O
lives	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
The	O
goal	O
keeper	O
was	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
large	O
since	O
his	O
conviction	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
large	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
school	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
remember	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Haslet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
hens	O
from	O
'Squire	O
Hunter	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
at	O
Abingdon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Haslet	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
and	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
's	O
turnkey	O
at	O
Reading	O
goal	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bringing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
merchant	O
Forward	O
's	O
ship	O
.	O
He	O
cut	O
off	O
his	O
irons	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
in	O
Maidenhead	O
Thicket	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
thing	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
's	O
voice	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
will	O
swear	O
to	O
mine	O
.	O
Holloway	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
your	O
voice	O
is	O
so	O
remarkable	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
you	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
years	O
:	O
you	O
have	O
threatened	O
my	O
life	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
John	O
.	O
Lancelot	O
Howlet	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
Portsoken	O
Ward	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
abused	O
our	O
watchman	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
warrant	O
served	O
on	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
abusing	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
wounded	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
in	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
him	O
that	O
day	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
riot	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
abuse	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Howlet	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Howlet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
Patrick	O
's	O
Court	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
with	O
a	O
common	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
creature	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
creature	O
?	O
Howlet	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
a	O
whore	O
or	O
a	O
harlot	O
,	O
or	O
whatever	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
call	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
quarrel	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
very	O
much	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Warder	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
the	O
Beadle	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
doing	O
us	O
a	O
mischief	O
:	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
chop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
cut	O
you	O
?	O
Howlet	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
Lordship	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
the	O
watchmen	O
would	O
cut	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
steps	O
by	O
Devonshire	O
Squire	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
partner	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Howlet	O
.	O
Jack	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
or	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
Howlet	O
any	O
questions	O
?	O
Simmons	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
asking	O
that	O
man	O
any	O
questions	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
will	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
any	O
trouble	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
honourable	O
Court	O
will	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
what	O
that	O
man	O
says	O
without	O
my	O
exposing	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
says	O
I	O
cut	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
cut	O
him	O
with	O
.	O
Howlet	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
fist	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
chop	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
cut	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
cut	O
?	O
Howlet	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
cut	O
upon	O
my	O
wrist	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
the	O
wristband	O
of	O
my	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
shew	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
shirt	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Simmons	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
I	O
cut	O
you	O
with	O
?	O
Howlet	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
you	O
cut	O
me	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
instrument	O
about	O
him	O
?	O
Howlet	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
throw	O
that	O
away	O
as	O
he	O
run	O
along	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
[	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Patrick	O
's	O
court	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
[	O
for	O
this	O
mischief	O
was	O
done	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
]	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
the	O
beadle	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
at	O
night	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
resistance	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
:	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
reeling	O
[	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
]	O
My	O
Partner	O
Howlet	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
my	O
partner	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
strike	O
,	O
for	O
am	O
I	O
uppermost	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
watchman	O
[	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
]	O
who	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
about	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Beadle	O
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
Watchman	O
,	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
upon	O
a	O
surprize	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
desperate	O
fellow	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
difficult	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
ask	O
this	O
gentleman	O
what	O
they	O
first	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
for	O
cutting	O
and	O
abusing	O
the	O
watchmen	O
;	O
and	O
cutting	O
that	O
watchman	O
's	O
[	O
Bentley	O
]	O
hand	O
almost	O
off	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
or	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Bentley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
quarrel	O
in	O
the	O
alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
good	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
cross	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
cut	O
cross	O
my	O
wrist	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
leaders	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
have	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
custody	O
before	O
?	O
Bentley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
at	O
liberty	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Bentley	O
.	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
know	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
me	O
remember	O
you	O
.	O
Richard	O
Baddington	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
warder	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
for	O
Covent-garden	O
precint	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Simmons	O
had	O
abused	O
her	O
husband	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Simmons	O
before	O
?	O
Boddington	O
.	O
Only	O
by	O
his	O
living	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
unkind	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
disturbance	O
and	O
a	O
noise	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
o'night	O
?	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
.	O
My	O
watchmen	O
hearing	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fray	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
stout	O
,	O
lusty	O
fellow	O
(	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
fearing	O
something	O
of	O
danger	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
)	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
submit	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
the	O
honourable	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
273	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	I-pers
late	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
parish	I-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Andrew	I-pers
Holborn	I-pers
,	I-pers
London	I-pers
,	I-pers
Spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Anderears	I-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
three	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
jumps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
caps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
long	O
lawn	O
aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
quilted	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Morton	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
May	O
1st	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
daughter	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
:	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
fore-room	O
up	O
stairs	O
(	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
)	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
daughter	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sherrar	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
by	O
an	O
advertisement	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
she	O
might	O
come	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
her	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
stopped	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
,	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Evans	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carver	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
Dirty	O
Lane	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
habitation	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
chints	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
black	O
silk	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
picked	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sherrar	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
gown	O
,	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
one	O
apron	O
,	O
an	O
under	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
jumps	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
remarkable	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
,	O
almost	O
every	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
husband	O
?	O
Sherrar	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carver	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Boswell	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
reputation	O
,	O
he	O
works	O
with	O
a	O
carver	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Dirty	O
Lane	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
(	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
places	O
called	O
Dirty	O
Lane	O
,	O
)	O
one	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
chairwoman	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
from	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
till	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
one	O
day	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Clare	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
her	O
aunt	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
her	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
recommend	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
honest	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
knew	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
pawn	O
them	O
herself	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sherrar	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
have	O
cleared	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
pull	O
the	O
black	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
herself	O
mourning	O
for	O
her	O
aunt	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blower	O
.	O
Your	O
landlady	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
picked	O
that	O
black	O
gown	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Sherrar	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Sherrar	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
say	O
the	O
woman	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
[	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
]	O
was	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
there	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rollison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
her	O
husband	O
?	O
Rollison	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
carver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
she	O
do	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
?	O
Rollison	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
dress	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
wash	O
and	O
mend	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
washed	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
shift	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
this	O
May	O
is	O
out	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
May	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
last	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
one	O
day	O
in	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
particularly	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
my	O
work	O
;	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
leisure	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
generally	O
wash	O
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
say	O
this	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
news	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
hardly	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
marked	O
.	O
Morton	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
this	O
man	O
[	O
Boswell	O
]	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
husband	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
another	O
wife	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
Davis	O
is	O
my	O
maiden	O
name	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
and	O
perriwig-maker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
place	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
there	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
In	O
Jackson	O
's	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
there	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
infirmary	O
nine	O
weeks	O
for	O
fits	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
seized	O
for	O
rent	O
.	O
Before	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
five	O
years	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
parish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
dishonestly	O
by	O
her	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
She	O
married	O
one	O
Boswell	O
a	O
carver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
behaving	O
ill	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Now	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
warrant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
warrants	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Not	O
capital	O
warrants	O
,	O
only	O
warrants	O
about	O
scolding	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
she	O
a	O
good	O
or	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Morton	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ever	O
here	O
before	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
was	O
here	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Morton	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
for	O
selling	O
a	O
sheet	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
Morton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
who	O
worked	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
pawned	O
a	O
sheet	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
274.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ninn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
eleven	O
saucers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
basons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
April	O
27th	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
two	O
sets	O
of	O
china	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Homerton	O
Row	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
lodging	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
Because	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
himself	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
(	O
daughter	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
)	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
gate	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
stole	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
missed	O
the	O
china	O
off	O
the	O
tea	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
yard	O
:	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
china	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
clothes	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
You	O
had	O
a	O
whitish	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
the	O
same	O
clothes	O
on	O
then	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
like	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bolton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
china	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
stopped	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
china	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
may	O
be	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
they	O
are	O
yours	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
275	O
,	O
276	O
,	O
277	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Jeffs	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Toss	I-pers
off	I-pers
Dick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ninn	I-pers
*	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Agnes	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
;	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
;	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
called	O
lustring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Page	I-pers
;	O
18	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
16	O
lawn	O
stocks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
damask	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
seven	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
four	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
skirt	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
cambrick	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
transportation	O
upon	O
the	O
preceding	O
indictment	O
.	O
He	O
refused	O
to	O
plead	O
to	O
the	O
name	O
Lucas	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Ninn	O
.	O
278	O
.	O
And	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Young	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
[	O
At	O
Lucas	O
's	O
desire	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hand	B-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
High	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
On	O
Good	O
Friday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
who	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
considerably	O
past	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
regard	O
to	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
door	O
fastened	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
after	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
discover	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
looked	O
round	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
something	O
white	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
shirts	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
after	O
you	O
saw	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
fast	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
is	O
a	O
mantua	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
remembered	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
five	O
gowns	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
linen	O
besides	O
:	O
the	O
gowns	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
parcel	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
five	O
gowns	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
gowns	O
of	O
one	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
's	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
charged	O
five	O
guineas	O
for	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
gown	O
which	O
is	O
called	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
my	O
wife	O
paid	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
;	O
a	O
tabby	O
gown	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
she	O
valued	O
at	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
18	O
shirts	O
which	O
I	O
charge	O
at	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
though	O
they	O
cost	O
17	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
:	O
(	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
things	O
than	O
my	O
wife	O
or	O
I	O
could	O
think	O
of	O
;	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
lowest	O
I	O
could	O
set	O
them	O
at	O
they	O
amounted	O
to	O
19	O
l.	O
10s	O
.	O
or	O
11s	O
.	O
which	O
is	O
much	O
less	O
than	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
upon	O
your	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shirts	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
while	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
hear	O
them	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
surprizing	O
thing	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
hear	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
louder	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
partition	O
was	O
there	O
between	O
the	O
room	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
very	O
thin	O
wainscot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
not	O
shut	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
partly	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
more	O
surprized	O
at	O
the	O
robbery	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
misty	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
till	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
sev'night	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
Long	O
Lane	O
by	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
from	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
by	O
Bye	O
's	O
Direction	O
[	O
the	O
accomplice	O
]	O
I	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
which	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Lucas	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
[	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
showed	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chitty	O
.	O
]	O
Chitty	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
skirt	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
upon	O
the	O
backs	O
of	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
children	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
stocks	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
things	O
there	O
of	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
information	O
had	O
you	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
my	O
goods	O
twice	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
the	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
and	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
three	O
guineas	O
reward	O
and	O
no	O
questions	O
asked	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
have	O
taken	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
is	O
in	O
Woodstreet	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
this	O
Bye	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
[	O
another	O
person	O
in	O
Court	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Tawney	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
Lucas	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
thieftaker	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tawney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
both	O
open	O
.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
lock	O
or	O
the	O
hinges	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
broke	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
broke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
family	O
up	O
or	O
in	O
bed	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
What	O
particular	O
things	O
were	O
the	O
goods	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
did	O
they	O
lie	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
four	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
bureau	O
stand	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
It	O
stood	O
just	O
within	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Which	O
parlour	O
door	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
I	O
mean	O
the	O
door	O
which	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
it	O
stands	O
between	O
that	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
that	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Jeffs	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
follow	O
the	O
business	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
he	O
follow	O
now	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
followed	O
thieving	O
these	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
he	O
followed	O
since	O
you	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
followed	O
nothing	O
but	O
thieving	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Richard	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
Yes	O
-	O
he	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Toss	O
off	O
Dick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
follow	O
driving	O
of	O
carts	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
two	O
months	O
he	O
has	O
followed	O
nothing	O
but	O
thieving	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
in	O
two	O
robberies	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
picking	O
of	O
pockets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Lucas	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
here	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ninn	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
assizes	O
at	O
Chelmsford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
himself	O
down	O
in	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
record	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
brought	O
up	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
Bye	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
her	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
Ever	O
since	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
she	O
live	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
then	O
in	O
Moor	O
Lane	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
say	O
she	O
lives	O
now	O
in	O
Long	O
Lane	O
by	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
Black	O
Smith	O
's	O
wife	O
[	O
commonly	O
called	O
Black	O
Sam	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
affair	O
of	O
Chitty	O
's	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Jeffs	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Toss	O
off	O
Dick	O
,	O
and	O
Lucas	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
Lucas	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
dusk	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Hand	O
Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
there	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
four	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
watchmaker	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
what	O
watchmaker	O
's	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Chitty	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
then	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
Lucas	O
opened	O
the	O
latch	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
opened	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
that	O
stand	O
?	O
was	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
or	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
go	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Toss	O
off	O
Dick	O
and	O
Jeffs	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
waiting	O
for	O
what	O
things	O
we	O
brought	O
out	O
;	O
Lucas	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
then	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
Lucas	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
light	O
the	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
misty	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
rained	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
lighted	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
between	O
my	O
fingers	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
blind	O
before	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
and	O
left	O
Jeffs	O
and	O
Toss	O
off	O
Dick	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
to	O
Lucas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
returned	O
with	O
some	O
womens	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Horton	O
for	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
Lucas	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
Jeffs	O
's	O
hand	O
through	O
a	O
mistake	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
Jeffs	O
he	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
stand	O
at	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
Gate	O
;	O
Lucas	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
as	O
many	O
things	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
carry	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
slaps	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
under	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
Toss	O
off	O
Dick	O
took	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
carry	O
away	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
Lucas	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
carry	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
breast	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Jeffs	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
this	O
coat	O
[	O
the	O
coat	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
]	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
dunghill	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
as	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
into	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
Lucas	O
ordered	O
Jeffs	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
Lucas	O
ordered	O
Toss	O
off	O
Dick	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
the	O
dunghill	O
till	O
he	O
and	O
Jeffs	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
returned	O
with	O
as	O
many	O
things	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
well	O
bring	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
off	O
our	O
necks	O
to	O
tie	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
shirts	O
and	O
stocks	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
this	O
damask	O
cap	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
button	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
things	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
carried	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
Lucas	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
persuaded	O
Toss	O
off	O
Dick	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Young	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
Lucas	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
kept	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
their	O
own	O
use	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
for	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
*	I-pers
to	O
come	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
40s	O
.	O
so	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
them	O
:	O
Toss	O
off	O
Dick	O
came	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Young	I-pers
would	O
give	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
December	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Alexander	B-pers
Forfar	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Headborough	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
powder	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Part	O
III	O
.	O
Page	O
54	O
.	O
Trial	O
106	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
had	O
you	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
a-piece	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
Lucas	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
delivered	O
to	O
Young	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
bring	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
her	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Jeffs	O
,	O
Lucas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
sold	O
her	O
as	O
many	O
things	O
another	O
time	O
as	O
were	O
worth	O
15	O
l.	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Lucas	O
tell	O
her	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
Bye	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
this	O
place	O
to	O
Chitty	O
