TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
On	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
19th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
C.	O
NUTT	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Pamphlet-Shops	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
.	O
1746	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ABNEY	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRACEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Spier	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholl	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Lolt	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Harvest	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Tunstall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broomly	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Wincope	I-pers
,	O
Periam	O
Wright	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Meriton	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	O
Lake	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mellor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haswell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radley	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rude	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dakin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
194.	O
Jane	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
and	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
stealing	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
are	O
the	O
Stockings	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
here	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
those	O
Stockings	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
pink-colour	O
'd	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
;	O
the	O
Worsted	O
the	O
other	O
Evidence	O
has	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
these	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Worsted	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
Wife	O
a	O
Farthing	O
that	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
:	O
My	O
Wife	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Stockings	O
then	O
;	O
the	O
Worsted	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
knows	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Marybon-Street	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
Stockings	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Parry	O
's	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
at	O
Parry	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Business	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
A	O
Hosier	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
Haberdasher	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Parry	O
.	O
She	O
lodg	O
'd	O
Things	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Times	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
these	O
Stockings	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
swear	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Stockings	O
?	O
Parry	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Possession	O
from	O
that	O
Time	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
upon	O
these	O
Stockings	O
?	O
Parry	O
.	O
Eighteen-Pence	O
.	O
My	O
Neighbour	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
;	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
me	O
ask	O
this	O
Person	O
?	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
You	O
hear	O
these	O
Things	O
are	O
pretty	O
strong	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
before	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Crime	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
195.	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sacking	O
,	O
Value	O
14	O
s.	O
from	O
Brook's-Wharf	B-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
the	O
second	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
some	O
Sacking	O
out	O
of	O
Brook's-Wharf	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
Sacking	O
that	O
you	O
now	O
produce	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Make	O
and	O
Mark	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hide	O
any	O
Question	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
above	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Clement	B-pers
Corderoy	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Corderoy	O
.	O
Three	O
Months	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sacking	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
did	O
very	O
right	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
brought	O
you	O
that	O
Sacking	O
?	O
Corderoy	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
brought	O
this	O
Sacking	O
first	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
Witness	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
to	O
ask	O
five	O
Shillings	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
worth	O
fourteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
196.	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
216	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
Valentine	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
Sacking	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Quantity	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Quantity	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
nine	O
Pieces	O
found	O
at	O
London-Bridge	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pieces	O
.	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Corderoy	O
,	O
stopt	O
these	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Quantity	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
'till	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Quantity	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
then	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
by	O
the	O
Bulk	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
thousand	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
are	O
near	O
one	O
hundred	O
Pieces	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
these	O
nine	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Corderoy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
Hide	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
found	O
the	O
nine	O
Pieces	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Corderoy	O
's	O
Possession	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Cloths	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
these	O
two	O
Pieces	O
are	O
yours	O
.	O
Hide	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Yards	O
are	O
there	O
in	O
these	O
two	O
Pieces	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
There	O
should	O
be	O
twenty-four	O
Yards	O
in	O
each	O
Piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
fourteen	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
valued	O
at	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
lost	O
them	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
they	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
little	O
Wooden	O
Bars	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
have	O
put	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
and	O
book	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
as	O
you	O
would	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
Warehouse	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
At	O
Brook's-Wharf	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Wharf	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
it	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
made	O
for	O
Hammocks	O
of	O
Men	O
of	O
War	O
I	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
since	O
taken	O
a	O
wider	O
Sort	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
useless	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cart	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
Please	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
this	O
good	O
Woman	O
that	O
stands	O
here	O
,	O
Carlisle	O
,	O
she	O
comes	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
at	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Sacking-Bottom	O
Weaver	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
comes	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
before	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cloth	O
that	O
were	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
West-Country	O
Barge	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
let	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Carter	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
came	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
to	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cloth	O
upon	O
Sale	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
desire	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
I	O
consulted	O
with	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
first	O
to	O
stop	O
these	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Corderoy	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
to	O
consult	O
with	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Carlisle	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
there	O
.	O
Carter	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
who	O
shew	O
'd	O
you	O
the	O
Cloth	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
That	O
Man	O
that	O
stands	O
there	O
in	O
Blue-grey	O
,	O
Carter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
you	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Water-side	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Cart	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
nor	O
bid	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Waterside	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pretended	O
that	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
this	O
good	O
Woman	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Corderoy	O
's	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
of	O
having	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Carlisle	O
say	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
Pieces	O
?	O
These	O
two	O
Pieces	O
were	O
at	O
Carlisle	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
a	O
Fullpot	O
of	O
Beer	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Carter	O
said	O
,	O
bring	O
me	O
what	O
Money	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Are	O
you	O
any	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Carlisle	O
?	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
own	O
Wife	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
then	O
with	O
relation	O
to	O
Carter	O
.	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
brought	O
these	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Sackcloth	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
?	O
Did	O
not	O
Carter	O
bid	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cart	O
's	O
;	O
did	O
she	O
or	O
Corderoy	O
stop	O
you	O
?	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
stopt	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
(	O
to	O
Prisoner	O
Carter	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
this	O
Witness	O
says	O
;	O
will	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
any	O
Question	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
for	O
this	O
Man	O
to	O
the	O
Waterside	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Clement	B-pers
Corderoy	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Corderoy	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
Sacking	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
too	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Cart	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
are	O
Sack-Weavers	O
;	O
they	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
weaving	O
of	O
Cloth	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
Corderoy	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
fifth	O
Piece	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
more	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Persons	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
they	O
brought	O
two	O
Pieces	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Carlisle	O
who	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
for	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Disposal	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
them	O
and	O
her	O
too	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
takes	O
her	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
before	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Sitting	O
Aklermen	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
went	O
to	O
Fleetditch	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
said	O
Carter	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cart	I-pers
had	O
decoy	O
'd	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Cart	O
bring	O
Carlisle	O
's	O
Wife	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
appointed	O
?	O
Corderoy	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Carlisle	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cart	O
came	O
together	O
.	O
Carlisle	O
's	O
Wife	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Cart	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
Carlisle	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Pieces	O
?	O
Corderoy	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Pieces	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
Carter	O
's	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
Carlisle	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
bring	O
Carlisle	O
here	O
:	O
If	O
your	O
Witness	O
speaks	O
true	O
,	O
even	O
Cart	O
says	O
Carter	O
was	O
at	O
Carlisle	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Carter	O
said	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
Carter	O
's	O
Goods	O
in	O
Carlisle	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
Now	O
Carlisle	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
Man	O
.	O
Corderoy	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
Carter	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Carter	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
You	O
hear	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
you	O
.	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-Street	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
Carlisle	O
)	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
eat	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
Victuals	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
sitting	O
together	O
,	O
says	O
Mrs.	O
Cart	O
and	O
Carlisle	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
carry	O
these	O
Things	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Water-side	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
Goods	O
.	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
Cart	O
says	O
;	O
that	O
you	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
your	O
Goods	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
disprove	O
this	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
Character	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Carlisle	O
,	O
the	O
Accessory	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
197	O
,	O
198.	O
William	B-pers
Donnington	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Apron	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Corrock	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Corrock	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Corrock	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Se'nnight	O
this	O
William	B-pers
Donnington	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Corrock	O
.	O
In	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
both	O
?	O
Corrock	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
such	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
just	O
keeping	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
'till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
that	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
nobody	O
come	O
in	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
these	O
People	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
'till	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
pledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
checqu	O
'd	O
Shirt	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
about	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
roll	O
'd	O
and	O
twisted	O
the	O
Apron	O
about	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
about	O
her	O
Middle	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Apron	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
Corrock	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Confession	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
would	O
acquit	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
could	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
,	O
did	O
they	O
make	O
any	O
Confession	O
?	O
Corrock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
when	O
they	O
made	O
the	O
Confession	O
.	O
The	O
Husband	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
how	O
they	O
both	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
Possession	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
pledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
they	O
sold	O
one	O
chequ	O
'd	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
chequ	O
'd	O
Apron	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
made	O
the	O
Confession	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
at	O
what	O
Place	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Things	O
?	O
Corrock	O
.	O
Near	O
Wellclose-Square	O
.	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
told	O
you	O
;	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
pledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
?	O
Corrock	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
pledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
New-Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
it	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Dupee	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Question	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rickelworth	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Rickelworth	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
St.	O
Katherine	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Corrock	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
Rickelworth	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
opposite	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
T	O
he	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
.	O
Rickelworth	O
.	O
We	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Aprons	O
about	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Side	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
?	O
Rickelworth	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Apron	O
?	O
Corrock	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
Cheque	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
my	O
Servant	O
made	O
the	O
Apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
particular	O
Marks	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
For	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cheque	O
alike	O
.	O
Corrock	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Woman	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Apron	O
?	O
Rickelworth	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
little	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
?	O
Rickelworth	O
.	O
The	O
Gown	O
and	O
Shirt	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
this	O
Witness	O
says	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
these	O
Things	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
them	O
them	O
to	O
your	O
Wife	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Body	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
your	O
Character	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Friends	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Donnington	I-pers
Guilty	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Donnington	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Woollen	O
Bed-Curtains	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
Blanket	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Brass	O
Frying-Pan	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Stephens	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
them	O
with	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
I	O
charge	O
them	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
In	O
Whitechappel-Road	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
these	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
let	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
Earnest	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
let	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
let	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
What	O
Furniture	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Bed	O
and	O
Bedding	O
,	O
and	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
Grate	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
let	O
these	O
Things	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
what	O
Things	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Stephens	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
a	O
Fire-shovel	O
,	O
Poker	O
,	O
Pillows	O
,	O
Blankets	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
Frying-Pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Napkin	O
and	O
Pillowbeers	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Donnington	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
Five	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
Goods	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
'till	O
last	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
them	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
last	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
about	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
My	O
Business	O
is	O
a	O
Fish-Meeter	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
Things	O
out	O
when	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
a-Bed	O
and	O
a	O
Sleep	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
carrying	O
a	O
Bundle	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
overtook	O
them	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
away	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
coming	O
back	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
steps	O
home	O
again	O
and	O
takes	O
a	O
Ladder	O
and	O
goes	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
St.	O
Katherine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Rickelworth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
the	O
Rug	O
out	O
that	O
Morning	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
Rug	O
here	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
bring	O
it	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
should	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
other	O
Things	O
did	O
he	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Corrock	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
Napkin	O
and	O
Saucepan	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Corrock	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
Curtains	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherine's-Lane	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Blanket	O
and	O
Sheet	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
.	O
in	O
Black-Horse-Yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
to	O
this	O
Broker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
may	O
get	O
these	O
Things	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
are	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
of	O
these	O
Brokers	O
join	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
publick	O
Sale	O
every	O
Month	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
indict	O
her	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Donnington	I-pers
.	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
this	O
Man	O
says	O
;	O
will	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
Questions	O
,	O
or	O
make	O
your	O
Defence	O
?	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witness	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
your	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Wife	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
199.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
stands	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Jane	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
robbing	O
George	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
putting	O
them	O
in	O
bodily	O
Fear	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
or	O
Night	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
As	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
alone	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Husband	O
?	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
In	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
Road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashborn	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
he	O
follow	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
He	O
follows	O
no	O
Business	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
lives	O
upon	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Now	O
tell	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
took	O
my	O
Cloak	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
by	O
himself	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
Men	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
clapp	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
laid	O
Hold	O
of	O
my	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
your	O
Cloak	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Husband	O
throw	O
'd	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Escape	O
;	O
the	O
Moon	O
shone	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Face	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
wrong	O
Side	O
outwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
run	O
swiftly	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
plain	O
Hat	O
or	O
a	O
laced	O
Hat	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
directly	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
a	O
plain	O
Hat	O
.	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Madam	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
pray	O
how	O
many	O
Persons	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
particular	O
to	O
know	O
this	O
Person	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
The	O
others	O
run	O
swiftly	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
this	O
Man	O
stopt	O
us	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
had	O
he	O
a	O
Wig	O
on	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
own	O
Hair	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
His	O
own	O
Hair	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Coat	O
turn	O
'd	O
blue	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
blue	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Halfway	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
Mother	O
Red	O
Cap	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
that	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
attack	O
'd	O
;	O
to	O
this	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashborn	I-pers
said	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
three	O
Soldiers	O
with	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
something	O
over	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashborn	I-pers
says	O
,	O
Cousin	O
,	O
stand	O
still	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
honest	O
Soldiers	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
Two	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
moved	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
by	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Honest	O
Friend	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
swear	O
at	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
)	O
he	O
clapped	O
his	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
No	O
Words	O
,	O
No	O
Words	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
Brains	O
out	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Wife	O
into	O
my	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
she	O
seeing	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
another	O
Word	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
Brains	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
lifted	O
my	O
Wife	O
over	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
he	O
catched	O
my	O
Wife	O
by	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
Hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
she	O
slipt	O
her	O
Head	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
she	O
run	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
a	O
rifling	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
kept	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
then	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Man	O
goes	O
back	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashborn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Bayonet	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
to	O
7	O
s.	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Remembrance	O
he	O
had	O
Eight	O
between	O
the	O
Post	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
more	O
to	O
your	O
Wife	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Wife	O
almost	O
frighten	O
'd	O
to	O
Death	O
upon	O
a	O
Heap	O
of	O
Stones	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
before	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
In	O
Earl-Street	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
paid	O
Twenty	O
Guineas	O
a	O
Year	O
to	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
Business	O
before	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Baker	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashborn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
Innkeeper	O
by	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
Road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Inn	O
did	O
you	O
keep	O
there	O
?	O
Ashborn	O
.	O
The	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
understand	O
Morris	O
is	O
some	O
Relation	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Ashborn	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Now	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
Ashborn	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mother	O
Red	O
Cap	O
's	O
to	O
eat	O
a	O
fat	O
Pig	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
on	O
coming	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
in	O
Company	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Ashborn	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Men	O
that	O
we	O
met	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
.	O
Ashborn	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
George	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
are	O
you	O
in	O
Jest	O
or	O
in	O
Fannest	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
whips	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
against	O
my	O
Breast	O
;	O
I	O
up't	O
with	O
my	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
a	O
cross	O
the	O
Nose	O
and	O
Eyes	O
,	O
I	O
hit	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
Blow	O
as	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
backward	O
;	O
I	O
beat	O
them	O
both	O
so	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
a	O
Top	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
had	O
got	O
Hold	O
of	O
my	O
Foot	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Buckles	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Plunge	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
neither	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
Ashborn	O
.	O
She	O
run	O
away	O
up	O
to	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swooned	O
away	O
upon	O
a	O
Heap	O
of	O
Stones	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
rise	O
up	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
Men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
apprehended	O
him	O
?	O
Ashborn	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
carries	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Now	O
is	O
your	O
Time	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
any	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Isaac	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
my	O
Lord	O
in	O
Flanders	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
abroad	O
;	O
he	O
throwed	O
off	O
his	O
Pay	O
the	O
17th	O
or	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Bradford	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Bradford	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Ghent	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
abroad	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
little	O
more	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Huson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
but	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
from	O
Flanders	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Duty	O
very	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
18	O
Months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Trade	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Huson	O
.	O
A	O
Breeches-maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
About	O
22	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
A	O
Glover	O
by	O
Trade	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
nothing	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Matthew	O
Hall	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
worked	O
like	O
other	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
have	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
Not	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Flanders	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Bedwin	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Bedwin	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Years	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
he	O
rented	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
and	O
all	O
lived	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	O
Brown	O
)	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Business	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Swearing	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
Thing	O
to	O
ask	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
what	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
for	O
upon	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Hours	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
these	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
At	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
has	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
14	O
Years	O
.	O
Reply	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
bad	O
if	O
your	O
Wife	O
knows	O
him	O
better	O
than	O
you	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
known	O
him	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
200.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Parran	I-pers
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Corporal	O
Fear	O
and	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe	O
Buckles	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Parran	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
and	O
how	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
Watson	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
this	O
Soldier	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
lighting	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Parran	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
to	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
lodge	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
one	O
Fuller	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
dark	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
Body	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
Soldier	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
Name	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
light	O
you	O
with	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
stopt	O
at	O
a	O
Grocer	O
's	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Link	O
in	O
Mutton	O
Lane	O
to	O
light	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Soldier	O
a	O
Dram	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Pancras	B-place
Field	I-place
we	O
met	O
three	O
Men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
they	O
dress	O
'd	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
so	O
perfectly	O
see	O
their	O
Dress	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
Watson	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
Coat	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
muffled	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brown	O
Coat	O
about	O
his	O
Chin	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
so	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
positive	O
to	O
Watson	O
than	O
Taylor	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
Because	O
Watson	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
but	O
Watson	O
said	O
first	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Soldier	O
,	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Light	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Watson	O
,	O
said	O
these	O
Words	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
pitch	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
riffled	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
20	O
and	O
upwards	O
:	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
d	O
-	O
nd	O
them	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
Watson	O
took	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
or	O
better	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
In	O
no	O
Purse	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
loose	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
:	O
Also	O
the	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Knee-Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Knees	O
,	O
my	O
Hat	O
off	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
Tobacco-Stopper	O
tipp	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
a	O
Memorandum-Book	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
Papers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
in	O
particular	O
what	O
Watson	O
took	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
biggest	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
He	O
tore	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
off	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
aboard	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
Steward	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Parran	O
,	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
so	O
particularly	O
to	O
distinguish	O
Watson	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
Soldier	O
?	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
spoke	O
those	O
Words	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
the	O
Monday	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Clerkenwell-Bridewell	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
accidentally	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
third	O
Person	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
particularly	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
Parran	O
,	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
on	O
?	O
Parran	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
plain	O
Hat	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
put	O
your	O
own	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shepard	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Watson	O
or	O
Taylor	O
?	O
Shepard	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Voice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
lighting	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
?	O
Shepard	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
an	O
Attack	O
made	O
?	O
Shepard	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
lost	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
his	O
Voice	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Eyes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
't	O
was	O
Watson	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
beg	O
'd	O
the	O
Favour	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
and	O
Papers	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
a	O
your	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
general	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Broom	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
would	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
indeed	O
were	O
too	O
big	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
them	O
fit	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Breeches	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Broom	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
'till	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Taylor	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Taylor	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Defence	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Steak	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Bryant	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
Habitation	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
laid	O
there	O
but	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Place	O
of	O
his	O
Habitation	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
Brother	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
Thursday	O
in	O
Easter	O
Week	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
at	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
in	O
Easter	O
Week	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chiswell-Street	O
)	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Chap	O
for	O
this	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
we	O
made	O
last	O
Week	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
thirteen	O
S	O
hillings	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
exactly	O
fit	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
alter	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Clogster	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
the	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Now	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Broom	O
's	O
Boy	O
,	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Brother	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
attend	O
upon	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
his	O
Irons	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
half	O
happy	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
fear	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Aunt	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
the	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
sadly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
Bryant	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
had	O
threaten	O
'd	O
the	O
Witness	O
highly	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
Insolence	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Lordship	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
commit	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Taylor	O
;	O
what	O
is	O
his	O
Character	O
?	O
Willis	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
wrong	O
a	O
Wrm	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
something	O
for	O
supper	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
Steaks	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
Taylor	O
?	O
Willis	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
eat	O
his	O
Beef	O
Steaks	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Willis	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
Seven	O
to	O
Ten	O
.	O
Watson	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Taylor	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
201.	O
Walter	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
mov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
did	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Malice	O
and	O
Forethought	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
strike	O
and	O
stab	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Breast	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Blackwell	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
Half	O
an	O
Inch	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
feloniously	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Golden-Lane	B-place
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
a	O
Cook's-Shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
Near	B-place
Old-Street	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Rejoicing	O
Night	O
for	O
the	O
Victory	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
A	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
About	O
Dusk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
Sight	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
Fellows	O
making	O
Game	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
:	O
Presently	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Instrument	O
that	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Three-square	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
it	O
any	O
Handle	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
Men	O
making	O
Game	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
with	O
this	O
Instrument	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
clos	O
'd	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
seeing	O
this	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
went	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Endeavour	O
,	O
the	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
reel	O
'd	O
back	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
dropp	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
,	O
but	O
died	O
immediately	O
;	O
and	O
Roberts	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
Roberts	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
is	O
dead	O
?	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
A	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Servant	O
doing	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
Roberts	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
Roberts	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Mens	O
talking	O
to	O
Roberts	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Words	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
gone	O
from	O
them	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
Roberts	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
fetch	O
this	O
Instrument	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
the	O
Instrument	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
something	O
of	O
their	O
making	O
Game	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
make	O
Game	O
at	O
him	O
for	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
They	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
shame	O
him	O
for	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
scold	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
tell	O
us	O
in	O
what	O
way	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Dew	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Passion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Wound	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
Wound	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
little	O
Wound	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
Ribs	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
they	O
clos	O
'd	O
in	O
before	O
they	O
parted	O
them	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
.	O
Questions	O
to	O
Dew	O
by	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
Mob	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
People	O
about	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Soldier	O
there	O
with	O
his	O
Piece	O
;	O
was	O
the	O
Soldier	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
the	O
Mischief	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
The	O
Soldier	O
was	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
this	O
the	O
Night	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Rejoicing	O
for	O
the	O
Victory	O
of	O
Culloden	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
no	O
Conversation	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
about	O
breaking	O
of	O
Windows	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
were	O
talking	O
of	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
within-side	O
of	O
his	O
Groundsel	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
and	O
clos	O
'd	O
how	O
far	O
were	O
they	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
somebody	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stagger	O
'd	O
toward	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
the	O
Man	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
Dew	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
did	O
not	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
insist	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Man	O
enough	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
him	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
that	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
about	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
walking	O
thro	O
'	O
Whitecross-Street	O
into	O
Playhouse-Street	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
Golden-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
have	O
many	O
Words	O
:	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
must	O
pawn	O
his	O
Shirt	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
Thing	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
That	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
they	O
clos	O
'd	O
in	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
glitter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
what	O
follow	O
'd	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
ran	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
ran	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
dropp	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
never	O
sigh	O
'd	O
nor	O
groan	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Soldier	O
there	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Talk	O
of	O
putting	O
out	O
Lights	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
Rejoicing	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
Words	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
about	O
?	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
him	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
down	O
his	O
Arms	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Roberts	O
with	O
any	O
Arms	O
?	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
!	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Half	O
a	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
nor	O
a	O
Shirt	O
to	O
his	O
A	O
-	O
e	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
turn	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
him	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
down	O
his	O
Arms	O
:	O
Then	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Men	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
laugh	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
stepp	O
'd	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
clos	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Blows	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
bright	O
Weapon	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
another	O
Word	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Carlisle	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Seal	O
A	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Seal	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
Work	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Rejoicing	O
was	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bonfire	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
Upper-end	O
of	O
Golden-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
this	O
Roberts	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
?	O
Seal	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Beginning	O
.	O
The	O
deceas	O
'd	O
Man	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Windows	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
Lights	O
put	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
round	O
the	O
Fire	O
side	O
of	O
breaking	O
Windows	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
Roberts	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
Words	O
?	O
Seal	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
Roberts	O
goes	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
Words	O
passing	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
Roberts	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Words	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
challeng	O
'd	O
to	O
fight	O
Roberts	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
:	O
With	O
that	O
Roberts	O
takes	O
up	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
all	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
were	O
not	O
worth	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Said	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
worth	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
will	O
fight	O
you	O
:	O
With	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
Roberts	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
collar	O
'd	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
scuffled	O
'till	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
Threshold	O
of	O
Roberts	O
's	O
Door	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Roberts	O
make	O
an	O
Offer	O
of	O
striking	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Weapon	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Blow	O
struck	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Man	O
dead	O
?	O
Seal	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
dead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Seal	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Ten	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
no	O
Weapon	O
?	O
Seal	O
.	O
No	O
Weapon	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
Soldier	O
there	O
?	O
Seal	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
his	O
Piece	O
?	O
Seal	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Scarborough	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
about	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Scarborough	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
as	O
dead	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rebels	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
quarrel	O
about	O
?	O
Scarborough	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
this	O
Fellow	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Roberts	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
Duke	O
William	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Family	O
;	O
must	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
Windows	O
shut	O
up	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Well	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
complaining	O
that	O
his	O
Windows	O
were	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
angry	O
?	O
Scarborough	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
angry	O
at	O
,	O
except	O
it	O
was	O
shooting	O
at	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
;	O
though	O
this	O
Fellow	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
never	O
shot	O
nor	O
ever	O
gave	O
any	O
Provocation	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
close	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Roberts	O
had	O
a	O
Weapon	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
?	O
Was	O
not	O
there	O
some	O
Guns	O
fired	O
at	O
some	O
People	O
's	O
Windows	O
?	O
and	O
were	O
no	O
Windows	O
broke	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
Scarborough	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
why	O
should	O
he	O
address	O
himself	O
so	O
particularly	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
hear	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
light	O
Candles	O
?	O
Scarborough	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
concerning	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Affair	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
George	B-pers
Alehouse	I-pers
in	O
Old-Street	O
,	O
and	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
,	O
many	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
:	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Door	O
;	O
Roberts	O
steps	O
in	O
and	O
comes	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
engag	O
'd	O
with	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
Roberts	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
pulling	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Skirt	O
:	O
I	O
stepp	O
'd	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
fight	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
strong	O
in	O
his	O
scuffling	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
He	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
manage	O
him	O
;	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
apprehend	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Mischief	O
then	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Wound	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Wound	O
under	O
the	O
Rib	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
big	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
Hole	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
put	O
a	O
Straw	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Body	O
open	O
'd	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
call	O
'd	O
you	O
to	O
assist	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
Roberts	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
fight	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Hawes	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
a	O
Cooper	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
Ten	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
,	O
follow	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
hollowing	O
and	O
hooting	O
;	O
when	O
Roberts	O
had	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Stone	O
of	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
stand	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
warrant	O
you	O
I	O
am	O
Man	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
clos	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
Minute	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
fight	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
had	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
Woman	O
takes	O
hold	O
of	O
Roberts	O
and	O
gets	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
immediately	O
the	O
Man	O
is	O
kill	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
a	O
Blow	O
struck	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fire	O
at	O
them	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
dead	O
Man	O
lie	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Window	O
.	O
Osborne	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
.	O
At	O
the	O
Goat	O
Alehouse	O
the	O
poor	O
Fellow	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
singing	O
a	O
merry	O
Song	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Robert	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
subpoenied	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
cross	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Liquor	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Health	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
said	O
they	O
magnify	O
'd	O
their	O
Loss	O
and	O
lessen	O
'd	O
our	O
own	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Rebel	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Skinner	O
,	O
Roberts	O
has	O
kill	O
'd	O
Blackwell	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
dead	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
Patch	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Hole	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
black	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
big	O
as	O
my	O
Finger	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
Roberts	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
That	O
Night	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
myself	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
opposite	O
Chiswell-Street	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Skinner	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
refuse	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
because	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
to	O
serve	O
of	O
my	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
dead	O
Body	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Puncture	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Fingers	O
below	O
the	O
Nipple	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
Breast	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
The	O
Left	O
Breast	O
,	O
an	O
Inch	O
below	O
the	O
Nipple	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
deep	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
quite	O
pierc	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
immediate	O
Death	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
wide	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
suppose	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Triangle	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
depend	O
upon	O
God	O
's	O
Mercy	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
this	O
honourable	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Rejoycing	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
Victory	O
?	O
Haws	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
?	O
Haws	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
looking	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
for	O
Stones	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
their	O
Guns	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wonder	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
Patience	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
malicious	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
,	O
but	O
willing	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
good	O
Action	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
temper	O
'd	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
know	O
nothing	O
extraordinary	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
another	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Shop	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
-	O
Nicks	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Skinner	O
say	O
?	O
Nicks	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Headborough	O
to	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
Parish	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
we	O
broke	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
:	O
The	O
Clerk	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
ask	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
take	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
at	O
the	O
Taphouse	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
Skinner	O
say	O
was	O
this	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
had	O
said	O
many	O
treasonable	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
talking	O
so	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
as	O
a	O
disaffected	O
Person	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
commended	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Oliver	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Banks	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
paid	O
him	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
for	O
Work	O
;	O
he	O
alter	O
'd	O
me	O
three	O
Guns	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
before	O
these	O
Wars	O
:	O
I	O
maintain	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
shoot	O
the	O
Pretender	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
-	O
Dukeson	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
you	O
by	O
at	O
this	O
Quarrel	O
?	O
Dukeson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Old-Street	O
;	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
quarrelling	O
;	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
to	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Rebel	O
,	O
a	O
Villain	O
and	O
a	O
Roman	O
;	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
him	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
knock	O
his	O
Head	O
off	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
struck	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
drawing	O
near	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Man	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
or	O
went	O
in	O
himself	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
shut	O
?	O
Dukeson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Skinner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
this	O
Affair	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
change	O
a	O
Word	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
Affair	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
202.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bundy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
she	O
your	O
Apprentice	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
yet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Business	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Winding	O
of	O
Silk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
With	O
robbing	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
Bed-side	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
my	O
Bed-side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Silk	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Luca	O
s.	O
Soft	O
Silk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
an	O
Ounce	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
An	O
Ounce	O
my	O
Master	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
your	O
Master	O
charges	O
you	O
with	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
charge	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Girl	O
.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
an	O
easy	O
Matter	O
to	O
miss	O
such	O
a	O
little	O
Quantity	O
as	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Silk	O
?	O
When	O
did	O
they	O
charge	O
you	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
They	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
suppose	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
your	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
so	O
you	O
take	O
this	O
Way	O
.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
desire	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
good	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Dangy	I-pers
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Box	O
;	O
the	O
Child	O
is	O
but	O
thirteen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Dangy	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
.	O
Dangy	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
threaten	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
threaten	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
good	O
Words	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
Silk	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
to	O
wind	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
's	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Goger	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
203.	O
Anne	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
four	O
Linnen	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Thing	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
too	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
four	O
Days	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
what	O
happen	O
'd	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
At	O
Night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
Bed	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
got	O
the	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
came	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
four	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Shift-Sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Children	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Ashly	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
on	O
Easter-Monday	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Hat	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
when	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Field-Alley	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
sure	O
are	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Hat	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
she	O
says	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Napkins	O
again	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Only	O
one	O
old	O
one	O
that	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Salter	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
Hat	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
A	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
striped	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
Shew	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
Gown	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
six	O
Shillings	O
;	O
I	O
hid	O
her	O
five	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
six	O
Shillings	O
;	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
five	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
;	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
Hat	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
lent	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
Napkins	O
and	O
Gown	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Cousin	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
Gown	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
204.	O
William	B-pers
Hoyles	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Quilted	O
Petticoats	O
from	O
a	O
Hedge	O
in	O
Finchley-Common	B-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Burton	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
William	B-pers
Hoyles	I-pers
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Hedge	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Things	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
Finchley-Common	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
hung	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
Hedge	O
.	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
a	O
poor	O
,	O
Vagabond	O
Creature	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Majesty	O
25	O
Years	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
205.	O
Jane	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Barrs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Barrs	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Barrs	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
Service	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
:	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Barrs	O
.	O
Only	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
:	O
She	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
charge	O
her	O
'till	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
your	O
Mistress	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
willfully	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Burgess	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Barrs	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
Beadle	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Difference	O
between	O
a	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
and	O
her	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-Rings	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
'till	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
diligent	O
Search	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
tell	O
your	O
Mistress	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Fears	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
,	O
who	O
insisted	O
to	O
know	O
were	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
Three-pence	O
and	O
sit	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
:	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
Three-pence	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
her	O
checqu	O
'd	O
Apron	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Pawmbroker	O
's	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
Character	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
sufficient	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
make	O
an	O
Enquiry	O
:	O
At	O
first	O
she	O
stifly	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Confession	O
;	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Sir	O
Thomas	O
,	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
this	O
Witness	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
these	O
Ear-Rings	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Barrs	O
.	O
)	O
Madam	O
,	O
are	O
these	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Barrs	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
Daughter	O
's	O
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Barrs	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
I	O
heard	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
as	O
since	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Transportation	O
.	O
206.	O
Anne	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Laban	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Parr	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
did	O
actually	O
take	O
the	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Laban	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
Bosworth-Court	B-place
,	I-place
Cary-Street	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Parr	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Laban	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
found	O
?	O
Parr	O
.	O
In	O
St.	O
Anne	O
's	O
,	O
Blackfryars	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Spoon	O
again	O
?	O
Parr	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Fellow	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
this	O
Spoon	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grainger	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
there	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
there	O
to	O
pledge	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Blackfryars	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
a	O
Place	O
at	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
it	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Mistress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
Name	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
live	O
up	O
a	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
Hatters	O
by	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
;	O
her	O
Name	O
is	O
Littleton	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
207.	O
John	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Bed	O
Quilt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Box	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregory	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
We	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Coat	O
and	O
two	O
Waistcoats	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
Bed	O
Quilt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Please	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
these	O
Things	O
;	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Coat	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
Things	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Bed	O
Quilt	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Darking	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
the	O
Things	O
again	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
208.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Till	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Button	O
wash	O
'd	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
1/2	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Plough-Alley	B-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
)	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Goods	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
Till	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
made	O
of	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
made	O
of	O
Wood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
Four-pence	O
Half-penny	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whence	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
From	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Plough-Alley	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
Nothing	O
else	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
Buttons	O
worth	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
They	O
might	O
be	O
worth	O
18	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
young	O
Men	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
Till	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Moon	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Moon	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
away	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
Plough-Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Moon	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Making	O
away	O
with	O
what	O
Things	O
?	O
these	O
Drawers	O
,	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Moon	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
making	O
away	O
with	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Moon	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
making	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
?	O
Moon	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
by	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
little	O
Boys	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Moon	O
.	O
About	O
Eight	O
or	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
any	O
Questions	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Moon	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Moon	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
can	O
you	O
recollect	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
there	O
?	O
Was	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Moon	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Ab	O
.	O
Humm	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Humm	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
we	O
took	O
these	O
Things	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Humm	O
.	O
The	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Things	O
you	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Humm	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Humm	O
.	O
In	O
Plough-Alley	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Children	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
upon	O
what	O
was	O
told	O
us	O
by	O
the	O
Children	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
?	O
Humm	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Now	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
Witness	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
contradict	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Witness	O
to	O
your	O
Character	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Mother	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
big	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
stand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
209.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Mary	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Delahaye-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Coat	O
made	O
of	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Silk	O
Camblet	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Drawers	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Sir	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
that	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
was	O
confessing	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
writing	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
so	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
thought	O
so	O
,	O
than	O
let	O
that	O
be	O
return	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
sign	O
any	O
Confession	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
will	O
you	O
tell	O
us	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
laid	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
her	O
Charge	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
true	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
Question	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
three	O
blue	O
Balls	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-Lane	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Coat	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Name	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
redeem	O
them	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Order	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
this	O
Witness	O
says	O
;	O
that	O
you	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
you	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
Blue	O
Balls	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
three	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
Woman	O
before	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
My	O
Landlady	O
let	O
her	O
lay	O
there	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Caddy	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Caddy	O
.	O
One	O
Margaret	B-pers
Penterton	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
this	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
had	O
she	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
Caddy	O
.	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
lent	O
the	O
Woman	O
the	O
three	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Caddy	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
before	O
?	O
Caddy	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
take	O
in	O
such	O
Sort	O
of	O
Things	O
of	O
any	O
Body	O
?	O
Caddy	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Woman	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
find	O
you	O
know	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
no	O
Questions	O
at	O
all	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Caddy	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Penterton	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
lent	O
but	O
three	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
Caddy	O
.	O
They	O
wanted	O
more	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
her	O
Name	O
.	O
Caddy	O
