TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
19th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
C.	O
NUTT	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Pamphlet-Shops	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
.	O
1746	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
FOSTER	O
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLING	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vickers	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hutchings	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Porkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lindsay	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Crakentbrop	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Okeman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Skeates	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Durbam	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Patker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Eventon	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
88.	O
Anne	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Augustine	B-pers
Darosario	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wadders	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Language	O
does	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
speak	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Bengal	O
Language	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Lord-Mayor	O
please	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knows	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
let	O
him	O
tell	O
the	O
whole	O
Story	O
.	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
In	O
Kirby-Street	B-place
.	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Anchor	B-place
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
She	O
shut	O
his	O
Eyes	O
with	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
next	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
they	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
?	O
The	O
Man	O
or	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
shut	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
not	O
threaten	O
his	O
Life	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
that	O
Sort	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
assured	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
some	O
Hurt	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
have	O
this	O
Witness	O
ask	O
'd	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
you	O
shut	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Black	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Daughter	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Night	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
The	O
Girl	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
none	O
to	O
disprove	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
89.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Leugan	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Austen	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Interpreter	O
)	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
knows	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
took	O
any	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
the	O
other	O
Black	O
lost	O
his	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
meet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
In	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Widow	O
Austen	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
About	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Woman	O
wak	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
,	O
he	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Women	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
two	O
Women	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
carry	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Quarril	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Examination	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Man	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
He	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Thackhouse	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
this	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Black	O
,	O
was	O
beating	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
-	O
Said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
-	O
The	O
Watchman	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
Charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
insisted	O
on	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
-	O
Upon	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
Guineas	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
five	O
Guineas	O
;	O
two	O
Guineas	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
had	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Lodging	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
He	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
another	O
Woman	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
odd	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
5	O
l.	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Constable	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
is	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Coal	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mother	O
ow	O
'd	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
And	O
my	O
Mother	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
Guineas	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny-worth	O
of	O
Annifeed	O
.	O
Seeing	O
this	O
Man	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
Dram	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
:	O
Upon	O
that	O
he	O
forced	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Watchman	O
charge	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
pay	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
?	O
Susannah	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
acted	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Part	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Daughter	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
forswear	O
myself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
90.	O
Adam	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
near	O
Holloway-Mount	B-place
,	O
upon	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Colet	I-pers
;	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Colet	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
On	O
January	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
said	O
with	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
Near	O
Holloway-Mount	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
present	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
took	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
blow	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
With	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fir	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistol	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
it	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
my	O
Hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
fire	O
the	O
Pistol	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
you	O
had	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Hat	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
the	O
Hat	O
off	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
behind	O
Holloway-Mount	O
,	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
had	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Person	O
said	O
,	O
blow	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
Upon	O
that	O
you	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
fir	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fir	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
produced	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
at	O
that	O
very	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Colet	O
)	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
About	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
apprehend	O
him	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
my	O
Shop	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
recollect	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
you	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
before	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
make	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
what	O
passed	O
then	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Crooked	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
among	O
the	O
Porters	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Hughson	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Porter	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Oysters	O
about	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
Side	O
of	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Person	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
Trouble	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
as	O
the	O
Clock	O
struck	O
Six	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
comes	O
down	O
a	O
Man	O
from	O
the	O
Blue-Anchor	O
,	O
St.	O
Mary-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Porter	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Blue-Anchor	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
Game	O
.	O
-	O
After	O
that	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
comes	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Robbery	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Justices	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
Money	O
for	O
Goods	O
when	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
be	O
as	O
particular	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Monday	O
,	O
either	O
the	O
12th	O
or	O
13th	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
About	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
some	O
more	O
Oysters	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
call	O
again	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
you	O
up	O
enough	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
take	O
your	O
Basket	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
to	O
Cannon-Street	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
keep	O
pace	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
staid	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
reckon	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
emptied	O
my	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Five	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Fog	O
arose	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
his	O
Pace	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Colet	O
)	O
So	O
Mr.	O
Colet	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
on	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Fog	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
that	O
Day	O
?	O
Colet	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Edridge	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
s.	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Rachel	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Russel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
just	O
,	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
4	O
s.	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
up	O
some	O
Goods	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
me	O
my	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
)	O
What	O
Day	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
violent	O
Fog	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Lodging-House	O
in	O
Cheek-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Ruth	O
-	O
(	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
)	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
Bell	O
rung	O
.	O
It	O
commonly	O
rings	O
at	O
Six	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cheater	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
these	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
'Prentice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
?	O
Cheater	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
general	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
begun	O
to	O
have	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
20	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
of	O
late	O
?	O
Cheater	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
very	O
minute	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Pistol	O
or	O
Sword	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
worth	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
none	O
could	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
Character	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
bears	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Elliet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Only	O
this	O
John	B-pers
Colet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
kill	O
you	O
?	O
Really	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Fellow	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
20	O
Times	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
)	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
In	O
Cheek-Lane	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
Doors	O
from	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Lodging-House	O
in	O
Cheek-Lane	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
for	O
this	O
Reason	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
from	O
Holloway-Mount	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
Cheek-Lane	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Sparks	O
)	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
In	O
Thames-Street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
there	O
28	O
Years	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Now	O
recollect	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
what	O
Time	O
did	O
this	O
Man	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
with	O
Oysters	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Five	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
Ruth	B-pers
Macneller	I-pers
declares	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Six	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
91.	O
William	B-pers
Parford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
from	O
a	O
Yard	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bear-Key	B-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Everal	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Sugar	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
?	O
Everal	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whence	O
was	O
this	O
taken	O
?	O
Everal	O
.	O
From	O
a	O
Yard	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bear-Key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
him	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Everal	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
48	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
this	O
Sugar	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Did	O
he	O
own	O
it	O
?	O
Everal	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Evidence	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
Charge	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
Sugar	O
to	O
Tower-Hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
that	O
Precence	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Everal	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Elion	I-pers
,	O
Serjeans	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Elion	O
.	O
I	O
enlisted	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
farther	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Regiment	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
orderly	O
Fellow	O
,	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
92.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Cotton	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Jones	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
I	O
was	O
weighing	O
off	O
some	O
Cotton	O
at	O
Chester-Key	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
weighing	O
while	O
the	O
Landwaiter	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
myself	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
detected	O
for	O
taking	O
of	O
some	O
Cotton	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
reckon	O
about	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
Ebenezar	O
Hartly	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
of	O
Chester-Keys	O
.	O
Coming	O
on	O
the	O
Key	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Woman	O
and	O
another	O
at	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Cotton	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Porter	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
Porter	O
could	O
give	O
Merchant	O
's	O
Goods	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
out	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
particular	O
Bag	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Jones	O
)	O
Was	O
this	O
Bag	O
your	O
Father	O
's	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
farther	O
?	O
Hartly	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Porter	O
that	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
take	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Keys	O
and	O
picking	O
up	O
Bits	O
of	O
Chips	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
let	O
me	O
put	O
this	O
into	O
your	O
Basket	O
?	O
The	O
Constable	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
Woman	O
and	O
Girl	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
could	O
call	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
93.	O
Edward	B-pers
Crowther	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
37	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
was	O
Sen'night	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
Day	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Leadenhall-Market	B-place
with	O
some	O
Pork	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
six	O
Pigs	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Edge	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
five	O
Minutes	O
Time	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
Side	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
about	O
it	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Simson	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
carry	O
away	O
a	O
Side	O
of	O
Pork	O
.	O
We	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hulse	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Hulse	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
my	O
Duty	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
an	O
Outcry	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
which	O
Way	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
shoot	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
Meat	O
off	O
his	O
left	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Knot	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
And	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
directly	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Meat	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Hulse	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
Pork	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
Meat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Who	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
Hulse	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
He	O
could	O
make	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
Defence	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
Had	O
you	O
sold	O
this	O
Pork	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
hir	O
'd	O
me	O
heard	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Meat	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
94.	O
Francis	B-pers
Otter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
half	O
Peck	O
Loaf	O
and	O
two	O
Quartern	O
Loaves	O
of	O
Bread	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Caleb	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Whiteland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Baker	O
's	O
Man	O
usually	O
sets	O
his	O
Basket	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
every	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Bread	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Bevis	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
these	O
Loaves	O
.	O
Bevis	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Basket	O
Mr.	O
Whiteland	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Bread	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
Bread	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Bevis	O
.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Bevis	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
at	O
the	O
Rose-Alehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
deliver	O
them	O
back	O
?	O
Bevis	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witness	O
to	O
your	O
Character	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
appear	O
for	O
me	O
To-morrow	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Touchal	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Bevis	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
with	O
Bread	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
?	O
Bevis	O
.	O
Not	O
with	O
Bread	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
with	O
Bakers	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Whiteland	O
to	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Creature	O
,	O
for	O
corporal	O
Punishment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
95.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bridgewater	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Blanket	O
and	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Doney	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
taking	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
?	O
Is	O
it	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Doney	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
out	O
to	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
hire	O
it	O
of	O
?	O
Doney	O
.	O
Of	O
Elizabeth	O
Cookson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Doney	O
.	O
In	O
Tyburn-Road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
do	O
you	O
let	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
Doney	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
enter	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Doney	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
let	O
any	O
Blankets	O
or	O
any	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
?	O
Doney	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Doney	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
Things	O
?	O
Doney	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Doney	O
.	O
Seeing	O
this	O
Sheet	O
double	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
my	O
Linnen	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
make	O
any	O
Excuse	O
for	O
herself	O
when	O
you	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Doney	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
why	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
Things	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
cut	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sheets	O
for	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
with	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
96.	O
Anne	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
)	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
your	O
Sheets	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
lost	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Moor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
inspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
pail	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Body	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
my	O
Room	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Neighbour	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
her	O
at	O
last	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
in	O
Half-Moon-Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
own	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Sheets	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Woman	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
Sheets	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkin	I-pers
)	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
Sheet	O
?	O
Atkin	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
97.	O
Mary	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Ford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Copper	O
Saucepans	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thackwaite	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thackwaite	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
Two	O
Copper	O
Saucepans	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
?	O
Thackwaite	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Thackwaite	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Copper	O
Saucepans	O
we	O
missed	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Se'nnight	O
;	O
the	O
Pot	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
Gown	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whence	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Thackwaite	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
in	O
Marsham-Street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Thackwaite	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
Copper	O
Saucepans	O
we	O
missed	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
on	O
Friday	O
Evening	O
,	O
between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
catch	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
with	O
the	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
and	O
the	O
Gown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
her	O
?	O
In	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
?	O
Thackwaite	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Passage	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
this	O
Pot	O
?	O
What	O
had	O
she	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
?	O
Thackwaite	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
one	O
Thing	O
or	O
another	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
she	O
there	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Pot	O
and	O
Saucepan	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Thackwaite	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Thackwaite	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
.	O
She	O
missed	O
her	O
Step	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
discover	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
this	O
Bed-Gown	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Pot	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Thackwaite	I-pers
.	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
pass	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Pot	O
beyond	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
Husband	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thackwaite	I-pers
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
two	O
Saucepans	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
lay	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Thackwaite	I-pers
.	O
She	O
lay	O
there	O
unknown	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
you	O
likewise	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thackwaite	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
Things	O
again	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Thackwaite	I-pers
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
here	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbroker	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
large	O
Pot	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
neihad	O
she	O
any	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
98.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pillowbears	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
liv	O
'd	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
several	O
Things	O
were	O
missing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
we	O
made	O
them	O
open	O
their	O
Boxes	O
.	O
All	O
were	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
but	O
this	O
Person	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
Cap	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
farther	O
Search	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
Pillowbears	O
and	O
a	O
Towel	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jenison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear-Rings	O
lost	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
keeps	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Servants	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
my	O
Mistress	O
to	O
search	O
their	O
Boxes	O
and	O
Trunks	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
together	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
of	O
the	O
Ear-Rings	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Mistress	O
as	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
we	O
might	O
all	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
Pockets	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
House	O
Maid	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Cook	O
and	O
another	O
Servant	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
She	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
had	O
his	O
Child	O
by	O
,	O
a	O
Youth	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Reason	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
search	O
your	O
Box	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
Gown	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Thing	O
my	O
Master	O
saw	O
was	O
these	O
two	O
Pillowbears	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
was	O
a	O
Towel	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
five	O
Candles	O
conceal	O
'd	O
:	O
And	O
my	O
Master	O
was	O
angry	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
concealing	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
Reason	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
keep	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
clean	O
.	O
Five	O
or	O
six	O
Candles	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
fine	O
Things	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
clean	O
indeed	O
!	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
99.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pagram	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Hayward	O
)	O
What	O
say	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Hayward	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
Friday	O
Evening	O
at	O
Mr.	O
-	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Little-Minories	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
awak	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
Page	O
.	O
About	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
brought	O
this	O
Watch	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whose	O
Watch	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Necessary	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
is	O
not	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
whose	O
Husband	O
is	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
?	O
Page	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Toll	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
bought	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
Watch	O
on	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
Maker	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
please	O
your	O
Honour	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Well	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
hear	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
against	O
you	O
;	O
now	O
't	O
is	O
your	O
Time	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
witness	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
myself	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
Watch	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
Time	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Things	O
:	O
I	O
troubled	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
?	O
Did	O
she	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
Watch	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
call	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
your	O
Character	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
couple	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Hayward	O
)	O
She	O
says	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
Hayward	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
sat	O
by	O
fast	O
asleep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
thoroughly	O
sober	O
?	O
Hayward	O
.	O
I	O
cant	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
100.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tallow	O
Candles	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
George	O
)	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
George	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
and	O
stole	O
some	O
Candles	O
.	O
my	O
Wife	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
.	O
Some	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
Candle	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
Candles	O
that	O
were	O
hung	O
upon	O
the	O
Pegs	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
found	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
We	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
hour	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
declar	O
'd	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
St.	O
John-Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
with	O
any	O
Certainty	O
that	O
these	O
are	O
your	O
Goods	O
?	O
George	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
fresh	O
made	O
Candles	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
was	O
question	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
Candles	O
they	O
were	O
ours	O
;	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
more	O
Candles	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
ours	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
George	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Anne	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
I	O
had	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
myself	O
and	O
little	O
Girl	O
.	O
a	O
Customer	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
them	O
then	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
several	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Candles	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
Candle	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
aside	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
Negro	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Candles	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
George	O
declar	O
'd	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
on	O
what	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
in	O
St.	O
John-Street	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
or	O
a	O
short	O
Man	O
that	O
serv	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
corporal	O
Punishment	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
101.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
Fire-Shovel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Webster	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
justly	O
the	O
Day	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
she	O
stole	O
Sheets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
?	O
You	O
lost	O
Sheets	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
c	O
arry	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
examine	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Webster	O
)	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
these	O
People	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
the	O
Sheets	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
now	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
brought	O
the	O
Sheets	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
I	O
cant	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
Sheets	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
brought	O
Sheets	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Times	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
past	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
'T	O
is	O
now	O
your	O
Time	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
these	O
People	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
They	O
sell	O
Spiritous	O
Liquors	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
their	O
Daughter	O
got	O
fuddled	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Sheets	O
,	O
accordingly	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
102	O
,	O
103.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Barthia	B-pers
Whitefield	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Funnel	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lowrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Lowrey	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
large	O
Copper	O
Funnel	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Seven	O
and	O
Two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Lowrey	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
first	O
inform	O
'd	O
you	O
where	O
this	O
Funnel	O
was	O
?	O
Lowrey	O
.	O
The	O
Broker	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Broker	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Lowrey	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
David	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
)	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
Broker	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
touching	O
the	O
Matter	O
now	O
in	O
Question	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
large	O
Copper	O
Funnel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
what	O
Purpose	O
did	O
he	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
To	O
sell	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
Pound	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
Furnace	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Distiller	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
odd	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
Distiller	O
,	O
and	O
ignorant	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Henly	O
upon	O
Thames	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Distiller	O
,	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
Misfortunes	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
when	O
I	O
question	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
leave	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
fetch	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
Things	O
left	O
,	O
without	O
he	O
said	O
himself	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
a	O
Widow	O
of	O
a	O
Common-Council-Man	O
of	O
our	O
Ward	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
some	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
charge	O
an	O
Officer	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
equivocated	O
in	O
several	O
Shapes	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
bought	O
these	O
Things	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
sold	O
Rags	O
and	O
old	O
Iron	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
imagine	O
your	O
Wife	O
might	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
give	O
a	O
Great	O
2	O
Pound	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Father	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
his	O
Brother	O
.	O
They	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
deny	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Broad-Way	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
keep	O
Distiller	O
's	O
Shops	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Pray	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
one	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
what	O
is	O
your	O
Business	O
?	O
This	O
Morning	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
a	O
Copper	O
Funnel	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
imagine	O
was	O
some	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Property	O
hereabouts	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Person	O
lives	O
hereabouts	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
Business	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lowrey	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Funnel	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
we	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
From	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
upon	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
because	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Lowrey	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
Mr.	O
Lowrey	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Funnel	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Lowrey	O
)	O
Look	O
upon	O
that	O
Funnel	O
:	O
Is	O
it	O
yours	O
?	O
Lowrey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Broker	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
what	O
you	O
stopp	O
'd	O
?	O
Broker	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
please	O
to	O
observe	O
that	O
any	O
Confession	O
the	O
Woman	O
may	O
make	O
,	O
must	O
be	O
against	O
herself	O
,	O
it	O
wont	O
do	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
charg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
with	O
being	O
the	O
Principal	O
.	O
Carter	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Groat	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Broker	O
)	O
Who	O
brought	O
the	O
Copper	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Broker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
This	O
Man	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Funnel	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
emptied	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
People	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
frighted	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Broker	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
to	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
Brother	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
him	O
Pay	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
sending	O
his	O
own	O
Boy	O
.	O
The	O
Broker	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Impudence	O
to	O
ask	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Pound	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
only	O
mention	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
this	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
conscious	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
certain	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
Barthia	O
Whitefield	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
never	O
light	O
on	O
no	O
Copper	O
Pots	O
,	O
no	O
distilling	O
Things	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
them	O
lie	O
about	O
in	O
Shops	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Thing	O
I	O
ever	O
took	O
was	O
two	O
Funnels	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
large	O
Funnel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Shop	O
is	O
clear	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
now	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Pound	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Theodosia	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
taking	O
up	O
Barthia	O
Whitefield	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Clarke	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Crown	O
Reward	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Wilson	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
?	O
Clarke	B-pers
In	I-pers
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
some	O
Reward	O
for	O
taking	O
of	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Clarke	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Of	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Spouse	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
catch	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
Whitefield	O
had	O
never	O
absconded	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
)	O
You	O
are	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
what	O
Character	O
does	O
he	O
bear	O
in	O
his	O
Neighbourhood	O
?	O
Cherry	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Thing	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Dealings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Sort	O
of	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Cherry	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
People	O
come	O
to	O
buy	O
Rags	O
,	O
Bottles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
by	O
you	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
know	O
no	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Cherry	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Franklin	O
.	O
Very	O
near	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Character	O
does	O
he	O
bear	O
in	O
his	O
Neighbourhood	O
?	O
Franklin	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
principled	O
Man	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Franklin	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
have	O
no	O
Acquaintance	O
or	O
Dealings	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
good	O
Night	O
and	O
good	O
Morrow	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
)	O
You	O
are	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
how	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
that	O
Neighbourhood	O
;	O
what	O
Character	O
does	O
he	O
bear	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Acquaintance	O
;	O
have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
His	O
Parents	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
just	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
too	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Alice	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
)	O
What	O
Character	O
does	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
bear	O
in	O
his	O
Neighbourhood	O
?	O
Hughs	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
any	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Hughs	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
)	O
You	O
are	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
:	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Person	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
set	O
this	O
Matter	O
in	O
a	O
clearer	O
Light	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
give	O
the	O
Close	O
of	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Charge	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
seems	O
to	O
lie	O
pretty	O
strong	O
against	O
Wilson	O
.	O
His	O
having	O
stolen	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Possession	O
,	O
carrying	O
them	O
about	O
in	O
a	O
suspicious	O
Manner	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
find	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
three	O
different	O
Stories	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
strong	O
presumptive	O
Evidences	O
of	O
Guilt	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
has	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
that	O
Presumption	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
instrumental	O
in	O
apprehending	O
of	O
Barthia	O
Whitefield	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
make	O
any	O
Use	O
of	O
her	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
taken	O
together	O
:	O
That	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Wilson	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Wilson	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
for	O
seven	O
.	O
104.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cardwell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
four	O
Towels	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Coply	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Coply	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Goods	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
all	O
your	O
Goods	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
At	O
different	O
Times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
when	O
you	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
The	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
these	O
Goods	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
my	O
Dwelling-House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
Dwelling-House	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
In	O
Chancery-Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
been	O
your	O
Servant	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
Valentine	O
Day	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Having	O
lost	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
By	O
her	O
eloping	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Did	O
she	O
go	O
without	O
Notice	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
Without	O
Notice	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
upon	O
that	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
A	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
she	O
taken	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
In	O
Eagle-Street	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
She	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mention	O
all	O
the	O
particulars	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
mention	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
make	O
any	O
Excuse	O
for	O
herself	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Lawyer	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
four	O
Guineas	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
carry	O
her	O
before	O
any	O
Magistrate	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Before	O
Justice	O
Burdus	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
make	O
any	O
other	O
Excuse	O
there	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Excuse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
the	O
Things	O
again	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Johnson	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
these	O
Goods	O
?	O
Are	O
they	O
here	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
bring	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
pawn	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
different	O
Times	O
for	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
part	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
came	O
in	O
July	O
44	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Coply	O
)	O
You	O
say	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
then	O
these	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
July	O
44	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
your	O
Goods	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Johnson	O
)	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
Valentine	O
Day	O
was	O
12	O
Month	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
The	O
major	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
since	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
first	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
any	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
any	O
Linnen	O
Shift	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
six	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
laced	O
Apron	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
Napkin	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
's	O
Hat	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
Silk	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
Worsted	O
Stocking	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Two	O
pair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
brought	O
here	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
look	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Johnson	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
Things	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
prosecute	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
by	O
Justice	O
Burdus	O
against	O
me	O
for	O
receiving	O
Goods	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
brought	O
an	O
Action	O
against	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Coply	O
)	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Action	O
;	O
Is	O
the	O
Action	O
depending	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Attorney	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
bad	O
Hands	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
determin	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Use	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
my	O
Master	O
had	O
at	O
different	O
Times	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
Fish	O
,	O
Liquors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Coply	O
)	O
She	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
near	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
pay	O
her	O
any	O
Wages	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
13	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
s	O
my	O
Wife	O
lent	O
her	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
engag	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
due	O
than	O
this	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
had	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
she	O
wore	O
it	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Summer	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Coply	O
)	O
Had	O
your	O
Wife	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
my	O
Wife	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
at	O
pawn	O
,	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
my	O
Wife	O
said	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
Wife	O
wear	O
it	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
wear	O
it	O
for	O
ought	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
says	O
,	O
she	O
wore	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
Summer	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
was	O
she	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
cost	O
13	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Coply	O
)	O
Then	O
you	O
have	O
paid	O
her	O
no	O
Wages	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
9	O
s.	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
had	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
Shilling	O
he	O
borrow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
had	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
sometimes	O
when	O
he	O
wanted	O
Change	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
ask	O
for	O
2	O
d.	O
or	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Coply	O
)	O
At	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
pretended	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
were	O
you	O
indebted	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Coply	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
paid	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
turn	O
'd	O
a	O
Servant	O
away	O
without	O
their	O
Wages	O
in	O
my	O
Lifetime	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Distiller	O
upon	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
have	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
promiss	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
my	O
Trial	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Send	O
for	O
your	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
Supper	O
.	O
Her	O
Master	O
was	O
desir	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
her	O
Wages	O
,	O
upon	O
receiving	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
105.	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Slater	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Slater	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
dark	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
two	O
Books	O
off	O
of	O
my	O
Stand	O
;	O
one	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
Milton	O
's	O
Paradice	O
Lost	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
a	O
Poem	O
in	O
12	O
Books	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Thoughts	O
,	O
Moral	O
and	O
Divine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
did	O
she	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Slater	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
Purpose	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
saw	O
nobody	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
very	O
Day	O
lost	O
another	O
of	O
these	O
Books	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Stand	O
was	O
you	O
?	O
Slater	O
.	O
One	O
or	O
two	O
Doors	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
met	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Book	O
under	O
her	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
upon	O
that	O
?	O
Slater	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
shuffled	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
caught	O
these	O
two	O
Books	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
had	O
she	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
?	O
Slater	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
nothing	O
amiss	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
demalt	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
her	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
bold	O
in	O
her	O
Expressions	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
else	O
to	O
live	O
upon	O
but	O
this	O
;	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
follow	O
this	O
Employment	O
to	O
maintain	O
them	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
saw	O
you	O
take	O
these	O
two	O
Books	O
from	O
the	O
Stand	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
you	O
coming	O
up	O
towards	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
confess	O
'd	O
you	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
Now	O
make	O
your	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
a	O
Plaid	O
Morning	O
Gown	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Books	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
Book	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
se	O
Books	O
for	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
To	O
read	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
put	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
read	O
Milton	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
but	O
very	O
indifferently	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
read	O
Welsh	O
better	O
than	O
English	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Order	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
Corporal	O
Punishment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
passed	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
106.	O
Mary	B-pers
Inwood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
Stuff	O
Bed-Curtains	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whichurch	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Whichurch	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Stuff	O
Bed-Curtains	O
?	O
Whichurch	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Whichurch	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
last	O
Sabbath	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whence	O
?	O
Whichurch	O
.	O
From	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Whichurch	O
.	O
In	O
Cucumber-Alley	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Seven-Dials	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
come	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Whichurch	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
her	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Whichurch	O
.	O
Before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
particular	O
Words	O
she	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Did	O
she	O
own	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Tea-Kettle	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Whichurch	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Harper	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
this	O
good	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Tea-Kettle	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
Tea-Kettle	O
and	O
Curtains	O
?	O
Harper	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
come	O
suddenly	O
to	O
my	O
Spouse	O
;	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
almost	O
ready	O
to	O
starve	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
Loaf	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
She	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
bring	O
the	O
right	O
Proprietor	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
have	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
107.	O
William	B-pers
Morr	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Saws	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Saws	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
they	O
are	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
They	O
belong	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
But	O
Edwards	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
108.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gooden	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
,	O
King-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Morley	O
)	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Morley	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Morley	O
.	O
Eighteen	O
Pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
let	O
her	O
any	O
Goods	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
lend	O
her	O
two	O
Sheets	O
?	O
Morley	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
Sheets	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
your	O
Lodgings	O
?	O
Morley	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
her	O
Week	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheets	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Morley	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
the	O
Sheets	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
Shirt	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
the	O
Husband	O
taken	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
Lodgings	O
together	O
?	O
Morley	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
live	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
in	O
your	O
Lodging	O
?	O
Morley	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
109.	O
Adam	B-pers
Mccarnie	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stocking	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Peter	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robert	O
Mills	O
?	O
Paris	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
almost	O
right	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
)	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Business	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Linnen-draper	O
's	O
and	O
Slop-Shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
sell	O
Stockings	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
On	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
,	O
lose	O
any	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Shop	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
here	O
in	O
Court	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
has	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
say	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
The	O
Week	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Lad	O
take	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Stockings	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
loose	O
Great-Coat	O
on	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
flipt	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Peter	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Paris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
,	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Boy	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
reaching	O
over	O
the	O
Hatch	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
between	O
Three	O
and	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
come	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Stockings	O
;	O
I	O
stept	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
lame	O
;	O
)	O
by	O
that	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
even	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
you	O
Rascal	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
any	O
Question	O
?	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
110.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
-	O
Gimox	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
Business	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
a	O
saw	O
Fellow	O
:	O
At	O
last	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
saucy	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
satisfied	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
second	O
or	O
third	O
Time	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Stop	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Pot	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Hammer	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mackey	O
)	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
this	O
?	O
Mackey	O
.	O
The	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
Necessity	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Stays	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Broth	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
buy	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
Meat	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
warm	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pushed	O
me	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Hammer	O
Head	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
without	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Gimox	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
Hammer	O
Head	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Had	O
she	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
?	O
Gimox	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
before	O
.	O
As	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
presumptive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
111.	O
Anne	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Frances	B-pers
Langstaff	I-pers
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Goods	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
?	O
Langstaff	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whence	O
?	O
Langstaff	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
Castle-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Spital-Fields	I-place
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
your	O
Name	O
was	O
Robinson	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
it	O
is	O
Anne	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
my	O
Daughter	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
6	O
d.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Way	O
to	O
do	O
Good	O
;	O
God	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
40	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Dram	O
first	O
.	O
She	O
promised	O
what	O
great	O
Things	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
besides	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Quarter	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
Ten	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
One	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
winded	O
my	O
Silk	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
Now	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
George	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
They	O
know	O
her	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
carry	O
your	O
Work	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
there	O
and	O
order	O
a	O
Steake	O
,	O
something	O
hot	O
for	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
against	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
:	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
at	O
One	O
:	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
another	O
Person	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
decoy	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Story	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
here	O
last	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
a	O
Spoon	O
.	O
This	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
,	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
.	O
Says	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
is	O
just	O
gone	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
very	O
softly	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Perguson	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
:	O
I	O
clapt	O
my	O
Hands	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Stockings	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Darn	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Spoon	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
many	O
Wishes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
feel	O
in	O
your	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
F.	O
L.	O
accordingly	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
the	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Room	O
?	O
Langstaff	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Things	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
near	O
60	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
112.	O
Peter	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
one	O
Pillow	O
,	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Gilson	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Gilson	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
charg	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
let	O
him	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
?	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
these	O
Goods	O
;	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Gilson	I-pers
.	O
He	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
prove	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
let	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Gilson	I-pers
.	O
About	O
four	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
miss	O
the	O
Goods	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Gilson	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Gilson	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
distrust	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
pawn	O
them	O
to	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Gilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
People	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
First	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Sheets	O
;	O
the	O
Blanket	O
or	O
Pillow	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
I	O
find	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
and	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
?	O
[	O
The	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Glass	O
and	O
Sheets	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Thing	O
farther	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
this	O
Man	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
She	O
says	O
,	O
you	O
own	O
'd	O
you	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
your	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
meer	O
Necessity	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
wrong	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
discharg	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
nor	O
given	O
the	O
Key	O
up	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pulling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Warrant	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
nothing	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Parish	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
People	O
to	O
buy	O
out	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
Curtain	O
and	O
Sheet	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Warrant	O
was	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
His	O
Wife	O
told	O
us	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
own	O
to	O
you	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
?	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
People	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
?	O
Pulling	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
Defence	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
rob	O
you	O
.	O
Found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
feloniously	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
113.	O
George	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Pillow	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Best	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
let	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
In	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
continue	O
in	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
'Till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
follow	O
'd	O
upon	O
that	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
found	O
them	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
there	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
Three	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
and	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
Tea-kettle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
these	O
were	O
your	O
Goods	O
?	O
They	O
were	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Furniture	O
of	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Question	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
is	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
those	O
Things	O
were	O
pawned	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Witness	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
found	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
missing	O
about	O
ten	O
Days	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
first	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
Days	O
ago	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
entertain	O
'd	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
you	O
about	O
ten	O
Days	O
or	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
above	O
three	O
Months	O
since	O
:	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
2	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
teaz	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Rent	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
too	O
dear	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
it	O
good	O
I	O
would	O
quit	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
quitted	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
obliged	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
bring	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
laid	O
down	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
He	O
made	O
an	O
Agreement	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
five	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
by	O
little	O
and	O
little	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
something	O
that	O
vexed	O
him	O
that	O
made	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
wrong	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
114.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
called	O
Half-Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Clarke	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Drawers	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
three	O
Guineas	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
That	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
ago	O
?	O
Clarke	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
My	O
Child	O
was	O
sick	O
of	O
the	O
Small-Pox	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
two	O
Women	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
This	O
Catherine	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
unlock	O
'd	O
my	O
Drawers	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
thought	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
up	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
them	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
searching	O
of	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
about	O
Piece	O
of	O
small	O
Money	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
which	O
she	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
throw	O
behind	O
the	O
Clock	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
carry	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
?	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Examination	O
taken	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Clarke	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
your	O
Master	O
any	O
Questions	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Your	O
Master	O
says	O
you	O
were	O
making	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
a	O
Shirt	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Aldchurch	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
?	O
Aldchurch	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
the	O
Drawers	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
Drawers	O
?	O
Aldchurch	O
.	O
In	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
forward	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
Drawers	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
you	O
were	O
?	O
Aldchurch	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Time	O
she	O
stoop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
fideling	O
Way	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
People	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
Aldchurch	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Clarke	O
)	O
Then	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
in	O
Paper	O
,	O
was	O
your	O
's	O
.	O
Clarke	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Clock	O
;	O
did	O
she	O
throw	O
it	O
behind	O
the	O
Clock	O
?	O
Clarke	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
hit	O
against	O
the	O
Clock	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
One	O
Guinea	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
nineteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
one	O
Crown	O
Piece	O
,	O
four	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Money	O
resembling	O
a	O
Half	O
Crown	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
.	O
The	O
Pieces	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Clarke	O
.	O
This	O
Piece	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
above	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Aldchurch	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
Money	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mouth	O
?	O
Aldchurch	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Money	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Aldchurch	O
.	O
A	O
27	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
two	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bundle	O
?	O
Aldchurch	O
.	O
Not	O
just	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
?	O
Aldchurch	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
justly	O
say	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
;	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Money	O
gingle	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
mend	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Stockings	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
Cloathes	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
against	O
the	O
Drawers	O
.	O
She	O
drew	O
away	O
the	O
Chair	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
beside	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
before	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
her	O
Mouth	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
and	O
small	O
Money	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
My	O
Gold	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
own	O
Money	O
:	O
How	O
came	O
your	O
Money	O
in	O
your	O
Master	O
's	O
Drawers	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
consider	O
here	O
was	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Half	O
Crown	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
both	O
swear	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
Half	O
Crown	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
Master	O
swears	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
If	O
your	O
Money	O
was	O
your	O
own	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
your	O
Mouth	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
tore	O
to	O
Pieces	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
Master	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
deny	O
'd	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
about	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Judge	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
laid	O
as	O
a	O
capital	O
Felony	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
prov	O
'd	O
one	O
Moidore	O
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
two	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
see	O
how	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
lower	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
115.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Rachel	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
1/2	O
,	O
two	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
1/2	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
North	O
)	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
picking	O
your	O
Pocket	O
.	O
North	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
my	O
proper	O
Witness	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
,	O
I	O
expect	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
every	O
Moment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
.	O
North	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
's	O
House	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
.	O
Coming	O
home	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
late	O
,	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
North	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
last	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
;	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Bow	I-place
Church	I-place
:	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Creatures	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
good	O
Woman	O
?	O
She	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
got	O
up	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
whereas	O
my	O
Pocket	O
hung	O
as	O
it	O
does	O
now	O
:	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
good	O
Woman	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
you	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Creatures	O
together	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
