TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commition	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
and	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
20th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
C.	O
NUTT	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Pamphlet-Shops	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
.	O
1746	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
PARKER	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BURNET	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENISON	O
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRACEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Herropp	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Morran	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sandwish	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boorsecher	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Ellcock	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hutt	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
240	O
.	O
241.	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
James	B-pers
Crey	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pinchheck	O
Metal	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoe	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Crey	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
The	O
22	O
d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
my	O
Father-in-Law	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bow	O
Fair	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
his	O
Children	O
about	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fair	O
and	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
stray	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Common	O
;	O
in	O
coming	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Booth	O
upon	O
the	O
Common	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Children	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
Fields	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Common	O
,	O
near	O
Stepney	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
pass	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
Night	O
;	O
presently	O
after	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
Night	O
also	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
me	O
well	O
home	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
Moonlight	O
and	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
'till	O
I	O
got	O
under	O
the	O
Shade	O
of	O
the	O
Trees	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
my	O
Stick	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
immediately	O
another	O
jump	O
'd	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Stile	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
also	O
:	O
They	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
blow	O
my	O
Brains	O
one	O
in	O
Case	O
of	O
Refusal	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Fob	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Frock	O
and	O
a	O
Regimental	O
Waistcoat	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Watch	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
A	O
Pinchheck	O
Metal	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Dial-Plate	O
and	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
my	O
Pockets	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Linnen	O
;	O
they	O
also	O
took	O
my	O
Pocket-Book	O
:	O
One	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
my	O
Pocket-Book	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
rifling	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
my	O
Pocket-Book	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
Service	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
return	O
it	O
:	O
They	O
took	O
the	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Knead	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Stile	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
towards	O
Limehouse	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Mile	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
two	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
robbing	O
my	O
Father-in-Law	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Father-in-Law	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
His	O
Name	O
is	O
Bitch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
is	O
your	O
Father-in-Law	O
.	O
Crey	O
.	O
A	O
Perukemaker	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
the	O
Way	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
sent	O
you	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
one	O
bad	O
on	O
a	O
Footman	O
's	O
Frock	O
and	O
a	O
Regimental	O
Waistcoat	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
the	O
other	O
apparel	O
'd	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
Shade	O
of	O
the	O
Trees	O
;	O
only	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
pass	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Moon-shine	O
,	O
he	O
that	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
Footman	O
's	O
Frock	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
Pistols	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Holster	O
Pistols	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinctly	O
see	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Men	O
to	O
be	O
Troopers	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Moses	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Bow	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Field	O
from	O
the	O
Common	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
high	O
Ridge	O
of	O
Trees	O
that	O
shaded	O
the	O
Moon	O
:	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
Children	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
their	O
Way	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
my	O
Son	O
:	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
bid	O
good	O
Night	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
Money	O
just	O
now	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
nor	O
none	O
would	O
I	O
give	O
them	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Confusion	O
and	O
Hurry	O
about	O
my	O
Children	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
stop	O
my	O
Son	O
and	O
head	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
said	O
;	O
my	O
Son	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
valuable	O
about	O
me	O
but	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
and	O
Knee-Buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
About	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Leads	O
.	O
While	O
two	O
were	O
robbing	O
my	O
Son	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
thinking	O
he	O
could	O
cope	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
ask	O
your	O
Son	O
if	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
.	O
Birch	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
upon	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
weigh	O
some	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
The	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
those	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
and	O
Knee-Buckles	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
and	O
weigh	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warning	O
from	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
Company	O
to	O
stop	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Knee-Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Things	O
answering	O
the	O
Description	O
in	O
the	O
warning	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Maid	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Warning	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
directly	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Women	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
In	O
Fleet-Lane	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
who	O
the	O
Buckles	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
who	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
Return	O
:	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
who	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
that	O
sat	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Brother	O
;	O
so	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
this	O
Warning	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
read	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Place	O
backward	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
a	O
Soldier	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
there	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Buckles	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Man	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Humphrys	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
those	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Knee-Buckles	O
.	O
Barns	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
mean	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
he	O
must	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Lord	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
Goldsmith's-Hall	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
Information	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
gave	O
this	O
Warning	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Crey	O
)	O
Are	O
these	O
your	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Buckles	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Mark	O
upon	O
these	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Crey	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
foreign	O
Make	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Mark	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
made	O
in	O
Barbadoes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Johnson	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barns	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Barns	O
had	O
some	O
Talk	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
some	O
Confusion	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
good	O
Woman	O
,	O
these	O
Buckles	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
bring	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
owns	O
them	O
we	O
must	O
charge	O
you	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
backward	O
,	O
and	O
beckon	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Hand	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Barns	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
backward	O
,	O
there	O
sat	O
Humphry	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Cloaths	O
had	O
he	O
on	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
It	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Woman	O
and	O
there	O
you	O
found	O
this	O
Man	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
and	O
these	O
Buckles	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
fearful	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Foul	O
Disease	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Sister	O
gave	O
him	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
yesterday	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
these	O
Buckles	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
no	O
better	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
him	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
as	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
Sir	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
with	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
robbing	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Crey	I-pers
?	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Bray	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
or	O
the	O
Day	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
between	O
Bow	O
and	O
Stepney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
you	O
with	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
describe	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
goes	O
and	O
sees	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
Company	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Signal	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
come	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
passed	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Crey	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
Company	O
then	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Then	O
two	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
were	O
with	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Crey	O
)	O
When	O
I	O
demanded	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
's	O
Money	O
he	O
tristed	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
knock	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
Time	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crey	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pinchbeck	O
Watch	O
and	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
took	O
this	O
Watch	O
and	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Tongs	O
of	O
the	O
Buckles	O
was	O
broke	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Crey	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoe-buckles	O
and	O
Knee-Buckles	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
for	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
knock	O
'd	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
an	O
Instrument	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
Service	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
Use	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
keep	O
it	O
and	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Instrument	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Instrument	O
to	O
draw	O
Teeth	O
with	O
.	O
Then	O
John	O
Humphrys	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
G.	O
B.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Knee-buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
one	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
together	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
towards	O
Bow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
this	O
Watch	O
and	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
Buckles	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
cheated	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Buckles	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
Humphrys	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
afterterwards	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
some	O
where	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
valued	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
frequented	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
He	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
that	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
In	O
Ice-Alley	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
of	O
my	O
going	O
there	O
was	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
Streak	O
Iron	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
desir	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
could	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
goes	O
into	O
Black-Boy-Alley	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shar	O
'd	O
it	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Humphrys	O
and	O
you	O
frequented	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
and	O
drank	O
there	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barns	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Barns	O
,	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Sign	O
;	O
they	O
sell	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Johnson	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Humphrys	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Defence	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
Buckles	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Half-Guinea	O
my	O
Sister	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
call	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Jennings	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Defence	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Company	O
.	O
He	O
charges	O
me	O
with	O
being	O
present	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
)	O
Was	O
you	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
He	O
hit	O
me	O
a	O
Blow	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
draw	O
back	O
and	O
support	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Instruments	O
about	O
you	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
can	O
you	O
have	O
of	O
a	O
poor	O
Barber	O
?	O
Will	O
you	O
have	O
this	O
Instrument	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
Bray	O
,	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
was	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
this	O
last	O
Question	O
being	O
put	O
to	O
Birch	O
now	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
mention	O
'd	O
the	O
Circumstance	O
in	O
his	O
former	O
Evidence	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
Bray	O
had	O
aken	O
Notice	O
of	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
)	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
appear	O
for	O
?	O
Randal	O
.	O
For	O
John	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
his	O
Sister	O
?	O
Randal	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Randal	O
.	O
At	O
Mrs.	O
Due	O
's	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
?	O
Randal	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Remembrance	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
17th	O
or	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
this	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
deal	O
in	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Randal	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
-	O
Martingal	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
?	O
Martingal	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
242	O
,	O
243.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
and	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
and	O
rob	O
Edmund	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Edmund	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
)	O
Was	O
you	O
assaulted	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
?	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
and	O
when	O
?	O
Knapp	O
.	O
A	O
coming	O
from	O
Hampstead	B-place
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
this	O
Side	O
Mother	O
Red	O
Caps	O
,	O
just	O
entering	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Path	O
Way	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Manner	O
did	O
they	O
attack	O
you	O
?	O
Knapp	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
struggled	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
my	O
Escape	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
struggled	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
free	O
from	O
them	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
Person	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Senses	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
observe	O
the	O
two	O
Persons	O
that	O
attack	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Knapp	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
struggled	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
upon	O
my	O
Legs	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
litted	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Pistol	O
put	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Blow	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Pistol	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
at	O
my	O
Breast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
they	O
do	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
?	O
Knapp	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
upon	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Knapp	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
know	O
nothing	O
further	O
with	O
Relation	O
to	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
?	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
further	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
)	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
perform	O
'd	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Between	O
Mother	O
Red	O
Caps	O
and	O
Tottenham-Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
High	O
Road	O
or	O
Foot	O
Path	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Foot	O
Path	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
present	O
there	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
do	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Thing	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Jennings	O
went	O
forward	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Signal	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
attack	O
'd	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
attack	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
I	O
attack	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
stopt	O
him	O
?	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Struggle	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
Not	O
much	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
loose	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
when	O
you	O
struck	O
him	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
what	O
passed	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
John	O
Jennings	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
helped	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
said	O
,	O
Blow	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
wont	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Murder	O
,	O
so	O
pushed	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
one	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Breast	O
;	O
We	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Coat	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
that	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
another	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
his	O
Coat	O
off	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
I	O
ripp	O
'd	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Pockets	O
of	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
and	O
an	O
Indenture	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
else	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
An	O
Explanation	O
of	O
the	O
Bass	O
Relievo	O
of	O
the	O
Mansion	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
?	O
Bray	O
.	O
The	O
Coat	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
for	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
-	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
to	O
Poplar	O
with	O
something	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
Money	O
for	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Stephens	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
I	O
ever	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
doing	O
my	O
Duty	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
otherwise	O
.	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
244.	O
James	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
lost	O
the	O
Watch	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
my	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
and	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
Shop	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Boy	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
my	O
Wife	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Cutosh	O
,	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
press	O
down	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
readily	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Nail	O
and	O
crook	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
haul	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
whipt	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
others	O
Bosom	O
.	O
They	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
their	O
Hand	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
a	O
crooked	O
Nail	O
haul	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
's	O
Bosom	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
through	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
Crutched-Fryers	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Tower-Hill	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
Boy	O
gave	O
this	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Fob	O
or	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
's	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
Rice	O
Jones	O
's	O
Wife	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
West-Smithfield	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Watch	O
worth	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
Seventeen	O
Guineas	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
Age	O
this	O
Boy	O
is	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
fine	O
Thing	O
the	O
Ladies	O
use	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Wife	O
missing	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
took	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Thing	O
that	O
the	O
Ladies	O
put	O
in	O
their	O
Ears	O
,	O
or	O
another	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
Boy	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
my	O
Watch	O
Five	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
that	O
make	O
it	O
their	O
Business	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
these	O
Boys	O
,	O
they	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
from	O
between	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Whores	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
)	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
A	O
Salesman	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
understand	O
any	O
Thing	O
with	O
Relation	O
to	O
this	O
Robbery	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
's	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Nothing	O
more	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
Boy	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
it	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Paul	O
's	O
Head	O
Tavern	O
facing	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Lad	O
,	O
one	O
Cutosh	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
's	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Manner	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
has	O
expressed	O
,	O
by	O
drawing	O
of	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Nail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
he	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
Crutched	O
Fryers	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
there	O
that	O
buy	O
's	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Long	O
Lane	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
to	O
Rice	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
gave	O
him	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Gold	O
or	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Metal	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
preety	O
Thing	O
in	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
Bar-Ring	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
another	O
Watch	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
nothing	O
further	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Nothing	O
further	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
than	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
)	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
Conversation	O
with	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
promise	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
free	O
Confession	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
promise	O
any	O
Thing	O
directly	O
or	O
indirectly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Encouragement	O
given	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
fair	O
Declaration	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
the	O
Truth	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Confession	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
me	O
Wine	O
and	O
Liquors	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
fuddled	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Drams	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
)	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Lewin	O
.	O
The	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
your	O
Son	O
?	O
Lewin	O
.	O
Fourteen	O
at	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
he	O
out	O
?	O
Lewin	O
.	O
He	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
any	O
Complaint	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Lewin	O
.	O
Never	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
before	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
)	O
Your	O
Son	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
?	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Tricks	O
like	O
Roguery	O
?	O
did	O
you	O
employ	O
him	O
in	O
any	O
Business	O
?	O
Lewin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Carmen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Lewin	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
drive	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
Hay	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
to	O
your	O
own	O
Business	O
,	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
work	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Gardner	O
)	O
When	O
was	O
he	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
following	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
245.	O
John	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Cotton	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
in	O
Relation	O
to	O
this	O
Cotton	O
?	O
Grey	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
about	O
some	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
My	O
Man	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
packed	O
up	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Cotton	O
,	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
Pounds	O
Weight	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Friday	O
Evening	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
receiving	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
Acceptance	O
of	O
a	O
Note	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Draught	O
upon	O
Alderman	O
Hankey	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
my	O
Sister	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
Cotton	O
was	O
that	O
John	O
carried	O
out	O
to	O
Iron	O
Gate	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
sold	O
no	O
Cotton	O
:	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
be	O
frighten	O
'd	O
and	O
uneasy	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
shall	O
know	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
said	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Rogue	O
:	O
Indeed	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
extremely	O
frighten	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Thing	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
both	O
my	O
Brother	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
our	O
Surprize	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
Power	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
.	O
With	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Iron	O
Gate	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Bristol	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
good	O
Character	O
and	O
Fortune	O
,	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
frequently	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
Cotton	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
something	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
say	O
that	O
Cotton	O
was	O
exceeding	O
dear	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
little	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Cotton	O
was	O
worth	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Pounds	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Thing	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
Relation	O
's	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
Burr-Street	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
this	O
House	O
together	O
,	O
talking	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
a	O
sad	O
Character	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
how	O
is	O
this	O
Thing	O
?	O
You	O
have	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
here	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
his	O
Relation	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
Thing	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
desperate	O
,	O
but	O
confess	O
the	O
Truth	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
to	O
that	O
Purpose	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
whole	O
Affair	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
bag	O
up	O
the	O
Cotton	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
very	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
my	O
Cotton	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Relation	O
and	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
Relation	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
do	O
in	O
a	O
Thing	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
act	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
Will	O
you	O
be	O
Security	O
that	O
this	O
Man	O
will	O
appear	O
on	O
Monday	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
is	O
necessary	O
?	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
him	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
:	O
Indeed	O
,	O
the	O
Relation	O
said	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
so	O
tender	O
a	O
Thing	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Security	O
for	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Pound	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
gave	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
these	O
Things	O
appear	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Man	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Trade	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
worth	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Surprize	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
over	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
candid	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
whole	O
Thing	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
24	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
your	O
Cotton	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scarsbrook	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Peter	B-pers
Scarsbrook	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
buy	O
any	O
Cotton	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Scarsbrook	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
buy	O
Cotton	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
that	O
lives	O
near	O
the	O
May-Pole	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
spun	O
or	O
unspun	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
in	O
five	O
Minutes	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
staid	O
fifteen	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Cotton	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
ask	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
18	O
or	O
20	O
Pence	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Seven	O
Stars	O
in	O
Bishopgate-Street	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Tobacco-Cutter	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Cotton	O
from	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Gloucestershire	O
from	O
a	O
Sister	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
18	O
d.	O
per	O
Pound	O
.	O
It	O
weigh	O
'd	O
23	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
34	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
Question	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
246.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cumbridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cumbridge	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Did	O
your	O
Husband	O
lose	O
any	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
?	O
Cumbridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Cumbridge	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Cumbridge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Back	O
Parlour	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Woman	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Ladies	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Cumbridge	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
your	O
Shop	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
determin	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
?	O
Cumbridge	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
whic	O
h	O
Cloth	O
was	O
twenty-two	O
Yards	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
because	O
that	O
very	O
Morning	O
I	O
mark	O
'd	O
twenty	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
Hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
so	O
easily	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Cumbridge	O
.	O
There	O
lay	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
mark	O
'd	O
that	O
very	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
Manner	O
?	O
Cumbridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Cumbridge	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
rest	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Mark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
.	O
Cumbridge	O
.	O
She	O
prmended	O
the	O
Child	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
almost	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
's	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlewoman	O
run	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Gaol	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
Time	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
Cowcross	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
247.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Duffil	O
Joseph	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Lawn	B-pers
Apron	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Pollen	I-pers
in	O
Great	B-place
Russel-Street	I-place
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pollen	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Pollen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
House-Maid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Pollen	O
.	O
The	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q.	O
Madam	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Pollen	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
many	O
Things	O
;	O
a	O
black	O
Coat	O
of	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Joseph	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
Duffil	I-pers
which	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Stockings	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shirt	O
Sleeves	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
lost	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Pollen	O
.	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
every	O
other	O
Servant	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Cook	O
:	O
About	O
a	O
Months	O
afterwards	O
I	O
discharg	O
'd	O
two	O
Servants	O
upon	O
her	O
Account	O
.	O
The	O
Way	O
we	O
first	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
was	O
this	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Pollen	O
wanted	O
his	O
black	O
Coat	O
;	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
for	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
,	O
my	O
Joseph	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
out	O
to	O
Monmouth-street	O
to	O
the	O
Taylor	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
n	O
the	O
same	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
traced	O
the	O
Matter	O
out	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
bought	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
her	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Person	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Joseph	O
to	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
Things	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
a	O
Mark	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Pollen	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
but	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
your	O
Mistress	O
any	O
Question	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
plead	O
'till	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
Clothes	O
deliver	O
'd	O
.	O
Pollen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
Order	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
at	O
Justice	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
are	O
guilty	O
or	O
acquitted	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
intitled	O
to	O
your	O
Clothes	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
colour	O
'd	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bradock	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Bradock	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
'Squire	O
Pollen	O
's	O
Coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Bradock	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
Things	O
must	O
either	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
or	O
sold	O
;	O
I	O
recollector	O
about	O
a	O
Fornight	O
before	O
this	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Coat	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
certain	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pollen	O
's	O
Coat	O
;	O
my	O
Son	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Wheat-Sheaf	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
myself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
amiss	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
having	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
sold	O
him	O
the	O
Coat	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Thief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
?	O
Bradock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
when	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Coat	O
for	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
the	O
Coat	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
?	O
Bradock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
concerning	O
the	O
Breeches	O
?	O
Bradock	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
Breeches	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Grange	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Joseph	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
Person	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
?	O
Bradock	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
Sale-Shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
?	O
Bradock	O
.	O
For	O
20	O
s.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
248.	O
Jane	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Dowlass	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
six	O
Plate	O
Buttons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
Woman	O
or	O
a	O
single	O
Woman	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
A	O
married	O
Woman	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
She	O
feloniously	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Goods	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
A	O
Dowlass	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
six	O
Plate	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
made	O
of	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
Of	O
Silver	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
Goods	O
were	O
they	O
all	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Shift	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
this	O
Woman	O
bought	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Question	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
Shift	O
to	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
Woman	O
;	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
he	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
Handkerchief	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
Jones	O
,	O
what	O
more	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
another	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
all	O
dirty	O
;	O
one	O
I	O
gave	O
Eighteen-pence	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Three-pence	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Now	O
is	O
your	O
Time	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Buttons	O
are	O
not	O
brought	O
home	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
249.	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Iron	O
Chains	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Liney	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Wynne	O
.	O
No	O
further	O
than	O
taking	O
my	O
Oath	O
concerning	O
the	O
Chains	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
the	O
Chains	O
?	O
Wynne	O
.	O
The	O
Lad	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
's	O
Premisses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Chains	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Wynne	O
.	O
His	O
Cart	O
Chains	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
they	O
lost	O
?	O
Wynne	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
's	O
Farm	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
Cart	O
and	O
Harness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Chains	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Wynne	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
the	O
Chains	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
Boy	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Wynne	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
veil	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Wynne	O
.	O
At	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Tyburn-Road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Thing	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
Writing	O
?	O
Wynne	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Parents	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Father	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
Nothing	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
this	O
Lad	O
brought	O
these	O
Chains	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
Manner	O
of	O
Value	O
to	O
me	O
but	O
for	O
old	O
Iron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
buy	O
these	O
Chains	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
indifferent	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
me	O
than	O
old	O
Iron	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
that	O
and	O
more	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
want	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
Blacksmith	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
many	O
Chains	O
are	O
there	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
Four	O
Chains	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
,	O
where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
,	O
Friend	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
In	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Boy	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
do	O
n't	O
live	O
far	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
what	O
Occasion	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Grate	O
of	O
him	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
assur	O
'd	O
was	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
him	O
about	O
these	O
Things	O
too	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
ask	O
him	O
a	O
Question	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
very	O
strict	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
A	O
mighty	O
little	O
Boy	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
old	O
Iron	O
!	O
'T	O
is	O
pretty	O
odd	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
three	O
Farthings	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
these	O
Chains	O
for	O
old	O
Iron	O
;	O
in	O
my	O
Opinion	O
you	O
are	O
more	O
guilty	O
than	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
desires	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
a	O
Chain	O
.	O
Marsh	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
any	O
such	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
such	O
as	O
you	O
that	O
incourage	O
such	O
little	O
Thefts	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Receiving	O
of	O
Stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
250.	O
James	B-pers
Searle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
taking	O
the	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
framed	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Walnut-Tree	O
Frame	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Size	O
might	O
it	O
be	O
of	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Size	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Warehouse	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
there	O
three	O
Glasses	O
standing	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
myself	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
taking	O
the	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
follow	O
him	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Glass	O
down	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
broke	O
.	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
the	O
taking	O
up	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Frame	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
broke	O
.	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Is	O
not	O
Thomas	O
Turner	O
here	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
it	O
to	O
your	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
About	O
200	O
Yards	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
any	O
Questions	O
of	O
these	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
251.	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Side-Pocket	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Candles	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Camden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Camden	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Camden	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
28th	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Camden	O
.	O
A	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Candles	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
with	O
upwards	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Camden	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
first	O
Sleep	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
with	O
nothing	O
but	O
my	O
Buckles	O
;	O
all	O
was	O
dropp	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Camden	O
.	O
My	O
Spouse	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
her	O
Bed-Side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
he	O
taken	O
?	O
Camden	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
another	O
Robbery	O
that	O
he	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
'till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
's	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Buckles	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
at	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Round-House	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Judith	B-pers
Camden	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Judith	B-pers
Camden	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
as	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
this	O
Boy	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
brought	O
a	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
lost	O
the	O
Key	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
at	O
the	O
Light	O
and	O
thought	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
on	O
Fire	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Hand	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
:	O
He	O
saw	O
I	O
was	O
startled	O
and	O
flew	O
away	O
;	O
directly	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dog	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
leave	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
?	O
Judith	B-pers
Camden	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
your	O
Husband	O
's	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Judith	B-pers
Camden	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
Bride-Lane	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
-	O
Jarvice	O
)	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Jarvice	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Watchman	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Flower-de-luce-Court	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
A	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Eleven	O
,	O
this	O
Davis	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
Saunders	O
,	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
Pit	O
of	O
Candle	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
wanted	O
Candle	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Tallow-Chandler	O
's	O
hard	O
by	O
;	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Boy	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
run	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
hardly	O
gone	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Camden	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
saw	O
any	O
Body	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Cropton	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
?	O
Cropton	O
.	O
These	O
Buckles	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
's	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
came	O
to	O
pawn	O
these	O
Buckles	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
252.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bouthe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Box	O
Value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
call	O
'd	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Gwyn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Gwyn	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Gwyn	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Brass	O
Box	O
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
some	O
Lace	O
and	O
a	O
Certificate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
stole	O
them	O
?	O
Gwyn	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Brass	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bosom	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
there	O
?	O
Gwyn	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
'tell	O
any	O
further	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
or	O
a	O
Lodger	O
?	O
Gwyn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
but	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
from	O
be	O
land	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
in	O
my	O
Brother-in-Law	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Gwyn	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
either	O
the	O
26th	O
or	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
or	O
Night	O
?	O
Gwyn	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
there	O
but	O
these	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
what	O
did	O
they	O
do	O
?	O
Gwyn	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Musse	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
between	O
Four	O
and	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
Box	O
?	O
Gwyn	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
before	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Pint	O
of	O
Anniseed	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
have	O
her	O
ask	O
'd	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Anniseed	O
and	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
two	O
Pints	O
more	O
and	O
one	O
was	O
spilt	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
The	O
Creature	O
got	O
herself	O
in	O
Liquor	O
and	O
then	O
would	O
have	O
swore	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gwyn	I-pers
being	O
very	O
confus	O
'd	O
and	O
doubtful	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
]	O
253.	O
Jane	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Spoon	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
eras	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
sent	O
this	O
Spoon	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
herself	O
I	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
as	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
me	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Tyler	O
)	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
this	O
Spoon	O
?	O
Tyler	O
.	O
The	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
[	O
When	O
Tyler	O
was	O
closely	O
charg	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Spoon	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
one	O
Spoon	O
was	O
like	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
frequently	O
to	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
as	O
Tyler	O
would	O
neither	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
nor	O
claim	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
the	O
Spoon	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
]	O
254.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Shoe	O
and	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Box	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
hard	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
or	O
two	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
my	O
Wife	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Times	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
big	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
heavy	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
Bench	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
I	O
slept	O
,	O
but	O
during	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shoe	O
and	O
Buckle	O
from	O
my	O
Right	O
Foot	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
her	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Buckle	O
from	O
my	O
Left	O
Foot	O
I	O
awak	O
'd	O
and	O
caught	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Shoe	O
and	O
Buckle	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
directly	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
a	O
Watchman	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
my	O
Hat	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Shelf	O
;	O
about	O
Two	O
or	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
they	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
escap	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
that	O
or	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
you	O
take	O
care	O
what	O
you	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Conver	O
sation	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
youself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Persons	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
your	O
Character	O
?	O
Judith	B-pers
Harebottom	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
hard-working	O
Body	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Market	O
to	O
buy	O
something	O
for	O
her	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
Business	O
?	O
Harebottom	O
.	O
She	O
spins	O
when	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Winter	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
she	O
goes	O
to	O
Haymaking	O
and	O
works	O
in	O
Gardens	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Crumpton	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Crumpton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
above	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Character	O
does	O
she	O
bear	O
?	O
Crumpton	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
Course	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
poor	O
hard-working	O
Woman	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
her	O
own	O
ancient	O
Mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
she	O
behav	O
'd	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
praise	O
God	O
she	O
never	O
behav	O
'd	O
amiss	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
255	O
,	O
256.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cummings	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Plumin	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Candy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Candy	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Candy	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Candy	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cummings	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Candy	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
back	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Bed	O
was	O
not	O
down	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
drink	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
sold	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
for	O
drinking	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
sold	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
bring	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Punch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
bad	O
House	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
pay	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
Woman	O
told	O
me	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
but	O
thinking	O
that	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
swore	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
'till	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
strip	O
me	O
:	O
The	O
Women	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
I	O
had	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
two	O
new	O
Shillings	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
Fellow	O
pretended	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
and	O
Yet	O
a	O
Mark	O
upon	O
the	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
cut	O
a	O
Notch	O
in	O
the	O
Timber	O
and	O
three	O
Crosses	O
on	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Candy	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
Woman	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Cummings	I-pers
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Cummings	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
in	O
Gaol	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
sworn	O
falsly	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
257.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
nor	O
regarding	O
the	O
Laws	O
and	O
Statues	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Pains	O
and	O
Penalties	O
there	O
in	O
contain	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
shooting	O
at	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1743	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Gun	O
loaded	O
with	O
Gunpowder	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
May	O
it	O
please	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Council	O
against	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
the	O
Indictment	O
is	O
grounded	O
on	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
wherein	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
Clauses	O
;	O
for	O
Instance	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
Person	O
shall	O
unlawfully	O
cut	O
down	O
or	O
destroy	O
Trees	O
,	O
set	O
fire	O
to	O
any	O
Barn	O
,	O
House	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
or	O
shall	O
willfully	O
shoot	O
at	O
any	O
Person	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
dwelling	O
House	O
or	O
other	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
:	O
The	O
clause	O
we	O
go	O
upon	O
is	O
for	O
willfully	O
shooting	O
at	O
a	O
Person	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
necessary	O
to	O
shew	O
for	O
what	O
Reason	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Wheelwright	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
:	O
The	O
Defendant	O
,	O
Mills	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
deem	O
'd	O
a	O
notorious	O
Cheat	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
under	O
artful	O
Pretences	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
confin	O
'd	O
for	O
such	O
an	O
Offence	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
like	O
Account	O
he	O
lately	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Mills	O
knowing	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Dealings	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
large	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Wood	O
,	O
says	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
this	O
wood	O
grew	O
in	O
my	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
.	O
Mills	O
ask	O
'd	O
Lewis	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Higgs	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
more	O
Timber	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
likewise	O
of	O
Sheep	O
and	O
Lambs	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
Market	O
,	O
though	O
none	O
were	O
brought	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Colour	O
for	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Mr	O
.	O
Jewel	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
much	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
Hand	O
for	O
12	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
he	O
expected	O
to	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
this	O
Money	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
such	O
Persons	O
as	O
Mills	O
or	O
Nichols	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
:	O
so	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
they	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
this	O
Place	O
,	O
Bassildon	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Higgs	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
particular	O
Information	O
of	O
Mills	O
;	O
however	O
he	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
Lewis	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
he	O
willfully	O
shot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
by	O
Expressions	O
or	O
Words	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
:	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
Lewis	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
spoke	O
those	O
words	O
than	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Musket	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
hearing	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Aim	O
:	O
On	O
finding	O
the	O
Man	O
get	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
Malice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
dead	O
,	O
bring	O
the	O
Blunderbuss	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
blow	O
his	O
Brain	O
,	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
happily	O
fell	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
escap	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
seem	O
extraordinary	O
that	O
this	O
Thing	O
should	O
end	O
dormant	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
but	O
Mills	O
was	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
apprehended	O
sooner	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
brought	O
on	O
before	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
)	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
The	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
1743	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
these	O
are	O
brave	O
Felleys	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nicholls	O
was	O
very	O
handsomly	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Says	O
Mills	O
,	O
Master	O
Lewis	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Higgs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
They	O
also	O
wanted	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
lain	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Bed	O
for	O
them	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
good	O
Bargain	O
;	O
)	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
a	O
Lodging	O
elsewhere	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
Mills	O
and	O
Nichollas	O
had	O
some	O
Money	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Barges	O
were	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Higgs	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
defraud	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
Story	O
?	O
He	O
swore	O
about	O
Mills	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
dealing	O
in	O
London	O
again	O
?	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Bassildon	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
this	O
Mill	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
near	O
a	O
Common	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
Mills	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
levell	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Distance	O
was	O
you	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
you	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Blunderbuss	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
Ball	O
or	O
Shot	O
,	O
it	O
whistled	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
apply	O
to	O
any	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
against	O
this	O
Man	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Justice	O
did	O
you	O
apply	O
to	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
At	O
Straitly	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
forged	O
Note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
your	O
Information	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
complain	O
of	O
his	O
Shooting	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
desire	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
grant	O
you	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
bad	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
Complaints	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
a	O
Warrant	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
trick	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
vile	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
safe	O
in	O
lying	O
in	O
their	O
Beds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
request	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
your	O
Information	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
at	O
Straitly	O
for	O
Advice	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
Cheat	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
for	O
shooting	O
at	O
you	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
shot	O
at	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
exhibit	O
this	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
now	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
for	O
shooting	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
find	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
endeavour	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Cheat	O
,	O
or	O
shooting	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Shooting	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Ah	O
ye	O
London	O
Fools	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
..	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brigs	I-pers
)	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Bassildon	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Defendant	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
at	O
Bassildon	O
about	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
William	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Timber-Merchant	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
his	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
them	O
between	O
Five	O
and	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
Bassildon-Heath	O
to	O
Mill	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
tell	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
saw	O
Mills	O
do	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
he	O
stripp	O
'd	O
himself	O
into	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
or	O
Musket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
away	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
levell	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
I	O
run	O
behind	O
the	O
Barn	O
,	O
or	O
Straw-Cock	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
,	O
and	O
fir	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Piece	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
As	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Piece	O
I	O
ran	O
behind	O
the	O
Hovel	O
,	O
or	O
stable	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
Danger	O
in	O
going	O
Home	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Per	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
meeting	O
with	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
Mill	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
As	O
fine	O
a	O
Moon-shine	O
Evening	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
stood	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
stabb	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Lewis	O
)	O
Had	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
a	O
Penknife	O
in	O
your	O
Hand	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
threaten	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
your	O
Money	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Rishton	I-pers
)	O
Pray	O
how	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
Dealings	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Rishton	O
.	O
Nichols	O
and	O
Mills	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
three	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
?	O
Rishton	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Reading-Jail	O
and	O
found	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
send	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mills	O
?	O
Rishton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
Berkshire	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
William	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
for	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
Mills	O
.	O
]	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Nicholls	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
;	O
was	O
you	O
with	O
Mills	O
when	O
Lewis	O
came	O
there	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
Lewis	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
shooting	O
off	O
the	O
Gun	O
.	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Nothing	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
's	O
Man	O
say	O
;	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
little	O
Boy	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
[	O
As	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
so	O
long	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
]	O
218.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
140	O
Gold	O
Beads	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
also	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
21	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Corbut	O
.	O
The	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
from	O
a	O
Ship	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
One	O
and	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
away	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
Purse	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
that	O
laid	O
by	O
the	O
Bedside	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
my	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
Necklace	O
made	O
of	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
Gold	O
Beads	O
,	O
two	O
Rows	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
you	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Corbut	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
Pocket	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Bedside	O
as	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
?	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
She	O
laid	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
awake	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Corbut	O
.	O
She	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
the	O
Room	O
too	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
up	O
before	O
you	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
39	O
s.	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
but	O
18	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
before	O
you	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
rife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
long	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
Ship	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
that	O
Ship	O
lie	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
Hope	O
and	O
the	O
Nore	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
tax	O
her	O
about	O
this	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
any	O
Questions	O
of	O
this	O
Witness	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
up	O
two	O
Hours	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
Buckles	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
Corbut	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
this	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
or	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
since	O
you	O
lost	O
them	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
has	O
the	O
Necklace	O
in	O
Custody	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Buckles	O
in	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Shoebuckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
's	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
these	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
At	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
's	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
had	O
lain	O
there	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
lain	O
there	O
two	O
Nights	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
Hewitt	O
shew	O
'd	O
you	O
these	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
She	O
hir	O
'd	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Week	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
Hewitt	O
hir	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
Anne	O
Corbut	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
farther	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
's	O
Mother	O
had	O
the	O
Necklace	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Morning	O
after	O
.	O
Q.	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Corbut	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
then	O
,	O
was	O
she	O
not	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
her	O
Mother	O
fetch	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
farther	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
bid	O
me	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
ask	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Buckles	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
any	O
Questions	O
of	O
this	O
Anne	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
give	O
me	O
the	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Nicholls	O
)	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
first	O
Morning	O
after	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
lay	O
there	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
second	O
Morning	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
make	O
any	O
Enquiry	O
about	O
the	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
or	O
Buckles	O
;	O
or	O
was	O
you	O
there	O
when	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
went	O
away	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
was	O
a-bed	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
Buckles	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Possession	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
should	O
ask	O
about	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
say	O
Anne	O
Corbut	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
after	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
drinking	O
Tea	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
present	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
assisting	O
in	O
Tea-drinking	O
Time	O
?	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Conversation	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
they	O
be	O
together	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
by	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
nothing	O
past	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Necklace	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
Buckles	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
they	O
dine	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
they	O
dined	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
that	O
Gentlewoman	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Name	O
is	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
after	O
Dinner	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
home	O
then	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
then	O
Anne	O
Corbet	O
had	O
lain	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
went	O
up	O
by	O
herself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
before	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
Were	O
they	O
any	O
Time	O
together	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
say	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
did	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
go	O
away	O
?	O
Did	O
your	O
Mistress	O
come	O
home	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Did	O
she	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
lay	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
down	O
while	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
together	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
About	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
During	O
that	O
Time	O
was	O
you	O
present	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
's	O
complaining	O
of	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
might	O
it	O
be	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
Five	O
or	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
left	O
them	O
together	O
about	O
Five	O
or	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Corbut	I-pers
)	O
Was	O
this	O
Loss	O
you	O
mention	O
of	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
second	O
Night	O
?	O
Corbut	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
'till	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
'till	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
on	O
Easter-Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Mother	O
's	O
Name	O
.	O
Corbut	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Isaac	B-pers
Pinor	I-pers
)	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Pinor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
brought	O
this	O
Necklace	O
to	O
pawn	O
along	O
with	O
this	O
Girl	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
Pinor	O
.	O
Eighteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
whose	O
Necklace	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Pinor	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
Daughter	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
Pinor	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
only	O
she	O
sent	O
this	O
Girl	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
cheat	O
her	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Peter	O
Nettle	O
,	O
Headborough	O
)	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Nettle	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pinor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
he	O
should	O
produce	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Service	I-pers
)	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
when	O
your	O
Daughter	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
together	O
?	O
Service	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
my	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
Whether	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
?	O
Service	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
my	O
Child	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
that	O
lives	O
at	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
Shop	O
that	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Service	O
.	O
To	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Service	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Memory	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
27th	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
what	O
Time	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
there	O
?	O
Service	O
.	O
About	O
Ten	O
or	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
Daughter	O
come	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
's	O
?	O
Service	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
dare	O
to	O
come	O
before	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
passionate	O
Woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
,	O
what	O
past	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
?	O
Service	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
this	O
Necklace	O
and	O
the	O
Buckles	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
Time	O
did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Service	O
.	O
She	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
Disturbance	O
or	O
Confesion	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Newgate	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
Daughter	O
is	O
a	O
married	O
Woman	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
live	O
there	O
she	O
should	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
your	O
Daughter	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
live	O
there	O
?	O
Service	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
Daughter	O
was	O
frighten	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Wits	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
Daughter	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
made	O
Use	O
of	O
that	O
Expression	O
?	O
Service	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
Daughter	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
or	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
