TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
FRIDAY	O
January	O
16	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
17	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
19	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
20th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Benn	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
HINTON	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
in	O
St	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
1746	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BENN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
FOSTER	O
,	O
Mr	O
Baron	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRACEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ramshire	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Stot	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Wardell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Seamack	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Rabbitts	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Cradock	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Tost	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bracket	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
68	O
.	O
+	O
Anne	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Henry	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
being	O
moved	O
by	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Henry	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
traiterously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
Rib	O
,	O
with	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
give	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Oct.	O
28	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
Marlow	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
some	O
Time	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
First	O
tell	O
the	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
.	O
Marlow	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
at	O
the	B-place
Sign	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Three-Tuns	I-place
in	I-place
Ayloff-street	I-place
,	I-place
Goodmans-fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Twopenny	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
the	O
Beer	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
backward	O
;	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
backward	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
half	O
Pint	O
of	O
Twopenny	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
my	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
backward	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Minutes	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
fuddled	O
,	O
he	O
started	O
up	O
immediately	O
at	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
!	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
Man	O
here	O
?	O
Marlow	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
backward	O
about	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Minutes	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Banister	O
,	O
he	O
turns	O
his	O
Face	O
round	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
has	O
stabbed	O
,	O
killed	O
,	O
or	O
murdered	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
three	O
things	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
positively	O
say	O
.	O
He	O
turned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
me	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Back	O
was	O
all	O
bloody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
Marlow	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
Back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprize	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
the	O
remaining	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
half	O
Pint	O
of	O
Twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
not	O
seeing	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
nor	O
knowing	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
backward	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
murdered	O
or	O
stabbed	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
what	O
Purpose	O
did	O
she	O
make	O
that	O
Exclamation	O
?	O
Marlow	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
reading	O
the	O
News-paper	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
get	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
crying	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
Women	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
up	O
in	O
Arms	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Marlow	O
.	O
Nothing	O
more	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Truth	O
I	O
can	O
stand	O
too	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Gowry	I-pers
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
.	O
Gowry	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
stabbed	O
and	O
murdered	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
above	O
Stairs	O
or	O
below	O
?	O
Gowry	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Knife	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
stabbed	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
immediately	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Wound	O
slightly	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dangerous	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
bleeding	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
proper	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Describe	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Gowry	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Right-Shoulder	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
Rib	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
deep	O
was	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
Gowry	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
justly	O
tell	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
since	O
about	O
five	O
Inches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
further	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Gowry	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
further	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
-	O
Harrison	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
this	O
Place	O
by	O
Mr	O
Gowry	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
as	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
described	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Wound	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
with	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Knife	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
short	O
,	O
sharp	O
,	O
broad	O
Point	O
;	O
I	O
discovered	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
had	O
penetrated	O
the	O
Thorax	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
the	O
Man	O
die	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
Two	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
suppose	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
-	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
inspect	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
upon	O
viewing	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Wound	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
Right-Shoulder	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
fifth	O
and	O
sixth	O
Rib	O
,	O
entirely	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Back-bone	O
;	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
the	O
Cavity	O
,	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Thorax	O
,	O
was	O
quite	O
full	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
forced	O
into	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
Syringe	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
are	O
of	O
Opinion	O
this	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
now	O
is	O
your	O
Time	O
to	O
enter	O
upon	O
your	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Two	O
Men	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
drank	O
several	O
Pints	O
of	O
Twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Drams	O
:	O
At	O
length	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
my	O
Husband	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
Dinner	O
ready	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
,	O
which	O
went	O
down	O
three	O
Steps	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
Twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
talk	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
in	O
struggling	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
killed	O
!	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
dress	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
ailed	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Repeat	O
what	O
you	O
said	O
of	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
in	O
your	O
Hand	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Beef	O
and	O
Cabbage	O
for	O
Dinner	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
came	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
What	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
With	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Place	O
being	O
narrow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Struggle	O
I	O
fell	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Knife	O
fell	O
into	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
that	O
Man	O
that	O
your	O
Husband	O
struggled	O
with	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
expect	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
here	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Witness	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
back	O
Yard	O
?	O
Marlow	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Account	O
did	O
the	O
deceased	O
give	O
?	O
Marlow	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
killed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
?	O
Marlow	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
that	O
such	O
an	O
Accident	O
should	O
happen	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
drank	O
my	O
Twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
Man	O
there	O
?	O
Marlow	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
she	O
speaks	O
of	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
sitting	O
you	O
thought	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
did	O
that	O
Man	O
go	O
back	O
before	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
or	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Did	O
any	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
go	O
back	O
before	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
?	O
Marlow	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Christopher	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Brother	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Brother	O
was	O
murdered	O
.	O
I	O
goes	O
down	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
Harry	O
did	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
lying	O
like	O
a	O
Man	O
dead	O
,	O
groaning	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
recover	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
so	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
our	O
Beds	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
,	O
looking	O
at	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
says	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
a	O
fine	O
Thing	O
to	O
laugh	O
at	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
laugh	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
her	O
Face	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
in-Law	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
Damage	O
to	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
in	O
the	O
Fore	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Nanny	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
sit	O
here	O
for	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Nanny	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
to	O
butcher	O
one	O
that	O
you	O
liked	O
so	O
well	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
through	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
along	O
with	O
some	O
fresh	O
Women	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
this	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
says	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Who	O
was	O
that	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
wooden-legged	O
Peg	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
wooden-legged	O
Peg	O
says	O
the	O
same	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
you	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
forgives	O
you	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
Reply	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
where	O
the	O
deceased	O
lay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
follow	O
her	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
past	O
then	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Nothing	O
farther	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
Night	O
following	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
as	O
usual	O
serving	O
of	O
Customers	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
her	O
Husband	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
was	O
better	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Magnus	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
some	O
Words	O
arose	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
die	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
threw	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Latham	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
killed	O
?	O
Latham	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
imagine	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Latham	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
something	O
of	O
Jealously	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
Words	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
Latham	O
.	O
She	O
believed	O
she	O
should	O
die	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
screen	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
some	O
Heat	O
and	O
Anger	O
when	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
was	O
thrown	O
?	O
Latham	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Cooper	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
play	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Mississippi	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
pacified	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
he	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
good	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
loving	O
seemingly	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
?	O
Latham	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Hurst	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
about	O
some	O
Business	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Misfortune	O
had	O
happened	O
between	O
Mr	O
Boswell	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
Mischief	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
I	O
shook	O
my	O
Head	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
her	O
crying	O
and	O
ringing	O
her	O
Hands	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
see	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
till	O
Mr	O
Green	O
and	O
Mr	O
Gowry	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
Bason	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
bleeding	O
:	O
when	O
Mr	O
Green	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
his	O
Fee	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Foot	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
ringing	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
her	O
Husband	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
yet	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
shook	O
my	O
Head	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
expect	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr	O
Boswell	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
to	O
see	O
such	O
Differences	O
between	O
your	O
Wife	O
and	O
you	O
,	O
be	O
reconciled	O
to	O
your	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
owe	O
her	O
no	O
ill	O
Will	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
my	O
Fault	O
as	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
his	O
Fault	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
happened	O
?	O
Hurst	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
look	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
her	O
Husband	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Nurse	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
careful	O
Woman	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
recommended	O
,	O
asked	O
too	O
much	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Holywright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
Love	O
and	O
Unity	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
come	O
away	O
twelve	O
Months	O
last	O
Michaelmas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
there	O
?	O
Holywright	O
.	O
Above	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
Love	O
and	O
Harmony	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
Harry	O
and	O
Nanny	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lyons	I-pers
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
House-keeping	O
;	O
they	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
together	O
four	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
in	O
Love	O
and	O
Unity	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Ironing	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
to	O
work	O
Journey-work	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
ago	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brawley	I-pers
.	O
All	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
about	O
eight	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
served	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
with	O
Drink	O
since	O
they	O
have	O
kept	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
sociable	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
other	O
People	O
are	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
69	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
Mr	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
he	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
Stockings	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket-Apron	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
step	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
then	O
nodded	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
come	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
so	O
Mr	O
Wilson	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Now	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
satisfied	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Thief	O
?	O
She	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
pushed	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
drawn	O
in	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
Forgiveness	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
70	O
.	O
+Mary	O
Allen	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Smith	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Yards	O
of	O
Chints	O
Lawn	B-pers
Gown	I-pers
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Riston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Riston	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Riston	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
remember	O
seeing	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
several	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Linnen	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
lowest	O
Price	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
sold	O
a	O
pretty	O
many	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
sold	O
was	O
in	O
Gentlemens	O
Families	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Sister	O
kept	O
a	O
Shop	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
St	O
Martin's-Lane	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
used	O
her	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Customer	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
of	O
them	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Piece	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
Has	O
not	O
this	O
Woman	O
stole	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
her	O
leaning	O
over	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
Chints	O
Lawn	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Sister	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
if	O
her	O
Sister	O
was	O
within	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
meant	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Bite	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
that	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
Chints	O
?	O
Riston	O
.	O
The	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
Mr	O
Wilson	O
heard	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Chints	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
that	O
and	O
all	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Linnen-drapery	O
Goods	O
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Chints	O
Lawn	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Piece	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Hand-writing	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Description	O
,	O
as	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
red	O
Pencil	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Bilby	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
Park	O
street	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Mr	O
Kenton	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
?	O
Bilby	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
the	O
Rent	O
?	O
Bilby	O
.	O
Mr	O
Kenton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
claimed	O
a	O
Property	O
in	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Mr	O
Kenton	O
's	O
Room	O
?	O
Bilby	O
.	O
After	O
Kenton	O
found	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Right	O
to	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
claimed	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
as	O
her	O
Property	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
convicted	O
:	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
those	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
Chints	O
,	O
was	O
claimed	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
[	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Indictments	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
try	O
her	O
on	O
any	O
other	O
.	O
]	O
71.	O
Ann	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
7	O
s	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Black-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Rosemary-Lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
rather	O
too	O
old	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
willing	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Back-lane	O
by	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
old	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
am	O
never	O
so	O
old	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
willing	O
as	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
young	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Hot	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
fatigued	O
in	O
walking	O
;	O
sitting	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
fall	O
asleep	O
,	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
she	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
locked	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
fell	O
asleep	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
picked	O
your	O
Pocket	O
then	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
more	O
she	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
she	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
she	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
?	O
Q.	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
more	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
never	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
Headborough	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Now	O
is	O
your	O
Time	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
this	O
Man	O
comes	O
in	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
can	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
sell	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
you	O
may	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
freely	O
give	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
Landlord	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
brought	O
a	O
Candle	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
goes	O
up	O
and	O
sets	O
himself	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Maid	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Hot	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
locked	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
walked	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
till	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
a	O
Street-walker	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
your	O
Pocket	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
Woman	O
's	O
Company	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
walking	O
the	O
Streets	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
did	O
you	O
awake	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
I	O
awaked	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
72.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Iron	O
Anchor	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cowse	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cable	O
Rope	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Trinity	O
House	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Cowse	I-pers
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Anchor	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
charged	O
with	O
?	O
Cowse	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Ballast-lighter	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
this	O
Ballast-lighter	O
,	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
Anchor	O
and	O
Cable	O
in	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
gone	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Frayer	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
Anchor	O
and	O
Cable	O
with	O
the	O
Lighter	O
?	O
Frayer	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Lighter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
brought	O
an	O
Anchor	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
my	O
Son	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
an	O
Anchor	O
,	O
such	O
an	O
one	O
has	O
brought	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
dragged	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
William	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
goes	O
down	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
How	O
was	O
you	O
pleased	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Anchor	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Hand	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Anchor	O
?	O
Mackenzie	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
Cowse	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
bringing	O
any	O
Anchor	O
that	O
was	O
sold	O
at	O
your	O
Father	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mackenzie	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
by	O
our	O
Shop	O
at	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
he	O
says	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
is	O
Mr	O
Mc	O
Anoy	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Father	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Anchor	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
examined	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
my	O
Father	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
dragged	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Thames	O
;	O
my	O
Father	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Mr	O
Scot	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
Father	O
said	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
till	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Scott	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
another	O
Man	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Anchor	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
73	O
,	O
74.	O
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
and	O
Luke	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Rope	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
Wapping	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Woodward	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
for	O
six	O
Months	O
together	O
lately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
this	O
Confession	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
has	O
sworn	O
to	O
a	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
my	O
Servants	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Peter	B-pers
Mellard	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
Rope	O
lost	O
from	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
?	O
Mellard	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
draw	O
up	O
his	O
Boat	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Back-door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
he	O
brought	O
up	O
his	O
Boat	O
for	O
?	O
Mellard	O
.	O
For	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Rope	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
in	O
some	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
Mellard	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Shore	O
the	O
first	O
Parcel	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
carry	O
down	O
a	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
looked	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
put	O
a	O
Stop	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Waterman	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Boat	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Rope	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
one	O
thing	O
nor	O
another	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
Luke	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
staid	O
for	O
an	O
Order	O
from	O
John	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
confessed	O
before	O
Justice	O
Duckenfield	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
once	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
six	O
Weeks	O
past	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Ropes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Anderson	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Mellard	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Confession	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Luke	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
take	O
the	O
Rope	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
Back-door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
bring	O
Anderson	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Petty	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Rope	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Boat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
Rope	O
might	O
there	O
be	O
?	O
Petty	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Woodward	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
Master	O
once	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
?	O
Petty	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Luke	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
had	O
tempted	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
?	O
Petty	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
Luke	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
by	O
or	O
know	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Woodward	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Woodward	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
old	O
Stuff	O
that	O
they	O
make	O
brown	O
Paper	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
him	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
of	O
Rope	O
that	O
was	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
thought	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
,	O
if	O
Anderson	O
had	O
not	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
drawed	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
drink	O
several	O
Times	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Woodward	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
whole	O
Family	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dozen	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
to	O
hear	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
alledged	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Culburth	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Woodward	O
has	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
four	O
Years	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Anderson	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
of	O
my	O
tempting	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Need	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
Rogue	O
enough	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
without	O
my	O
tempting	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
75.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Mermaid-Inn	B-place
in	I-place
Carter-lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
lost	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Mermaid-Inn	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
with	O
another	O
young	O
Man	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
send	O
some	O
Money	O
and	O
two	O
Rings	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
:	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
Man	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
together	O
,	O
this	O
Joseph	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
my	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
again	O
about	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
my	O
Room	O
was	O
all	O
safe	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
out	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
in	O
my	O
Mind	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Company	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Friends	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
sorry	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Friend	O
that	O
has	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
Bed	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
throws	O
out	O
his	O
Breeches	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
Pockets	O
;	O
so	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
only	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
Three-half-pence	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
part	O
from	O
his	O
Breeches	O
:	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
to	O
?	O
the	O
Constable	O
answered	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Breeches	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
searched	O
in	O
another	O
Pocket	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Rings	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
First	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
ruined	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
a	O
Coachman	O
with	O
Mr	O
Chitty	O
about	O
eight	O
Months	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
Constable	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
for	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Robbery	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
Stairs	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
last	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
unwilling	O
we	O
should	O
search	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
10	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Walker	O
lay	O
claim	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
vex	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
Fun	O
,	O
and	O
designed	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
took	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
Joke	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
take	O
more	O
Care	O
of	O
it	O
another	O
Time	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr	O
Chitty	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Chitty	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
about	O
nine	O
Months	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
:	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
soberly	O
and	O
honestly	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
Accident	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
't	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
Family	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
is	O
a	O
reputable	O
Family	O
.	O
Bowler	O
Miller	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Belcher	O
,	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
honest	O
Lad	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
frequently	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Brother	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Plate	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Defence	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Jest	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
good	O
Character	O
he	O
bore	O
,	O
induced	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
76.	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Cup	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Sink	O
.	O
He	O
not	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
or	O
coming	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Cup	O
to	O
Mr	O
Holland	O
,	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
,	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
the	O
Cup	O
again	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
upon	O
the	O
Fast-Day	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Gore	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Cup	O
to	O
Mr	O
Holland	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
then	O
the	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr	O
Holland	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Holland	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Cup	O
produced	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Harley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
you	O
owned	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
-	O
Holland	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
it	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
Family	O
wanted	O
Bread	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
ordinary	O
black	O
Cup	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
was	O
the	O
full	O
Value	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
Weight	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
77.	O
David	B-pers
Dalphe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wekes	I-pers
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Homewood	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Delamot	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
principal	O
Witness	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lock	O
up	O
the	O
Ware	O
houses	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
lifted	O
off	O
the	O
Hinge	O
;	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
Sugar	O
in	O
an	O
Apron	O
;	O
mistrusting	O
some	O
Body	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
he	O
hastened	O
down	O
for	O
some	O
Body	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Slings	O
flung	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
to	O
conclude	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
to	O
let	O
themselves	O
down	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Soldier	O
held	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
some	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
lift	O
off	O
the	O
Door	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lifted	O
off	O
the	O
Door	O
by	O
main	O
Strength	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Fault	O
before	O
.	O
This	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
two	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
big	O
with	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
78.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Pound-weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
with	O
the	O
Sugar	O
coming	O
down	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouses	O
at	O
the	O
Water-side	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
compared	O
with	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
of	O
Sugar	O
that	O
was	O
opened	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
higher	O
than	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Sort	O
of	O
Sugar	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hensman	I-pers
declared	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
commit	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
Mercy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
those	O
Warehouses	O
for	O
a	O
Weight	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
79.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
from	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
Greybound	O
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Waterman	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
my	O
Partner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Comber	I-pers
,	O
he	O
says	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
coming	O
from	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Ships	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
something	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
said	O
let	O
us	O
row	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
boarded	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
into	O
a	O
Lighter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
right	O
against	O
Pellican	O
Stairs	O
,	O
my	O
Partner	O
(	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
into	O
the	O
Barge	O
)	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
our	O
Boat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
when	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Partner	O
took	O
the	O
Sugar	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
about	O
his	O
Waist	O
in	O
a	O
Stocking	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Comber	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Roberts	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
escaped	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
failed	O
in	O
Point	O
of	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
particular	O
Ship	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Greybound	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
admonished	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
against	O
such	O
Practices	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
80.	O
Charles	B-pers
Lawen	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lawrin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
the	O
Greybound	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
of	O
a	O
profession	O
they	O
call	O
a	O
Lumper	O
:	O
Though	O
the	O
Matter	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
vast	O
deal	O
,	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
but	O
these	O
are	O
Facts	O
of	O
infinite	O
Prejudice	O
against	O
all	O
the	O
Traders	O
at	O
the	O
Water-side	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
scarce	O
a	O
Ship	O
gets	O
unloaded	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
vast	O
Quantities	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
observing	O
something	O
concealed	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
Sugar	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
Pardon	O
:	O
he	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
common	O
Cant	O
of	O
these	O
People	O
,	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pallister	I-pers
,	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Greybound	O
,	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
Totherly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
accused	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
81.	O
Mary	B-pers
Braswell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
,	O
December	O
25	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tothil-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Shoe	O
thrown	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Shoes	O
we	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
This	O
Fact	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Slose	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
first	O
Witness	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Shoes	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Damask	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
before	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Mr	O
Howse	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Damask	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
his	O
Wife	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
82	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
December	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
proved	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
his	O
Clogs	O
;	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
two	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
83	O
,	O
84.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Boys	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bason	I-pers
,	O
December	O
11	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Linnen	O
off	O
a	O
Hedge	O
at	O
Westbourn-Green	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
Paddington-Green	I-place
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
Wright	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
84	O
,	O
85	O
,	O
86	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
,	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Dugard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
five	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckels	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
87	O
,	O
88.	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Manley	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Dugard	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Clark	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
that	O
Evening	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
one	O
Pint	O
after	O
another	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
made	O
it	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
they	O
left	O
my	O
House	O
:	O
about	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
as	O
if	O
my	O
Till	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
listened	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
a	O
Pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
broke	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
Till	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
;	O
the	O
Till	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
Clark	O
and	O
Saunders	O
being	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
that	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
Saunders	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
:	O
Some	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
Advertisment	O
that	O
the	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
Salts	O
were	O
stopped	O
at	O
Mr	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Plate	O
that	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Sight	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
Mr	O
Lloyd	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
remembered	O
Sparks	O
,	O
Saunders	O
,	O
and	O
Howse	O
so	O
particularly	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
described	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
Mr	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
Desire	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
apprehend	O
these	O
People	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
Saunders	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
Sparks	O
was	O
stopped	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
;	O
Sparks	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
Howse	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
into	O
Prison	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
Discoveries	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Sparks	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Remainder	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
Sparks	O
said	O
you	O
must	O
ask	O
Howse	O
;	O
then	O
Howse	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
;	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
Spoons	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
three	O
Places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
King	O
was	O
not	O
immediately	O
committed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
King	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
impeached	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Manley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
pawn	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Sparks	O
,	O
asked	O
this	O
Witness	O
,	O
Dugard	O
.	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
ever	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
brought	O
my	O
Master	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
a	O
Salt	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
supposed	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
three	O
several	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Sparks	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
Plate	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
shew	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
first	O
one	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
an	O
Ounce	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
Mark	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
:	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
are	O
known	O
here	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Persons	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
;	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
Sparks	O
says	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
You	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
serious	O
Matter	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
cautious	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
about	O
some	O
Plate	O
being	O
stopped	O
;	O
the	O
Person	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
,	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
Howse	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Man	O
disowned	O
him	O
,	O
immediately	O
Sparks	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
pushed	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
these	O
young	O
Fellows	O
have	O
stole	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
advertise	O
it	O
:	O
Upon	O
advertising	O
it	O
,	O
Mr	O
Dugard	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
give	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Mark-lane	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Winchmore-hill	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr	O
Dugard	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
could	O
describe	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
loose	O
Men	O
his	O
Way	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
assist	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
two	O
Horses	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
accordingly	O
Sparks	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
since	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
denied	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
Howse	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
caused	O
Nick	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Howse	O
was	O
commited	O
for	O
not	O
keeping	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
they	O
confessed	O
the	O
Things	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
can	O
I	O
get	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
wash	O
my	O
Hands	O
of	O
all	O
such	O
Fellows	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
says	O
,	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
says	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
three	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
another	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
Playhouse	O
yard	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
Sparks	O
and	O
Howse	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goss	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Buckles	O
,	O
pawned	O
by	O
Howse	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
cleaned	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
Master	O
Dugard	O
's	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Spurling	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
committed	O
Sparks	O
;	O
at	O
his	O
first	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
nothing	O
;	O
but	O
Howse	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
Buckles	O
in	O
Enfield	O
Highway	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Father	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
Buckles	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
Howse	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Buckles	O
he	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Nick	O
Saunders	O
of	O
Waltham	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
was	O
going	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
.	O
Howse	O
did	O
his	O
Endeavour	O
to	O
secure	O
Saunders	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
forced	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Howse	O
endeavour	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Saunders	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
himself	O
?	O
Mr	O
Spurling	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no-body	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourselves	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
Man	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
happened	O
to	O
light	O
with	O
Nick	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
Spoons	O
and	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
And	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
offered	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
any	O
Benefit	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
very	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Salt	O
?	O
Sparks	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
nothing	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
you	O
referred	O
to	O
Howse	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Howse	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Howse	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pawn	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
nor	O
nothing	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Clark	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Nick	O
's	O
Company	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
City	O
Hounds	O
,	O
the	O
Common-Hunt	O
;	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
these	O
Men	O
till	O
last	O
May	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Sparks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
them	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
four	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
going	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
Gate	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
no	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
trust	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
gave	O
me	O
7	O
s.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
7	O
s.	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
their	O
Hands	O
;	O
Sparks	O
and	O
Howse	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Manley	I-pers
.	O
Howse	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
Court	O
to	O
Sparks	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
call	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Greygoose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Sparks	O
and	O
Howse	O
for	O
a	O
Term	O
of	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
always	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
Manner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Clark	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
?	O
Greygoose	O
.	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
none	O
but	O
Sparks	O
and	O
Howse	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Left-Hand	O
.	O
(	O
meaning	O
King	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Lads	O
for	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
Years	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
People	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
young	O
Lads	O
.	O
Sparks	O
and	O
Howse	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
they	O
were	O
11	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
accused	O
of	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Clark	O
,	O
or	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr	O
Dugard	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
neither	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
robbing	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
As	O
for	O
Sparks	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
Howse	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
to	O
signify	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Character	O
does	O
Sparks	O
bear	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
Mr	O
Dugard	O
lives	O
now	O
)	O
with	O
his	O
Uncle	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Clark	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
lived	O
by	O
me	O
at	O
Winchmore	O
hill	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
lived	O
creditably	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
Sparks	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
Opinion	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bassel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
,	O
they	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
close	O
by	O
them	O
almost	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
As	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
for	O
sixteen	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
do	O
they	O
follow	O
?	O
Chambers	O
.	O
Sparks	O
is	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
and	O
Howse	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Sparks	O
and	O
Howse	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
well	O
,	O
could	O
they	O
have	O
brought	O
People	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
Bed	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
both	O
ever	O
since	O
they	O
could	O
walk	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
alledged	O
against	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Mr	O
Dugard	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
Nick	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
was	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
none	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
but	O
Howse	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Pains	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
this	O
Affair	O
;	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
enquire	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
have	O
an	O
excellent	O
Character	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
were	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
in	O
December	O
,	O
you	O
knew	O
the	O
Charge	O
against	O
you	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
material	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
brought	O
Persons	O
of	O
your	O
Family	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
every	O
Night	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
you	O
always	O
kept	O
good	O
Hours	O
:	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
expected	O
that	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
generally	O
keep	O
good	O
Hours	O
,	O
are	O
out	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Manley	I-pers
,	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
89.	O
Anne	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Half	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Clasp	O
.	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
up	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
forced	O
her	O
Discourse	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Upton	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
she	O
forced	O
her	O
Discourse	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
into	O
Angel-court	B-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Apprehensions	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
her	O
Discourse	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Upton	O
.	O
She	O
intreated	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
denied	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
up	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Upton	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Place	O
's	O
Name	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
Hand	O
upon	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
Silver	O
Clasp	O
and	O
Stock	O
off	O
my	O
Neck	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Women	O
there	O
?	O
Upton	O
.	O
This	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
her	O
to	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Business	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
those	O
Women	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
made	O
off	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Knife	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
Assistance	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
begged	O
their	O
Assistance	O
,	O
accordingly	O
they	O
assisted	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Place	O
into	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
the	O
other	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
Clasp	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
:	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Disputes	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Upton	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
delivering	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Was	O
you	O
under	O
any	O
Fear	O
?	O
Upton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
when	O
they	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Knife	O
.	O
Charles	O
Church	O
.	O
Coming	O
up	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Brother	O
Soldier	O
,	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
Clasp	O
and	O
Stock	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
one	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
other	O
Part	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
rescue	O
her	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
send	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
struggled	O
vastly	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
Covent-Garden	O
Market	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
blustering	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
:	O
Just	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Russel-Street	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Betty	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
me	O
;	O
yes	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
kissed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
in	O
my	O
Bosom	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
do	O
as	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
half	O
a	O
Clasp	O
and	O
Stock	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
90.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griggs	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Books	O
,	O
intituled	O
,	O
The	O
Moral	O
Philosopher	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
Shops	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stop	O
him	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
gone	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Yards	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
these	O
two	O
Books	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
Guild-hall	O
he	O
denied	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Book	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Swift	O
's	O
Tale	O
of	O
a	O
Tub	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
your	O
Defence	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Them	O
three	O
Books	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Shop	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Times	O
,	O
could	O
find	O
nobody	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
three-score	O
Yards	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swears	O
these	O
Books	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
prove	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
91	O
,	O
92.	O
Mary	B-pers
Valey	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Cloth	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hulet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Hulet	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Hulet	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Cloysters	O
in	O
St	O
Bartholomew	O
's	O
Parish	O
:	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
fit	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
Motion	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
Pair	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
would	O
stand	O
while	O
Valey	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
be	O
fitted	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
Motion	O
with	O
her	O
Hand	O
towards	O
the	O
Shelves	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
about	O
forty	O
Yards	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Instead	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Pair	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
stolen	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Shoes	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Shoes	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
fell	O
upon	O
their	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Shoes	O
fixed	O
between	O
Mary	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
's	O
Thighs	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
possible	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
thus	O
for	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
?	O
Hulet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
John	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Valey	I-pers
acquitted	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
93.	O
William	B-pers
Prossey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Glass	O
Globe	O
Lamps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Times	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
Lamps	O
from	O
Smithfield	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
made	O
of	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
of	O
Glass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
them	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
away	O
four	O
Lamps	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
more	O
Persons	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
last	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
own	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
Day	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
away	O
four	O
Glass	O
Lamps	O
from	O
the	O
Sheep-pens	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr	O
Smith	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
taking	O
four	O
Lamps	O
out	O
of	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Wing	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
In	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
he	O
taken	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Lamps	O
been	O
found	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
Lamp-posts	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Caps	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Iron	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
into	O
small	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
broken	O
Glass	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
William	B-pers
Prossey	I-pers
went	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
Half	O
pence	O
a	O
Pound	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Sister	O
sold	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
about	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
We	O
spent	O
it	O
in	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Drink	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
appeared	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
them	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
faithful	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
94	O
,	O
95.	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Prossey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Sween	I-pers
,	O
and	O
certain	O
other	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
56	O
Pound-weight	O
of	O
Coals	O
from	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fee	O
lane	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Tripe-man	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
Coals	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
these	O
young	O
Men	O
,	O
Miller	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Prossey	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
House	O
near	O
us	O
;	O
my	O
neighbour	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Chaps	O
that	O
stole	O
my	O
Coals	O
;	O
they	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
several	O
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
after	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
(	O
the	O
thin	O
one	O
)	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
comes	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Coals	O
in	O
Fee-lane	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Sween	O
and	O
Lawrence	O
selling	O
of	O
Coals	O
in	O
Fee-lane	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
about	O
two	O
Bushels	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
one	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
another	O
Part	O
.	O
Q.	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
these	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
taking	O
Coals	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
Smith	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
Day	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
Jack	B-pers
Sween	I-pers
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
taking	O
another	O
Bushel	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Sween	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Shore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
afterwards	O
in	O
taking	O
Coals	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
these	O
Coals	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs	O
Sleep	O
in	O
St	O
John	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
October	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
That	O
we	O
got	O
Two	O
and	O
twenty	O
Pence	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
your	O
Sack	O
hold	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Six	O
Half	O
Bushels	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Short	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Sween	I-pers
were	O
concerned	O
that	O
Day	O
se'nning	O
in	O
taking	O
another	O
Sack	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
you	O
invited	O
Lawrence	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
Company	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
John	O
Shore	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
Time	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
Time	O
John	B-pers
Shore	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
taking	O
another	O
Sack	O
.	O
As	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
but	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
Miller	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
ordered	O
to	O
continue	O
till	O
the	O
breaking	O
up	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
96.	O
William	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pound	O
and	O
six	O
Ounces	O
of	O
white	O
Thread	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Edgerton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Amoss	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Throwster	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Charles	B-pers
Edgerton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Amoss	I-pers
;	O
this	O
Boy	O
I	O
employed	O
in	O
turning	O
the	O
Stick	O
,	O
in	O
beating	O
this	O
Thread	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
out	O
a	O
Draught	O
of	O
Thread	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
weighed	O
out	O
some	O
white	O
Thread	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
about	O
Business	O
;	O
I	O
give	O
out	O
70	O
or	O
80	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
you	O
be	O
frightned	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Thief	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
many	O
Pounds	O
to	O
these	O
Gentlemen	O
for	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
Goods	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
one	O
Pound	O
and	O
six	O
Ounces	O
of	O
sewing	O
Thread	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
Pound	O
and	O
six	O
Ounces	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Darby	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
take	O
that	O
Thread	O
away	O
?	O
you	O
have	O
often	O
heard	O
me	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
work	O
for	O
nothing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Flower	O
and	O
Dcan-street	O
,	O
Spital	O
fields	O
,	O
he	O
described	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
lusty	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
keeps	O
an	O
Old-Cloaths-Shop	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Thread	O
not	O
salable	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Thread	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
sometimes	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
sometimes	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
Hanks	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
three	O
Hanks	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
Colour	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
sold	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
worth	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Pound	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Ascrost	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
String	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Darby	O
's	O
Shirt	O
hung	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
)	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
instead	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
being	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Thread	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
Place	O
in	O
Flower	O
and	O
Dean-Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
this	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Ascroft	O
.	O
The	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Darby	O
,	O
is	O
but	O
thirteen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
by	O
this	O
wicked	O
Practice	O
,	O
Mr	O
Hunt	O
declared	O
he	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
ruined	O
,	O
both	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
and	O
Substance	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
97.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Watch	O
(	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
)	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lowin	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
did	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
tried	O
the	O
Sessions	O
before	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
a	O
Silver	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
she	O
lived	O
?	O
Neal	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
beyond	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Direction	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
?	O
Neal	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
did	O
receive	O
such	O
a	O
Watch	O
as	O
we	O
described	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Lowin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
while	O
he	O
stayed	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
1	O
s.	O
for	O
selling	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bagnel	I-pers
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bagnel	I-pers
live	O
?	O
Neal	O
.	O
In	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
House-keeper	O
?	O
Neal	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
dreadful	O
Character	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bagnel	I-pers
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Bagnel	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Salesman	O
;	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
Mr	O
Neal	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
Watch	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
about	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Bagnel	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
no	O
Questions	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
only	O
one	O
Case	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
going	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
Street	O
for	O
two	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
Watches	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
Bagnel	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
buy	O
all	O
Kind	O
of	O
Things	O
?	O
Bagnel	O
.	O
I	O
buy	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
Watches	O
?	O
Bagnel	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
a	O
Shilling	O
or	O
two	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
buy	O
things	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
understand	O
?	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
would	O
buy	O
Diamonds	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
them	O
cheap	O
?	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Constable	O
the	O
last	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
Mary	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
was	O
an	O
associate	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Mc	O
Lane	O
,	O
[	O
This	O
Mc	O
Lane	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
of	O
Eleven	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
tried	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Sessions	O
ago	O
for	O
stealing	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
acquitted	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
by	O
Lewin	O
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
this	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
and	O
come	O
at	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Clement	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
Watch	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Boy	O
before	O
?	O
Clement	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
a	O
Bed	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
the	O
Boy	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
much	O
the	O
worse	O
;	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Stranger	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
your	O
Character	O
,	O
how	O
you	O
behave	O
in	O
your	O
Neighbourhood	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
Time	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
kept	O
me	O
three	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
98	O
,	O
99.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Savcrey	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Mortar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pestle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberson	I-pers
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Wimpey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
themselves	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
facing	O
the	O
Chimney-Place	O
where	O
the	O
Brass	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
stood	O
.	O
-	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
Chinking	O
,	O
and	O
hinted	O
something	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
knowing	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
coarse	O
thing	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
Jennings	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
of	O
the	O
Frock	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
something	O
tied	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
opened	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Brass	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Roberson	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
Mrs	O
Roberson	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
Saverey	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Box	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Chimney-side	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
stood	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
to	O
toast	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
upon	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
toast	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
Looks	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Curiosity	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
the	O
Things	O
wrapped	O
up	O
were	O
opposite	O
to	O
Brown	O
,	O
I	O
declared	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
Saverey	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Blow	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
them	O
both	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
being	O
sturdy	O
Men	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
manage	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Wimpey	I-pers
,	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
upon	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
stabbed	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Elbow	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
However	O
,	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
me	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Brown	O
,	O
but	O
Brown	O
dragged	O
me	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
upon	O
advanced	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
Brown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
broke	O
his	O
Jaw	O
;	O
the	O
Parcel	O
being	O
opened	O
,	O
the	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
be	O
Mrs	O
Roberson	O
's	O
.	O
Before	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Frock	O
lying	O
there	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
t	O
he	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
Years	O
and	O
better	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
Trade	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
A	O
Butcher	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Master	O
Butcher	O
the	O
best	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
most	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Brown	O
a	O
